<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 17:42:57 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 17:42:57 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download LDPlayer 9.1.57.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 08 Aug 2025 19:14:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ldplayer-2331.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ldplayer-2331.html
</guid><description>
LDPlayer is software that emulates Android, allowing users to play games, run apps on a Windows computer. LDPlayer support play heavy games, run chat applications, photo editing, video and many other Android apps, LDPlayer compatible with Android 5.1 and above, supports multitasking for experience not inferior when used on Mobile.
Installation is a simple process and quickly without the need for special attention from your side, there's more. installed, you can't touch them. This...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mozilla Firefox 141.0.3</title><pubDate> Fri, 08 Aug 2025 19:10:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-firefox-quantum-501.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-firefox-quantum-501.html
</guid><description>
Firefox Quantum is a web browser independently provide the tabbed browsing combined with numerous handy features like pop-up blocker, Bookmarks, direct (integrated RSS), password manager, and more. Functionality can be extended with dozens of plugins available for free (extensions).
Firefox Quantum are interface completely new, beautiful, neat, minimalistic and delicate, eats less RAM to 30% compared with the old version and solve the condition consuming capacity
Firefox can import all...
</description></item><item><title>Download Transcend SSD Scope 4.27</title><pubDate> Fri, 08 Aug 2025 19:10:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-transcend-ssd-scope-7662.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-transcend-ssd-scope-7662.html
</guid><description>
Transcend SSD Scope is an advanced and user-friendly software that makes it easier than ever to clone and maintain a healthy and efficient SSD. It brings together the latest technology to determine the health and optimize the performance of your SSD.
Useful features of Transcend SSD Scope include:
	View drive information
	View SMART status
	Diagnostic scan
	Clear Security
	Updating the firmware
	Enable TRIM, Health Indicator, and System Clone.
</description></item><item><title>Download Opera One 120.0.5543.161</title><pubDate> Fri, 08 Aug 2025 19:09:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-972.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-972.html
</guid><description>
Opera is a fast, safe, configurable and compliant intranet web browser, which includes both the reader and the application. The Opera browser supports web browsing, listening to music, watching high speed movies, you can open many tabs on the Opera without affecting your browsing speed. Opera now supports almost all devices and operating systems such as windows, IOS, Android, linux, MacOS ...
Opera is a beautiful interface and many interesting features, operating on both PCs and mobile,...
</description></item><item><title>Download RapidRAW 1.3.5</title><pubDate> Fri, 08 Aug 2025 19:07:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rapidraw-13957.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rapidraw-13957.html
</guid><description>
RapidRAW is a modern, high-performance, open-source RAW photo editor, designed to deliver a fast and clean editing experience with a lightweight footprint (under 30MB). Built with performance and usability in mind, the software is aimed at photographers who want a simple, efficient, and fun workflow without compromising performance.
Key Features
	GPU-accelerated processing: Uses a custom WGSL shader to process all image adjustments on the GPU, allowing for smooth, responsive editing...
</description></item><item><title>Download MEmu Android Emulator 9.2.6</title><pubDate> Fri, 08 Aug 2025 19:07:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-memu-2975.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-memu-2975.html
</guid><description>
MEmu or also known as Android Emulator is the Android emulator light and free, allowing Windows users to enjoy Android experience the original on the computer and device Microsoft their. This app provides outstanding performance, allowing you to play on PC a series of games designed to run on Android devices. This app allows you to play the game favorite Android on larger screens, to bring you a better gaming experience.
MEmu - Android emulator, lightweight and free
Software MEmu also...
</description></item><item><title>Download Soft Organizer Pro 10.20</title><pubDate> Fri, 08 Aug 2025 19:07:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-soft-organizer-498.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-soft-organizer-498.html
</guid><description>
Soft Organizer is versatile software just install the software to help uninstall software quickly and safely to release the hard drive or restore when necessary.  That side, Soft Organizer also keep track of the changes made to the system during installation of new utilities or help test the new version of the software on the computer to update timely, classification, and management of programs for users to follow easily.
Soft Organizer has a modern interface with simple manipulation to...
</description></item><item><title>Download iDownerGo Pro 10.7.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 08 Aug 2025 19:06:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idownergo-12439.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idownergo-12439.html
</guid><description>
iDownerGo is the best tool that allows users to download videos, music and playlists from more than 10,000 streaming sites. It can easily convert videos to MP4, MOV, MKV, 3GP, AAC, WAV, FLAC and other formats on PC and Mac. With this amazing program, users can enjoy their favorite media content without restrictions.
iDownerGo Features
	Download any video up to 8K resolution
	Download 1080p videos online from over 10,000 popular streaming sites easily.
	Save any video in various...
</description></item><item><title>Download MedCalc 23.3.4</title><pubDate> Fri, 08 Aug 2025 19:06:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-medcalc-1536.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-medcalc-1536.html
</guid><description>
MedCalc is a statistical software for biomedical research can analyze many performance curve system with a set of rich functionality, chart types and advanced module. MedCalc was designed to meet the needs and requirements of the study nature and aims to analyze the statistical calculations of the project. This software provides the tools and means essential to analyze the characteristic curve of the system (ROC), drawing data and perform the statistical calculations.
MedCalc -...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube Downloader 3.9.16 (0708)</title><pubDate> Fri, 08 Aug 2025 19:05:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube Downloader  is a dedicated software that helps users  downloading youtube videos  Favorites on PC for offline viewing. With MediaHuman YouTube  Downloader  you can download videos from youtube website to your computer with  fast speed , with special software development technology that automatically receives videos from Websites, in addition to the ability to download videos from software websites, can convert downloaded video formats to various formats for the purpose...
</description></item><item><title>Download Autodesk 3ds Max 2026.2 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Fri, 08 Aug 2025 19:05:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-autodesk-3ds-max-0001-1273.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-autodesk-3ds-max-0001-1273.html
</guid><description>
Autodesk 3ds Max 2024 provides a tool powerful, integrated three-dimensional modeling, animation, rendering, and synthesis to work with speed and efficiency. Autodesk 3ds Max provides innovative methods to build and texture models, accumulated data, forming character and creating high quality images. Application for three-dimensional environments, animated, rendered, and combined Autodesk 3ds Max is designed for professionals graphics and computer animation, who developed computer games,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Visual Studio Code 1.103.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 08 Aug 2025 19:04:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-visual-studio-code-3182.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-visual-studio-code-3182.html
</guid><description>
Visual Studio Code is the encryption tool of Microsoft has met most of the needs of the developer. Environment this encoding was introduced to compete with other products such as Sublime and Nodepad ++ . Microsoft, in its new product, has not been released in many years, has provided many features in a simple environment. In addition to the familiar with a dozen programming languages, the syntax and get to know coding language as soon as be encrypted and allows for syntax highlighting, it...
</description></item><item><title>Download Autodesk Maya 2026.2 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Fri, 08 Aug 2025 19:03:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-maya-autodesk-0005-4322.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-maya-autodesk-0005-4322.html
</guid><description>
Autodesk Maya is a powerful tool that provides a set of innovative features, comprehensive for computer animation, 3D modeling, simulation, rendering and combination on the production platform has high scalability. Maya has the display technologies of the next generation, accelerated workflow modeling and tools for handling complex data. This is the top tool for animation, modeling, simulation, and rendering Maya 3D provides a set of tools integrated strong. Use it for animation,...
</description></item><item><title>Download iTubeGo YouTube Downloader 10.7.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 08 Aug 2025 19:02:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-itubego-youtube-downloader-3681.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-itubego-youtube-downloader-3681.html
</guid><description>
iTubeGo YouTube Downloader  is the best way to download live video from 1000+ streaming sites. iTubeGo YouTube Downloader is a powerful download tool that allows you to save video and audio for free. The output format of high speed converter is high quality MP4, MP3. Fully compatible with iPhone, iPad, iTunes, iMovie, Android Phone and more.
iTubeGo YouTube Downloader - Solution for downloading high quality Youtube video 
Features of iTubeGo YouTube Downloader
	Download videos from...
</description></item><item><title>Download Remote Desktop Manager Enterprise 2025.2.25</title><pubDate> Fri, 08 Aug 2025 19:01:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-remote-desktop-manager-enterprise-242.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-remote-desktop-manager-enterprise-242.html
</guid><description>
Remote Desktop Manager Enterprise software is the complete management of remote connections and virtual machines from a single location, at the same time access support data online and cloud storage. Remote Desktop Manager supports multiple types of connections, not only connections for the protocol connect remote computer Remote Desktop Protocol (RDP).
Remote Desktop Manager easily add, edit, delete, share, organize and find your remote connection of you quickly. Compatible with...
</description></item><item><title>Download Drupal 11.2.3</title><pubDate> Fri, 08 Aug 2025 19:00:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-drupal-3607.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-drupal-3607.html
</guid><description>
Drupal is a content management framework open Source written in PHP. Drupal provides the framework back-end for at least 2,3% of all websites worldwide, from blogs to commercial sites.
Drupal is a tool for web content management online, as well as a customized platform - to help you build the right tool to serve the strategic management of your content. The business leaders and technology use Drupal to create enterprise solutions in the real world, allowing for innovation website. When...
</description></item><item><title>Download Calibre 8.8.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 08 Aug 2025 19:00:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-calibre-1669.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-calibre-1669.html
</guid><description>
Calibre  is an eBook library management application that allows you to manage your eBook collection, convert eBooks between different formats, Sync with popular e-reading devices and read your e-books with included viewer. You can sort books by author, title, date and other details, download meta information and book covers, add personalized tags and comments, and view your images in the cover display.
Collection of essential tools for adding metadata editing books or managing your...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Substance 3D Sampler 5.1.0 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Fri, 08 Aug 2025 18:59:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-substance-3d-sampler-6625.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-substance-3d-sampler-6625.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Substance 3D Sampler allows you to create and iterate on collections of materials by refining and blending existing materials or by extracting new materials from scans ( one or more images). A new set of powerful tools that combine different technologies and creation methods (AI-based and manual) will help you manage your entire document library and export them to other applications.
Features of Adobe Substance 3D Sampler
	AI-powered scan processing
	Use your content everywhere....
</description></item><item><title>Download Robin YouTube Video Downloader Pro 6.15.3</title><pubDate> Fri, 08 Aug 2025 18:58:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-video-downloader-pro-2828.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-video-downloader-pro-2828.html
</guid><description>
YouTube Video Downloader Pro is a Windows application professional to download and convert videos from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion and thousands of video sharing sites, other. It accelerates your download up to 5 times. YouTube Video Downloader Pro allows you to download multiple videos at the same time. It also allows you to pause, resume and cancel a download at any time.
YouTube Video Downloader Pro - Download online videos on social networks
Features of YouTube Video Downloader...
</description></item><item><title>Download Reg Organizer 9.80</title><pubDate> Fri, 08 Aug 2025 18:58:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reg-organizer-1595.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reg-organizer-1595.html
</guid><description>
Reg Organizer is a software to scan and clean your registry windows register errors and help optimize performance computer system. Reg Organizer is a software subscription, professional, and professional, and any way that the Windows registry are necessary and therefore, the overall performance of Windows improves, there is this software.
Reg Organizer - registry Cleaning and pc optimization
The main features of Reg Organizer
	Cleaning the registry of the lock is not valid and not...
</description></item><item><title>Download Private Windows Script (PrivWindoze) 5.6.5</title><pubDate> Fri, 08 Aug 2025 18:57:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-private-windows-script-12878.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-private-windows-script-12878.html
</guid><description>
Are you concerned about your personal information sent to others? Or do you feel that your Windows settings have many programs that you never use? Private Windows Script (or Privwindoze) provides a comprehensive anti -remote monitoring set designed to enhance your privacy when using Windows operating system.
The main features
	End the positive process. All unnecessary processes are turned off while the scanning program. A small white list is maintained.
	Clean up the positive runonce....
</description></item><item><title>Download Xmanager Power Suite 8.0.0014</title><pubDate> Fri, 08 Aug 2025 18:57:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xmanager-power-suite-4036.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xmanager-power-suite-4036.html
</guid><description>
Xmanager Power Suite is the network connection complete. The products include: Xmanager (server, PC X high performance); Xshell (SSH client, strong); Xftp (client-SFTP / FTP); Xlpd (a print management tools work). Xmanager Power Suite is a solution all-in-one includes Xmanager, Xshell, Xftp and Xlpd in a single set. Xmanager run the app window X and Xshell manage servers Unix / Linux remotely with a terminal safety. Xftp transfers files between systems securely, and Xlpd runs in locally...
</description></item><item><title>Download Internet Video Downloader 7.3.3</title><pubDate> Fri, 08 Aug 2025 18:56:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hdapplications-hd-downloader-6041.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hdapplications-hd-downloader-6041.html
</guid><description>
Internet Video Downloader is a small tool designed to help you download video clips from YouTube, Dailymotion and many other similar sites with high quality that can easily run on smartphones, tablets or the latest Xbox devices. After the quick and simple installation process, you will be welcomed by a user-friendly interface without the ability to cause any problems for you.
Although you can set the app start to download immediately, but you can also create a download list that can be...
</description></item><item><title>Download HTTP Toolkit 1.22.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 08 Aug 2025 18:56:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-http-toolkit-6246.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-http-toolkit-6246.html
</guid><description>
HTTP Toolkit is software that provides the ability to automatically block HTTP and HTTPS traffic from most client applications, including web browsers such as Chrome and Firefox, most CLI tools and auxiliary languages such as Node.js, Python, Ruby etc. You can browse through traffic by marking the content type, status, and source or search by URL, status, and title to find important notifications.
You can check the URL, status, title, and content of each request or feedback, along with...
</description></item><item><title>Download ProtonVPN 4.2.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 08 Aug 2025 18:56:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-protonvpn-10433.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-protonvpn-10433.html
</guid><description>
ProtonVPN app for Windows is the best way to stay safe and private while surfing the internet. It is open source, easy to use, and packed with useful security features. ProtonVPN will secure your connection by routing your traffic through multiple servers to protect you against advanced network-based attacks.
It helps keep your IP address safe if something goes wrong with your VPN connection. If your VPN connection fails, the kill switch feature will prevent your device from connecting...
</description></item></channel></rss>