<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 20:05:12 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 20:05:12 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Everything 1.4.1.1030</title><pubDate> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 19:35:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-everything-385.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-everything-385.html
</guid><description>
Everything is a search tool on the desktop that lets you find files and folders instantly by entering the name software or certain applications. The interesting thing for Everything that can be indexed for the whole of your computer in a few seconds and automatically updates the index.
The software is split into two main controls: the search box and the results page. When you first run Everything it will create an index of all the files and folders on your machine. Unless you have...
</description></item><item><title>Download ProfiCAD 13.3.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 19:34:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-proficad-1546.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-proficad-1546.html
</guid><description>
ProfiCAD is a software Program to draw diagram and circuit diagram of the electrical circuit and electronics with many features to support users. ProfiCAD will search the control circuit is different then help, you can design a variety of diagram techniques, such as diagrams, pneumatic and hydraulic. One of the obvious features of this product is the simplicity of it. Simple in the tool bar and the icons represent the parts. Simply arrange the menu, just put the items on the screen and...
</description></item><item><title>Download SoftPerfect NetWorx 25.11</title><pubDate> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 19:33:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-softperfect-networx-1592.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-softperfect-networx-1592.html
</guid><description>
SoftPerfect NetWorx is a software simple and effective way to manage traffic and bandwidth consumption in Windows. If we ignore traffic not regular, and occasionally of the operating system to update itself, as well as updates for the different drivers, one of the important factors in the job vacancy Internet soon is the use of the Internet is hidden by the software is installed on your system. . If you are the user settings clock software and you don't pay attention to it, the existence...
</description></item><item><title>Download n-Track Studio Suite 10.2.3.10303</title><pubDate> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 19:33:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-n-track-studio-2991.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-n-track-studio-2991.html
</guid><description>
n-Track Studio is a recording software allows you record and create MIDI music and sounds top quality. The software allows you to add effects, VST3, DirectX, AU (Mac), VST and ReWire different on each track or channel. This program also allows you to automatically fade out, fade in and fade out or increase the volume of the music to indicate the voice of the singer.
n-Track Studio can record and playback the number of audio, MIDI and sound unlimited. In addition, you can handle the...
</description></item><item><title>Download BS.Player Pro 2.79 Build 1095</title><pubDate> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 19:32:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bsplayer-pro-2056.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bsplayer-pro-2056.html
</guid><description>
BS.Player Pro is the multimedia world's most popular can edit, add new files from any folder as well as the URL. With the new function is improved, it will play YouTube videos directly from the net and it can save these videos to your hard drive as a flv file for later playback. Now, you can directly download all the YouTube videos of his favorite down the computer using BS.Player. BS.Player Pro has full functionality as YouTube player and as a download at YouTube, for any YouTube content...
</description></item><item><title>Download GiliSoft USB Lock 10.8</title><pubDate> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 19:32:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-usb-lock-866.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-usb-lock-866.html
</guid><description>
GiliSoft USB Lock is a tool that prevents leakage of data to prevent leakage and copy of your data to USB Drives, external DRIVES, CD / DVD, or the other mobile device. GiliSoft USB Lock lets you block all the drives and devices do not belong to you. With USB Lock, you can share your PC with anyone without fear of data theft. This is a security software easy USB and Endpoint DLP Suite that helps you lock the usb port, making recording a dvd / cd read-only, block some websites, forbid some...
</description></item><item><title>Download XL-Connector 3.6.20.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 19:31:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xl-connector-12415.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xl-connector-12415.html
</guid><description>
XL-Connector is a popular plugin that securely integrates Excel and Salesforce to export, import, refresh and transform data seamlessly with ultra-fast api connection. It provides Salesforce administrators with a comprehensive toolbox that easily performs data and metadata management activities in a familiar Excel environment.
Features
Export from Salesforce to Excel
	Get data from existing Salesforce reports or build your own SOQL queries directly into Excel.
Import data into...
</description></item><item><title>Download Free Music and Video Downloader 3.11</title><pubDate> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 19:31:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-music-and-video-downloader-123.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-music-and-video-downloader-123.html
</guid><description>
Free Music &amp;amp; Video Downloader (formerly the Free Music Downloader) allows you to download his favorite music at the form of MP3 files from many different online sources, including Last.FM, Grooveshark, Sogou, VKontakte, SoundCloud, and many other things.Just enter name of artist or song you are looking for and click the Search button to see a list of results and download the songs you want.You can customize the services that applications will use to search, put the download folder...
</description></item><item><title>Download PhraseExpress 17.0.132</title><pubDate> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 19:30:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-phraseexpress-41.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-phraseexpress-41.html
</guid><description>
PhraseExpress is a useful application that helps users save time when typing frequently used text or commands. This application allows users to create shortcuts to automatically insert text quickly and conveniently.
With PhraseExpress, users can create "templates" for common commands, regular emails, chat messages, or any text they have to retype frequently. Users only need to set up shortcuts for each template and when needed, just type that shortcut and the text will automatically...
</description></item><item><title>Download Directory Opus Pro 13.19.3 Beta</title><pubDate> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 19:24:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-opus-pro-779.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-opus-pro-779.html
</guid><description>
Directory Opus Pro is a software replacement for Explorer with traditional strength and function more than any manager other files. Directory Opus Pro full support for high DPI screen (for example 4K and 5K) with the rename dialog is redesigned, with new features. Besides being a recording macro only allows you to perform mass renaming complex that don't need regular expressions. In addition, Directory Opus Pro also enhances the ability to script.Better handling of renaming recursive and...
</description></item><item><title>Download MyLanViewer Enterprise 6.6.4 / Business</title><pubDate> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 19:23:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mylanviewer-enterprise-1274.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mylanviewer-enterprise-1274.html
</guid><description>
MyLanViewer is a program for scanning IP address, Netbios and LAN / Network powerful for Windows tool whois and traceroute, remote shutdown and process management Wake On LAN (WOL), scan and monitor wireless networks. This app will help you find all IP addresses, MAC addresses and shared folders of computers on the network wired or wireless (Wi-Fi).
MyLanViewer Enterprise - Scan IP address LAN/Network
The program scans network and displays the computer network in your window, friends...
</description></item><item><title>Download goScreen Corporate 21.0.0.1099</title><pubDate> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 19:23:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-goscreen-corporate-6310.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-goscreen-corporate-6310.html
</guid><description>
goScreen Corporate  creates some virtual pages on the console screen. When a program is started, it will be placed on the current screen "active" page. When one then turns to another page, the program is left on the page where it was started, one can always find it there. Program windows can be moved from one desktop page to another.
Features of goScreen Corporate
	Change the size, position, font, color of goScreen UI windows,
	Assign a name to the screen pages,
	Assign icons to...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Downloader 9.17.17</title><pubDate> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 19:23:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html
</guid><description>
YTD Youtube Downloader is an application that reliable and intuitive, allowing you to quickly download YouTube videos and save them to your computer. You can also convert the media files to the format desired video or extract audio streams and save separately. YTD Youtube Downloader lets you save your favorite clips of yourself from Youtube, Facebook, Vimeo and Dailymotion to your desktop. The software supports URLS from many web site hosting, multimedia and allows you to download desired...
</description></item><item><title>Download EverNote 10.161.1.25556</title><pubDate> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 19:22:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-evernote-3261.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-evernote-3261.html
</guid><description>
EverNote is the all in one tool allows you to track notes, todo items, memos, outlines, excerpts, websites, ideas and other things and automatically synchronize them between multiple computers and mobile devices (iPhone, Android, etc.). You can choose to sort their notes into categories, password protect them, export them to XML and more. EverNote supports a number of pattern notes allow you to add to-do list, spreadsheet like Excel to calculate costs (automatic sum), notes, phone, contact...
</description></item><item><title>Download lessmsi 2.10.4</title><pubDate> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 19:21:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lessmsi-12392.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lessmsi-12392.html
</guid><description>
Lessmsi (Less MSIerables) is a free and portable application that allows users to view and extract the contents of MSI files.
How does it work? Files with the .msi extension are not as widely used as their .exe cousins, but both contain programs for Windows. The main difference between them is that the latter does not always come with an installer, while it comes standard with the former. However, there will be cases where you just need to view or want to extract specific content from...
</description></item><item><title>Download BitComet 2.18</title><pubDate> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 19:20:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bitcomet-1220.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bitcomet-1220.html
</guid><description>
BitComet is the program that supports the download of torrent files quickly supports multiple security protocols and modern interface. BitComet is free software file-sharing p2p fully compatible with Bittorrent, this is one of the p2p protocols the most popular is designed for high-speed distribution of files with size 100MB or GB. BitComet is a bittorrent client powerful, clean, fast and easy to use. It support to download at the same time, download queue, downloads the selected in...
</description></item><item><title>Download Kong Audio Qin Engine 3.1.5</title><pubDate> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 19:20:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kong-audio-qin-engine-11420.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kong-audio-qin-engine-11420.html
</guid><description>
What is QIN? QIN Engine is the original sample playback plugin developed by KONG AUDIO. All current KONG AUDIO products are based on the QIN engine. QIN is more flexible, more efficient, more stable and more useful than what has been used previously for product development.
Qin Engine Features
	Flexible design: You can make your own musical instrument.
	Features can be extended using and combining Expansion Sets.
	Another model for accessing and combining patterns.
	Designed to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Nomad Factory Magnetics Bundle 3.1.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 19:19:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nomad-factory-magnetics-bundle-11884.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nomad-factory-magnetics-bundle-11884.html
</guid><description>
Magnets Bundle v3 is a comprehensive collection of three Nomad Factory plugins, including Magnet 3, Echoes 3 and Cosmos 3. This bundle is the ultimate toolkit to bring tape and analog richness to your mix, equipped with improved DSP, a resizable user interface, and support for the latest audio standards.
Features:
	Three diverse plugins: Get Magnet 3, Echoes 3 and Cosmos 3 in one package.
	Improved DSP and UI: Enhanced for better performance and usability.
	Supports VST3 and Apple...
</description></item><item><title>Download Nomad Factory Retro EQs Bundle 2.3.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 19:19:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nomad-factory-retro-eqs-bundle-10600.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nomad-factory-retro-eqs-bundle-10600.html
</guid><description>
Nomad Factory Retro EQs Bundle is a faithful emulation of the Pultec &amp;amp; Legendary Altec from the 50s. The hardware has been heard on countless records and is still in use today. With v2, it adds adjustable analog circuit modules (in both Pulse-Tec &amp;amp; ALL-Tec plug-ins), simulating the complex operation of the original tubes and transformers. head. They create pleasantly similar saturation effects to any sound you feed them. V2 features a completely rewritten DSP, an all-new...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sync Breeze Ultimate 17.4.26 + Enterprise + Pro</title><pubDate> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 19:18:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sync-breeze-ultimate-enterprise-1462.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sync-breeze-ultimate-enterprise-1462.html
</guid><description>
Sync Breeze Ultimate / Enterprise is software sync files fast, powerful and reliable for the local disk, shared network storage devices, NAS and storage systems business. Users are provided with multiple modes sync files one-way and two-way sync files periodically, sync file real time sync file-level bits, sync files multi-threading, synchronization, files, wallpaper and more.
Sync Breeze Ultimate / Enterprise - synchronize files
App GUI main Sync Breeze Ultimate allows a person to...
</description></item><item><title>Download OsmAnd+ — Maps &amp;amp; GPS Offline 5.2.7</title><pubDate> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 16:46:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-osmand-maps-gps-offline-8245.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-osmand-maps-gps-offline-8245.html
</guid><description>
OsmAnd+ (OSM Automatic Navigation Directions) is a mapping and navigation application with access to free, global, and high-quality OpenStreetMap (OSM) data. Enjoy voice and optical navigation, view POIs (points of interest), create and manage GPX routes, use contour visualization and elevation information, choose between driving modes, cyclists, pedestrians, OSM editing, etc.
This is a mobile navigation app that uses OpenStreetMap (OSM) data to provide users with detailed maps and...
</description></item><item><title>Download WiFi Pro FTP Server 2.2.7</title><pubDate> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 16:46:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wifi-pro-ftp-server-8831.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wifi-pro-ftp-server-8831.html
</guid><description>
Convert your Android phone/tablet into an FTP Server! Use this cool app to host your own FTP Server on your phone/tablet. Use FTP Server to transfer files, photos, movies, songs, etc. to/from your Android device using an FTP client like FileZilla.
Features of WiFi Pro FTP Server Pro
	Full-fledged FTP server with configurable port numbers
	Supports FTP over TLS/SSL (FTPS)
	Configurable anonymous access
	Configurable home directory (mount point)
	Configurable username/password
	Avoid...
</description></item><item><title>Download WiFi Direct + 10.0.21</title><pubDate> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 16:45:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wifi-direct-10153.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wifi-direct-10153.html
</guid><description>
Wi-Fi Direct is a Wi-Fi standard for peer-to-peer wireless connections that allows two devices to establish a direct Wi-Fi connection without the need for an intermediate wireless access point, router, or Internet connection.
Features of WiFi Direct +
	Fast
	Completely free, no intrusive ads.
	Supports all file transfers.
	Supports multiple file transfers.
	Supports folder transfer.
	Supports file transfer to and from external sdcard.
	Tested on many devices.
	Advanced file chooser.
</description></item><item><title>Download Add Text: Text on Photo Editor 12.6.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 16:44:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-add-text-text-on-photo-editor-10483.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-add-text-text-on-photo-editor-10483.html
</guid><description>
Add Text app is an all-in-one tool for creating text. You can add text to photos, gradients, solid colors, or transparent backgrounds.
Highlights
	Besides text, add other overlays: photos, shapes, stickers, and saved text styles
	Design parts of text separately: supported in Format, Color, Stroke, Markup tools
	3D Text Tools: 3D Rotation, 3D Depth, Perspective
	In addition to 800+ fonts, add an unlimited number of custom fonts (including emoji fonts)
	Change text size, line wrapping,...
</description></item><item><title>Download StbEmu (Pro) 2.0.17.03</title><pubDate> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 16:44:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-stbemu-pro-9840.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-stbemu-pro-9840.html
</guid><description>
StbEmu is an application for Android 5.0+, allowing downloading IPTV web portals, designed to run on IPTV STB (Set-Top-Box), on devices running Android, such as phones, tablets tablets and TV boxes. Currently, the application supports simulation of many STBs created by the Ukrainian company Infomir, such as MAG 250, MAG 270 or MAG 322.
StbEmu (Pro) for IPTV: Remember that this application is configured for a demo IPTV portal for testing purposes. If you want to use the app, you must...
</description></item></channel></rss>