<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 01:37:07 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 01:37:07 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro 15.25.0829</title><pubDate> Sat, 30 Aug 2025 17:00:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-videotube-downloader-pro-1276.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-videotube-downloader-pro-1276.html
</guid><description>
ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro is the professional version support download videos and playlists from YouTube, videos from Dailymotion, BBC iPlayer, ITV Player, ABC,  FOX,CBS.com Vimeo, Prosieben, Metacafe, Blip.tv CBC.ca many more video sites. After the video is downloaded, you can convert them to the formats compatible with iPad, iPhone, iPod, MPEG-4, H. 264, MP3, AC3.
ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro - Download videos on Youtube
This is one of the software download the most...
</description></item><item><title>Download Bandicam 8.2.1.2530</title><pubDate> Sat, 30 Aug 2025 17:00:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bandicam-243.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bandicam-243.html
</guid><description>
Bandicam is the software screen recording powerful, helps users to record all activities happening on the computer such as video games, presentations,..
Software Bandicam uses graphics technology DirectX / OpenGL will help you carry out a video record with high compression ratio, while keeping the video quality closer to the original work and provide superior performance compared with other programs providing the same functionality.
Bandicam can create video with quality high but...
</description></item><item><title>Download Hypersnap 9.5.4</title><pubDate> Sat, 30 Aug 2025 16:59:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hypersnap-764.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hypersnap-764.html
</guid><description>
Hypersnap is a software screen capture from Windows screen and capture text (TextSnap) from places can't copy normal text. HyperSnap combines the power of screen capture app class with utility image editing advanced is packaged in a easy to use tool! It's perfect for capturing images that you want to put into the help system, online tutorials, manuals, training guides, presentations, marketing materials, website, email, and more. Use HyperSnap to quickly share a picture perfect...
</description></item><item><title>Download Psiphon 186.202500829</title><pubDate> Sat, 30 Aug 2025 16:58:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-psiphon-7347.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-psiphon-7347.html
</guid><description>
Psiphon is a firewall bypass tool by Psiphon Inc. Uses VPN, SSH and HTTP Proxy technology to give you uncensored access to Internet content. Your Psiphon app automatically learns about new hotspots to maximize your chances of bypassing censorship.
The way the software works is that Psiphon constantly changes the proxy, so the user's IP address is also constantly changing, the server will not detect the user's real address, so you can feel free. roof. access to websites and software...
</description></item><item><title>Download RecordFab 1.0.1.5</title><pubDate> Sat, 30 Aug 2025 16:58:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-recordfab-12525.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-recordfab-12525.html
</guid><description>
RecordFab is software that records streaming videos, live and online courses in 720p/1080p quality. Different from regular desktop screen recorders, RecordFab is specifically designed for streaming services. Almost all streaming platforms are supported for recording. RecordFab automatically detects the video stream, eliminating the need for you to set up recording frames, helping to reduce the frustration of accidentally capturing redundant pop-ups during recording.
Currently, RecordFab...
</description></item><item><title>Download CorelDRAW Technical Suite 2025 v26.2.0.170</title><pubDate> Sat, 30 Aug 2025 16:58:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coreldraw-technical-suite-4733.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coreldraw-technical-suite-4733.html
</guid><description>
CorelDRAW Technical Suite 2020 allows you to create instructions for assembly details, instructions, use complex material, face and many more. Achieve superior productivity with the new features, caliber to increase the speed, efficiency and getting full support for the technical standards to publish, share or print with the software sketches and technical illustrations this extension.
CorelDRAW Technical Suite 2020 offers a wide range of design tools and illustrates exactly to create...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Dreamweaver 2021 v21.6.0 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Sat, 30 Aug 2025 16:57:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-0010-adobe-dreamweaver-1701.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-0010-adobe-dreamweaver-1701.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Dreamweaver 2021 is software that provides you with faster, easier ways to design, write code and publish websites and web apps that look great on every screen size. Quickly create and publish websites almost everywhere with the web design software that supports HTML, CSS, JavaScript and more.
After using Adobe Dreamweaver CC, users will quickly create and publish web pages almost everywhere with the web design software that supports HTML, CSS, JavaScript and more. Create, encrypt...
</description></item><item><title>Download Awesome Miner Ultimate 11.2.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 30 Aug 2025 16:56:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-awesome-miner-9041.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-awesome-miner-9041.html
</guid><description>
Awesome Miner is a software application designed to manage and monitor cryptocurrency mining operations. It supports a wide variety of mining hardware, including ASICs and GPUs, and can be used to manage mining for a variety of cryptocurrencies, including Bitcoin, Ethereum, and Litecoin.
Powerful tool to manage and monitor cryptocurrency mining activities. With support for a wide variety of mining hardware and cryptocurrencies, mobile apps, and customizable alerting and performance...
</description></item><item><title>Download Abelssoft YouTube Song Downloader Plus 2025 v25.09</title><pubDate> Sat, 30 Aug 2025 16:56:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-abelssoft-youtube-song-downloader-plus-111.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-abelssoft-youtube-song-downloader-plus-111.html
</guid><description>
Abelssoft YouTube Song Downloader Plus 2018.18.17 Program YouTube Song Downloader Plus will help you search the music and video files from YouTube, after you can download them at. To search for music you just need to enter song name in the required field and you will get results, then you can download all videos and audio files. The program can search the entire album, this function will help to find individual songs from separate albums, because of this we specify the name of the artist...
</description></item><item><title>Download MiniMeters 1.0.17.1913</title><pubDate> Sat, 30 Aug 2025 16:55:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minimeters-9410.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minimeters-9410.html
</guid><description>
MiniMeters is a simple standalone sound meter application for Windows. Monitor your System Audio*, Any Input, or insert the MiniMeter Server Plug-in (VST3/AU/CLAP) at the end of your main channel in the DAW of your choice. Customize the layout in a horizontal bar (perfect for above or below the audio engine of your choice) or pop out into modules to create custom layouts.
Features of MiniMeters
	6 modules to choose from to build your perfect metering setup: Spectrogram, Waveform,...
</description></item><item><title>Download ShaperBox 3 3.5.6</title><pubDate> Sat, 30 Aug 2025 16:55:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-shaperbox-3630.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-shaperbox-3630.html
</guid><description>
Six effects Cableguys strong in a plugin. For with a mixture of modern and inspiring infinite. With six powerful effect - TimeShaper 2 , CrushShaper , VolumeShaper 6 , FilterShaper Core 2 , PanShaper 3 &amp;amp; WidthShaper 2 - ShaperBox 2 to create the effect of music, great rhythm and help solve the problem of mixing complex.
Cableguys ShaperBox 2
Inspired: transform loops, beats, vocals, melodies or bass into the hook addictive to launch the next song of you. Then, finishing a remix of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tixati 3.37</title><pubDate> Sat, 30 Aug 2025 16:55:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tixati-2355.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tixati-2355.html
</guid><description>
A Bittorrent free, good have been updated, are designed for operating systems Microsoft Windows and Linux (for the OS Monday, you can download a version from the official website of the developer). The difference between a client and a large number of others is that users are provided a wide opportunity to control the torrent of them, they also write on your program that it consumes less memory than uTorrent and Halite famous.
Tixati - App download torrent
Tixati is also ready to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cableguys FilterShaper XL 1.0.5</title><pubDate> Sat, 30 Aug 2025 16:54:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cableguys-filtershaper-xl-10972.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cableguys-filtershaper-xl-10972.html
</guid><description>
FilterShaper XL is a plugin developed by Cableguys, a company famous for creating plugins and audio effects. FilterShaper XL is a flexible and powerful tool used in music production and audio processing. It's essentially a filter plugin, offering a variety of audio shaping and tuning capabilities through various filtering techniques.
FilterShaper XL allows users to create complex filter modulations, process audio signals in real time, and create dynamic effects using its advanced...
</description></item><item><title>Download PrivaZer Donors 4.0.110</title><pubDate> Sat, 30 Aug 2025 03:27:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-privazer-donors-198.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-privazer-donors-198.html
</guid><description>
PrivaZer Donors  cleans and removes filth traces from the system. Intensive cleaning of unwanted traces of what you've done, viewed, downloaded, deleted, etc. Take ownership of your security and freedom - Free up disk space. Keep your PC snug and secure !!!
With one click, PrivaZer can safely clean: Internet browsers, Index.dat, Cookies, Tor Cookies, Flash Cookies, Silverlight Cookies, DOM Storing, IndexedDB, AppCache Registry, RAM, Pagefile.sys and Hiberfil.sys files.  PrivaZer  can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Advanced Installer Architect 23.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 30 Aug 2025 03:26:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-installer-128.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-installer-128.html
</guid><description>
Advanced Installer is a Windows utility designed to help you build the package Windows Installer in a working environment clean and intuitive.
Although it has many parameters dedicated but the user interface is very simple and gives users the ability to create new projects by selecting the type, namely installer (for example: application Visual Studio or .NET, pack 32/64-bit mixture), Java , updates, support, mobile devices, and other things.
Advanced Installer - An environment for...
</description></item><item><title>Download CorelDRAW Graphics Suite 2025 v26.2.0.170</title><pubDate> Sat, 30 Aug 2025 03:26:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coreldraw-graphics-suites-01en-1429.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coreldraw-graphics-suites-01en-1429.html
</guid><description>
CorelDRAW Graphics Suite is the software graphic designers with all the tools vector illustration, layout, photo editing and professional design. This is a comprehensive tool to help you work faster, smarter and in more places with software graphics design superiority this.
You will achieve superior productivity with new features are high-calibre program in graphic design this versatile. You will appreciate the process work smoother with support for PDF / X-4 standard and industrial...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cockos REAPER 7.45</title><pubDate> Sat, 30 Aug 2025 03:25:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cockos-reaper-889.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cockos-reaper-889.html
</guid><description>
Cockos REAPER is a powerful software for for windows, chp lets you record, arrange, edit, and display the audio waveform multi-track. Cockos REAPER offers an extensive feature set includes many effects and a sample project. REAPER supports ASIO, Kernel Streaming, WaveOut, and DirectSound for playback and recording. It reads the files in WAV, OGG and MP3 files and records WAV files. You can arrange any number of items in any number of tracks and use plug-in sound processing (DirectX and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Monkeys Audio 11.40</title><pubDate> Sat, 30 Aug 2025 03:25:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-monkeys-audio-949.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-monkeys-audio-949.html
</guid><description>
Monkey\'s Audio is software that compresses digital music without loss of quality. Supports high quality WAV files and CD ripping. Monkeys Audio will compress .wav tracks into .ape files to reduce their size without loss of sound quality, decompress .ape, convert files, check file integrity and manage tags.
Unlike traditional methods like MP3 and OGG, which permanently remove quality to save space, Monkey\'s Audio only creates perfect copies with the same sound quality as the originals....
</description></item><item><title>Download MusConv 4.10.411 Lifetime</title><pubDate> Sat, 30 Aug 2025 03:24:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html
</guid><description>
MusConv transfers playlists, albums, followed artists and liked songs across a variety of services – Spotify, Apple Music, Amazon Music, YouTube, YouTube Music, iTunes, Deezer, Tidal, SoundCloud, Pandora and more 125 music services!
Features of MusConv Ultimate
	Transfer playlists, albums, followed artists and liked tracks between over 125 music servicesManage playlists (Delete, Merge, Split, Copy...)
	More than 125 music services supported
	Access DAILY updated music charts on...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Premiere Pro 2025 v25.4.1.003 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Sat, 30 Aug 2025 03:24:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-premiere-pro-0021-1361.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-premiere-pro-0021-1361.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Premiere Pro is the leading video editing software for film, TV, and the web. Creative tools, integration with other Adobe apps and services, and the power of Adobe Sensei help you turn footage into finished movies and videos in a seamless workflow. It offers high-quality video editing at 4K x 4K resolution and beyond, with 32-bit color, in both RGB and YUV color spaces. Edit audio samples, support for VST audio plug-ins (plug-ins), and 5.1 surround sound tracks. The Premiere Pro...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Lightroom Classic 2025 v14.5.1 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Sat, 30 Aug 2025 03:23:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-photoshop-lightroom-classic-0004-734.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-photoshop-lightroom-classic-0004-734.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Photoshop Lightroom Classic is a desktop-optimized photo editing and organizing software. Lightroom Classic gives you powerful one-click tools and advanced controls to make your photos look great. Easily organize all your photos on your desktop and share them in a variety of ways.
In addition, Lightroom Classic has a powerful import process that allows users to preview images before importing. It supports many camera raw formats and includes a database system for efficient photo...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Media Encoder 2025 v25.4.1.001 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Sat, 30 Aug 2025 03:23:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-0010-adobe-media-encoder-1360.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-0010-adobe-media-encoder-1360.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Media Encoder 2024 is a professional audio and video converter that allows you to encode audio and video files into various distribution formats for applications different uses and audiences. Such video and audio formats are characterized by a high degree of compression. By downloading this program on taiwebs.com, you can export videos in formats supported by various devices, from DVD players and websites to mobile phones, portable media players and High Definition and High...
</description></item><item><title>Download LibreWolf 142.0.1-1</title><pubDate> Sat, 30 Aug 2025 03:22:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-librewolf-11967.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-librewolf-11967.html
</guid><description>
LibreWolf is a customized and independent version of Firefox, with the main goals being user privacy, security and freedom. LibreWolf is designed to provide increased protection against tracking and fingerprinting techniques and includes a number of security enhancements. This is achieved through our security and privacy oriented settings and patches. LibreWolf also aims to remove all telemetry, data collection and annoyances, as well as disable anti-free features like DRM.
LibreWolf...
</description></item><item><title>Download QueueExplorer Professional 5.0.54</title><pubDate> Sat, 30 Aug 2025 03:21:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-queueexplorer-professional-4823.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-queueexplorer-professional-4823.html
</guid><description>
QueueExplorer is a tool indispensable to work with queues and messages: understand and manage your system, find the error and fix it. Or you can use QueueExplorer to sort them by any field available. Because of the sort display the messages in another order with them will be handled, QueueExplorer more columns of Ms Ms # # so you can still see what is processed first.
The features of QueueExplorer
Move, copy or delete messages
	Messages can be handled the same as in process explorer,...
</description></item><item><title>Download HTML Compiler 2025.17</title><pubDate> Sat, 30 Aug 2025 03:21:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-html-compiler-2548.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-html-compiler-2548.html
</guid><description>
HTML Compiler is a program for Microsoft Windows (tm) allows you to put an entire HTML application (including HTML, CSS, JavaScript, images, etc.) into a Windows application independent can be executed like any other application window the application. HTML Compiler allows you to customize file real exam results by changing the icon of them and set some other options. For example, you can allow or not allow the ability to print the HTML pages, allow or disallow the text selection and many,...
</description></item></channel></rss>