<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 19:55:23 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 19:55:23 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Bitsum Process Lasso Pro 16.0.2.10</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Sep 2025 17:21:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bitsum-process-lasso-pro-289.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bitsum-process-lasso-pro-289.html
</guid><description>
Bitsum Process Lasso Pro is software compact statistics and troubleshoot computer systems, such as crashes by control CPU. Technological process Lassos ProBalance (process balance) adjust the smart priority of running programs so that the process works poorly or too active will not affect the ability to use your computer!
Software Process Lasso to help manage the program or application will be managed and controlled to not have the ability to monopolize the CPU. Process Lasso also...
</description></item><item><title>Download StartAllBack 3.9.14.5310</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Sep 2025 17:21:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-startallback-6857.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-startallback-6857.html
</guid><description>
With the official release of Windows 11, chances are that most of you want to try it out. As the name suggests, StartAllBack is a small, lightweight tool that can help you enjoy the power of the new operating system while keeping the look and feel, especially because main work area, desktop of Windows 7, Windows 10 as taskbars and start menu styles.
StartAllBack is specially designed for Windows 11 and will not work on any older operating systems. If you want to get the start menu back...
</description></item><item><title>Download dslrBooth Photo Booth Software Pro 7.48.0903.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Sep 2025 17:20:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dslrbooth-photo-booth-software-666.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dslrbooth-photo-booth-software-666.html
</guid><description>
Photo Booth Software is a software to create, list and combine the images back together in the same theme as travel, haloween. Created by the professional photographer for the operator photo booth at all skill levels, photo booth software dslrBooth built from scratch with the sole purpose of running the photo booth. The software uses the latest technology to provide you and your guests, high quality prints and the ability to share photos and GIF on the means of social media including...
</description></item><item><title>Download WindowTop Pro 5.28.4</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Sep 2025 17:20:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windowtop-6955.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windowtop-6955.html
</guid><description>
WindowTop is a program that pins windows on Desktop, in other words it sets the window to float above all other program windows, creating transparency for the windows. that window via a dedicated slider, which supports adjusting transparency, changing the color of application windows or similar programs with the dark theme of the Windows 10 operating system, creating contrast and reducing tension straight, painful for the eyes.
Features of WindowTop
	Put window on top
	Set window to...
</description></item><item><title>Download n-Track Studio Suite 10.2.2.10182</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Sep 2025 17:19:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-n-track-studio-2991.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-n-track-studio-2991.html
</guid><description>
n-Track Studio is a recording software allows you record and create MIDI music and sounds top quality. The software allows you to add effects, VST3, DirectX, AU (Mac), VST and ReWire different on each track or channel. This program also allows you to automatically fade out, fade in and fade out or increase the volume of the music to indicate the voice of the singer.
n-Track Studio can record and playback the number of audio, MIDI and sound unlimited. In addition, you can handle the...
</description></item><item><title>Download xplorer2 Professional / Ultimate 6.2.0.3</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Sep 2025 17:18:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xplorer2-ultimate-1024.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xplorer2-ultimate-1024.html
</guid><description>
Xplorer2 Ultimate is software, file manager replaces Windows explorer traditional with more advanced functions and flexibility. Xplorer2 Ultimate give the user the extension name space, such as FTP, zipprinters, webprinters, v. v. the model browser, find the ratio of good up large folders with thousands of files. Software, quick read, providing image filters and a variety of selection mechanism that allows you to manage your files effectively.
Xplorer2 Ultimate - file Management,...
</description></item><item><title>Download NWinfo 1.4.3</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Sep 2025 17:13:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nwinfo-12590.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nwinfo-12590.html
</guid><description>
NWinfo is a Win32 program that allows you to obtain system and hardware information. It displays essential information about CPU, memory, disk, network, and even system operating details. Because it's portable, you can carry NWinfo on a USB stick and use it on any Windows machine, making it a useful tool for both tech enthusiasts and troubleshooters.
Features of NWinfo
	Get detailed information about SMBIOS, CPUID, S.M.A.R.T., PCI, EDID, etc.
	Supports export in JSON, YAML and LUA...
</description></item><item><title>Download XL-Connector 3.6.8.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Sep 2025 17:12:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xl-connector-12415.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xl-connector-12415.html
</guid><description>
XL-Connector is a popular plugin that securely integrates Excel and Salesforce to export, import, refresh and transform data seamlessly with ultra-fast api connection. It provides Salesforce administrators with a comprehensive toolbox that easily performs data and metadata management activities in a familiar Excel environment.
Features
Export from Salesforce to Excel
	Get data from existing Salesforce reports or build your own SOQL queries directly into Excel.
Import data into...
</description></item><item><title>Download Picture Window Pro 8.0.526</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Sep 2025 17:12:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-picture-window-pro-7452.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-picture-window-pro-7452.html
</guid><description>
Picture Window Pro is a powerful image editing tool designed for serious photographers with strict creative and quality standards. Its comprehensive set of photo editing and editing tools let you control and shape every aspect of your images.
Picture Window Pro 8 is a complete rewrite of Picture Window Pro 7. It features non-destructive image editing through a novel interface based on an image tree. It also fully supports large, high-resolution displays and can be used in dual monitor...
</description></item><item><title>Download Advanced Renamer Commercial 4.16.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Sep 2025 17:10:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-renamer-2647.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-renamer-2647.html
</guid><description>
Advanced Renamer is a program to rename multiple files and folders at the same time. By configuring the method name change, the name can be manipulated in many different ways. It's easy to set up a batch job using multiple methods on a large number of files. 14 different modes allow you to change the name, attributes and timestamp of the file in once. The file can also be copied or moved to new location based on information in the file.
The program can rename files in many different ways,...
</description></item><item><title>Download AutoHideDesktopIcons 6.51</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Sep 2025 17:10:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-autohidedesktopicons-1747.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-autohidedesktopicons-1747.html
</guid><description>
AutoHideDesktopIcons allows you to automatically hide the icons on his screen after some seconds of inactivity, certain to your screen is not cluttered and your wallpaper in full view. The program works very similar to the screen saver, but instead of making the desktop look your beautiful eyes, it makes it look clean.
AutoHideDesktopIcons - Hides icons on the Desktop
Must say that AutoHideDesktopIcons is software features auto hide and show on the computer screen. It has a lot of apps...
</description></item><item><title>Download Flyby11 1.7.277</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Sep 2025 17:10:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-flyby11-12467.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-flyby11-12467.html
</guid><description>
Flyby11 is a simple patcher that removes annoying restrictions that prevent you from installing Windows 11 (24H2) on unsupported hardware. Do you have an old PC? No TPM, Secure Boot or your processor is not supported? Flyby11 allows you to install Windows 11 24H2. There are no complicated steps. Just run the tool and you'll be running Windows 11 on your outdated machine in no time.
Technical overview
Flyby11 takes advantage of a feature of the Windows 11 setup process that uses the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Database Tour Pro 11.5.4.1905</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Sep 2025 17:09:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-database-tour-pro-5321.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-database-tour-pro-5321.html
</guid><description>
Database Tour Pro application is a comprehensive software that allows you to organize all the database is connected his. It provides support for Borland Database Engine (BDE) and Microsoft ActiveX Data Objects (ADO), SQL scripts, reports, along with conversion and data export, among others.
It contains a browser object for the function, package, triggers, folders, users, roles, profiles, sequences, work, style, Java, exception, link, database, general properties, table, schema, and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Advanced CSV Converter 7.80</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Sep 2025 17:09:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-csv-converter-4508.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-csv-converter-4508.html
</guid><description>
Advanced CSV Converter is a conversion tool CSV to DBF, Excel (XLS, XLSX), TXT, HTML, PRG, XML, SQL, RTF. To convert a file, the program provides an interface controlled by the wizard, guides you step by step conversion. Use the wizard, you select file input, select the format and destination folder. If necessary, you can set the filter switch according to the example and select columns you want to exclude from the process. When the conversion process is started, the program will extract...
</description></item><item><title>Download AmoyShare AnyVid 10.8.5</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Sep 2025 17:08:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-amoyshare-anyvid-7833.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-amoyshare-anyvid-7833.html
</guid><description>
AmoyShare AnyVid is the best video downloader that allows you to download videos from 1000+ websites. It offers HD video downloads of various categories, including streaming videos, TV episodes, TV series and more. Besides video format, you can directly convert video to MP4 or MP3 with the best video downloader.
Easy to download videos from any website, such as TikTok, Facebook, Instagram, Reddit, Tumblr, Twitch, Niconico, V Live, Naver, Lynda, TED Talk. With AmoyShare AnyVid, you can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Flyoobe 1.7.277</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Sep 2025 17:08:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oobelux-13956.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oobelux-13956.html
</guid><description>
Flyoobe was born out of the frustration many users felt with the Windows 11 setup experience. Whether it was the mandatory online account, the endless "Next, next, next..." screens, or the incomplete configuration options when you finally reached the desktop, the current setup lacked focus on what users really wanted.
Why choose Flyoobe?
	Simplifies the Windows 11 setup process right out of the box.
	Allows easy local account creation without need to hunt for hidden options.
	Includes...
</description></item><item><title>Download EstlCAM 12.146</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Sep 2025 17:07:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-estlcam-13476.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-estlcam-13476.html
</guid><description>
EstlCAM is a user-friendly CNC and CAM (Computer-Aided Manufacturing) control software, designed to generate toolpaths and G-code for CNC machines, especially suitable for 2D, 2.5D and 3D milling operations. The software supports importing a variety of design file formats, including 2D drawings (.dxf, .svg, .png, .jpg) and 3D models (.stl), allowing users to position, scale, and rotate designs before generating toolpaths.
The software is especially popular among enthusiasts and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Macro Expert Enterprise 4.9.8.5</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Sep 2025 14:19:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-macro-expert-enterprise-3558.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-macro-expert-enterprise-3558.html
</guid><description>
Macro Expert Enterprise is a powerful tool that will help you save time and money by empowering you to automate fully the work repetitive and regular. Macro Expert Enterprise can simplify a lot of work your computer, providing more than 260 action will meet most all your needs, automate your task. To keep they have the ability to access and organize high Macro Expert Enterprise split these actions into separate groups: Email, Excel document, database, Text, window, FTP, Internet, File,...
</description></item><item><title>Download AmoyShare AnyMusic 10.8.5</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Sep 2025 14:17:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-amoyshare-anymusic-14132.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-amoyshare-anymusic-14132.html
</guid><description>
AmoyShare AnyMusic is a multi-purpose music downloader and player. The app allows users to search, explore and download unlimited high-quality music (MP3, M4A, WebM, etc.) from over 1,000 online music streaming sites, including SoundCloud, Bandcamp, TikTok, etc. Users can download entire playlists, batch download multiple songs, and enjoy music offline with the built-in music player. The software supports music video downloading and provides fast download speed with multi-threading...
</description></item><item><title>Download Omidsoft Red Burner 18.25</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Sep 2025 01:34:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-red-burner-10119.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-red-burner-10119.html
</guid><description>
Red Burner is a lightweight burning software based on Blue Burner with full functionality to work with ISO/CUE images and drives. Start the move to a lightweight, yet powerful, and time-saving standalone optical disc burner with the simplest user interface and fastest possible burning algorithm.
Features of Red Burner
	Fastest possible CD/DVD/BD burning algorithm
	Standard, dual-layer and high-capacity media recording
	Browse ISO/CUE images via internal image browser
	Writable M-Disc,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Acrobat Reader DC 2025.001.20672</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Sep 2025 01:34:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-acrobat-reader-3707.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-acrobat-reader-3707.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Acrobat Reader DC is a system of application software and Web services developed by Adobe Systems to view, create, manipulate, print and manage PDF files. With Adobe Acrobat Reader DC, you can create, export, edit, and track PDF files from anywhere - and maintain connection with the recent set of files on all your devices.
Adobe Acrobat Reader current DC is connected with Adobe Document Cloud - help working on the computers and mobile devices becomes easier than ever before. This is...
</description></item><item><title>Download Typora 1.11.7</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Sep 2025 01:32:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-typora-6764.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-typora-6764.html
</guid><description>
Typora gives you a seamless experience as both a reader and a writer. It removes the preview window, the mode switcher, the syntax symbols of the markup source code, and all other unnecessary distractions. Instead, it provides an actual live preview to help you focus on the content itself.
Features of Typora:
	Typora allows you to manage your files easily, providing both a file tree panel and a side panel (file list).
	Automatically view the Outline structure of your document in the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Draftable Desktop 25.9.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Sep 2025 01:31:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-draftable-desktop-3749.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-draftable-desktop-3749.html
</guid><description>
Draftable Desktop is comparison tool documents the fastest. Compare over 300 pages in a few seconds. Draftable Desktop 2.0 is now available - faster and stronger than ever! See all the changes in your documents, locally and online. Take your work to the next level. Compare secret and private do not use the internet and your documents never leave your computer. Specifically, Draftable Desktop compatible with .xls, .xlsx, .xlsxm. With Office 2013, 2016 or 365, you can compare text in...
</description></item><item><title>Download Canvas X Pro 20.0.1009</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Sep 2025 01:31:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-acd-systems-canvas-x-821.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-acd-systems-canvas-x-821.html
</guid><description>
Canvas X is an environment fully integrated to illustrations, page layouts, images, presentations, and Web publishing. Canvas lets you work with vector objects, images, text and graphics are entered that do not have to switch to other apps. Whether you are a beginner or an experienced design, the tools and features in Canvas can make you more effective.
ACD Systems Canvas X - design, illustration, technical
ACD Systems Canvas X : illustration, design and share technical illustrations...
</description></item><item><title>Download Macro Commander Pro+ 2.6.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Sep 2025 01:31:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-macro-commander-pro-12815.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-macro-commander-pro-12815.html
</guid><description>
Macro Commander is an all-in-one data entry and desktop automation software. It is designed to empower users to easily create, manage, and trigger macros and scripts to automate manual, repetitive tasks quickly and error-free. Its clean user interface allows for quick and easy creation and organization of macros either manually or using the built-in macro recorder.
While Macro Commander offers powerful data entry features to quickly and easily fill in data in other applications, it also...
</description></item></channel></rss>