<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 10:13:58 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 10:13:58 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Internet Download Manager (IDM) 6.42 Build 61</title><pubDate> Fri, 20 Feb 2026 01:17:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-inetnet-download-manager-161.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-inetnet-download-manager-161.html
</guid><description>
Internet Download Manager is the download acceleration software, the best download support now, it can help you speed up the download up to five times, continue and schedule downloads. The latest version of IDM adds the compatibility of Windows 10 and Windows 11, it has supported all current popular browsers such as Internet Explorer, Mozilla Firefox, Opera, Google Chrome, ..
Download IDM with the latest version on taiwebs.com making it easy to download and manage your downloaded files...
</description></item><item><title>Download IDM Retail 6.42 Build 61</title><pubDate> Fri, 20 Feb 2026 01:17:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-internet-download-manager-retail-3609.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-internet-download-manager-retail-3609.html
</guid><description>
IDM - Internet Download Manager Retail is a reliable utility and high efficiency will help you to increase your download speed and manage download at better. The program allows you to easily schedule, pause and resume downloads with a single click. Moreover, the application provides error resilience robust and can restart the download at the interrupted or broken. You can restore the download is interrupted due to network problems, lost connections, unexpected power outages, computer...
</description></item><item><title>Download CrystalMark Retro 2.0.7</title><pubDate> Fri, 20 Feb 2026 01:16:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-crystalmark-retro-11737.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-crystalmark-retro-11737.html
</guid><description>
CrystalMark Retro allows you to evaluate hard drive performance thoroughly. With CrystalMark Retro, you can measure both sequential and random read/write speeds of your hard drive. Sequential read/write speed refers to the speed of accessing data in a linear or sequential manner, while random read/write speed refers to the speed of accessing data in a non-sequential or random manner . By measuring these speeds, you can better understand your hard drive's overall performance and identify...
</description></item><item><title>Download ColorPicker Max 6.9.0.2602</title><pubDate> Fri, 20 Feb 2026 01:10:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-colorpicker-7039.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-colorpicker-7039.html
</guid><description>
ColorPicker is a modern color picker for developers available on Windows. This is the next major evolution of the existing ColorPicker 2 software, released in 2020.
ColorPicker allows you to choose a color from your monitor, or you can choose it manually; it will then save the color history so you can go back and review the selected colors. ColorPicker can also randomize a color for you if you want. Then the color can be converted to another (RGB, HEX, HSL, HSV, CMYK). It has a sleek...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Acrobat Pro DC 2025.001.21223 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Fri, 20 Feb 2026 00:49:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-001en-adobe-acrobat-pro-458.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-001en-adobe-acrobat-pro-458.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Acrobat Pro DC is a comprehensive software that helps you create and edit the PDF&amp;nbsp;document, or create form, sign, protect PDF, connect, split PDF, export PDF to various formats. The Acrobat Pro DC is the latest version of Adobe with improvements in the interface with the polished ribbon bar and the ability to create and handle pdf files as well as its male versions.
The highlight of the Acrobat Pro DC is probably the ability to connect, store documents on the cloud, you can...
</description></item><item><title>Download DesktopOK 12.31</title><pubDate> Thu, 19 Feb 2026 23:56:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopok-1635.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopok-1635.html
</guid><description>
DesktopOK is software save and restore the positions of icons. DesktopOK also offers a solution small but effective for the user to change the screen resolution often. DesktopOK is not installed and can be executed easily from the desktop, and can be carried on a small USB or memory device to another. Start of the program. The first time you use the program, the program will show you screen license. Free program and license info is only displayed the first time (on each PC).
DesktopOK -...
</description></item><item><title>Download Master PDF Editor 5.9.96</title><pubDate> Thu, 19 Feb 2026 23:55:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-master-pdf-editor-612.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-master-pdf-editor-612.html
</guid><description>
Master PDF Editor is a powerful software that helps users to view, create and modify PDF documents or combine multiple files into one, split a source document into several documents, and also review, sign, and encrypt PDF files. With Master PDF Editor you can add text with any format to documents in PDF or edit existing text. You can also insert images into your document, select and move the object, change the size of the object save image to a file and copy them to the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Net Monitor for Employees Professional 6.5.3</title><pubDate> Thu, 19 Feb 2026 23:54:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-network-lookout-net-monitor-for-employees-professional-2098.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-network-lookout-net-monitor-for-employees-professional-2098.html
</guid><description>
Network LookOut Net Monitor for Employees Professional is a software platform to help manage user activity, gives the ability to inspect and control computer activities, as well as record activity on the screen as AVI file. Net Monitor for Employees Professional allows access from remote computers. This feature proved particularly useful when you want to see the activity of each user on the computer, or assist them perform the work on the computer with the mouse manipulation or the...
</description></item><item><title>Download EarthTime 6.31.3</title><pubDate> Thu, 19 Feb 2026 23:53:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-earthtime-185.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-earthtime-185.html
</guid><description>
EarthTime is software that displays the time and date local time of any place in the world. This application has database integration good for 3000 city, users can manually add, download at EarthTime if you want to. EarthTime allows you to install for the time zone and current local time.EarthTime displays the Earth according to the view night and day, you can view the map in full screen mode.
EarthTime
The feature on EarthTime
	EarthTime allows users to interact with visualization...
</description></item><item><title>Download Opera GX (Gaming Browser) 127.0.5778.75</title><pubDate> Thu, 19 Feb 2026 23:52:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-gx-3170.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-gx-3170.html
</guid><description>
Opera GX is a special version of the Opera browser is built to complement gamers avid. Browser this game comes with the unique features to help users make maximum use of both the game and their browser. Opera GX is built specifically to support the game. This browser includes the unique features to help users have the best experience when gaming and surfing the web.
Opera GX - special browser for gamers
GX Control allows you to set a limit on the level of use RAM, CPU and network where...
</description></item><item><title>Download Red Gate SmartAssembly Professional 8.4.3.6747</title><pubDate> Thu, 19 Feb 2026 23:51:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-red-gate-smartassembly-1593.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-red-gate-smartassembly-1593.html
</guid><description>
Red Gate SmartAssembly is a tool that helps protect your application against reverse engineering or modifications prevent side Tuesday access to source code. This comprehensive solution protects the data card of you and more likely to report errors. This program makes files difficult can disassemble and injection code does not use, to help engineer can reverse and understand the core structure of the code. With your smartphone, you will have many features to tamper with the code as the...
</description></item><item><title>Download AB Download Manager 1.8.7</title><pubDate> Thu, 19 Feb 2026 23:50:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ab-download-manager-12399.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ab-download-manager-12399.html
</guid><description>
With this application, you can easily download files from anywhere. Enjoy fast, free downloads with seamless browser extension support. It is built to be a desktop application that allows you to manage and organize your downloads better than before.
AB Download Manager features
	Simple and modern UI: Simple UI and dark mode by default
	Faster download speeds: Download files using multiple connections to increase your download speed by up to 500%
	Download Queue: Create and manage your...
</description></item><item><title>Download Monkeys Audio 12.31</title><pubDate> Thu, 19 Feb 2026 23:49:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-monkeys-audio-949.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-monkeys-audio-949.html
</guid><description>
Monkey\'s Audio is software that compresses digital music without loss of quality. Supports high quality WAV files and CD ripping. Monkeys Audio will compress .wav tracks into .ape files to reduce their size without loss of sound quality, decompress .ape, convert files, check file integrity and manage tags.
Unlike traditional methods like MP3 and OGG, which permanently remove quality to save space, Monkey\'s Audio only creates perfect copies with the same sound quality as the originals....
</description></item><item><title>Download PDQ Inventory 19.6.39.0 Enterprise</title><pubDate> Thu, 19 Feb 2026 23:48:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdq-inventory-1468.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdq-inventory-1468.html
</guid><description>
PDQ Inventory is a software application to manage your system. This software will be able to manage your system by scanning the Windows operating system of you to provide information hardware, software, and configuration for the Windows operating system in your your tools. The tools available in this software helps you can scan the computer correctly.
In addition, the software PDQ Inventory can give you very detailed information. This software application is one of the management...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaMonkey Gold 2024.2.1.3210 RC3</title><pubDate> Thu, 19 Feb 2026 23:47:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediamonkey-gold-231.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediamonkey-gold-231.html
</guid><description>
MediaMonkey Gold is music manager and music player multimedia for the music collection and iPod users. MediaMonkey lists the audio file of you as CD, OGG, WMA, MPC, FLAC, APE, WAV and MP3 and includes the edit smart card and an automatic file and folder to arrange your music library.
MediaMonkey Gold also has CD ripper, CD / DVD Burner, and audio converter for saving music, and manual or editor list automatically to create mixed music.
Features MediaMonkey Gold
	Automatically find...
</description></item><item><title>Download DeskSoft EarthView 7.14.3</title><pubDate> Thu, 19 Feb 2026 23:46:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desksoft-earthview-184.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desksoft-earthview-184.html
</guid><description>
With software DeskSoft EarthView you can easily create wallpapers to your computer or select screen saver of your favorite. the program can change day and night, the clouds will also change according to weather conditions current on one or another part of the earth, you can see the lights of the city.
Features of DeskSoft EarthView can be interesting, because of DeskSoft EarthView support for day and night, you can view atmospheric phenomena, light city can see, the cloud is displayed,...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDQ Deploy 19.6.39.0 Enterprise</title><pubDate> Thu, 19 Feb 2026 23:45:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdq-deploy-1469.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdq-deploy-1469.html
</guid><description>
PDQ Deploy Enterprise is an application to keep the Windows PC and the programs installed on it. Software PDQ Deploy helps you to connect multiple patch or a windows app (.exe, .msi) with multiple operating systems. The deployment software can be install, delete, run script, reboot, copy the file, sliding mode, send messages, etc.
PDQ Deploy Enterprise
Features of PDQ Deploy Enterprise
	Send notifications (alerts) via email
	Run the script as popular as .vbs, .reg .bat and .ps1
	Run...
</description></item><item><title>Download Rollback Rx Pro 12.9 Build 2711739098</title><pubDate> Thu, 19 Feb 2026 23:44:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rollback-rx-pro-387.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rollback-rx-pro-387.html
</guid><description>
Rollback Rx Pro is recovery software for instant data, this solution is system restore Windows comprehensive. It allows users and IT administrators to easily restore their PC on any state earlier in few seconds! RollBack Rx offers a fresh approach to the management PC. Any unforeseen incidents such as user errors, viruses, or even installed software is error can be easily and completely reversed.
Features Rollback Rx Pro
	Restore back to any previous point in time in few...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Acrobat Reader DC 2025.001.21223</title><pubDate> Thu, 19 Feb 2026 23:43:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-acrobat-reader-3707.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-acrobat-reader-3707.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Acrobat Reader DC is a system of application software and Web services developed by Adobe Systems to view, create, manipulate, print and manage PDF files. With Adobe Acrobat Reader DC, you can create, export, edit, and track PDF files from anywhere - and maintain connection with the recent set of files on all your devices.
Adobe Acrobat Reader current DC is connected with Adobe Document Cloud - help working on the computers and mobile devices becomes easier than ever before. This is...
</description></item><item><title>Download Free Download Manager 6.33.1.6644</title><pubDate> Thu, 19 Feb 2026 16:31:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-download-manager-3105.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-download-manager-3105.html
</guid><description>
Free Download Manager is free application download manager, Free Download Manager will significantly increase downloads by splitting the files into several smaller parts and then downloads at the same time. Speed your download will be significantly increased. Manager download free can also continue to download at broken or not responding, so you don't need start downloading from the beginning after occasionally interrupted.
Free Download Manager - Manage and speed up downloads
You can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Text Editor Pro 35.4.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 19 Feb 2026 16:29:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-text-editor-pro-800.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-text-editor-pro-800.html
</guid><description>
Text Editor Pro is software to handle text, HTML, Perl, Ruby, or Fortran with features syntax highlighting, professional. Text Editor provides syntax highlighting for over 50 scripts and has a simple interface and easy access. In addition, the Text Editor Pro also supports more than 50 programming languages like C ++, COBOL, graph DOT, DSP, DWScript, Fortran, Foxpro, Java, Perl, Python, Ruby, SQL and many other languages.
Text Editor Pro - text Processing professional
The software can...
</description></item><item><title>Download ALLPlayer 9.6.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 19 Feb 2026 16:28:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allplayer-2522.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allplayer-2522.html
</guid><description>
ALLPlayer is perhaps the most popular program for watching movies with subtitles matching . It play all media formats know files, RAR and more can LiveUpdate function is implemented to update the latest codecs if there is a problem with opening a movie file. The program also automatically searches for matching subtitles in all languages . Subtitles smart to keep subtitles on the screen for the period of time required for you to read them. AVI Doctor helps when you are downloading a torrent...
</description></item><item><title>Download ACDSee Luxea Video Editor Pro 8.0.2.3533</title><pubDate> Thu, 19 Feb 2026 16:27:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-acdsee-luxea-video-editor-5312.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-acdsee-luxea-video-editor-5312.html
</guid><description>
ACDSee Luxea Video Editor is a software simple and effective to edit and edit all types of video files (with the ability to record video from the screen), unlike the video editing software professional and heavy the other, with the environment simple and easy, the task video editing for non-professional users he's doing that. Using software ACDSee Luxea Video Editor, you can edit or mixed film and do things like quickly edit audio and video of the video file, set video effects, simple to...
</description></item><item><title>Download CoolUtils Total Doc Converter 5.1.0.376/148</title><pubDate> Thu, 19 Feb 2026 16:26:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-total-doc-converter-84.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-total-doc-converter-84.html
</guid><description>
CoolUtils Total Doc Converter Program that will allow you to document conversion DOC to others, the list can be viewed on the official website or you can watch carefully the screenshot, I think the question would no longer can download CoolUtils Total Doc Converter below. There is batch processing,in general, everything is convenient, I hope you like it.
Total Doc Converter is conversion tools text comprehensive and multi-featured, very necessary when storing or printing the text. It also...
</description></item><item><title>Download ExpanDrive 2026.02.09</title><pubDate> Thu, 19 Feb 2026 16:25:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-expandrive-609.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-expandrive-609.html
</guid><description>
ExpanDrive is software sync cloud storage strong support BackBlaze B2, Google Team Drive, SMB / CIFS and new interface and easy user search file version, share links and much more.  ExpanDrive mapped network drives for macOS and Micosoft Windows connect with all the provide major cloud storage such as Dropbox, Google Drive, Google Team Drive, Amazon Drive, Box, OneDrive, OneDrive for Business, Sharepoint, Openstack Swift , BackBlaze B2, Amazon S3 or SFTP servers, FTP or WebDAV on your own...
</description></item></channel></rss>