<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 20:11:55 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 20:11:55 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download MobiOffice: Word, Sheets, PDF 16.1.58761</title><pubDate> Wed, 14 Jan 2026 23:09:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-officesuite-word-sheets-pdf-8508.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-officesuite-word-sheets-pdf-8508.html
</guid><description>
OfficeSuite allows you to easily view, edit, and create Word, Excel, and PowerPoint documents and perform advanced PDF operations. Our integrated file manager, Chat app with document exchange capabilities, and tons of other handy tools make this the most feature-rich mobile office solution available on Android. Pre-installed by leading manufacturers including Sony, ZTE, Amazon, Sharp, Acer, CAT, Alcatel, Kyocera, Toshiba, etc.
Features of OfficeSuite for Android
	View, create, and...
</description></item><item><title>Download AnExplorer Pro File Manager 5.9.4</title><pubDate> Wed, 14 Jan 2026 23:09:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-file-manager-pro-tv-usb-otg-8358.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-file-manager-pro-tv-usb-otg-8358.html
</guid><description>
AnExplorer File Explorer is a unique file manager for TV and Watch file management tool. It is simple, small, fast and efficient File Explorer. Only file managers support RTL and display the size of folders on storage. It is designed for all devices including Phones, Phablets, Tablets, Watches and TVs. It is completely designed using Material Design.
Pro TV USBOTG File Manager Features
	Full-featured It provides all file management features including cut, copy, delete, rename,...
</description></item><item><title>Download SAI: Split APKs Installer 2.1.8</title><pubDate> Wed, 14 Jan 2026 23:08:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sai-split-apks-installer-14094.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sai-split-apks-installer-14094.html
</guid><description>
SAI – Fast Split APK Installer for Android. Easily install APK, XAPK, APKM and split APK on your Android device. Whether you need to install large games, APK packages or .apks files, SAI makes it fast, safe and easy.
Key Features
Fast APK &amp;amp; XAPK Installer: Install APK, XAPK and APKM formats without errors. Supports large apps, games, and APK packages of any size.
APK Installer &amp;amp; Split APK Packages: Easily install split APKs and APK packages from any source. Batch...
</description></item><item><title>Download YoWindow Weather - Unlimited 2.55.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 14 Jan 2026 23:08:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-yowindow-weather-unlimited-8421.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-yowindow-weather-unlimited-8421.html
</guid><description>
YoWindow is a unique new weather app. The magic of YoWindow is a living landscape that reflects your real-life weather. For example, if it rains - it will rain in YoWindow. Sunset and sunrise in YoWindow take place at the same time as in real life. But the cool thing is you can roll time forward. Just swipe the screen and you'll see how the weather changes throughout the day.
YoWindow Weather Features - Unlimited
	All the weather at your fingertips. You see the current weather,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Folder Player Pro 5.37 build 363</title><pubDate> Wed, 14 Jan 2026 23:08:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-folder-player-pro-8330.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-folder-player-pro-8330.html
</guid><description>
Folder Player Pro is a mobile music player application available for Android devices. It allows users to play and organize their music files by folders, instead of just by artist or album. This app is perfect for users who have a lot of music files on their device and want to listen to them in a more organized way.
Features of Folder Player Pro APK
	Ability to play music files by folder, making it easy to find and listen to specific songs or albums
	Supports many audio file formats,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Smart Launcher 6 ‧ Home Screen 6.6 build 001</title><pubDate> Wed, 14 Jan 2026 23:07:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-smart-launcher-8412.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-smart-launcher-8412.html
</guid><description>
Smart Launcher is a mobile app that provides users with a customized home screen and app launcher on their Android devices. It includes features like minimalist interface, automatic app sorting, and gesture controls. The app also includes many customizable settings, such as the ability to change the theme, icon size, and screen layout, as well as the ability to create custom categories for the app.
Smart Launcher Features
	Ambient theme: Smart launcher automatically changes theme...
</description></item><item><title>Download Duolingo: language lessons 6.61.4</title><pubDate> Wed, 14 Jan 2026 23:07:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-duolingo-language-lessons-8265.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-duolingo-language-lessons-8265.html
</guid><description>
Duolingo is a popular language learning app that offers interactive lessons to help users learn new languages. This application offers many languages for you to choose from, including Spanish, French, German, Italian, Portuguese, Chinese, Japanese and many more.
This app offers an gamified learning experience with interactive lessons, exercises, and quizzes designed to help users learn new words, phrases, and grammar rules. This app is designed to be easy to use and suitable for people...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Photoshop Express Photo Editor 17.8.20 build 1994</title><pubDate> Wed, 14 Jan 2026 23:07:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-photoshop-express-photo-editor-02en-8249.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-photoshop-express-photo-editor-02en-8249.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Photoshop Express is a mobile photo editing app that allows users to edit photos quickly and easily on their Android devices. Join millions of creators who trust and use Adobe Photoshop Express, one of the best photo editors and collage makers on Android for fast, easy, and powerful editing on mobile devices.
Premium version / No Adobe ID account required
Features of Adobe Photoshop Express APK
	Basic photo editing: Users can crop, rotate, adjust brightness, contrast and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Lucky Patcher 11.9.9</title><pubDate> Wed, 14 Jan 2026 23:06:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-lucky-patcher-11914.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-lucky-patcher-11914.html
</guid><description>
Lucky Patcher is a free Android app that can modify many apps and games, Block ads, remove unwanted system apps, backup apps before and after modification, Move apps apps to SD card, remove license verification from paid apps and games, etc.
Lucky Patcher features and details:
	Remove or block ads on Android apps and games. You can easily block ads with Lucky Patcher.
	Block in-app purchase verification with the app. You can use premium apps and games for free by removing in-app...
</description></item><item><title>Download WolframAlpha Classic 1.4.27.20251229578</title><pubDate> Wed, 14 Jan 2026 23:06:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wolframalpha-classic-11267.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wolframalpha-classic-11267.html
</guid><description>
Use the computational intelligence power of Wolfram to answer your questions. Built on more than 35 years of development led by Stephen Wolfram, Wolfram|Alpha is the world's source for instant computing and expert knowledge.
Across thousands of continuously added domains Wolfram|Alpha uses a vast collection of algorithms and data to calculate answers and generate reports for you.
Use Wolfram|Alpha to calculate the following information and more
	Identify an aircraft.
	Learn the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Battery HD Pro 1.99.43</title><pubDate> Wed, 14 Jan 2026 23:05:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-battery-hd-pro-8140.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-battery-hd-pro-8140.html
</guid><description>
Battery HD Pro is the perfect battery monitor for your phone or tablet. It's simple, beautiful, and can be specially calibrated for your device. Battery HD Pro is an application designed to help users monitor their device's battery usage and optimize device performance. Some features of this application include:
	Monitor battery usage: The app shows the remaining battery percentage and the estimated time remaining until the battery is depleted.
	Charging History: The app tracks the...
</description></item><item><title>Download 365Scores: Live Scores &amp;amp; News 14.5.3</title><pubDate> Wed, 14 Jan 2026 23:05:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-365scores-live-scores-news-8220.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-365scores-live-scores-news-8220.html
</guid><description>
365Scores is a sports app that provides users with real-time scores, statistics, and news for many sports including football, basketball, soccer, and more. Some features of the application include:
	Live scores and notifications: 365Scores provides live scores and push notifications for many sports, including football, soccer, basketball, baseball, etc.
	Match statistics: The app includes detailed match statistics such as ball control, number of shots on goal, etc.
	Latest News:...
</description></item><item><title>Download QuickEdit Text Editor Pro 1.12.5 build 260</title><pubDate> Wed, 14 Jan 2026 23:05:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-quickedit-text-editor-pro-9059.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-quickedit-text-editor-pro-9059.html
</guid><description>
QuickEdit is a fast, stable and full-featured text editor for Android devices. It has been optimized for both phones and tablets. This app is designed to provide a variety of features and tools that make editing and formatting text on mobile devices as easy and efficient as possible.
QuickEdit Text Editor Pro Features
	Advanced notepad application with many improvements.
	Code editor and syntax highlighting for over 40 languages ​​(C++, C#, Java, XML, Javascript, Markdown, PHP,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Weather - Meteored Pro News 8.9.5_pro</title><pubDate> Wed, 14 Jan 2026 23:04:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-weather-meteored-pro-news-10473.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-weather-meteored-pro-news-10473.html
</guid><description>
With the Weather - Meteored Pro News app, you get official weather alerts and live radar alerts for your area from the National Weather Service, including warnings for storms, strong winds, Tornadoes, tropical storms and other adverse weather events are forecast for the next few days. Additionally, our Ultimate Assistant app can notify you of important weather changes in the coming days.
Features of weather - Meteored Pro News
	Warnings and notices
	Real-time radar, forecast maps and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Reminder Pro 4.1.3</title><pubDate> Wed, 14 Jan 2026 23:04:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-reminder-pro-8695.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-reminder-pro-8695.html
</guid><description>
Are you looking for a simple pop-up reminder app? Do you want to create reminders for one-time and recurring tasks? Get reminders and increase your productivity. Never forget an important task again! Finally, a simple and easy way to set reminders or deadline notifications. This hourly reminder app gets straight to the point. Set notifications to remind you of all your tasks, chores, and to-do list items, then sit back and clear your head.
No unnecessary or complicated features....
</description></item><item><title>Download Librera PRO - Book reader 9.3.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 14 Jan 2026 23:04:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-librera-pro-all-my-books-9008.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-librera-pro-all-my-books-9008.html
</guid><description>
PRO Librera Reader is an easy-to-use and highly configurable reading application that supports most popular document formats, including: PDF, EPUB, EPUB3, MOBI, DjVu, FB2, FB2.zip, TXT, RTF, AZW, AZW3, CBR, CBZ, HTML, XPS, MHT and more. With a simple yet powerful interface, Librera Reader makes reading documents a real pleasure. Librera even has a unique hands-free, auto-scrolling music mode.
Some key features of Librera reader include:
Easily explore documents with optional and...
</description></item><item><title>Download TuneIn Radio Pro - Live Radio 40.7</title><pubDate> Wed, 14 Jan 2026 23:03:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-tunein-radio-pro-live-radio-8217.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-tunein-radio-pro-live-radio-8217.html
</guid><description>
TuneIn Radio Pro allows users to listen to many radio stations and podcasts from around the world. The Pro version offers additional features like the ability to record live stations, remove ads, and access more premium content. It is available for download on Google Play Store as an apk file.
All your sounds in one app:
	News: Listen and update live news 24/7 from local, national and global news sources, including CNBC, CNN, MSNBC and FOX News Radio.
	Sports: Listen live to NFL, NHL...
</description></item><item><title>Download Bluelight Filter for Eye Care 6.5.16</title><pubDate> Wed, 14 Jan 2026 23:03:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-bluelight-filter-for-eye-care-8192.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-bluelight-filter-for-eye-care-8192.html
</guid><description>
Blue light from smartphones or tablets causes eye strain and makes it difficult to sleep at night. This app adjusts your screen color to reduce blue light and relax your eyes, helping you sleep better.
Features of Blue Light Filter for Eye Care
	Free screen filter app to protect your eyes
	Screen filter with natural colors
	Easy operation
	Turn on or off quickly and easily
	Automatic start
	Eye care on your smartphone or tablet
	This app works on most smartphones like Samsung Galaxy,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Appteka 18.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 14 Jan 2026 23:03:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-appteka-11075.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-appteka-11075.html
</guid><description>
Appteka is a free Android application market. Download Appteka to get access to hundreds of thousands of free Android apps created by talented developers around the world.
What's new
	Completely new authorization, using one-time email codes, solves the problem of forgotten passwords and misspellings in mailbox addresses.
	New session system improves security with further authorization management across different devices
	The smoothness of the application has been improved, switching...
</description></item><item><title>Download FotMob - Soccer Live Scores 221.15449.20260107.rc</title><pubDate> Wed, 14 Jan 2026 23:02:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-fotmob-soccer-live-scores-8241.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-fotmob-soccer-live-scores-8241.html
</guid><description>
FotMob gives you all the live scores, stats and storylines to help you keep up with the world of football. Personalized news and notifications make it easy to follow your favorite teams and players. And lightning-fast match updates ensure you never miss a goal, no matter where you are.
Features of FotMob - Live soccer scores
	Live match score
	Results, schedule, standings and lineup
	Detailed statistics, including expected goals (xG) and expected assists (xA)
	Capture map
	Player...
</description></item><item><title>Download Gaia GPS: Offline Trail Maps 2025.9 build 10319</title><pubDate> Wed, 14 Jan 2026 23:02:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-gaia-gps-offroad-hiking-maps-8610.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-gaia-gps-offroad-hiking-maps-8610.html
</guid><description>
Gaia GPS is a navigation app that provides hiking maps, topographic maps, and satellite images for outdoor enthusiasts. It allows users to plan trips, navigate the wilderness, and track their progress. The app is available for both iOS and Android devices, and offers a premium subscription for offline maps, aerial imagery, and advanced features.
Features of Gaia GPS for Android
	Offline maps: Ability to download maps for offline use, ideal for use in areas with limited or no Internet...
</description></item><item><title>Download Hermit - Lite Apps Browser 31.3.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 14 Jan 2026 23:02:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-hermit-lite-apps-browser-9896.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-hermit-lite-apps-browser-9896.html
</guid><description>
Hermit APK is a professional web browser with great built-in features that extend users' operations and productivity to new heights by allowing them to explore optimized applications and functions. good optimization. In addition, it automatically helps users search for Lite version specialized applications that they can use in the browser to save a lot of performance. It also includes integration of more extensions to take user personalization to the next level while exploring or...
</description></item><item><title>Download Muviz Edge: AOD &amp;amp; Edge Lights 2.0.8.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 14 Jan 2026 23:01:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-always-on-edge-music-lighting-8536.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-always-on-edge-music-lighting-8536.html
</guid><description>
Muviz Edge is the first app to display a live Music Visualizer around the edges of the screen while you are listening to music from your favorite music apps. It is the perfect music companion to add musical lighting to your new-age devices with its edge-to-edge display. No root required.
Features of Always On: Edge Music Lighting
Supports major music applications
	Enjoy the audio visualizer with music from various music apps whether they are offline or streaming.
Customizable...
</description></item><item><title>Download Multi Calculator 1.9.5 build 476</title><pubDate> Wed, 14 Jan 2026 23:01:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-multi-calculator-9018.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-multi-calculator-9018.html
</guid><description>
A general-purpose calculator is a type of calculator that allows users to perform many types of calculations in a single application. It often includes features like basic arithmetic operations, scientific functions, unit conversions, currency conversions, etc.
Universal Calculator apps are typically available for smartphones and other mobile devices as well as for desktop computers. They can be useful for many users, including students, professionals, and anyone who needs to perform...
</description></item><item><title>Download G-Stomper Producer 6.1.0.3</title><pubDate> Wed, 14 Jan 2026 23:00:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-g-stomper-producer-13532.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-g-stomper-producer-13532.html
</guid><description>
G-Stomper Producer is a fast and flexible music arranger and digital audio workstation (DAW) designed for both live performance and music production on Android devices. It features a powerful sample-based drum machine with up to 24 tracks, a monophonic step sequencer, 24 drum pads for live play, and the VA-Beast synthesizer - a polyphonic, multi-timbral virtual analog performance synthesizer with advanced FM synthesis and multi-sampling capabilities.
Key Features:
	Multi-track...
</description></item></channel></rss>