<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 01:55:00 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 01:55:00 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download ApowerREC 1.8.5.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 23 Jan 2026 00:02:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-apowerrec-592.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-apowerrec-592.html
</guid><description>
ApowerREC is software video, screen capture computer to record the live program stream. ApowerREC can record everything on the screen of you, include the active desktop, video streaming meetings on the web, etc., You can record their activities in full screen or in an area to be customized are placed separately on the screen along with sound and it has great ability to keep the video synced with audio. Besides this, recorded, webcam, or screen capture, along with webcam also feasible and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Drive SnapShot 1.50.0.1839</title><pubDate> Fri, 23 Jan 2026 00:02:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-drive-snapshot-701.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-drive-snapshot-701.html
</guid><description>
Drive SnapShot is a backup software, Restore disk, including operating system, installed programs, your data and all security attributes - while windows is running and you continue to work. With Drive SnapShot you backup partition or hard drive and it can also create disk image of your system. If a disaster occurs (a virus, trojan or the fixed hard disk), the recover complete and accurate your system will be able to accomplish after only a few minutes. The image file can be mounted as...
</description></item><item><title>Download 3uTools 9.02.020</title><pubDate> Fri, 23 Jan 2026 00:01:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-3utools-4336.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-3utools-4336.html
</guid><description>
3uTools is tool data management and file iOS the most effective. 3uTools help easily manage the apps, photos, music, ringtones, video files and other multimedia. Watch full the different status of iOS devices, including activating, unlocking, status, pin lock and iCloud, as well as detailed information about iOS &amp;amp; iDevice. 3uTools can automate the hardware available for iOS devices. iOS flashing in normal mode, DFU mode and recovery mode are supported. Unlocking with a click of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDF Annotator 10.0.0.1006</title><pubDate> Fri, 23 Jan 2026 00:00:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-annotator-178.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-annotator-178.html
</guid><description>
PDF Annotator software user open any PDF file and add annotations, using the mouse or pen Tablet PC, directly on the Page of the PDF file. PDF Annotator allows users to perform editing operations on PDF files such as: add notes, edit signature, highlight, insert images or text... From the this useful tool, you can completely modify PDF files as you like in order to meet the different work.
PDF Annotator
With the PDF Annotator the document has annotations can then be saved directly back...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mp3Tag 3.33</title><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 23:59:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mp3tag-150.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mp3tag-150.html
</guid><description>
Mp3tag is a powerful tool and easy to use to edit ID3 tags and OGG comments about the files MP3 - and Ogg Vorbis. It can rename files based on the tag information, replace characters or words from tags and filenames. Help users create and add the tag information for MP3 files to manage the information that is reasonable.
The program supports lookup database freedb online for the selected files, allowing you to automatically gather tag information appropriate for the files or CD selection....
</description></item><item><title>Download KLS Backup Professional 2025 v14.0.3.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 23:57:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kls-backup-professional-2951.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kls-backup-professional-2951.html
</guid><description>
KLS Backup Professional is a tool to backup and synchronize powerful allows you to backup or synchronize your information with the local drive and network, cloud storage, media, CD and DVD, WebDAV and FTP server. The backup documents can be stored uncompressed or compressed in Zip format or 7z basic. Backup KLS can backup: files or folders from the local disk, database, network locations or cloud storage, the mailbox data and other specific program (profile). Management in turn can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Glary Disk Cleaner 6.0.1.42</title><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 23:57:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-disk-cleaner-1341.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-disk-cleaner-1341.html
</guid><description>
Glary Disk Cleaner is the software helps to erase the file system temporarily, cleanup your browser cache, or release the folder. Glary Disk Cleaner show scan results in detail, help you pick exactly each file to delete. The list file is much more wide open, with temporary files, user-generated, or the file system, cache, bug report, log files, data in recycle bin, the shortcut expires.
Glary Disk Cleaner - garbage system
Glary Disk Cleaner is designed to be simple as possible in use....
</description></item><item><title>Download Dont Sleep 9.96</title><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 23:57:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dont-sleep-89.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dont-sleep-89.html
</guid><description>
Don't Sleep allows you can set the date and custom time that you want to reactivate the feature manager usual sources or you can set a countdown fast to pause the power management in X hours.
Can temporarily disable the protection of your screen or off your computer at a certain time.
The main features of the Dont Sleep:
- Optimal power supply for computer
- Installation time power source according to
- Prevent computer reboot
Content update Dont Sleep 5.66:
The official website...
</description></item><item><title>Download Fast File Encryptor 26.1.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 23:56:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fast-file-encryptor-2606.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fast-file-encryptor-2606.html
</guid><description>
Fast File Encryptor is the encoder files fast designed for fast processing of the file very big. It can encrypt or decrypt files, contents of folders and contains a lot of additional tools. In addition, there is a tool responsible to completely remove files from the hard drive, you need it if you don't want to leave traces 100 percent in the system. You need to specify the password or key, then select the encryption method, remember remember everything, otherwise it will not work, then...
</description></item><item><title>Download ToDoList 9.1.9.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 23:56:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-todolist-1637.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-todolist-1637.html
</guid><description>
ToDoList is an application note and task management with multiple options, set up help you to easily split and track the progress of the work. Todolist helps millions of people feel in control of their lives more and be the leader in a number of organizations inspired the world to believe. Todolist keep all to-dos of I in one place and perfectly integrated with the other tools that I use. It helps me turn everything faster.
ToDoList - management software job
Every day you have to...
</description></item><item><title>Download reaConverter Pro 8.0.185</title><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 23:55:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html
</guid><description>
reaConverter Pro is software image processing feature with batch conversion and image editing periodically becomes simple. eaConverter also provide command line utilities allow you to process images automatically, thus helping you shorten the time for other work.
reaConverter Pro integrated powerful tool of Uber with many great features. It provides advanced solutions to process and adjust images. Management of the conversion process the base image with the latest version of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Clean Space Pro 2026 v717</title><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 23:55:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-clean-space-pro-545.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-clean-space-pro-545.html
</guid><description>
Clean Space Pro is the professional software remove junk files from the system to release the hard drive and improve computer performance. From time to time when using computer files as buffers, temporary files of various programs, files, internet cookies, internet browsing history, diary, file index.dat, registry entries and even the Windows will gradually increase, occupy wise space your hard drive and make the computer suffer from stagnation. The best solution is to use the Clean Space...
</description></item><item><title>Download Aquaveo GMS Premium 10.9.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 23:54:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aquaveo-gms-premium-3303.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aquaveo-gms-premium-3303.html
</guid><description>
Aquaveo GMS is an abbreviation of the software System Model of underground Water is provided by Aquaveo for modeling and simulation groundwater. It has the modeling tools complete, including geometric patterns, aquatic, mapping, data management and visualization, and also includes a variety of models of water flow include: MODFLOW, MODFLOW-LGR, MODFLOW-USG, MODPATH, MT3DMS, RT3D, SEAWAT, &amp;amp; PHT3D. In addition, online maps, PEST, Parallel PEST, etc. are supported. The program simulates...
</description></item><item><title>Download Extra Subst Home 26.1.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 23:46:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-extra-subst-2605.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-extra-subst-2605.html
</guid><description>
Extra Subst is program designed to help access to the folder is regular use of your computer easier. It is also used to create, edit and remove virtual drives of your computer. Extra Subst creates virtual drives on the basis of the selected folder. Physical drives remain unchanged and are not divided into additional partitions.
Create a new virtual disk is very simple, because you only need to specify the folder which will be connected to, then select the letters and go to it. New virtual...
</description></item><item><title>Download tinyMediaManager 5.2.6</title><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 23:45:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tinymediamanager-1819.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tinymediamanager-1819.html
</guid><description>
tinyMediaManager is a media manager full-featured to arrange and cleanup your media library your. Just choose (s) the folder containing your movies and the program can automatically get all meta data required for movies and program your TV from TheMovieDB.org, Imdb.com, OFDb.de and other online sources. tinyMediaManager download at artwork, film, cast, plot and details of other communication. Each film or program is presented with a unique art background, category, and appropriate...
</description></item><item><title>Download Opera GX (Gaming Browser) 126.0.5750.56</title><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 23:45:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-gx-3170.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-gx-3170.html
</guid><description>
Opera GX is a special version of the Opera browser is built to complement gamers avid. Browser this game comes with the unique features to help users make maximum use of both the game and their browser. Opera GX is built specifically to support the game. This browser includes the unique features to help users have the best experience when gaming and surfing the web.
Opera GX - special browser for gamers
GX Control allows you to set a limit on the level of use RAM, CPU and network where...
</description></item><item><title>Download Screencapt Professional 3.001</title><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 23:44:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-screencapt-professional-12260.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-screencapt-professional-12260.html
</guid><description>
Screencapt Professional is powerful Windows software for screen recording that allows you to accurately and easily record any on-screen activity. Whether you want to create tutorials, record webinars, or simply record your favorite games, Screencapt gives you all the tools you need.
With Screencapt, you can record the entire screen, a selected area, or a specific window. This flexibility makes Screencapt the perfect screen recorder for any type of application. Thanks to the built-in...
</description></item><item><title>Download Pale Moon 34.0.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 23:44:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pale-moon-1883.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pale-moon-1883.html
</guid><description>
Pale Moon is a copy of Firefox has been optimized for the Windows operating System with the processor performance, high current. It looks identical to Firefox browser standard, and supports the extensions, themes and identities of Firefox. All extensions, bookmarks and settings of your existing be entered during the installation process, so except for the logo, you won't notice any difference on function.
Pale Moon - secure web browser
However, what you may notice is the difference in...
</description></item><item><title>Download Coolmuster Android Assistant 6.0.111</title><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 23:43:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-android-assistant-226.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-android-assistant-226.html
</guid><description>
Coolmuster Android Assistant is a lightweight application that allows you to export the data important from your mobile device to your computer for safekeeping just in few clicks.
Coolmuster Android Assistant allows you to browse a number of types of data on your mobile device, you, namely the apps, contacts, SMS, music, photos, videos , and books. In case you can't preview the contents of the desired part, then you can fix this minor inconvenience by access to the child folder of...
</description></item><item><title>Download ExtraDisks Home 26.1.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 23:43:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-extradisks-home-7758.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-extradisks-home-7758.html
</guid><description>
ExtraDisks is a set of tools for creating virtual disks on your computer physical drives that do not change and are not divided into additional partitions. The program contains tools for creating encrypted disks, file-based virtual disks and directory-based virtual disks. The current version includes the following tools: Encrypted Disks, Virtual Disks, Folder Disks, Startup Manager, System Tweaker.
Features of ExtraDisks
ExtraDisks: Encrypted Disk
This tool is used to create encrypted...
</description></item><item><title>Download Disk Savvy Ultimate 17.7.18 + Enterprise + Pro</title><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 23:42:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-disk-savvy-ultimate-1290.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-disk-savvy-ultimate-1290.html
</guid><description>
Disk Savvy Ultimate is the analysis disk space visualization and powerful reporting, comprehensive operation management file and export options. This is the Disk Savvy Ultimate get bottle service for free on taiwebs.com software is the analyze disk space usage has the ability to analyze disks, network shares, NAS devices and storage systems business. Users are provided with more ability to analyze disk usage and classification of files, allows one to have is the ability to display more in...
</description></item><item><title>Download Coder Technologies Coder 2.28.7</title><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 23:42:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coder-oss-enterprise-8726.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coder-oss-enterprise-8726.html
</guid><description>
Coder OSS Enterprise is a development platform that provides a complete cloud-based solution for software development, testing and deployment. It is designed to simplify the software development process by providing developers with a collaborative and streamlined environment.
Coder offloads development from local workstations to your on-premises infrastructure and public cloud. Boost developer productivity with powerful server resources and instant integration. Keep the code and data...
</description></item><item><title>Download O&amp;amp;O DiskCommander Premium 5.0.1018</title><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 20:52:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-diskcommander-premium-14518.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-diskcommander-premium-14518.html
</guid><description>
DiskCommander is a digital detective that helps you solve memory-intensive problems – an advanced analysis tool that helps you understand and optimize your storage structure. With just a few clicks, you'll get a clear, reliable overview of disk usage, along with insights into your hard drive, partitions, and file systems like NTFS or FAT. It's perfect not only for freeing up space but also for diagnosing complex data storage layouts and tricky allocation issues.
Designed with a...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinToUSB Technician 10.5 + Professional</title><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:34:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wintousb-technician-2463.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wintousb-technician-2463.html
</guid><description>
WinToUSB Technician is a handy program that allows you to install Windows on a USB flash or hard drive and run Windows from that drive. The program is easy to use this provide the simple instructions to install the ISO image or CD / DVD into the drive of your USB. After installation, users can easily deploy Windows from the image on the USB drive.
WinToUSB lets you install and run Windows operating system on USB hard drive or USB flash drive, use ISO image or CD / DVD drive as the source...
</description></item><item><title>Download CyberLink PowerDirector Ultimate 2026 v24.1.1320.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:34:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-powerdirector-ultimate-425.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-powerdirector-ultimate-425.html
</guid><description>
CyberLink PowerDirector Ultimate is software editor, edit video and make movies on the computer from a variety of templates are made available, complete with effects, transitions, animations, and music. CyberLink PowerDirector 17 is a combination of video editing software with advanced video editing features powerful. Cblowing need to add your clips into the time line and click on 'Production'!
The tool design video in CyberLink PowerDirector have the ability to customize helps you...
</description></item></channel></rss>