<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 13:43:07 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 13:43:07 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download World VPN - Global Fast Secure 3.4</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Sep 2025 16:42:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-world-vpn-global-fast-secure-13462.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-world-vpn-global-fast-secure-13462.html
</guid><description>
Are you looking for a secure unlimited VPN to protect your privacy? Do you want this fast VPN for Android to have a stable and super fast VPN connection without lag? Meet World VPN, a free VPN app that will quickly protect your privacy and let you unlock geo-locked content. Protect your browsing data, connection and personal information from annoying intruders and enjoy peace of mind online.
World VPN protects your online activities from being tracked by hackers, government agencies or...
</description></item><item><title>Download IELTS Practice Test 5.19</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Sep 2025 16:42:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ielts-practice-test-13333.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ielts-practice-test-13333.html
</guid><description>
Are you aiming for a high IELTS score? IELTS Practice Test is the complete solution for comprehensive exam preparation. Whether you are aiming for a band 7 or higher, our app provides the tools and resources you need to succeed. It covers all four sections of the IELTS exam, ensuring you are fully prepared for either the Academic or General Training test.
Key Features
	Realistic Practice Tests: Simulate the real IELTS exam with full practice tests in Listening, Reading, Writing and...
</description></item><item><title>Download QR &amp;amp; Barcode Scanner PRO 2.5.97 build 147</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Sep 2025 16:42:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-qr-barcode-scanner-9214.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-qr-barcode-scanner-9214.html
</guid><description>
QR &amp;amp; Barcode Scanner is a popular scanning app for Android devices that allows users to scan and read QR codes and barcodes. QR &amp;amp; Barcode Scanner reads all popular QR and barcodes for you. The app shows you prices and information about any product you scan and allows you to create your own QR codes.
Features of QR &amp;amp; Barcode Scanner
	Scan, read, create QR &amp;amp; Barcodes
	Browse products and compare prices
	Read websites, contacts, messages, locations, phone numbers, emails,...
</description></item><item><title>Download IPTV Pro 9.1.7</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Sep 2025 16:40:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-iptv-pro-9093.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-iptv-pro-9093.html
</guid><description>
IPTV Pro is an Android application that allows you to watch live TV channels and movies on your Android device. It provides access to many channels from around the world, including sports, news, movies, and entertainment channels. IPTV Pro supports both M3U and XSPF playlists, and allows you to add your own playlists.
IPTV Pro Features
	Supports M3U and XSPF playlists
	Playlist history
	Play a multicast stream using a UDP proxy (the proxy needs to be installed in your LAN)
	Grid, list...
</description></item><item><title>Download Money Lover - Spending Manager 8.46.0.29</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Sep 2025 16:39:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-money-lover-spending-manager-8349.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-money-lover-spending-manager-8349.html
</guid><description>
Receive personal finance awards &amp;amp; Money management app to manage money now! Track your spending, monitor your transactions, create a monthly budget, motivate yourself to save money, and more. You can also link your Money Lover wallet to your bank account to automatically track your transaction history. Money Lover is a must-have app for personal finance management. Financial management becomes super easy and fast!
Managing personal finances can be difficult for many people. You need...
</description></item><item><title>Download English Phrasal Verbs 2.1.7</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Sep 2025 16:39:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-english-phrasal-verbs-12090.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-english-phrasal-verbs-12090.html
</guid><description>
Are you just starting to learn English or looking to improve your current English skills? This English learning app is for you! English is most widely used as a second language. You can use it in formal situations such as business, education, travel, shopping as well as in informal situations such as communicating with friends, etc.
The learning technique applied in the application allows you to learn English phrasal verbs (up to 900 per month), commonly used in common native English...
</description></item><item><title>Download Audials Play Pro Radio + Podcast 10.5.1-0</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Sep 2025 16:39:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-audials-play-pro-radio-podcast-8420.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-audials-play-pro-radio-podcast-8420.html
</guid><description>
Audials Pro is the only Radio App for smartphones and tablets that can easily find the right to receive the desired Hits Radio station with the Audials Network to satisfy music requests from thousands of radio stations Internet is monitored.
Features of Audials Play Pro for Android
	Find the best radio station for your music: Simply enter your favorite artist or select a music genre, country or local station near you. The Audials Radio app will find Internet radio for you.
	Your radio...
</description></item><item><title>Download Passwords &amp;amp; Passkeys－Safe 26.3.12</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Sep 2025 16:39:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-password-manager-safeincloud-pro-10227.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-password-manager-safeincloud-pro-10227.html
</guid><description>
Protect your data with a unique and secure password! Forget the headache of remembering PINs and passwords! START USING PASSWORD MANAGER TODAY! SafeInCloud is a complete password management solution: Free desktop app + Mobile app for phones and tablets.
Features of Password Manager SafeInCloud Pro
	Material Design
	Dark theme
	Strong encryption (AES)
	Cloud synchronization (Google Drive, Dropbox, OneDrive)
	Finger Scan and Multi-Window (Samsung devices)
	Analyze password...
</description></item><item><title>Download RateX Currency Converter 3.8.13</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Sep 2025 16:38:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ratex-currency-converter-10968.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ratex-currency-converter-10968.html
</guid><description>
RateX is an all-in-one currency converter app that helps you track global exchange rates.
Features of RateX Currency Converter
	130 currencies to choose from, including Euro and Dollar
	Instant currency conversion based on online exchange rates
	Offline mode for on-the-go access
	Convert multiple currencies at once
	Historical charts for trend analysis
	Latest financial news
	Custom exchange rates for personalized conversions
	Home screen widget for easy access
	User-friendly...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sugar Mail email app 1.4-349</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Sep 2025 16:38:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sugar-mail-email-app-8413.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sugar-mail-email-app-8413.html
</guid><description>
Reliable push mail using little battery. Internet mail like Gmail, Yahoo, Outlook.com, Yandex and many other email providers from AOL to Zoho. Exchange / Office 365 mail includes contacts and calendar synchronization.
Features of Sugar Mail APK
	Push mail (receive new mail almost immediately)
	Multiple accounts and folders
	Account/folder overview
	There is a dark theme
	Combined inbox shows messages from all accounts/folders
	Smart message sorting (optional, unread and pinned at...
</description></item><item><title>Download Business Calendar 2 Pro 2.53.3 build 253301</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Sep 2025 16:38:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-business-calendar-8433.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-business-calendar-8433.html
</guid><description>
Business Calendar 2 Pro is the premium version of our popular calendar app. It provides a great overview of your appointments, is easy to use, and gives you powerful tools to plan and schedule your events and tasks.
Features of Business Calendar
Your personal organizer
	calendar, planner and tasks in one app
	6 clearly designed main views: month, week, day, agenda, year and tasks
	popup with live event details in month view
	flexible daily and weekly planning that can be adjusted...
</description></item><item><title>Download BikeComputer Pro 9.2.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Sep 2025 16:37:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-bikecomputer-pro-8146.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-bikecomputer-pro-8146.html
</guid><description>
BikeComputer Pro is a mobile application that allows users to track their cycling and other outdoor activities using GPS. The app is available to download from the Google Play Store and Apple App Store. It is designed for cycling enthusiasts and offers many features to help users track and improve their performance. Some features of the application include:
	Track distance, speed and route with GPS
	Altitude tracking
	Audible signals for distance and speed
	Personalized training...
</description></item><item><title>Download Smart Launcher 6 ‧ Home Screen 6.5 build 045</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Sep 2025 16:37:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-smart-launcher-8412.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-smart-launcher-8412.html
</guid><description>
Smart Launcher is a mobile app that provides users with a customized home screen and app launcher on their Android devices. It includes features like minimalist interface, automatic app sorting, and gesture controls. The app also includes many customizable settings, such as the ability to change the theme, icon size, and screen layout, as well as the ability to create custom categories for the app.
Smart Launcher Features
	Ambient theme: Smart launcher automatically changes theme...
</description></item><item><title>Download MOLDIV - Photo Editor, Collage 4.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Sep 2025 16:37:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-moldiv-photo-editor-collage-8558.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-moldiv-photo-editor-collage-8558.html
</guid><description>
MOLDIV is a photo editing application that offers a variety of editing tools and features to enhance and beautify your photos. This is an all-in-one photo editor that offers everything you desire in photography. It's a professional photo editor that pleases everyone from beginners to experts. Whether it's the Frame/Collage/Magazine features that enable the most immersive storytelling or the Beauty Camera that captures naturally beautiful selfies, find the features you need in MOLDIV, the...
</description></item><item><title>Download WiFi Mouse Pro 5.5.5</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Sep 2025 16:36:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wifi-mouse-pro-8925.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wifi-mouse-pro-8925.html
</guid><description>
Convert your phone into a wireless mouse, keyboard and trackpad for your computer, it allows you to control your PC/Mac/Linux easily via local network connection. Media Controller, Presentation Controller and Remote File Explorer are all included in this controller app.
Now you can relax on the sofa and control movies or games in the comfort of your own home, replacing your broken mouse and keyboard with this app.
Features of WiFi Mouse Pro
	Fully simulated mouse
	Built-in support...
</description></item><item><title>Download NYTimes: US and Global News 11.41.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Sep 2025 16:36:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-the-new-york-times-8235.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-the-new-york-times-8235.html
</guid><description>
Understand the world around you with original reporting from The New York Times. Free to download, The Times app gives you access to expert news from 1700 journalists in 160 countries worldwide. From breaking news to opinion, business, technology and the arts, subscribers get unlimited access to groundbreaking reporting, analysis and commentary.
Features of The New York Times
	Wake up with The Morning, your morning guide to what's happening and why it matters. It's the news you need...
</description></item><item><title>Download Castro Premium - system info 4.8.1 build 364</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Sep 2025 16:36:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-castro-premium-system-info-10230.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-castro-premium-system-info-10230.html
</guid><description>
Castro is an information utility for your tablets and smartphones. It displays various diagnostic information about the device. Castro processes and displays a huge amount of information, namely
	Detailed processor statistics (CPU and GPU);
	Battery monitoring;
	Consumes all types of memory;
	Data usage over Wi-Fi and mobile networks;
	Real-time sensor data with helpful graphs;
	Detailed information about the device's camera;
	Full list of available audio and video codecs;
	Monitor the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Always On Edge - AOD &amp;amp; LED 9.2.4</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Sep 2025 16:35:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-always-on-edge-aod-led-10042.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-always-on-edge-aod-led-10042.html
</guid><description>
With AOE you can customize your phone from many aspects and make it unique as you are. It contains too many features with detailed options so it can be customized as you prefer, here are some of the main features.
Notifications led light
	It can be customized to work in a highly flexible way within system always on display or independent, or even both like tap to light feature.
	You can customize lighting color and style distinctively for each app and also for each contact or account...
</description></item><item><title>Download PM Pro: Password Manager 4.7.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Sep 2025 16:35:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-passwords-manager-pro-for-android-10925.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-passwords-manager-pro-for-android-10925.html
</guid><description>
Passwords Manager Pro for Android is a 100% offline password locker app that allows users to store, organize and manage passwords, notes and other sensitive information locally on their device without no need to rely on cloud-based services.
Features of Password Manager Pro for Android
Highly secure offline password management application
	This app is 100% offline even there is no internet connection in this app. It only stores data on the user's device and encrypts it with AES-256...
</description></item><item><title>Download Transparent clock weather Pro 8.48.3</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Sep 2025 16:34:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-transparent-clock-weather-pro-8872.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-transparent-clock-weather-pro-8872.html
</guid><description>
Transparent Clock Weather Pro: Get Accurate Local or Worldwide Weather Forecasts Easily with Live Weather Updates, Hourly and Daily Weather Forecasts and Timely Weather Alerts. Check The Weather for Today, Tomorrow or the weekend with our Easy to use app and widgets.
Features of Transparent Clock Weather Pro
	local Weather: Automatically keep track or your location as you move and get accurate real time weather reports and alerts
	Different Weather Preded for More Accurate Weather...
</description></item><item><title>Download Scientific Calculator Plus 8.1.3 build 93</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Sep 2025 16:34:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-scientific-calculator-plus-12199.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-scientific-calculator-plus-12199.html
</guid><description>
CalcTastic Plus is a feature-rich calculator with years of innovation and exceptional user ratings. Choose from 12 different themes, configurable screens and your choice of math, Algebra or RPN.
CalcTastic Plus includes two completely independent modes
	Highly accurate scientific calculator with Fractions, Complex Numbers, Physical Constants, Unit Converter, Advanced Statistics, History &amp;amp; Memory Registers and Full Online Help .
	Full-featured programmer's calculator with dedicated...
</description></item><item><title>Download Music Theory Companion 7.6.3</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Sep 2025 16:34:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-music-theory-companion-with-piano-guitar-8917.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-music-theory-companion-with-piano-guitar-8917.html
</guid><description>
Music theory is very important when composing any song. This music theory helper app is for all musicians interested in studying scales, chords, chord substitutions, circle of fifths, voicing, modulation or key changes, and more. and apply them in their works. Music Theory Companion is a quick reference to scales and chords useful for musicians and composers in finding new creative chord progressions while composing. This is also a very useful guitar chord application for learning guitar...
</description></item><item><title>Download Piktures: All-In-One Gallery 2.23 build 895</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Sep 2025 16:33:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-piktures-gallery-photo-video-9523.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-piktures-gallery-photo-video-9523.html
</guid><description>
Piktures is a simple photo gallery app with very advanced features. It supports dozens of cloud services like Google Drive and Microsoft Onedrive, your personal cloud server (WebDav), SD Cards, USB drives and even your computer! Piktures allows you to view your photos in grid, mosaic and list views. Organize them the way you like.
Features of Piktures
	Fast: Piktures has its own rendering engine so you can view photos very quickly.
	Secret Space: The secure space protects your most...
</description></item><item><title>Download ASICS Runkeeper - Run Tracker 16.13</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Sep 2025 16:33:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-asics-runkeeper-run-tracker-8334.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-asics-runkeeper-run-tracker-8334.html
</guid><description>
Join a community that helps people escape difficulties and stick with running forever! Track your workouts, set goals, sweat, and see your progress. Whether you're trying to track a 5K goal or train for a marathon, use the GPS app trusted by 50 million users and counting.
ASICS Runkeeper - Run Tracker is a mobile application that allows users to track running and fitness activities on their Android devices. The app uses GPS to track the user's distance, pace, and running time as well as...
</description></item><item><title>Download BeSoccer - Soccer Live Score 5.6.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Sep 2025 16:32:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-besoccer-soccer-live-score-8800.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-besoccer-soccer-live-score-8800.html
</guid><description>
All the football in the world at the click of a button. BeSoccer is the best live soccer app with soccer news, results and statistics. We cover over 10,000 competitions: you'll be able to follow all the matches live, receive goal notifications, line-ups, news, signings and today's televised matches . Explore the best database in the world of football with all the statistics about your team, favorite players around the world, comparisons, team form and the latest transfer rumours.&amp;lt;...
</description></item></channel></rss>