<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 17:45:53 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 17:45:53 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Privoxy 4.0.0-1 + Portable</title><pubDate> Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:53:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-privoxy-6216.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-privoxy-6216.html
</guid><description>
Privoxy is a free web proxy that does not save on buffers with filtering capabilities to enhance privacy rights, cookies manipulation, and modification of the HTTP header and the HTTP header before the page is displayed. Privoxy is a "proxy to enhance privacy", filtering websites and removing ads. Privoxy has a flexible configuration and can be customized to fit the needs and personal tastes. It has applications for both stand-alone systems and multi-user networks.
Features of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Q-Dir 12.45</title><pubDate> Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:50:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-q-dir-348.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-q-dir-348.html
</guid><description>
Q-Dir is software to manage the entire file and folder on the computer, allowing to see file in same time 4 different positions (viewport quadro) while still maintaining all the standard features of the Explorer.
It also provides a variety of management features, additional files included the filter file color-coding, layouts and columns can be customized, quick access to file and folder favorites and more.
Other features of Q-Dir , including directory listings (.txt, .doc .html .csv),...
</description></item><item><title>Download Bulk Rename Utility 4.1.0.1 Commercial</title><pubDate> Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:48:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bulk-rename-utility-2119.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bulk-rename-utility-2119.html
</guid><description>
Bulk Rename Utility is a utility batch rename allows you to easily rename multiple files and folders, based on the criteria flexible. Bulk Rename Utility lets you easily Add time / date stamp, replace numbers, insert text, convert case, add auto number, processing folder and sub-folder,..
Bulk Rename Utility - Change the name of the file series
Rename many files and / or directories has never been easier! It has a small memory footprint so it can be left running all the time without...
</description></item><item><title>Download Database .NET 36.5.9491</title><pubDate> Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:48:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-databasenet-1818.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-databasenet-1818.html
</guid><description>
Database.NET a common database allows you to connect to most of the server database to perform SQL queries, create databases and tables and edit the rows of the table. Program Database.NET includes a syntax enabled editor SQL tagged as well as a number of additional tools to perform facility maintenance data base (shrinking, backing up and viewing process). You can also export the data to CSV, HTML, XML and some other formats.
Database.NET - Management database
Management features,...
</description></item><item><title>Download O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro 22.1.233 / Server</title><pubDate> Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:47:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-diskimage-pro-218.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-diskimage-pro-218.html
</guid><description>
O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro is software backup data comprehensive and effective is provided to protect the data of the computer system, it creates images for individual drives or the entire system that still does not affect your system.
O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro allows the user to backup the entire computer or drive, the and files whenever you want even while the computer is being used. Or can use O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro to create a copy chinh sac of computer disk drives, can be used instead of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download mIRC 7.83</title><pubDate> Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:47:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mirc-756.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mirc-756.html
</guid><description>
mIRC is a client application used to communicate, share, play or work with others on IRC networks around the world. The software interface is practical, clean, highly configurable and supports features such as friends lists, file transfer, connect to multiple servers, IPv6, SSL encryption, proxy support, display UTF-8, UPnP, custom sound, spoken message, notification tray , logs messages, and more.
mIRC - Chat, chat online
mIRC also has a language powerful script can be used both to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Clean Media Player 2026.1.4.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:46:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-clean-media-player-12416.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-clean-media-player-12416.html
</guid><description>
If you've ever been offended by profanity in a movie, chances are you'll want the censored version of the movie. However, until the director decides to release it, you still have the option of muting unwanted scenes or editing the subtitles manually, if you are able to do so. The application mutes and displays subtitles without offensive words and phrases. Customize the profanity filter to your preferences. Skip inappropriate scenes by selecting their start and end times.
Clean Media...
</description></item><item><title>Download VidCoder 12.13 + Portable</title><pubDate> Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:46:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vidcoder-534.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vidcoder-534.html
</guid><description>
VidCoder is software to convert movies to MKV and MP4, as well as extract video content from DVDS and Blu-ray. This is a software utility to help people extract the video content from the BD and DVD as well as convert the clips specific to MKV and MP4.
VidCoder has an interface that includes a clear design, including a menu bar, several buttons and a panel to display the queue. The file can be added with the help of the file browser or drag and drop-out.
Features VidCoder
	VidCoder...
</description></item><item><title>Download NWinfo 1.5.4</title><pubDate> Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:45:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nwinfo-12590.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nwinfo-12590.html
</guid><description>
NWinfo is a Win32 program that allows you to obtain system and hardware information. It displays essential information about CPU, memory, disk, network, and even system operating details. Because it's portable, you can carry NWinfo on a USB stick and use it on any Windows machine, making it a useful tool for both tech enthusiasts and troubleshooters.
Features of NWinfo
	Get detailed information about SMBIOS, CPUID, S.M.A.R.T., PCI, EDID, etc.
	Supports export in JSON, YAML and LUA...
</description></item><item><title>Download EZ CD Audio Converter 12.4.0.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:45:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ez-cd-audio-converter-174.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ez-cd-audio-converter-174.html
</guid><description>
EZ CD Audio Converter is a software application advanced with purpose helps you extract audio tracks from CDS, convert files to different formats and burn them to disc. When using functions separate the audio from the disc, you are also edit the type of metadata and specify the file name to be separated.
EZ CD Audio Converter Ultimate has the ability to convert between multiple audio formats with high output quality assured, supported input formats, including 3GA, 3GP, AAC, AIF, AIFF,...
</description></item><item><title>Download EZ Meta Tag Editor 12.3.4.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:44:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ez-meta-tag-editor-4043.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ez-meta-tag-editor-4043.html
</guid><description>
EZ Meta Tag Editor is manager audio file, the metadata editing easy-to-use user interface with Windows style File Explorer. EZ Meta Tag Editor offers editing solutions card, tag, file management easier. EZ Meta Tag Editor now supports many popular formats such as AAC, HE AAC, AIFF, Monkey's Audio, DSF, DFF, FLAC, MP3, MP2, MP1, Musepack, Opus, real audio (TTA), WAV, Wavpack, WMA, Vorbis, 3g2, 3ga, 3gp, aac, aif, aiff, ape, asf, DSF, dff, flac, m4a, M4B, MP1, mp2, mp3, mp4, mpc, ogg, opus,...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDFArea PDF to Image Converter 5.6</title><pubDate> Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:44:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdfarea-pdf-to-image-converter-6933.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdfarea-pdf-to-image-converter-6933.html
</guid><description>
PDFArea PDF to Image Converter is a quick and easy-use PDF mass conversion utility designed to convert PDF documents to the image file. Output images can be JPG, TIF, GIF, PNG, JP2 (JPEG 2000), BMP and EMF formats. It can convert encrypted PDF documents and allow you to choose to convert all pages or pages specified. PDFArea PDF to Image Converter is independent software, without using Adobe Acrobat Reader. It does not depend on any print drivers so it will NOT install any print drivers...
</description></item><item><title>Download FRITZ 20.8</title><pubDate> Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:43:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fritz-14060.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fritz-14060.html
</guid><description>
FRITZ 20 is more than just a chess engine – it’s a training revolution for aspiring players and professionals. Whether you’re taking your first steps into the world of professional chess training, or are already playing at tournament level, FRITZ 20 will help you train more efficiently, intelligently and personally than ever before.
Simulate playing styles at the highest level
FRITZ 20 analyzes your next opponent – and plays just like them!
Use the style analysis feature in...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Geek YTDL Pro 12.1.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:43:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-geek-ytdl-pro-9895.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-geek-ytdl-pro-9895.html
</guid><description>
YT Geek YTDL Pro is software that helps users easily download videos from YouTube and hundreds of other video sites. It is very easy to use, just paste the video URL and you can download the video while keeping the original quality. Not only videos on Youtube, users can download any video from social networking sites like Facebook, Vimeo, Myspace video,...
Features of YT Geek YTDL Pro
	Download videos from YouTube and other video sites.
	Increase download speed up to 400%.
	Download...
</description></item><item><title>Download Vladovsoft Hotel 17.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:43:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vladovsoft-hotel-6008.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vladovsoft-hotel-6008.html
</guid><description>
Vladovsoft Hotel is an easy-to-use, affordable hotel management software. It tracks all delivery, sales, booking and dining and helps your hotel management more easily than ever.
Features of Vladovsoft Hotel
	Activities with non-limited product and service numbers
	Activity with no limited number of rooms, reservation and accommodation
	Work with operators with different user rights
	The forms for making delivery and sales
	Activity with bar code scanner and bar code reader
	Can be...
</description></item><item><title>Download Flyby11 2.4.854</title><pubDate> Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:42:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-flyby11-12467.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-flyby11-12467.html
</guid><description>
Flyby11 is a simple patcher that removes annoying restrictions that prevent you from installing Windows 11 (24H2) on unsupported hardware. Do you have an old PC? No TPM, Secure Boot or your processor is not supported? Flyby11 allows you to install Windows 11 24H2. There are no complicated steps. Just run the tool and you'll be running Windows 11 on your outdated machine in no time.
Technical overview
Flyby11 takes advantage of a feature of the Windows 11 setup process that uses the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Flyoobe 2.4.854</title><pubDate> Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:42:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oobelux-13956.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oobelux-13956.html
</guid><description>
Flyoobe was born out of the frustration many users felt with the Windows 11 setup experience. Whether it was the mandatory online account, the endless "Next, next, next..." screens, or the incomplete configuration options when you finally reached the desktop, the current setup lacked focus on what users really wanted.
Why choose Flyoobe?
	Simplifies the Windows 11 setup process right out of the box.
	Allows easy local account creation without need to hunt for hidden options.
	Includes...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT-DL 12.1.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:41:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-dl-5876.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-dl-5876.html
</guid><description>
YT-DL is a small program to download videos from YouTube and other video sites. Our goal is to make the program as simple as its name.
The features of YT-DL
	Download the video from YouTube and other video sites
	Increase download speed up to 400%
	Download multiple videos at the same time
	Pause and continue to download at any time
	Preview video content while downloading
</description></item><item><title>Download Vladovsoft Sklad Plus 17.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:41:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vladovsoft-sklad-plus-3994.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vladovsoft-sklad-plus-3994.html
</guid><description>
Vladovsoft Sklad Plus is a warehouse management software easy to use. It helps you keep track of products and customers, simplifies the process of delivery, sales and invoicing and the management and control of warehouse / your store easier than ever. Vladovsoft Sklad Plus help you to easily export tables and reports as interactive web pages (in HTML format) and to XML. Automatically calculate the weighted average after product delivery. Preview, print, choose printer and print tables,...
</description></item><item><title>Download VovSoft Search Text in Files 5.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:40:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-search-text-in-files-5417.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-search-text-in-files-5417.html
</guid><description>
VovSoft Search Text in Files is an application that searches through text files with simple queries, and the application will quickly find the file. Select the folder, enter the search text and filename filter, then click the Start button. All files including the search text will be listed. You can export the list to text or a CSV file. You can open, copy or delete files by right clicking. You can also display file sizes and file icons by using checkboxes.
VovSoft Features Search Text...
</description></item><item><title>Download Vladovsoft Fitorg 17.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:40:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vladovsoft-fitorg-5029.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vladovsoft-fitorg-5029.html
</guid><description>
Vladovsoft Fitorg is a software management room, easy to use, affordable. Vladovsoft Fitorg includes membership details, bookings, deliveries and sales, product, service, book, recipes, accounts, payments and track membership. Ideal for fitness clubs, gym, health club, entertainment center, and fitness.
The advantages of Vladovsoft Fitorg
	The software is optimized for fast operation even on the computer and old laptop
	Management software, club very easy to use
	User...
</description></item><item><title>Download lessmsi 2.11.5</title><pubDate> Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:40:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lessmsi-12392.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lessmsi-12392.html
</guid><description>
Lessmsi (Less MSIerables) is a free and portable application that allows users to view and extract the contents of MSI files.
How does it work? Files with the .msi extension are not as widely used as their .exe cousins, but both contain programs for Windows. The main difference between them is that the latter does not always come with an installer, while it comes standard with the former. However, there will be cases where you just need to view or want to extract specific content from...
</description></item><item><title>Download QOwnNotes 26.1.4</title><pubDate> Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:39:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qownnotes-3178.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qownnotes-3178.html
</guid><description>
QOwnNotes is notes bookmark file simple text (GPL) open source application for GNU / Linux , Mac OS X and Windows of Patrizio Bekerle ( pbek on GitHub and IRC) (optional) activity along with the notes application of ownCloud or Nextcloud. QOwnNote store your notes as plain text files and can be synchronized with synchronization function file of ownCloud / Nextcloud. You can also use other apps like Syncthing or Dropbox . Just write out your thoughts as they appear, and edit them if...
</description></item><item><title>Download Syncovery Premium 11.12.0.150</title><pubDate> Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:39:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncovery-pro-enterprise-232.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncovery-pro-enterprise-232.html
</guid><description>
Syncovery Pro Enterprise is a great application used to back up data and to synchronize personal computers, servers, laptops, notepads and storage online. The software comes with support for FTP and secure FTP servers, SSH, WebDAV, Amazon S3, http, update the part file, ZIP compression, data encryption, and schedule automatic backups.
Syncovery Pro Enterprise have the ability to freely select files and folders across the whole folder hierarchy in tree view and supports email...
</description></item><item><title>Download SmartGit 25.1.103</title><pubDate> Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:38:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-smartgit-13978.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-smartgit-13978.html
</guid><description>
SmartGit is a cross-platform, graphical Git application designed for professional users to simplify and enhance Git version control workflows. SmartGit supports major Git hosting services like GitHub, Bitbucket, GitLab, and Azure DevOps with built-in features to handle pull requests, comments, and code reviews directly in the app.
Why choose SmartGit as your Git Client?
	One for all.
	SmartGit helps new Git users as well as helps experienced developers work more efficiently.
	SmartGit...
</description></item></channel></rss>