<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 23:52:25 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 23:52:25 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Office Tool Plus 10.30.43.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 00:29:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-tool-plus-3664.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-tool-plus-3664.html
</guid><description>
Office Tool Plus based on the Office deployment tool from Microsoft. You can customize configuration files installation and install Office of to install Office without Internet. Configure install Office, as well as customize the product C2R have installed, such as add and remove components, language packs, etc.
Office Tool Plus - Download and install Office
The characteristics of Office Tool Plus
	1. Configure install Office, as well as customize the product C2R have installed, such...
</description></item><item><title>Download Media Player Classic Home Cinema 2.6.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 00:27:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-media-player-classic-home-cinema-2839.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-media-player-classic-home-cinema-2839.html
</guid><description>
Media Player Classic Home Cinema is a multimedia compact for Microsoft Windows 32 bit and 64 bit. MPC mimics the interface of Windows Media Player 6.4, but provides most options and features available in the modern means. Media Player Classic Home Cinema for free 100% no advertising, so you can directly access content and enjoy media playback without being distracted.
With Media Player Classic Home, you can now change the design a multimedia of the custom toolbar. There is a range to...
</description></item><item><title>Download StartAllBack 3.9.21.5352</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 00:26:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-startallback-6857.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-startallback-6857.html
</guid><description>
With the official release of Windows 11, chances are that most of you want to try it out. As the name suggests, StartAllBack is a small, lightweight tool that can help you enjoy the power of the new operating system while keeping the look and feel, especially because main work area, desktop of Windows 7, Windows 10 as taskbars and start menu styles.
StartAllBack is specially designed for Windows 11 and will not work on any older operating systems. If you want to get the start menu back...
</description></item><item><title>Download TeamViewer QuickSupport 15.74.3</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 00:25:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-teamviewer-quicksupport-1933.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-teamviewer-quicksupport-1933.html
</guid><description>
A different version of TeamViewer is TeamViewer QuickSupport is a solution easy to use allows you to share your desktop with a users TeamViewer other to receive technical support or other support. All what you need to do is run the TeamViewer QuickSupport and provides for the remote user ID and your password to grant access to the computer to your desk. Only people you trust can connect to your computer and access password will automatically change after each session.
The software also...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare Recoverit 14.0.15.25</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 00:25:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-recoverits-374.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-recoverits-374.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare Recoverit is a data recovery software that is easily lost at a rapid rate and is used by many people. You will do what happens if one day your data is suddenly lost due to the virus or deleted it, .. Wondershare Recoverit will provide you with an environment to protect important data.
Wondershare Recoverit has all the scanning processes that are divided into multiple types, from the typical recovery of the deleted files that are deleted to the recovery of missing files due...
</description></item><item><title>Download EverNote 11.1.2.45930</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 00:25:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-evernote-3261.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-evernote-3261.html
</guid><description>
EverNote is the all in one tool allows you to track notes, todo items, memos, outlines, excerpts, websites, ideas and other things and automatically synchronize them between multiple computers and mobile devices (iPhone, Android, etc.). You can choose to sort their notes into categories, password protect them, export them to XML and more. EverNote supports a number of pattern notes allow you to add to-do list, spreadsheet like Excel to calculate costs (automatic sum), notes, phone, contact...
</description></item><item><title>Download Aeon Timeline 3.5.37</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 00:24:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aeon-timeline-4952.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aeon-timeline-4952.html
</guid><description>
Aeon Timeline is a tool line-time for creative thinking. Most of the application time line traditional designed to suit a single need: to create attractive screen on time one way. They are present, static, and perfectly aligned with the slide and overhead projector.
With Aeon Timeline, you can split your timeline into logical groups, projects or arcs at the same time. You can model the relationships between events and people, places, and ideas. Aeon calculate ages of people for you. And...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDFsam -PDF Split and Merge 5.4.5</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 00:24:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-split-and-merge-2337.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-split-and-merge-2337.html
</guid><description>
PDF Split and Merge is free software that makes it easy to split PDF files into smaller files or merge them all into one complete PDF file. PDF Split and Merge is considered to be one of the best PDF file merging software available today, the special thing about this PDF file merge software is that it is completely free, this is one of the reasons that make up the attraction of this software.
PDF Split and Merge - Split and merge PDF 
This is a great alternative to the famous ARTS PDF...
</description></item><item><title>Download SingNext Receiver 1.4</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 00:16:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-singnext-receiver-12557.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-singnext-receiver-12557.html
</guid><description>
SingNext Receiver is a tool designed for karaoke servers to effectively manage song requests from singers. This system allows users to receive digital karaoke tickets via a wireless connection, enhancing the karaoke experience by eliminating the need for physical tickets and personal phone numbers.
Features
	Singers can submit their song requests via smartphone using the SingNext platform, which generates digital request tickets that are sent directly to the karaoke host's system
	The...
</description></item><item><title>Download O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Premium WinPE 22.2.1149</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 00:15:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-diskimage-workstation-4548.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-diskimage-workstation-4548.html
</guid><description>
O&amp;amp;O DiskImage WinPE is a program user friendly designed to help users create images of partitions and hard disk to keep them safe for their data in case disaster strikes. O&amp;amp;O DiskImage WinPE includes a set the ability to backup files and drives strong, helping users to easily keep data they want to secure. Users can create images of partitions or entire computer with just a few mouse clicks and they can also create the disk can boot if necessary.
Features of O&amp;amp;O DiskImage...
</description></item><item><title>Download Hard Disk Sentinel Pro 6.30.8 Beta</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 00:15:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hard-disk-sentinel-pro-562.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hard-disk-sentinel-pro-562.html
</guid><description>
Hard Disk Sentinel Pro is a tool for monitoring and optimal performance for hard drive HDD and help diagnose the HDD as well as SSD. Version of Hard Disk Sentinel Pro is a professional version, the most advanced of Hard Disk with many advanced features that meet basic needs, check the hard drive for the user.
The goal of it is to find, test, diagnose and repair the malfunction, hard drive, report and display the health status of the SSD and hard drive failure, decreased performance and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Awesome Miner Ultimate 11.4.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 00:15:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-awesome-miner-9041.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-awesome-miner-9041.html
</guid><description>
Awesome Miner is a software application designed to manage and monitor cryptocurrency mining operations. It supports a wide variety of mining hardware, including ASICs and GPUs, and can be used to manage mining for a variety of cryptocurrencies, including Bitcoin, Ethereum, and Litecoin.
Powerful tool to manage and monitor cryptocurrency mining activities. With support for a wide variety of mining hardware and cryptocurrencies, mobile apps, and customizable alerting and performance...
</description></item><item><title>Download MSI Center 2.0.66.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 00:14:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-msi-center-12314.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-msi-center-12314.html
</guid><description>
The AI ​​era of computing: MSI laptops are equipped with MSI's exclusive AI technology capable of providing completely new smart features. The AI ​​revolution has arrived on MSI laptops. MSI AI Engine automatically recognizes various user situations, triggering appropriate adjustments in performance, sound effects, display modes and keyboard backlighting. Users do not need to make manual adjustments to achieve optimal situations.
MSI Center combines all of MSI's exclusive...
</description></item><item><title>Download TeamViewer 15.74.3 + Portable</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 00:13:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-teamviewer-528.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-teamviewer-528.html
</guid><description>
TeamViewer is software that functions to connect and control the remote computer, the ability to connect with any system anywhere from all over the place. This is a support tool users is very convenient. TeamViewer to help users control remote computer becomes much more simple, help you interact and collaborate with others in the exchange and share of information, instruction manual, application software or fix the computer.
TeamViewer as a revolution of computer science. when you have...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinMerge 2.16.54</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 00:13:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winmerge-2028.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winmerge-2028.html
</guid><description>
WinMerge is a tool to merge and distinguish open source for Windows. WinMerge can compare and folders and files, presenting differences in a visual text easy to understand or manipulate. WinMerge is very useful for determining what has changed between the version of the project and merge the changes between the versions. WinMerge can be used as a tool to compare / merge, external or as a standalone application.
In addition, Winmerge has many helpful features helps to compare, synchronize...
</description></item><item><title>Download CPFD Barracuda Virtual Reactor 25.1.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 00:11:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cpfd-barracuda-virtuak-reactor-12053.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cpfd-barracuda-virtuak-reactor-12053.html
</guid><description>
CPFD Barracuda Virtuak Reactor is computational fluid dynamics (CFD) software specifically for simulating and analyzing complex fluidized bed and other multiphase reactor processes. It is developed by CPFD Software, LLC. It leverages advanced algorithms and numerical models to accurately predict and simulate the behavior of gases, solids, and their interactions in the reactor. It is widely used in industries such as oil refining, chemical manufacturing, power generation, etc., where...
</description></item><item><title>Download Hasleo Backup Suite Professional 5.6.2.0 Technician / Enterprise / Workstation</title><pubDate> Tue, 27 Jan 2026 21:21:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hasleo-backup-suite-professional-14539.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hasleo-backup-suite-professional-14539.html
</guid><description>
Hasleo Backup Suite Professional is Windows backup and recovery software that integrates backup, recovery, and cloning features. It's designed for Windows users and can be used on both personal computers and Windows servers. Hasleo Backup Suite's backup and recovery features help you back up and restore your Windows operating system, drives, and partitions to protect the security of your Windows operating system and personal data. Hasleo Backup Suite's cloning feature allows you to move...
</description></item><item><title>Download Resolume Arena 7.24.0.59769</title><pubDate> Tue, 27 Jan 2026 21:17:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-resolume-arena-001-760.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-resolume-arena-001-760.html
</guid><description>
Resolume Arena is software Visual Jockey for DJ help adjust, mix and match image combination screen displayed directly. Software control it from the lighting and synchronize with the DJ via SMPTE time code. Adjust the ratio and position of the clip to suit your needs. Apply effects to change the powerful interface of the video. Everything running on the card screen so you get fast performance and good image quality as possible.
Resolume Arena - software Visual Jockey for DJ
Features of...
</description></item><item><title>Download BETA-CAE Systems 2025.2.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 27 Jan 2026 21:14:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-beta-cae-systems-5871.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-beta-cae-systems-5871.html
</guid><description>
BETA CAE Systems is a private engineering software company committed to developing modern CAE software systems that meet the requirements of all simulations. The company's products, processors before the ANSA/the EPILYSIS department and the following processors META, and SPDRM, process management-data and resource process management, hold top positions worldwide in many industries, including automotive, vehicle rail, aerospace, sports car racing, chemical process engineering, energy,...
</description></item><item><title>Download BandiView Pro (Honeyview) 7.25</title><pubDate> Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:22:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-honeyview-4871.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-honeyview-4871.html
</guid><description>
HoneyView is an image viewer, comic book archive support with formats such as zip, cbz, rar....and support the photo format display, such as JPG, GIF, TIFF, PNG,... can see the photos automatically change after a period of time, adjust the time from 1 to 90 seconds and the options like repeat or random. In addition, support photo editing basics like rotate, add effects, zoom and pan or zoom display frame.
Features of HoneyView
	Operating system supported: Windows XP / Vista / 7/8 /...
</description></item><item><title>Download XYplorer 28.20.0000</title><pubDate> Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:22:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-533.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-533.html
</guid><description>
XYplorer - File Manager for Windows is software that supports users to manage files on the Window quickly and to arrange the folder tidy. XYplorer features tabbed browsing, search, files, powerful, preview, flexible, highly customizable interface, dual frame options and a variety of unique ways to automate effective tasks often repeat. It's fast, lightweight, and portable.
Features XYplorer
	XYplorer is a file manager mobile. It does not require any settings, store all configuration...
</description></item><item><title>Download Folder Guard Professional 26.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:21:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-folder-guard-professional-1314.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-folder-guard-professional-1314.html
</guid><description>
Folder Guard Professional (The most professional) software includes password computer folder to help you control access to files, folders and the Windows resource. Folder Guard to lock files and folders, your personal password to stop other users from peeking into your records.  You can even completely hide the private folder of his from almost all the apps and the folders that will be hidden until you enter the valid password. You can also protect files sensitive system from modification...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ableton Live Suite 12.3.5</title><pubDate> Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:20:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ableton-live-suite-663.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ableton-live-suite-663.html
</guid><description>
Ableton Live Suite is professional software to create, edit, music with effects, instruments, audio and all creative. Ableton Live Suite is the software fast, flexible and flexibility to create and perform music. Move freely between the musical elements and play with ideas, that don't stop the music and do not break the flow of your sound.
Features, Ableton Live Suite
	Meet Wavetable, Echo, Drum Buss and Pedal: the new equipment means new sounds, colorful can with the instruments and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Display Driver Uninstaller (DDU) 18.1.4.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:20:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-display-driver-uninstaller-1999.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-display-driver-uninstaller-1999.html
</guid><description>
Display Driver Uninstaller (DDU) help to easily completely remove the packages and drivers graphics cards AMD, NVIDIA and Intel from your system without leaving any rest whatsoever. Display Driver Uninstaller will automatically detect your current GPU and allows you to delete drivers, registry and files related only by the click of a button. It will also prevent Windows automatically re-install drivers when you reboot your computer, leaving you a drivers graphics common until you install...
</description></item><item><title>Download QOwnNotes 26.1.12</title><pubDate> Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:19:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qownnotes-3178.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qownnotes-3178.html
</guid><description>
QOwnNotes is notes bookmark file simple text (GPL) open source application for GNU / Linux , Mac OS X and Windows of Patrizio Bekerle ( pbek on GitHub and IRC) (optional) activity along with the notes application of ownCloud or Nextcloud. QOwnNote store your notes as plain text files and can be synchronized with synchronization function file of ownCloud / Nextcloud. You can also use other apps like Syncthing or Dropbox . Just write out your thoughts as they appear, and edit them if...
</description></item></channel></rss>