<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 11:45:08 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 11:45:08 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Google Chrome 139.0.7258.128</title><pubDate> Wed, 13 Aug 2025 17:59:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-chrome-1012.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-chrome-1012.html
</guid><description>
Google Chrome web browser is the most used today. Support surf the web, listen to music, watch movies, play web game effective no jerky lag with the internet connection stable. When you are surfing the web or performing an important task, whether it is operation big or small, work or entertainment, then Chrome has the smart features and the speed you need to make, create and explore on the net.
The latest version of Google Chrome is the third 114. But we are providing for users Google...
</description></item><item><title>Download Office Tool Plus 10.25.54.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 13 Aug 2025 17:57:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-tool-plus-3664.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-tool-plus-3664.html
</guid><description>
Office Tool Plus based on the Office deployment tool from Microsoft. You can customize configuration files installation and install Office of to install Office without Internet. Configure install Office, as well as customize the product C2R have installed, such as add and remove components, language packs, etc.
Office Tool Plus - Download and install Office
The characteristics of Office Tool Plus
	1. Configure install Office, as well as customize the product C2R have installed, such...
</description></item><item><title>Download Dropbox 230.4.8797</title><pubDate> Wed, 13 Aug 2025 17:56:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dropbox-1313.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dropbox-1313.html
</guid><description>
Dropbox on taiwebs.com is free tool, the data synchronization across multiple PC become easier than never before: after installation, all what you have to do is enter your name, email address and password before opening the folder My Dropbox. If you install the software on a different computer, Dropbox will reflect the content of the online storage. So you exchange any data between the different computer is connected to Dropbox account. In addition the client is installed on the computer,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wise Care 365 Pro 7.2.8.709</title><pubDate> Wed, 13 Aug 2025 17:53:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wise-care-365-pro-106.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wise-care-365-pro-106.html
</guid><description>
Wise Care 365 pro is a package of utilities registry, disk, and other systems important for your PC. Easy to use and effective, Wise Care 365 is the best solution to improve the performance of your computer. Get Wise Care 365 and your computer will never run slow again!
Wise Care 365 pro is what?
Wise Care 365 Pro
	Check PC a clicks
	Pc cleaning &amp;amp; speed up
	Inventory hardware
	Protecting your privacy
	Protect real-time system
	Silent mode
	Boot speed faster
	Freeing up disk...
</description></item><item><title>Download Bandicam 8.2.0.2524</title><pubDate> Wed, 13 Aug 2025 17:53:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bandicam-243.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bandicam-243.html
</guid><description>
Bandicam is the software screen recording powerful, helps users to record all activities happening on the computer such as video games, presentations,..
Software Bandicam uses graphics technology DirectX / OpenGL will help you carry out a video record with high compression ratio, while keeping the video quality closer to the original work and provide superior performance compared with other programs providing the same functionality.
Bandicam can create video with quality high but...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Camera Raw 17.5</title><pubDate> Wed, 13 Aug 2025 17:52:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-camera-raw-02en-785.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-camera-raw-02en-785.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Camera Raw is Plugin edit photo on photoshop with the ability to handle the raw photos after the shoot to create beautiful photos and quality than the input image initially, this program helps support the photographers in editing and photography, make the photo beautiful.
Adobe Camera Raw - edit Raw images Photoshop
Adobe Camera Raw is a plugin which is integrated accompanied by a number of software photo editing such as Photoshop, Photoshop Elements, After Effects and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft Office 365 Pro Plus - Online Installer 3.3.5</title><pubDate> Wed, 13 Aug 2025 17:52:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-office-2021-professional-plus-x86-x64-online-installer-7661.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-office-2021-professional-plus-x86-x64-online-installer-7661.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft Office 2021 Professional Plus x86-x64 - Online Installer is a small script that helps users to download and install Microsoft Office 2021 Professional Plus including all updates directly from Microsoft CDN Server.
The version of Office 2021 downloaded and installed on your computer will include the following programs: Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Outlook, OneNote, Publisher, Access, Visio, Project, ProofingTools, OneDrive Desktop.
Usage:
Unzip the downloaded ZIP Archive...
</description></item><item><title>Download Rhinoceros 8.22.25217.12451</title><pubDate> Wed, 13 Aug 2025 17:51:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rhinoceros-179.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rhinoceros-179.html
</guid><description>
Rhinoceros is design software 3D easy to learn, easy to use and has range of application in various industries. Rhinoceros (or Rhino, Rhino3D) is a graphics software CAD and 3D developed by Robert McNeel &amp;amp; Associates, a private company established in the year 1980. Rhinoceros is developed according to the algorithm NURBS mathematical model, algorithm, focus on the correct presentation of curves and surfaces mathematics in computer graphics (in contrast to the application polygon...
</description></item><item><title>Download Total Commander 11.56 RC 1</title><pubDate> Wed, 13 Aug 2025 17:51:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-total-commander-1148.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-total-commander-1148.html
</guid><description>
Total Commander is a file manager popular allows you to perform various actions with any files on the hard drive, work with archives, data, multimedia... Open top is Total Commander has a new user interface is updated with the button in Windows XP, new icons of files, store, button, drive, etc.
Total Commander - file Manager program
Besides, Total Commander has the ability to set different colors for the files and folder background. A editable mode and sync manually when you compare...
</description></item><item><title>Download AB Download Manager 1.6.9</title><pubDate> Wed, 13 Aug 2025 17:50:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ab-download-manager-12399.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ab-download-manager-12399.html
</guid><description>
With this application, you can easily download files from anywhere. Enjoy fast, free downloads with seamless browser extension support. It is built to be a desktop application that allows you to manage and organize your downloads better than before.
AB Download Manager features
	Simple and modern UI: Simple UI and dark mode by default
	Faster download speeds: Download files using multiple connections to increase your download speed by up to 500%
	Download Queue: Create and manage your...
</description></item><item><title>Download Q-Dir 12.31</title><pubDate> Wed, 13 Aug 2025 17:49:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-q-dir-348.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-q-dir-348.html
</guid><description>
Q-Dir is software to manage the entire file and folder on the computer, allowing to see file in same time 4 different positions (viewport quadro) while still maintaining all the standard features of the Explorer.
It also provides a variety of management features, additional files included the filter file color-coding, layouts and columns can be customized, quick access to file and folder favorites and more.
Other features of Q-Dir , including directory listings (.txt, .doc .html .csv),...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe DNG Converter 17.5</title><pubDate> Wed, 13 Aug 2025 17:49:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-dng-converter-2452.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-dng-converter-2452.html
</guid><description>
Adobe DNG Converter, a free utility that converts files from more than 350 cameras to DNG, enables you to easily convert the files raw exclusively for camera file raw DNG more universal. A program strong enough which allows you to convert the source files RAW to DNG format popular and more convenient with a few clicks of the mouse.
DNG allows photographers to archive files, raw images of them in a single format for easy cataloging and access in the future. With specification formats are...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Camera Raw for macOS 17.5</title><pubDate> Wed, 13 Aug 2025 17:48:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/mac/download-adobe-camera-raw-for-mac-786.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/mac/download-adobe-camera-raw-for-mac-786.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Camera Raw launches a version dedicated to Mac OS. This is a photo editing plugin on photoshop with the ability to process raw photos after taking them to create more beautiful and quality photos than the original input image. This program helps photographers in editing and taking photos, creating beautiful photos.
Adobe Camera Raw For Mac - Photoshop Raw photo editing plugin for Mac
Features of Adobe Camera Raw
	As a Photoshop Plugins.
	Quick Raw image editing...
</description></item><item><title>Download Marmoset Toolbag 5.02 (5021)</title><pubDate> Wed, 13 Aug 2025 17:48:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-marmoset-toolbag-1352.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-marmoset-toolbag-1352.html
</guid><description>
Marmoset Toolbag is a real-time rendering strong providing editing documents, editing, animation and the rendered graphics. The program brings a necessary tool for 3D rendering, editing, animation, providing all the tools you need to create images / videos not nearly as practical and display the artwork of your best light.
Marmoset Toolbag - rendering and graphics editing
The features of Marmoset Toolbag
	Tools build professional
	Enjoy the whole new system to enter and collage,...
</description></item><item><title>Download ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro 15.25.0812</title><pubDate> Wed, 13 Aug 2025 17:47:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-videotube-downloader-pro-1276.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-videotube-downloader-pro-1276.html
</guid><description>
ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro is the professional version support download videos and playlists from YouTube, videos from Dailymotion, BBC iPlayer, ITV Player, ABC,  FOX,CBS.com Vimeo, Prosieben, Metacafe, Blip.tv CBC.ca many more video sites. After the video is downloaded, you can convert them to the formats compatible with iPad, iPhone, iPod, MPEG-4, H. 264, MP3, AC3.
ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro - Download videos on Youtube
This is one of the software download the most...
</description></item><item><title>Download MassTube 2025 v20.1.7.142 Ultra</title><pubDate> Wed, 13 Aug 2025 17:47:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-masstube-plus-461.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-masstube-plus-461.html
</guid><description>
MassTube Plus is a small utility used to download the favorite videos of you on youtube on your computer. This is a software compact, has a simple design with few options to download videos fastest. The you complete peace of mind because the software is easy to use, built exclusively for a single goal: to retrieve the video file from YouTube, so it doesn't pack the other useful features such as search engine integrated and a download audio file.
MassTube can work with multiple output...
</description></item><item><title>Download KJ File Manager 4.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 13 Aug 2025 17:46:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kj-file-manager-2378.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kj-file-manager-2378.html
</guid><description>
KJ File Manager is a program that will allow you to easily manage the audio and video files in karaoke format, you can now record MP3 tags ID and edit metadata information, done all in batch mode.
Easily manage files karaoke, video and audio of you and fixes title easily with batch editing powerful. Support the format name standard most popular. Automatic fix for underscores and capitalization, swap title and artist, shift, split, and replace field data on multiple files at once,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe DNG Converter for macOS 17.5</title><pubDate> Wed, 13 Aug 2025 17:41:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/mac/download-adobe-dng-converter-for-mac-3708.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/mac/download-adobe-dng-converter-for-mac-3708.html
</guid><description>
Adobe DNG Converter for Mac (DNG) is a publicly available storage format for raw files created by various digital cameras. This addresses the lack of an open standard for raw files created by individual camera models and ensures that photographers have easy access to their files. Hundreds of software manufacturers such as Apple and Google have developed support for DNG. And venerable camera manufacturers like Leica, Casio, Ricoh, Samsung, and Pentax have introduced cameras that offer...
</description></item><item><title>Download UpdatePack7R2 25.8.12</title><pubDate> Wed, 13 Aug 2025 17:12:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-updatepack7r2-6614.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-updatepack7r2-6614.html
</guid><description>
UpdatePack7R2 is software that allows you to update a working system and integrate software updates in the distribution. Can be installed on any version of Windows 7 and Server 2008 R2, any digit and any language. Includes updates for all versions of Internet Explorer, all critical, recommended, and security updates.
How to use UpdatePack7R2 software:
	The system must have at least 10 GB of free space on the hard drive and preferably no less than 1 GB of free RAM.
	Key / Reboot to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Nmap Security Scanner 7.98</title><pubDate> Wed, 13 Aug 2025 17:11:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nmap-security-scanner-7784.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nmap-security-scanner-7784.html
</guid><description>
Nmap Security Scanner is a useful utility for network exploration or security testing. Many systems and network administrators also find it useful for tasks such as network inventory, managing service upgrade schedules, and monitoring host or service uptime. Nmap uses raw IP packets in new ways to determine which servers are available on the network, what services (application names and versions) that server is providing, the operating system (and version operating) they are running, the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft Malicious Software Removal Tool 5.135</title><pubDate> Wed, 13 Aug 2025 17:11:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-malicious-software-removal-tool-1131.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-malicious-software-removal-tool-1131.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft Malicious Software Removal Tool is tools remove malicious software from your computer Microsoft help computer always clean and works well. The software runs on Windows XP, Windows 2000 and Windows Server 2003 to detect the file can harm the computer by tool Blaster, Sasser, and Mydoom.
Microsoft Malicious Software Removal Tool - Uninstall malware
If the scan detected malicious files, tool Microsoft Malicious Software Removal Tool will display a report describing the outcome,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Foxit PDF Editor Pro 13.2.0.23874 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Wed, 13 Aug 2025 17:07:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-foxit-pdf-editor-pro-13375.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-foxit-pdf-editor-pro-13375.html
</guid><description>
Foxit PDF Editor Pro is a professional PDF editing software designed for personal and business users who need advanced capabilities to create, edit, secure and manage PDF documents. This Foxit software can combine, split or repackage multiple PDF files. Documents can be merged or split based on page numbers, page layout or bookmarks. Additionally, this Suite can batch convert existing documents into one or more PDF files.
Features of Foxit PDF Editor Pro 
Advanced PDF editing with...
</description></item><item><title>Download Edge Remover 18.22</title><pubDate> Wed, 13 Aug 2025 17:07:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-edge-remover-7689.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-edge-remover-7689.html
</guid><description>
Edge Remover is our mini user interfaceless tool to permanently remove Microsoft Edge from your system. Easily remove Microsoft Edge browser from your system, with just one click, with this simple, no UI app.
Features of Edge Remover
	Remove MSEdge and its components
	Prevent reinstalling MSEdge on your system
Requirements:
Operating System: Microsoft Windows 7 or later
Framework: Microsoft .NET Framework 4.0
</description></item><item><title>Download SecretDNS 3.7.4</title><pubDate> Wed, 13 Aug 2025 17:06:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secretdns-12481.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secretdns-12481.html
</guid><description>
SecretDNS provides a quick means to deploy DNS over HTPS, meaning it allows DNS (short for Domain Name Server) resolution to be performed remotely using the HTTPS protocol to encrypts data between the client and the DNS resolver. Its purpose, obviously, is related to data security and user privacy, to prevent unauthorized interception and manipulation of DNS data.
Default DNS settings in SecretDNS use CloudFlare to ensure security. You can change DNS configuration in the dedicated tab...
</description></item><item><title>Download QuickViewer 1.2.6</title><pubDate> Wed, 13 Aug 2025 17:05:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quickviewer-3263.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quickviewer-3263.html
</guid><description>
QuickViewer is a image viewer, graphics to browse from the comfort multiple images. The software performs read image data first. And drawing the image data entered on the screen using OpenGL. You can browse picture with response smoother than ever.
QuickViewer - fast picture viewer
The features of the QuickViewer
To display images very quickly (using OpenGL)
Portable (no installation, registration, library, external)
Tablet ready
See page spread 2 pages (two photos, a times, for books...
</description></item></channel></rss>