<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 20:02:09 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 20:02:09 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Glary Utilities Pro 6.33.0.37</title><pubDate> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 20:40:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-utilities-pro-76.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-utilities-pro-76.html
</guid><description>
Glary Utilities Pro is a collection of tools and system utilities to fix, speed up, maintain and protect your computer. Glary Utilities Pro allows you to clean junk files, system downloads, as well as the subscriptions are not valid and Internet traces (that support the plug-in more for the 45+ program outside). You can also manage and delete add-ons of the browser, analyze the use of disk and find the file duplicate.
Glary Utilities Pro - optimized system
Key features Glary Utilities...
</description></item><item><title>Download IObit Malware Fighter Pro 13.0.0.1588</title><pubDate> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 20:40:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iobit-malware-fighter-pro-257.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iobit-malware-fighter-pro-257.html
</guid><description>
IObit Malware Fighter Pro is security software, remove malicious program with many advanced features that help protect safety for your system. IObit Malware Fighter Pro integration inside is the power of technology Dual-Core help quick scan and deep scan the entire system to detect and eliminate concerns about the virus.
IObit Malware Fighter Pro a lot of attention by the ability to detect and remove programs spyware from the system with fast speed and the most accurate. More special is...
</description></item><item><title>Download BluffTitler Ultimate 16.7.7.3</title><pubDate> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 20:39:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bluffTitler-ultimate-39.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bluffTitler-ultimate-39.html
</guid><description>
Create 3D titles brilliant for your video with BluffTitler Ultimate. You want to impress your friends and clients with 3D titles interesting? But don't want to spend a fortune on 3D animation, as well as professional software video titling?
BluffTitler is the easiest way to add animated text, 3D spectacular for photos and videos of you! Other 3D programs always seemed too hard to learn and too expensive to justify. But thanks to BluffTitler, I can finally create all the wonderful...
</description></item><item><title>Download ThinkAutomation Studio Professional 5.1.1095.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 20:32:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thinkautomation-studio-professional-9635.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thinkautomation-studio-professional-9635.html
</guid><description>
ThinkAutomation Studio Professional is software that automates on-premises and cloud-based business processes to cut costs and save time. Automate incoming communication channels, monitor databases, react to incoming webhooks, web forms and chat bots. Handles documents, attachments, local files, and other message sources.
Parse and extract data from incoming messages and take actions in business processes, such as outbound communications, updating on-premises and cloud databases,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Directory Opus Pro 13.19.1 Beta</title><pubDate> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 20:32:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-opus-pro-779.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-opus-pro-779.html
</guid><description>
Directory Opus Pro is a software replacement for Explorer with traditional strength and function more than any manager other files. Directory Opus Pro full support for high DPI screen (for example 4K and 5K) with the rename dialog is redesigned, with new features. Besides being a recording macro only allows you to perform mass renaming complex that don't need regular expressions. In addition, Directory Opus Pro also enhances the ability to script.Better handling of renaming recursive and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Glarysoft Malware Hunter Pro 1.207.0.838</title><pubDate> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 20:31:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glarysoft-malware-hunter-pro-235.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glarysoft-malware-hunter-pro-235.html
</guid><description>
Glarysoft Malware Hunter capabilities, comprehensive protection against threats, data protection and privacy, ensure the computer is no longer virus. It allows you against many types of viruses, trojans with the ability to super fast scanning to detect and remove the malware quickly. Glarysoft Malware Hunter has a simple design of the interface, but the pace of new work is the most important problem of this software.
Features Glarysoft Malware Hunter Pro
	Automatically search, detect,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Glary Tracks Eraser 6.0.1.29</title><pubDate> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 20:31:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-tracks-eraser-1342.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-tracks-eraser-1342.html
</guid><description>
Glary Tracks Eraser is security software privacy when browsing the web, allows you to delete all traces of network access and trace number, including browser cache, cookies, the website is already open, the URL has been entered, the document new mines, temporary files,... Glary Tracks Eraser that helps you free up space in hard disk drives, scan entire junk files in the drive with the speed of processing is extremely fast. Data deleted by Glary Tracks Eraser will not be able to restore,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Glary Malware Hunter PRO 1.207.0.838</title><pubDate> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 20:30:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-malware-hunter-pro-77.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-malware-hunter-pro-77.html
</guid><description>
Glary Malware Hunter PRO - detection of file malware on your computer and delete dangerous content, allowing you to run on-demand scan of the area, important system or specific files. As suggested by its name, Malware Hunter is designed to find and remove the files and components potential danger on your computer, keep it out of the virus and the type of threat other.
Glary Malware Hunter PRO - perfect protection of your equipment
Features Glary Malware Hunter PRO
- Scan ultrasound...
</description></item><item><title>Download Argente Registry Cleaner 4.0.3.7</title><pubDate> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 20:30:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-argente-registry-cleaner-13814.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-argente-registry-cleaner-13814.html
</guid><description>
Argente Registry Cleaner is a free Windows utility designed to scan, clean and repair invalid or obsolete entries in the Windows Registry, helping to improve system stability and performance. This utility quickly analyzes the entire Registry for errors such as invalid entries left by uninstalled programs, missing keys, broken references, and other junk that can cause system crashes.
Key Features:
	Fast and Thorough Scan: Provides multiple scan modes including Safe (fastest), Normal...
</description></item><item><title>Download QILING Fast Cache Standard / Server 3.1 Build 20250818</title><pubDate> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 20:29:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qiling-fast-cache-standard-server-13700.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qiling-fast-cache-standard-server-13700.html
</guid><description>
QILING Fast Cache can improve the overall performance of the system. Temporary files are often accessed by the system or other applications, and the reading speed of RAM is much higher than that of a real hard drive, so storing frequently accessed data in RAM greatly improves the data reading speed; Additional hard drives and SSD storage media have limited read and write times, so QILING Fast Cache also improves the life of real hard drives.
Main Features
	Improve system performance:...
</description></item><item><title>Download EF Mailbox Manager 25.20</title><pubDate> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 20:29:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ef-mailbox-manager-3212.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ef-mailbox-manager-3212.html
</guid><description>
EF Mailbox Manager can manage as many POP3 accounts as you want. To check periodically, polling time can be set separately for each account. You can check for new messages on the server and / or delete messages on the server or download the message at the local computer for further use.
Email downloaded will be saved in the text file ascii and is stored in a mailbox. If you use Outlook Express or any E-Mail program any other automatically open attachments, you should open the message...
</description></item><item><title>Download Glary Registry Repair 6.0.1.18</title><pubDate> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 20:28:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-registry-repair-637.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-registry-repair-637.html
</guid><description>
Glary Registry Repair is the software cleans and repair the problems of registry safely, professionally and effectively. Glary Registry Repair scans quickly, thoroughly and safely. Glarysoft Registry Repair analyzes more than a dozen different areas in your registry, and can identify up to 18 types of errors. It is also possible to scan thoroughly the register of Windows to find errors, invalid entries, optimizes the Regedit, etc.
Glarysoft Registry Repair automatically creates a backup...
</description></item><item><title>Download HTTP Downloader 1.0.6.6</title><pubDate> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 20:28:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-http-downloader-1821.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-http-downloader-1821.html
</guid><description>
HTTP Downloader is a download manager for HTTP protocol(S). Maximize throughput download at your using the port complete input / output high-performance (I / o completion ports). HTTP Downloader can open thousands of connections at the same time and consumes very little system resources. You can Start, pause, stop, and queue up to 100 downloads at the same time and every download can be divided into 100 parts.
HTTP Downloader - Support downloading protocol HTTP
Other features include...
</description></item><item><title>Download Glary Disk Cleaner 6.0.1.36</title><pubDate> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 20:27:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-disk-cleaner-1341.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-disk-cleaner-1341.html
</guid><description>
Glary Disk Cleaner is the software helps to erase the file system temporarily, cleanup your browser cache, or release the folder. Glary Disk Cleaner show scan results in detail, help you pick exactly each file to delete. The list file is much more wide open, with temporary files, user-generated, or the file system, cache, bug report, log files, data in recycle bin, the shortcut expires.
Glary Disk Cleaner - garbage system
Glary Disk Cleaner is designed to be simple as possible in use....
</description></item><item><title>Download RA Beauty Retouch Panel 5.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 17:38:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ra-beauty-retouch-panel-14255.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ra-beauty-retouch-panel-14255.html
</guid><description>
Beauty Retouch Panel is a Photoshop plugin built for photographers and photo editors who want to deliver professional, high-quality results faster. Even if your editing process starts with a RAW or AI-based processor, most portraits and beauty shots still need to be detailed in Photoshop. So, Beauty Retouch Panel is your most trusted assistant, helping you deliver professional results with greater speed and consistency. The new Beauty Retouch v5 features AI-powered tools that speed up your...
</description></item><item><title>Download GibbsCAM 2026 v26.0.49</title><pubDate> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 17:31:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gibbscam-001-732.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gibbscam-001-732.html
</guid><description>
GibbsCAM is a full-featured CAM system that provides powerful CNC programming capabilities to optimize manufacturing production.GibbsCAM 12 introduces a modern, updated system Updated interface designed to increase efficiency and improve overall user experience.
GibbsCAM
GibbsCAM updates with a new interface that gives users the ability to customize, along with the ease-of-use features users expect, while still maintaining character, personality and traditional workflows. by...
</description></item><item><title>Download FastKeys Pro 6.04</title><pubDate> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 17:11:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fastkeys-219.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fastkeys-219.html
</guid><description>
FastKeys is a compact tool used to create the shortcut, assign a shortcut key to specify the string stands for the text often use and manage mouse gestures. Users can specify the mouse manipulation to increase the performance of the work or simply replace a string or use an acronym.
FastKeys trigger to allow for expansion of abbreviations for texts used frequently in any application and save time typing. Enter a few letters and automates the task of repeating in a professional manner....
</description></item><item><title>Download ChrisPC YTD Downloader MP3 Converter Pro 6.25.1026</title><pubDate> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 17:10:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-ytd-downloader-mp3-converter-pro-2767.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-ytd-downloader-mp3-converter-pro-2767.html
</guid><description>
ChrisPC YTD Downloader MP3 Converter Pro is a Windows software dedicated to download and convert YouTube videos to audio file MP3 high quality. ChrisPC YTD Downloader MP3 Converter is one of the few program convert YouTube to MP3 (if not unique) available in the market to help you have quality best sound in the YouTube video you want to download and convert to MP3.
A in what format is most commonly used for recording in this decade is the MP3 format and thus we store on our utility...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tiny11 25H2 Build 26200.6899 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 17:10:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tiny11-8649.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tiny11-8649.html
</guid><description>
Tiny11 is a compact Windows operating system based on Windows 11 Pro 22H2, Tiny11 has everything you need for a comfortable, hassle-free computing experience. cumbersome and messy like a standard Windows installation. The operating system requires only 8GB of disk space and 2GB of RAM, and requires no TPM (Trusted Platform Module) and Secure Boot support.
The main goal of Tiny11 is to extend the reach of systems that can access Windows 11. The custom edition can run on any system...
</description></item><item><title>Download Red Gate SmartAssembly Professional 8.3.9.6618</title><pubDate> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 17:05:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-red-gate-smartassembly-1593.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-red-gate-smartassembly-1593.html
</guid><description>
Red Gate SmartAssembly is a tool that helps protect your application against reverse engineering or modifications prevent side Tuesday access to source code. This comprehensive solution protects the data card of you and more likely to report errors. This program makes files difficult can disassemble and injection code does not use, to help engineer can reverse and understand the core structure of the code. With your smartphone, you will have many features to tamper with the code as the...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Downloader 9.17.16</title><pubDate> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 17:04:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html
</guid><description>
YTD Youtube Downloader is an application that reliable and intuitive, allowing you to quickly download YouTube videos and save them to your computer. You can also convert the media files to the format desired video or extract audio streams and save separately. YTD Youtube Downloader lets you save your favorite clips of yourself from Youtube, Facebook, Vimeo and Dailymotion to your desktop. The software supports URLS from many web site hosting, multimedia and allows you to download desired...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wipe Pro 2025.13</title><pubDate> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 17:04:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wipe-pro-710.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wipe-pro-710.html
</guid><description>
Wipe Pro is software that helps clean up litter, increase in hard drive space besides also protect your privacy on the Internet, it removes records about personal activity on the computer. You will be able to delete browser history and the cache, the file index.dat, registry, files, cookies, internet history, auto complete, temporary internet files and many other items. This program also delete all activities other individuals that you made when using the PC and regardless of which...
</description></item><item><title>Download FX Science Tools MultiDocs 25.10.26</title><pubDate> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 17:03:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fx-science-tools-3744.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fx-science-tools-3744.html
</guid><description>
FX Science Tools provided to teachers of chemistry and physics the effective means to create equations and chemical structures. Just type and create. FX Chem FX Chem makes writing chemical equations become simple. You just type and FX Chem know enough about chemistry to put all the components of the equation at the right point. FX Chem can even create the chemical equations for nuclear - a very difficult thing in the Word. FX ChemSturation FX ChemSturation made the organic structure, what...
</description></item><item><title>Download ReShade 6.6.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 17:03:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-450-3227.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-450-3227.html
</guid><description>
ReShade is an open Source tool help improve the look of the old games on modern video cards as well as allow additional display technology / new video over on the old game doesn't support the technology that.
ReShade, technically, is a tool processing general for the games and video software. Imagine you see your favorite game yourself with the obscure-around, effects market the true depth or color correction. Function ReShade by showing in an automatic way and general access to...
</description></item><item><title>Download NonCompressibleFiles 4.91</title><pubDate> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 17:03:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-noncompressiblefiles-1688.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-noncompressiblefiles-1688.html
</guid><description>
NonCompressibleFiles is software compressed file size, the ability to create the file is not compressed or is compressed a maximum ability to transfer files. NonCompressibleFiles has the big advantage that is the ability to create one or thousands of files under 2 mode no compression or maximum compression. This is a strong possibility of the program that is not software would also have to be aimed to help increase work performance and reduce the time as well as effort of the...
</description></item></channel></rss>