<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 21:31:02 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 21:31:02 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download KMPlayer (KMP) 2025.11.14.11 x64 / 4.2.3.29 x86</title><pubDate> Sat, 22 Nov 2025 18:28:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kmplayer-kmp-902.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kmplayer-kmp-902.html
</guid><description>
KMPlayer (KMP) is software watch movies listen to music multi-function for video enthusiasts. KMPlayer development is many types of the format different. KMPlayer has improved on sound quality, images when listening to music and watching movies, the playback speed of video is faster, more codec player is added to the software video decoder is optimized.
KMPlayer also supports a variety of audio formats and video and offers a the interface can be customized with the preview coverflow and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Internet Download Manager (IDM) 6.42 Build 53</title><pubDate> Sat, 22 Nov 2025 18:18:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-inetnet-download-manager-161.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-inetnet-download-manager-161.html
</guid><description>
Internet Download Manager is the download acceleration software, the best download support now, it can help you speed up the download up to five times, continue and schedule downloads. The latest version of IDM adds the compatibility of Windows 10 and Windows 11, it has supported all current popular browsers such as Internet Explorer, Mozilla Firefox, Opera, Google Chrome, ..
Download IDM with the latest version on taiwebs.com making it easy to download and manage your downloaded files...
</description></item><item><title>Download FastStone Image Viewer 8.2 Corporate</title><pubDate> Sat, 22 Nov 2025 18:17:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-faststone-image-viewer-278.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-faststone-image-viewer-278.html
</guid><description>
FastStone Image Viewer software is manager, converter and editor image fast, stable, user-friendly. FastStone Image Viewer has the features include image viewing, management, comparison, red-eye removal, emailing, resizing, cropping and color adjustments. Full screen mode innovative but intuitive its provides quick access to EXIF information, browse the thumbnails and the main functions via hidden toolbars that pop up when your mouse touch the four edges of the screen.
FastStone Image...
</description></item><item><title>Download Free YouTube Download 4.4.44.1120 Premium</title><pubDate> Sat, 22 Nov 2025 18:17:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-download-1177.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-download-1177.html
</guid><description>
Free YouTube Download Premium is the most popular application to download videos from YouTube. The program was released in 2006 and regularly updated since then. Use the program to download and convert YouTube videos to view offline anytime.
Free YouTube Download - added Support to download youtube
Download more videos! Save whole playlists and YouTube channels, videos from a playlist individually (history, video be favorite, favourites, Watch later), videos from many different...
</description></item><item><title>Download IDM Retail 6.42 Build 53</title><pubDate> Sat, 22 Nov 2025 18:16:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-internet-download-manager-retail-3609.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-internet-download-manager-retail-3609.html
</guid><description>
IDM - Internet Download Manager Retail is a reliable utility and high efficiency will help you to increase your download speed and manage download at better. The program allows you to easily schedule, pause and resume downloads with a single click. Moreover, the application provides error resilience robust and can restart the download at the interrupted or broken. You can restore the download is interrupted due to network problems, lost connections, unexpected power outages, computer...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Premiere Pro 2025 v25.6.2.001 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Sat, 22 Nov 2025 18:16:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-premiere-pro-0021-1361.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-premiere-pro-0021-1361.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Premiere Pro is the leading video editing software for film, TV, and the web. Creative tools, integration with other Adobe apps and services, and the power of Adobe Sensei help you turn footage into finished movies and videos in a seamless workflow. It offers high-quality video editing at 4K x 4K resolution and beyond, with 32-bit color, in both RGB and YUV color spaces. Edit audio samples, support for VST audio plug-ins (plug-ins), and 5.1 surround sound tracks. The Premiere Pro...
</description></item><item><title>Download VCap Downloader Pro 0.1.41.6837</title><pubDate> Sat, 22 Nov 2025 18:15:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vcap-downloader-pro-8474.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vcap-downloader-pro-8474.html
</guid><description>
VCap Downloader Pro (VCapDL) is a popular piece of software that allows you to record video and audio from websites on the internet. The interface of the software is similar to a normal browser, making it easy for users to get used to and work with this software. User just need to copy video url from favorite browser and convert it to VCap Downloader Pro. It will capture the video and make the quality available for download. You can also extract the audio track from any video and convert...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Substance 3D Sampler 5.1.2.8523 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Sat, 22 Nov 2025 18:14:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-substance-3d-sampler-6625.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-substance-3d-sampler-6625.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Substance 3D Sampler allows you to create and iterate on collections of materials by refining and blending existing materials or by extracting new materials from scans ( one or more images). A new set of powerful tools that combine different technologies and creation methods (AI-based and manual) will help you manage your entire document library and export them to other applications.
Features of Adobe Substance 3D Sampler
	AI-powered scan processing
	Use your content everywhere....
</description></item><item><title>Download Hot Door CADtools 2026 v30.2.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 22 Nov 2025 18:13:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hot-door-cadtools-5031.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hot-door-cadtools-5031.html
</guid><description>
Hot Door CADtools is a plug-in add features to Illustrator, the program will add 92 drawing tools, editing, labeling, sizing, conversion, create, and utilities are organized in 10 groups tool in the tool palette in Adobe Illustrator. New tools recently added include: Scale, Line, Repeat, Repeat Along the Path, Scaled Type, Grid, and Wave tools.
The main features of Hot Door CADtools
	Improved table and tools
	Preview label and size
	Compression table by hiding the parts you don't...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cockos REAPER 7.54</title><pubDate> Sat, 22 Nov 2025 18:13:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cockos-reaper-889.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cockos-reaper-889.html
</guid><description>
Cockos REAPER is a powerful software for for windows, chp lets you record, arrange, edit, and display the audio waveform multi-track. Cockos REAPER offers an extensive feature set includes many effects and a sample project. REAPER supports ASIO, Kernel Streaming, WaveOut, and DirectSound for playback and recording. It reads the files in WAV, OGG and MP3 files and records WAV files. You can arrange any number of items in any number of tracks and use plug-in sound processing (DirectX and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cutting Optimization Pro 5.18.16.18</title><pubDate> Sat, 22 Nov 2025 18:12:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cutting-optimization-pro-6573.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cutting-optimization-pro-6573.html
</guid><description>
Cutting Optimization Pro is a cutting software used to obtain the optimal cut layout for one-dimensional (1D) and two-dimensional (2D) pieces. The software also allows you to define and process complex products, such as desks, tables, cabinets, cabinets, bookshelves... Cutting Optimization Pro can be used to cut rectangular panels made of glass, wood, metal, plastic or any other material used in industrial applications.
Features of Cutting Optimization Pro
	Optimize 1D and 2D in the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Abelssoft YouTube Song Downloader Plus 2026 v26.01</title><pubDate> Sat, 22 Nov 2025 18:12:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-abelssoft-youtube-song-downloader-plus-111.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-abelssoft-youtube-song-downloader-plus-111.html
</guid><description>
Abelssoft YouTube Song Downloader Plus 2018.18.17 Program YouTube Song Downloader Plus will help you search the music and video files from YouTube, after you can download them at. To search for music you just need to enter song name in the required field and you will get results, then you can download all videos and audio files. The program can search the entire album, this function will help to find individual songs from separate albums, because of this we specify the name of the artist...
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 7.4.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 22 Nov 2025 18:11:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-11-7760.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-11-7760.html
</guid><description>
TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 is a program that allows users to discover hidden settings in Windows 11. This application is specially designed for Windows 11, groups many registry settings and distribute them from the easy and secure user interface. With TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 you can move the Windows taskbar to the top and resize the taskbar by editing the registry value. With any application that modifies the registry, we recommend that you have a backup copy...
</description></item><item><title>Download Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium 4.4.44.1120</title><pubDate> Sat, 22 Nov 2025 18:11:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-to-mp3-converter-premium-844.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-to-mp3-converter-premium-844.html
</guid><description>
Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium version is a software used to convert YouTube to MP3, extract audio from playlists YouTube, show listings, charts, video responses, channels, favorites of the user. With Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium, you can download and convert playlists, channels, stream original tv series and get them into iTunes at the same time.
Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium - convert YouTube to MP3
Features Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium from the...
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 7.4.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 22 Nov 2025 18:11:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-10-7759.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-10-7759.html
</guid><description>
TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 is a utility that allows users to discover hidden settings in Windows 10. This application is specially designed for Windows 10, groups many registry settings and provide them from an easy and secure user interface. With TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 you can move the Windows taskbar to the top and resize the taskbar by editing the registry value. With any application that modifies the registry, we recommend that you have a backup copy to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Malwarebytes Support Tool 1.9.16.1154</title><pubDate> Sat, 22 Nov 2025 18:10:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-malwarebytes-support-tool-4901.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-malwarebytes-support-tool-4901.html
</guid><description>
Malwarebytes Support Tool is designed to help you fix the problem with Malwarebytes for Windows. Tool support Malwarebytes combines many utilities, such as utilities cleanup Malwarebytes and scan tool recover Farbar. Tool support Malwarebytes collect information from your computer and create a new support ticket or update a ticket out there with the information collected.
Tool support Malwarebytes can do?
	Provides the option of self-help to troubleshoot
	Create a support ticket...
</description></item><item><title>Download PhoneRescue for iOS 4.3.1.20251119</title><pubDate> Sat, 22 Nov 2025 18:10:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-phonerescue-for-ios-2851.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-phonerescue-for-ios-2851.html
</guid><description>
PhoneRescue for iOS is the solution to restore lost data of iOS devices such as iPhone, iPad with the ability to work quickly find back all the data on the device such as music, videos, photos, call logs, contacts, or even sms. With PhoneRescue is that you don't need to connect iPhone device with the computer directly, the software works through the index and account, now you can completely assured when using data on the iPhone, by all user's data are lost, you can restore back...
</description></item><item><title>Download WindowTop Pro 5.29.1 Beta</title><pubDate> Sat, 22 Nov 2025 18:09:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windowtop-6955.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windowtop-6955.html
</guid><description>
WindowTop is a program that pins windows on Desktop, in other words it sets the window to float above all other program windows, creating transparency for the windows. that window via a dedicated slider, which supports adjusting transparency, changing the color of application windows or similar programs with the dark theme of the Windows 10 operating system, creating contrast and reducing tension straight, painful for the eyes.
Features of WindowTop
	Put window on top
	Set window to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Photoshop 2025 v27.1.0.17 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Sat, 22 Nov 2025 17:39:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-0010-adobe-photoshop-737.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-0010-adobe-photoshop-737.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Photoshop is a powerful raster graphics editor developed by Adobe Systems, primarily used for image editing, photo editing, and graphic design. Currently,&amp;nbsp;Adobe Photoshop 2025 is considered a graphic design software, creating and enhancing images, illustrations, and 3D artwork. In addition, it also supports website and mobile app design, video editing, real-life painting simulation, and more.
Adobe Photoshop 2025 - Graphic design
When it comes to Adobe Photoshop, it is...
</description></item><item><title>Download AnyTime Organizer Deluxe 16.2.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 22 Nov 2025 17:38:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anytime-organizer-deluxe-456.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anytime-organizer-deluxe-456.html
</guid><description>
AnyTime Organizer Deluxe 16 is a powerful tool used to organize your personal and professional life. Friendly and simple interface helps you to easily access Schedule, list of jobs, Contacts, Record Books, Password, Cost and hundreds of design combinations for printable calendar. Let AnyTime Organizer help you organize your life and you will see why more people choose Anymore than any other organizational software brand.
Features of AnyTime Organizer Deluxe
Organize your calendar for...
</description></item><item><title>Download Danil Pristupov Fork 2.14</title><pubDate> Sat, 22 Nov 2025 17:38:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fork-6879.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fork-6879.html
</guid><description>
Fork is a great Git client app that allows you to keep tabs on every file line so you can know who is the last person to make changes. The simple and intuitive design of this app helps the management of all of your warehouses much easier. The Fork interface is extremely friendly to users. There is a long list of repositories, branches, origins, tags and archives on the left side of the screen.
With Fork, you can also search and open any of the repositories quickly, from the top of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Aescripts Blace AI Face Detection 2.1.42</title><pubDate> Sat, 22 Nov 2025 17:37:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aescripts-blace-ai-face-detection-13112.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aescripts-blace-ai-face-detection-13112.html
</guid><description>
Blace is an AI-based plugin designed to automatically detect and blur faces, primarily used in video compositing and editing in Adobe After Effects and Premiere Pro. It is recognized as the world's first AI-driven system for this purpose, providing a streamlined and automated approach to face detection and privacy protection in video footage.
Key features of Blace:
	AI-based face detection: Uses artificial intelligence to automatically detect faces in video clips.
	Customizable...
</description></item><item><title>Download AnyTrans for iOS 8.9.13.20251119</title><pubDate> Sat, 22 Nov 2025 17:37:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anytrans-for-ios-755.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anytrans-for-ios-755.html
</guid><description>
AnyTrans for iOS is content manager essential fully managed iPhone, Android and content of your cloud. Including all mobile devices, all cloud drives from your iPhone, iPad, iPod touch to phones and tablets. From local disk to cloud storage. AnyTrans has protected them all, providing you convenient management for all data and your files, regardless of whether they are stored where.
AnyTrans is the one stop solution to meet all the management needs of your data. For the first time, you can...
</description></item><item><title>Download VovSoft Image Combiner 2.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 22 Nov 2025 17:36:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-image-combiner-7477.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-image-combiner-7477.html
</guid><description>
VovSoft Image Combiner is a simple software tool that allows you to combine unlimited images into a single image, even if the source image is in different formats . You can combine multiple photos into one with the size and quality of the original with this easy-to-use software.
You can add images individually, drag and drop or select a folder containing them and let the application extract all compatible images. All images are displayed in a list, along with their width and height. It...
</description></item><item><title>Download Converseen 0.15.1.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 22 Nov 2025 17:20:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-converseen-7644.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-converseen-7644.html
</guid><description>
Converseen is a free cross-platform batch image processor for Windows and Linux that allows you to convert, resize, rotate, and flip countless images with just one click. Moreover, Converseen can convert an entire PDF file into a series of images with the characteristics you like: you can choose one of more than 100 formats, you can set the size, resolution and name file.
Conversion, thanks to ImageMagick, the powerful image manipulation library on which the program is based, can...
</description></item></channel></rss>