<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:52:46 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:52:46 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download WinToUSB Technician 10.5 + Professional</title><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:34:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wintousb-technician-2463.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wintousb-technician-2463.html
</guid><description>
WinToUSB Technician is a handy program that allows you to install Windows on a USB flash or hard drive and run Windows from that drive. The program is easy to use this provide the simple instructions to install the ISO image or CD / DVD into the drive of your USB. After installation, users can easily deploy Windows from the image on the USB drive.
WinToUSB lets you install and run Windows operating system on USB hard drive or USB flash drive, use ISO image or CD / DVD drive as the source...
</description></item><item><title>Download CyberLink PowerDirector Ultimate 2026 v24.1.1320.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:34:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-powerdirector-ultimate-425.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-powerdirector-ultimate-425.html
</guid><description>
CyberLink PowerDirector Ultimate is software editor, edit video and make movies on the computer from a variety of templates are made available, complete with effects, transitions, animations, and music. CyberLink PowerDirector 17 is a combination of video editing software with advanced video editing features powerful. Cblowing need to add your clips into the time line and click on 'Production'!
The tool design video in CyberLink PowerDirector have the ability to customize helps you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Streamlabs OBS 1.20.4</title><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:33:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-streamlabs-obs-6531.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-streamlabs-obs-6531.html
</guid><description>
Streamlabs OBS is a free video and video game livestream. Streamlabs OBS uses the same OBS source code but is improved with a better user experience. The software is also free and provides the setup process even more easily than the OBS Studio. Thanks to a built-in editor, Streamlabs OBS allows you to create and preview your flow interface with only a few clicks. Streamlabs OBS offers you various layers of coating to customize and design your flow for a few minutes. Obviously, after you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Kalmuri 4.1.8</title><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:33:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kalmuri-12521.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kalmuri-12521.html
</guid><description>
Kalmuri provides one of the simplest means of recording screen activity, working as both a snapshot utility and a screen recorder. It requires no installation and is ready to go at any time, waiting for your action quietly in the tray area, thus not disturbing your work.
Features of Kalmuri
	Supports video recording (specify entire screen and area)
	Entire screen, active program, window control, application area
	Supports PNG, JPG, BMP, GIF, MP4 file formats
	Supports saving documents...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinToUSB Enterprise 10.5</title><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:32:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wintousb-enterprise-32.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wintousb-enterprise-32.html
</guid><description>
WinToUSB is the best software that allows you to install and run the Windows operating system on a USB hard drive or USB flash drive, using an ISO image or a CD/DVD drive as a setting source. With WinToUSB, you can copy the current Windows operating system settings (Windows 7 or more) to the USB drive as the WindowsToGo work space. WinToUSB also supports instalability USB WinPE drives, which can help you move WinPE's content to the USB drive and make the drive to boot.
Features of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Free YouTube Download 4.5.1.116 Premium</title><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:31:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-download-1177.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-download-1177.html
</guid><description>
Free YouTube Download Premium is the most popular application to download videos from YouTube. The program was released in 2006 and regularly updated since then. Use the program to download and convert YouTube videos to view offline anytime.
Free YouTube Download - added Support to download youtube
Download more videos! Save whole playlists and YouTube channels, videos from a playlist individually (history, video be favorite, favourites, Watch later), videos from many different...
</description></item><item><title>Download Office Timeline Plus 13.20.00.00 Expert / Pro / Pro+ Edition</title><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:31:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-timeline-2106.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-timeline-2106.html
</guid><description>
Office Timeline is an add-on very useful and powerful software for Microsoft PowerPoint. With add-ons, you can create PowerPoint documents look more beautiful. With add-ons, you can add the time Line on the project by yourself. Application time for the composition and different segments of the document, your PowerPoint will not only increase the beauty for your work, but also for customers and your manager. The people who created this product is also believe that add-ons this is the only...
</description></item><item><title>Download Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium 4.5.1.116</title><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:30:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-to-mp3-converter-premium-844.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-to-mp3-converter-premium-844.html
</guid><description>
Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium version is a software used to convert YouTube to MP3, extract audio from playlists YouTube, show listings, charts, video responses, channels, favorites of the user. With Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium, you can download and convert playlists, channels, stream original tv series and get them into iTunes at the same time.
Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium - convert YouTube to MP3
Features Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium from the...
</description></item><item><title>Download R-Studio 9.5 Build 191683 Network / Technician</title><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:29:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-studio-1415.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-studio-1415.html
</guid><description>
R-Studio is a group of software data recovery and data recovery powerful and effective. -STUDIO is the solution to recover most comprehensive data for the file restored from the variants NTFS, NTFS5, ReFS, FAT12 / 16/32, exFAT, HFS / HFS + (Macintosh), Little and Big Endian of UFS1 / UFS2 (FreeBSD / OpenBSD / NetBSD / Solaris) and Ext2 / Ext3 / Ext4 partition FS (Linux).
R-Studio is also used to recover file raw (scan known file types) for the file system is damaged or not determined. It...
</description></item><item><title>Download VideoPad Video Editor Pro 18.06 Beta</title><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:29:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-videopad-video-editor-pro-268.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-videopad-video-editor-pro-268.html
</guid><description>
VideoPad Video Editor Pro is software edit video from any camcorder, DV camcorder, VHS player or webcam for best quality. The interface of this utility is divided into several parts (for example: list of multi-media, Effects, transitions, Files, Clips, video track, audio track, overlay), which makes everything seem difficult to operate. You can capture videos from camcorder or other devices like webcam or capture card TV and after you have added files and sequence clips to the queue, you...
</description></item><item><title>Download StaxRip 2.50.6</title><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:28:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-staxrip-2930.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-staxrip-2930.html
</guid><description>
StaxRip app is a comprehensive and powerful, allowing you to convert all video files DVB, DVD, or DV video into a variety of file formats. The program is open Source, meaning completely free to download and use. StaxRip can support many video formats such as x264, MPEG-4, DivX, XviD, MPEG-2 and many other formats. The format sounds different also be supported, including MP2 / MPA, AAC, WAV, Ogg Vorbis, MP3, AC3, DTS and other formats. Moreover, the program also supports a variety of...
</description></item><item><title>Download ARES Commander 2026.3 SP3 Build 26.3.1.4145</title><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:28:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ares-commander-4235.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ares-commander-4235.html
</guid><description>
ARES Commander is professional software to help you create and modify DWG drawings in 2D and 3D on your computer. Take advantage of features drafting and design that you expect for the file DWG its with the cost savings significantly. ARES Commander bring your productivity to new heights with productivity tools, smart and a special concept: the Trinity of CAD. ARES Commander offers interface and feel familiar, intuitive for any user CAD have any experience. More than one solution...
</description></item><item><title>Download Avira System Speedup Pro 7.5.0.552</title><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:27:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avira-system-speedup-pro-1175.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avira-system-speedup-pro-1175.html
</guid><description>
Avira System Speedup is an optimization process operating powerful, penetrating to where there is no user that is using safe and carefully delete the programs and files not in use, optimizing Windows and return the job fast, no errors that you deserve. First, Avira System Speedup Pro will unleash gigabyte of space on your hard disk by deleting the files is obsolete and duplicate. Then stop software, no active consumption of your memory unnecessarily. In addition, with Just one click,...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter 3.9.18 (2001)</title><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:27:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-to-mp3-converter-1744.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-to-mp3-converter-1744.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter is the software support download youtube video and convert video to mp3 format fast and most simple. MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter allows you download and convert videos from YouTube and other websites to MP3 format by pasting the YouTube URL into the application. When you paste the URL, the program will display thumbnails for videos and you have the option to customize the title information, artist and album before you begin the process of...
</description></item><item><title>Download KeyScrambler Premium 3.19.0.1 + Professional</title><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:26:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-keyscrambler-premium-professional-143.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-keyscrambler-premium-professional-143.html
</guid><description>
KeyScrambler Premium / Professional allows users to search for and remove the malicious program, the spy program on the computer system. This program support users to handle a number of spy programs send user information to the server by way thoroughly remove them from the system.
KeyScrambler Premium Key key encryption real-time encryption key, every key you type deep in the Windows. It protects the personal information of you against all malware keylog already know and not know on...
</description></item><item><title>Download QOwnNotes 26.1.10</title><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:19:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qownnotes-3178.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qownnotes-3178.html
</guid><description>
QOwnNotes is notes bookmark file simple text (GPL) open source application for GNU / Linux , Mac OS X and Windows of Patrizio Bekerle ( pbek on GitHub and IRC) (optional) activity along with the notes application of ownCloud or Nextcloud. QOwnNote store your notes as plain text files and can be synchronized with synchronization function file of ownCloud / Nextcloud. You can also use other apps like Syncthing or Dropbox . Just write out your thoughts as they appear, and edit them if...
</description></item><item><title>Download Thimeo Stereo Tool 10.75</title><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:19:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stereo-tool-4066.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stereo-tool-4066.html
</guid><description>
Stereo Tool is an audio processor based on software, provide sound quality superior and comes with many unique features. It is used by over 1500 FM stations, from the station of the small local to the station 50 - 100 kW and nationwide network with dozens of generators, thousands of stations online and many radio DAB +, HD, AM and TV. Stereo Tool can make recordings sound equal and consistent in volume and sound color, highlight details and increase the stereo effect is there. It can...
</description></item><item><title>Download FreeFileSync 14.7</title><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:18:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-freefilesync-2447.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-freefilesync-2447.html
</guid><description>
FreeFileSync is a program open source and free to be used to sync files. It's available on Windows, Linux and OS X. The project is supported by donations. Donors get a few extra features like the automatic updates, synchronize, parallel, mobile version and install silent.
FreeFileSync - sync data
Features of FreeFileSync
	Detect moved and renamed files and folders
	Copy the file locked (Volume Shadow Copy Service)
	Detect conflicts and propagate delete
	Compare binary
	Full support...
</description></item><item><title>Download NVIDIA App 11.0.6.383</title><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:18:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nvidia-app-12646.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nvidia-app-12646.html
</guid><description>
NVIDIA App is an indispensable companion for PC gamers and creators. Make sure your PC is always updated with the latest NVIDIA drivers and technology. Optimize your games and apps with the new unified GPU control center, capture your favorite moments with powerful recording tools through in-game overlays, and explore new tools and features. Latest NVIDIA software.
The program consists of two main parts
	Game Ready Drivers: GeForce Game Ready Drivers are fine-tuned in collaboration...
</description></item><item><title>Download Chaos Vantage 3.1.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:17:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chaos-vantage-6178.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chaos-vantage-6178.html
</guid><description>
Explore and interact with enough 3D detail in real time. Chaos Vantage is even more outstanding than the V-Ray even though you ' re using the V-Ray version. Artists and designers only need to pull and drop their V-Ray (.vrscene) scenes to discover them immediately in real time-without taking the time to optimize the geometry, opening up the UV package. When in Vantage, the user has the freedom to define and recall views and scenes, create a role in the role and communicate better than...
</description></item><item><title>Download Puran Utilities 3.2.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:11:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-puran-utilities-14274.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-puran-utilities-14274.html
</guid><description>
Puran Utilities is a suite of over 20 software utilities, including but not limited to utilities that can help you get the most out of your computer's performance. It also provides automatic and one-click solutions to keep your computer clean and error-free.
Tools and Features Included
	Disk Check - Helps you fix errors and recover bad sectors on your hard drive using chkdsk.
	Uninstaller - Helps you uninstall unnecessary software and also software that cannot be uninstalled...
</description></item><item><title>Download YesLogic Prince 16.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:11:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yeslogic-prince-496.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yeslogic-prince-496.html
</guid><description>
YesLogic Prince is software that converts a HTML document into PDF document, while still maintaining the entire structure and style of CSS. Prince is an ingredient in the ideal for software-based servers, such as web applications need to print reports or invoices. Using Prince, it's quick and easy to create PDF files.
Prince can also be the author and publishers use to typeset and print documents written in HTML, XHTML, or one of the many document formats based on XML. Prince has the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Alternate Quick Audio 2.240</title><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:10:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-alternate-quick-audio-2275.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-alternate-quick-audio-2275.html
</guid><description>
Alternate Quick Audio is software support audio player, already know want to find something new for yourself. This program lets you play, record and convert your music in MP3 format and WAV. The interface is very simple, even boring in places, but it does not cause confusion, everything is clear immediately after launch. Transition allows you to work with formats such as MP2, MPG, MP4, OGG, FLAC, FLV, AAC.
Alternate Quick Audio - Listen to audio recording
Alternate Quick Audio has an...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adlice Protect (formerly RogueKiller) 16.5.5.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:10:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rogueKiller-171.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rogueKiller-171.html
</guid><description>
RogueKiller is a tool anti-malware independent can assist advanced users with the removal of a number of difficulties in the removal of malware, in security software rogue special.
The program can terminate processes, malware has to know to you can delete them manually or use the tool clear of the Tuesday to complete the work. RogueKiller can also restore HOSTS file as well as your DNS settings and Proxy, which is often modified by rogue applications.
RogueKiller
When you run...
</description></item><item><title>Download Draftable Desktop 25.12.200</title><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:10:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-draftable-desktop-3749.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-draftable-desktop-3749.html
</guid><description>
Draftable Desktop is comparison tool documents the fastest. Compare over 300 pages in a few seconds. Draftable Desktop 2.0 is now available - faster and stronger than ever! See all the changes in your documents, locally and online. Take your work to the next level. Compare secret and private do not use the internet and your documents never leave your computer. Specifically, Draftable Desktop compatible with .xls, .xlsx, .xlsxm. With Office 2013, 2016 or 365, you can compare text in...
</description></item></channel></rss>