<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 20:43:51 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 20:43:51 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download NanaZip 6.0.1630.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 18 Feb 2026 17:45:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nanazip-8074.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nanazip-8074.html
</guid><description>
NanaZip is an open source file archiver for the modern Windows experience, forked from the source code of the popular open source file archiver 7-Zip. NanaZip is considered an interesting alternative to WinRAR and WinZip. According to tests, NanaZip provides about 10% better compression ratio than WinRAR and WinZip.
Supported formats:
	Packing/unpacking: 7Z, ZIP, XZ, BZIP2, GZIP, TAR and WIM.
	Extract: RAR, AR, ARJ, CAB, CHM, CPIO, CramFS, DMG, EXT, FAT, GPT, HFS, IHEX, ISO, LZH,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Internet Download Manager (IDM) 6.42 Build 60</title><pubDate> Wed, 18 Feb 2026 17:43:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-inetnet-download-manager-161.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-inetnet-download-manager-161.html
</guid><description>
Internet Download Manager is the download acceleration software, the best download support now, it can help you speed up the download up to five times, continue and schedule downloads. The latest version of IDM adds the compatibility of Windows 10 and Windows 11, it has supported all current popular browsers such as Internet Explorer, Mozilla Firefox, Opera, Google Chrome, ..
Download IDM with the latest version on taiwebs.com making it easy to download and manage your downloaded files...
</description></item><item><title>Download JRiver Media Center 35.0.47</title><pubDate> Wed, 18 Feb 2026 17:42:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jriver-media-center-110.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jriver-media-center-110.html
</guid><description>
JRiver Media Center can help you strictly manage all your files media and enjoy them in a completely new way. Launching the application for the first time, users will be immediately impressed with the intuitive and eye-catching interface with many interesting features to explore. Most people who have used JRiver Media Center evaluate that the software interface design is youthful and modern.
The software for arranging cover art of music files is also extremely neat, especially Insert...
</description></item><item><title>Download IDM Retail 6.42 Build 60</title><pubDate> Wed, 18 Feb 2026 17:41:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-internet-download-manager-retail-3609.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-internet-download-manager-retail-3609.html
</guid><description>
IDM - Internet Download Manager Retail is a reliable utility and high efficiency will help you to increase your download speed and manage download at better. The program allows you to easily schedule, pause and resume downloads with a single click. Moreover, the application provides error resilience robust and can restart the download at the interrupted or broken. You can restore the download is interrupted due to network problems, lost connections, unexpected power outages, computer...
</description></item><item><title>Download Rufus 4.13 + Portable</title><pubDate> Wed, 18 Feb 2026 17:40:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rufus-2442.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rufus-2442.html
</guid><description>
Rufus support create a USB install Windows operating system like installing from a Windows installation disc often. Rufus offers to users the features from simple to lift the cap fit the needs as well as the ability of many objects. Rufus also has useful functions such as automatic identification, USB, display information about the connected USB.
A new version of a small program has been released that allows you to create and format the USB flash drive that can boot, it also can operate...
</description></item><item><title>Download Agisoft Metashape Professional 2.3.1 Build 22102</title><pubDate> Wed, 18 Feb 2026 17:39:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-agisoft-metashape-professional-1731.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-agisoft-metashape-professional-1731.html
</guid><description>
Agisoft Metashape (formerly PhotoScan) is a software product independently perform image processing and digital data creation, 3D space used in GIS applications, material cultural heritage and the production visual effects as well as the indirect measurement of the different subjects scale. Technical digital photography is deployed wisely is applied with the method of computer vision led to the system processor, smart auto, on the one hand, can be managed by a new person in the field of...
</description></item><item><title>Download K-Lite Codec Pack Update 19.5.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 18 Feb 2026 17:38:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-update-5145.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-update-5145.html
</guid><description>
K-Lite Codec Pack Update is the update of the set of codecs and related tools. Codec stands for Compressor-decompressor. Codec is necessary to encode and decode (play) audio and video. K-Lite Codec Pack Update is designed as a user-friendly solution with users to play all movie files your. With Codec Pack K-Lite, you can play 99% of all the movies found on your computer. A number of packages codec is not friendly with computers, as they tend to slow down Windows, break down multimedia...
</description></item><item><title>Download Picture Window Pro 8.0.551</title><pubDate> Wed, 18 Feb 2026 17:37:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-picture-window-pro-7452.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-picture-window-pro-7452.html
</guid><description>
Picture Window Pro is a powerful image editing tool designed for serious photographers with strict creative and quality standards. Its comprehensive set of photo editing and editing tools let you control and shape every aspect of your images.
Picture Window Pro 8 is a complete rewrite of Picture Window Pro 7. It features non-destructive image editing through a novel interface based on an image tree. It also fully supports large, high-resolution displays and can be used in dual monitor...
</description></item><item><title>Download TreeSize Free 4.8.1.610</title><pubDate> Wed, 18 Feb 2026 17:36:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-treesize-free-10656.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-treesize-free-10656.html
</guid><description>
TreeSize Free is a free disk space manager for Windows, it will show you the size of folders including its subfolders in a similar fashion like Explorer. Large folders can be identified at a glance thanks to the gradient bar displayed in the background. All scan results can be detailed at the file level and filters, e.g. for files of a certain type, can be applied.
Features of TreeSize Free
	Search space: clean up hard drive space
	Break down hard drive space usage to file level:...
</description></item><item><title>Download VMware InstallBuilder Enterprise 26.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 18 Feb 2026 17:36:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vmware-installbuilder-enterprise-6055.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vmware-installbuilder-enterprise-6055.html
</guid><description>
VMware InstallBuilder Enterprise  is a development tool for building cross-platform installers for desktop and server software. With InstallBuilder, you can quickly create professional, dynamic installers for Linux, Windows, Mac OS X, Solaris, and other platforms from a project file and build environment. In addition to the installer, InstallBuilder will create RPM and Debian packages and rich CD / DVD. The automatic update function makes it easy to deliver updates directly to users...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter 3.9.18 (1602)</title><pubDate> Wed, 18 Feb 2026 17:35:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-to-mp3-converter-1744.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-to-mp3-converter-1744.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter is the software support download youtube video and convert video to mp3 format fast and most simple. MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter allows you download and convert videos from YouTube and other websites to MP3 format by pasting the YouTube URL into the application. When you paste the URL, the program will display thumbnails for videos and you have the option to customize the title information, artist and album before you begin the process of...
</description></item><item><title>Download MaxCut Business Edition 2.9.6.6</title><pubDate> Wed, 18 Feb 2026 17:34:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-maxcut-business-edition-3912.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-maxcut-business-edition-3912.html
</guid><description>
MaxCut Business Edition is a software to create cutting diagrams, accurate, and cost estimate for the wood industry, cabinets and metal,.. You enter the size and material, MaxCut will do the rest! Produce optimized cutting diagrams, create estimates, orders, and labels - it's just a click. Run the application MaxCut Business Edition brings a pretty clean interface and slick quickly get you up and running. Most space represents the editing area, with the main function are stored cleverly in...
</description></item><item><title>Download Synchredible Professional 9.113</title><pubDate> Wed, 18 Feb 2026 17:33:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-synchredible-professional-1923.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-synchredible-professional-1923.html
</guid><description>
Synchredible Professional is the most advanced version help synchronize the folder and your drive quickly and easily. Whether it is a single file or an entire drive - Synchredible Professional will synchronize, copy and save them for you. The software guide will assist you to identify the work that is scheduled in advance or be done through the USB connection. This way, you can keep your files in sync - automatically.
In the past years, the advanced technology of the us in Synchredible...
</description></item><item><title>Download Synchredible 9.113</title><pubDate> Wed, 18 Feb 2026 17:33:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-synchredible-53.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-synchredible-53.html
</guid><description>
Synchredible is an easy to use tool to synchronize folders and files. It provides a wizard interface lets you set up the sync job, select files to exclude, schedule the job to execute automatically, and more.Additional features include support for network and external drives, check CRC32, and more.
Synchredible - synchronization of folders and files
Among other things, you can use the filter for the file type specific data synchronization according to the time or routine deletion of...
</description></item><item><title>Download WordWeb Pro 10.60</title><pubDate> Wed, 18 Feb 2026 17:32:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wordweb-pro-4045.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wordweb-pro-4045.html
</guid><description>
WordWeb Pro this is the most basic tool of WordWeb Software, Other than WordWeb Pro Ultimate Reference Bundle, WordWeb Pro includes only lookup the most basic use support references from other reliable sources such as Wikipedia,... WordWeb Pro help you lookup dictionaries to find the synonyms are widely used, great for helping you to write clear English easy to understand. In addition to using dictionary comprehensive English dictionary and thesaurus supplied, if you online, you can also...
</description></item><item><title>Download Fan Control v260</title><pubDate> Wed, 18 Feb 2026 17:31:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fancontrol-5749.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fancontrol-5749.html
</guid><description>
FanControl is a highly customizable fan control software for Windows. Stay in control of every aspect of your PC's GPU and CPU fan with the help of this highly customizable fan control app.
Features of FanControl
	Save, edit and load multiple configurations
	Multiple temperature sources (CPU, GPU, motherboard, hard drive, ".sensor" files)
	Custom fan curve
	Fine tune fan control response with steps,% start,% stop, response time and delay
	Mix different curves and sensors...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mullvad Browser 15.0.6</title><pubDate> Wed, 18 Feb 2026 17:31:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mullvad-browser-12254.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mullvad-browser-12254.html
</guid><description>
Mullvad Browser is a privacy-focused web browser developed through a partnership between Mullvad VPN and Tor Project. This browser is designed to minimize tracking and fingerprinting. You can say that this is the Tor browser to use without the Tor Network. Instead, you can use this browser with a reliable VPN. The idea is to provide one more alternative – besides the Tor Network – to browse the internet with more privacy. To get as many people as possible together against today's big...
</description></item><item><title>Download Bitwig Studio 6.0 Beta 13</title><pubDate> Wed, 18 Feb 2026 17:30:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bitwig-studio-3626.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bitwig-studio-3626.html
</guid><description>
Find new standard in the process of individual work. Bitwig Studio excite you good control over his music, give you access to all features of your production. Streamline course creation of you and quickly develop your ideas into the songs, compositions and music full.
Bitwig Studio - Create your own music
Arrange and record, perform and improvise, or do all at the same time. Choose among the many records displayed. Design your sound with the equipment container commitment. Mixing the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Quick Access Popup 12.2.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 18 Feb 2026 17:29:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quick-access-popup-984.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quick-access-popup-984.html
</guid><description>
Quick Access Popup  ( QAP ) is a software that provides quick access to files, files, windows applications and is  shortcut manager , mouse and keyboard.  Quick Access Popup  helps you quickly move between FILE, DOCUMENT, APPS in Windows Explorer or file dialog to quickly launch applications, documents or web pages at once 
To launch the pop-up menu, click the  QAP  icon in the Notifications area, press the Middle mouse button, or press Windows + W (these triggers can be changed under...
</description></item><item><title>Download Dropbox 242.4.5813</title><pubDate> Wed, 18 Feb 2026 17:27:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dropbox-1313.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dropbox-1313.html
</guid><description>
Dropbox on taiwebs.com is free tool, the data synchronization across multiple PC become easier than never before: after installation, all what you have to do is enter your name, email address and password before opening the folder My Dropbox. If you install the software on a different computer, Dropbox will reflect the content of the online storage. So you exchange any data between the different computer is connected to Dropbox account. In addition the client is installed on the computer,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Clean Space Pro 2026 v718</title><pubDate> Wed, 18 Feb 2026 17:26:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-clean-space-pro-545.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-clean-space-pro-545.html
</guid><description>
Clean Space Pro is the professional software remove junk files from the system to release the hard drive and improve computer performance. From time to time when using computer files as buffers, temporary files of various programs, files, internet cookies, internet browsing history, diary, file index.dat, registry entries and even the Windows will gradually increase, occupy wise space your hard drive and make the computer suffer from stagnation. The best solution is to use the Clean Space...
</description></item><item><title>Download Fast Video Cutter Joiner 7.0.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 18 Feb 2026 17:25:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fast-video-cutter-joiner-7542.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fast-video-cutter-joiner-7542.html
</guid><description>
Fast Video Cutter Joiner is a fast video cutter and joiner with an easy to use interface. It allows users to trim parts of a video quickly while maintaining the quality of the original video. It supports various formats like AVI, MPEG, MP4, WMV, 3GP, FLV...
This tool helps you to cut video files into small parts, to keep only the parts you need and remove unwanted parts like trailers and advertisements in a movie. The clips you cut can then be used for other video productions or for a...
</description></item><item><title>Download InternetTest Pro 9.1.0.2602</title><pubDate> Wed, 18 Feb 2026 17:25:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-internettest-6718.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-internettest-6718.html
</guid><description>
InternetTest is a small multipurpose tool to check internet connection status and more, you can easily verify if a particular website is down or not. no and navigate to it via the Down Detector function. You can also check the IP location in the app via OpenStreetMap, Bing Maps or Google Maps. It will also give you the connection history displayed on the right side of the simple interface.
Features of InternetTest
	Check your Internet connection
	IP Localization
	Down Detector
	Dark...
</description></item><item><title>Download Formware 3D Slicer 1.3.0.8</title><pubDate> Wed, 18 Feb 2026 17:22:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-formware-3d-slicer-8009.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-formware-3d-slicer-8009.html
</guid><description>
Formware 3D Slicer is a 3D Printing slicer and support software. It is compatible with devices from the following brands: ASIGA, Kudo 3d, Wanhao, Anycubic, Phrozen, Elegoo, Epaxx, NanoDLP, Peopoly and many other common LCD/DLP printer manufacturers.
Features of Formware 3D Slicer
	Automatically generate support structures
	Drag support with automatic post-correction
	Support can be represented as lines or points
	Angles/surfaces classified as important can be edited and even...
</description></item><item><title>Download Monkeys Audio 12.22</title><pubDate> Wed, 18 Feb 2026 17:22:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-monkeys-audio-949.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-monkeys-audio-949.html
</guid><description>
Monkey\'s Audio is software that compresses digital music without loss of quality. Supports high quality WAV files and CD ripping. Monkeys Audio will compress .wav tracks into .ape files to reduce their size without loss of sound quality, decompress .ape, convert files, check file integrity and manage tags.
Unlike traditional methods like MP3 and OGG, which permanently remove quality to save space, Monkey\'s Audio only creates perfect copies with the same sound quality as the originals....
</description></item></channel></rss>