<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 14:19:25 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 14:19:25 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Microsoft Safety Scanner 1.445.115.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 18 Feb 2026 17:02:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-safety-scanner-4512.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-safety-scanner-4512.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft Safety Scanner is a scanning tool designed to find and remove malware from a Windows computer. Just download and run the scan to find malware and try to reverse the changes made by the threat identified. Microsoft Safety Scanner has the ability to remove virus, spyware and files other dangers on your computer, Microsoft Safety Scanner completes scanning tasks in just a few minutes, while the computer is moderate stress during handling.
In other words, no real time protection...
</description></item><item><title>Download PortKiller 3.3.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 18 Feb 2026 17:01:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-portkiller-14468.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-portkiller-14468.html
</guid><description>
PortKiller is not just a tool for closing ports — it's a cross-platform solution for monitoring and managing ports with powerful functionality. It listens to all TCP ports, identifies active processes, and displays detailed information about each process. Specifically designed for software developers and network administrators, PortKiller goes beyond simple port monitoring and process termination: it lets you filter by process type, simplify process management, handle Kubernetes port...
</description></item><item><title>Download MDScan + OCR 3.9.97</title><pubDate> Wed, 18 Feb 2026 16:58:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-mobile-doc-scanner-mdscan-ocr-8307.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-mobile-doc-scanner-mdscan-ocr-8307.html
</guid><description>
Mobile Doc Scanner (MDS) is an application that allows users to scan, edit and save documents using the Android device's camera. It's designed to work as a portable scanner so you can easily digitize documents, receipts, business cards, and more.
All image processing is done on your device only! No material will be posted online without your wishes! Take photos with your camera, edit them with many advanced features, save to your favorite format and share on social networks, email,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sygic GPS Navigation &amp;amp; Maps 26.0.2-105446</title><pubDate> Wed, 18 Feb 2026 16:58:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sygic-gps-navigation-maps-8606.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sygic-gps-navigation-maps-8606.html
</guid><description>
Sygic GPS Navigation &amp;amp; Maps is the most downloaded GPS navigation app in the world, trusted by more than 200 million drivers. Offline 3D maps stored on your phone for GPS navigation without an internet connection. We update our maps for free multiple times each year so you can always rely on Sygic GPS Navigation.
Navigate anywhere, even without an Internet connection
	Offline maps of all the countries in the world, from TomTom and other providers
	Free map updates several times...
</description></item><item><title>Download YoWindow Weather - Unlimited 2.56.3</title><pubDate> Wed, 18 Feb 2026 16:58:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-yowindow-weather-unlimited-8421.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-yowindow-weather-unlimited-8421.html
</guid><description>
YoWindow is a unique new weather app. The magic of YoWindow is a living landscape that reflects your real-life weather. For example, if it rains - it will rain in YoWindow. Sunset and sunrise in YoWindow take place at the same time as in real life. But the cool thing is you can roll time forward. Just swipe the screen and you'll see how the weather changes throughout the day.
YoWindow Weather Features - Unlimited
	All the weather at your fingertips. You see the current weather,...
</description></item><item><title>Download PhotoRoom AI Photo Editor 2026.08.01 build 2282</title><pubDate> Wed, 18 Feb 2026 16:57:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-photoroom-ai-photo-editor-10083.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-photoroom-ai-photo-editor-10083.html
</guid><description>
PhotoRoom is an all-in-one app for great visual content editing, design, and optimization that helps you run your business from your phone. Remove or erase photo backgrounds, use templates, and create your own content. The app will automatically crop objects and people in your photos. With just one tap, you can remove the background and create highlight content that showcases a product or a person. Edit images, add text or logo, stickers, create collages....
What you can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Phone Dialer &amp;amp;amp; Contacts: drupe 3.22.0.3</title><pubDate> Wed, 18 Feb 2026 16:57:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-phone-dialer-contacts-drupe-11477.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-phone-dialer-contacts-drupe-11477.html
</guid><description>
Want to see caller ID, spam indicator and block spammers, directly from your call screen? drupe is your application. Trusted by over 20 million users worldwide. drupe replaces your boring call screen with a fresh interface, built and configured precisely for you! Forget about traditional Phone Book applications!
Main features:
	Smart Dialer - Dialing across multiple apps is quick and easy
	Smart caller ID tracker and blocker to find unknown numbers - drupe ID identifier will help you...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDF Scanner app - TapScanner 3.0.95 build 3095</title><pubDate> Wed, 18 Feb 2026 16:57:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pdf-scanner-app-tapscanner-12104.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pdf-scanner-app-tapscanner-12104.html
</guid><description>
TapScanner is a mobile application that allows you to scan documents with your smartphone camera and convert them into PDF files or image formats. It essentially turns your device into a portable scanner, making capturing and digitizing physical documents convenient on the go.
TapScanner Features
	Scan documents, receipts, QRs and business cards
	Document Scanner App - Automatic Border Detection
	Tweak your images with multiple filters to achieve perfection
	Easily manage your...
</description></item><item><title>Download analiti - Speed Test WiFi Analyzer 2026.02.92891</title><pubDate> Wed, 18 Feb 2026 16:56:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-speed-test-wifi-analyzer-8353.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-speed-test-wifi-analyzer-8353.html
</guid><description>
Speed ​​Test WiFi Analyzer is a tool that can be used to test the performance of a wireless network. It can measure various metrics, such as signal strength, channel interference, and network throughput.
Features of Speed ​​Test WiFi Analyzer
Speed ​​test:
	Internet or iPerf3 speed test (including server and client)
	Simultaneous ping, DNS and HTTP latency results – to multiple servers with configurable load
	Monitor uptime remotely 24/7 for downtime or slowdown
360...
</description></item><item><title>Download AdGuard Ad Blocker 4.14.35 Nightly</title><pubDate> Wed, 18 Feb 2026 16:56:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-adguard-block-ads-without-root-8215.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-adguard-block-ads-without-root-8215.html
</guid><description>
AdGuard for Android is the only root-free ad blocker for Android that removes ads in apps and browsers, protects your privacy, and helps you manage your apps. Adguard is designed to block unwanted ads, pop-ups and banners while you browse the web on your device. It uses a combination of local VPN technology and a custom DNS server to block ads, meaning it can block ads in apps as well as in web browsers.
In addition, Adguard also blocks tracking scripts from collecting information about...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDF Converter AI Convert files v258</title><pubDate> Wed, 18 Feb 2026 16:55:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pdf-converter-convert-file-11089.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pdf-converter-convert-file-11089.html
</guid><description>
PDF Converter Convert files and images to PDF, DOC, PPT, XLS, RTF, ODT, JPG, PNG. Convert documents, images and files to PDF, DOC, PPT, XLS, RTF, ODT, JPG, PNG.
PDF Converter Convert files and images to PDF by Offiwiz is a document converter to convert files to other extensions: you can convert PDF to Word, TXT, PPT, DOC, JPG, PNG, XLS and more. This PDF Converter app is also a PDF Reader and PDF Editor. Choose the extension, output format and convert any document, perfect for creating...
</description></item><item><title>Download Before Launcher - Go Minimal 8.3.1-0774686132</title><pubDate> Wed, 18 Feb 2026 16:55:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-before-launcher-go-minimal-12042.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-before-launcher-go-minimal-12042.html
</guid><description>
Are you tired of constantly being distracted by notifications, emails, and social media alerts on your phone? Do you find yourself wasting hours mindlessly scrolling through apps when you should be focusing on work or other important tasks? If so, Before Launcher might be the solution you're looking for. This innovative app is designed to help you organize your home screen and minimize distractions, allowing you to focus on what's really important.
Main features:
	Launch your most...
</description></item><item><title>Download Speedtest by Ookla 6.6.3</title><pubDate> Wed, 18 Feb 2026 16:55:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-speedtest-by-ookla-for-android-8605.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-speedtest-by-ookla-for-android-8605.html
</guid><description>
Speedtest by Ookla is a popular online service that allows users to measure the speed of their internet connection. The service works by sending small amounts of data to a user's device and measuring the time it takes for that data to return to the server. Based on this measurement, the service provides reports on the user's download and upload speeds as well as connection latency.
Features of Ookla Speedtest
	Explore your downloads, uploads, and pings
	The only Internet connection...
</description></item><item><title>Download Speed test 4G 5G WiFi &amp;amp; maps 2.15.29 build 21529001</title><pubDate> Wed, 18 Feb 2026 16:55:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-speed-test-4g-5g-wifi-maps-9642.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-speed-test-4g-5g-wifi-maps-9642.html
</guid><description>
More than just a simple speed test, nPerf offers you the best and most complete mobile connection quality measurement tool with speeds up to 1 Gbps! All your results are saved in history with all test locations on the map. Easily share your results on social networks with the nPerf share image that presents a useful summary of your test. Customize your app by switching the background theme using Settings.
Features of Speed ​​test 4G 5G WiFi &amp;amp; maps
	Full QoS test: In seconds,...
</description></item><item><title>Download radio.net PRIME 5.18.2.0-app 100133</title><pubDate> Wed, 18 Feb 2026 16:54:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-radionet-prime-8335.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-radionet-prime-8335.html
</guid><description>
radio.net PRIME is a mobile application that allows users to listen to a variety of radio stations on their Android devices. This app provides access to more than 30,000 radio stations around the world, including local and international stations in a variety of genres and formats.
Features of radio.net PRIME
	Access to more than 30,000 radio stations around the world
	Supports multiple genres and formats, including news, music, sports, and chat
	Option to create a list of favorite...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sticker.ly - Sticker Maker 3.29.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 18 Feb 2026 16:54:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-stickerly-sticker-maker-13206.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-stickerly-sticker-maker-13206.html
</guid><description>
Are you looking for animated WhatsApp stickers and funny video statuses? Try this Sticker.ly app Sticker Maker and Video Status for WhatApp and Telegram which includes over 500,000 animated sticker packs and thousands of video statuses! TV Shows &amp;amp; Movies, Celebrities, Models, Animals, Sports, Anime, Funny Memes, Illustrations, Beautiful Graphics, Lyrics, Quotes, Typos, Emojis, and more!
Sticker.ly is a free animated sticker maker for WhatsApp and Telegram that can easily turn your...
</description></item><item><title>Download PROTO - circuit simulator 1.47.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 18 Feb 2026 16:54:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-proto-circuit-simulator-8833.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-proto-circuit-simulator-8833.html
</guid><description>
Are you looking for tools like Multisim, SPICE, LTspice, Proteus or Altium? That's great! PROTO is an real time electronic circuit simulator which means you are able to setup a circuit with various components and simulate behaviour of the electronic circuit. During simulation you can check voltages, currents and many other variables. Check signals on multichannel oscilioscope and tune your circuit in real time! You can also use PROTO as logic circuit simulator and perform digital...
</description></item><item><title>Download Noteshelf 3: Digital Notes 4.0.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 18 Feb 2026 16:53:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-noteshelf-3-digital-notes-13087.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-noteshelf-3-digital-notes-13087.html
</guid><description>
Introducing the all-new Noteshelf 3 the perfect note-taking app for students, teachers, professionals, artists, and bullet journal enthusiasts to create and organize digital notes. Download for free and start your journey of seamless organization, productivity, and creativity.
PERSONALIZE YOUR NOTE-TAKING EXPERIENCE
	Create beautiful handwritten notes with a variety of realistic pens and highlighters. Try our fountain pens to add a touch of elegance to your handwriting.
	Take notes on...
</description></item><item><title>Download Meme Generator PRO 4.6765</title><pubDate> Wed, 18 Feb 2026 16:53:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-meme-generator-pro-11201.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-meme-generator-pro-11201.html
</guid><description>
Are you ready to enter the meme world and become a meme master? Look no further than Meme Generator, the app for meme enthusiasts and anyone who wants to start exploring the world of memes.
Main features
	Template Treasury: Explore a huge collection of 2000+ high-quality meme templates, carefully categorized for your convenience. From classic memes to the latest trends, we have it all!
	Unleash your creativity: Create completely custom memes with your own images or GIFs. Control...
</description></item><item><title>Download AI Photo to Art Converter 1.2.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 18 Feb 2026 16:53:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ai-photo-to-art-converter-12121.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ai-photo-to-art-converter-12121.html
</guid><description>
Photo to Art Converter is powered by AI. Ready to turn your photos into works of art? Download Photo to Art - AI Photo Converter and discover a whole new world of artistic possibilities! With this app, you can use AI to apply many creative styles to your personal photos. Turn your boring photos into unique works of art with AI Photo Enhancer!.
Let your imagination run wild and create something truly unique with sketch photo maker and cartoon photo editor features!
Main features:
	Art...
</description></item><item><title>Download G-Stomper Studio 6.1.1.4</title><pubDate> Wed, 18 Feb 2026 16:51:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-g-stomper-studio-13509.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-g-stomper-studio-13509.html
</guid><description>
G-Stomper Studio is a comprehensive music production tool optimized for live electronic performances with studio-quality sound. It features a step-based drum machine and groovebox, a sampler, and a virtual analog performance synthesizer called VA-Beast. The app includes polyphonic and monophonic step sequencers for melodies, a groove grid sequencer for beats, a piano keyboard, 24 drum pads, an effects rack, a master section, a line mixer, and a live sample/song sequencer, allowing users...
</description></item><item><title>Download 7Fon: Wallpapers &amp;amp; Backgrounds 6.3.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 18 Feb 2026 16:51:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-7fon-wallpapers-4k-pro-11673.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-7fon-wallpapers-4k-pro-11673.html
</guid><description>
7Fon Wallpapers 4K (PRO) Android is a great application for people who love beauty and art. With thousands of high-quality wallpapers, users can find the perfect photos for their phone screen.
This app offers a huge collection of 4K wallpapers from different categories like nature, animals, art, landscapes and more. Users can easily search for wallpapers by topic or keyword, helping them quickly find their favorite photos.
Outstanding features of the application include:
	More than...
</description></item><item><title>Download Simple Radio: Live AM FM Radio 6.1.5 build 844</title><pubDate> Wed, 18 Feb 2026 16:51:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-simple-radio-live-am-fm-radio-10456.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-simple-radio-live-am-fm-radio-10456.html
</guid><description>
Simple Radio: Live AM FM Radio is the easiest way to tune in to FM radio, AM radio and amp; Radio online. You can access music, news &amp;amp; Live sports radio in seconds with our free radio station app. With over 50,000 stations, you can follow the ones you already love or sit back and discover exciting new things from around the world.
Listen to FM radio &amp;amp; AM stations include: NPR Radio, BBC Radio, MRN, 77 WABC, La Mega 97.9, KNBR &amp;amp; WNYC. Keep up with the news, listen to music or...
</description></item><item><title>Download Glucose tracker - Diabetic diary 3.5.5</title><pubDate> Wed, 18 Feb 2026 16:50:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-glucose-tracker-diabetic-diary-13642.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-glucose-tracker-diabetic-diary-13642.html
</guid><description>
Diabetes Diary - will become an indispensable companion for anyone with gestational, type 1 or type 2 diabetes. The blood glucose diary will allow you to regularly track your hemoglobin, sugar, blood pressure, insulin reminders and also add tags, medications, conditions and weight to each record. With the help of regular sugar diary, observe the trends in the blood sugar diary and decide with that information how you can treat it and also provide your doctor with all the necessary...
</description></item><item><title>Download PCAPdroid - network monitor 1.9.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 18 Feb 2026 16:50:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pcapdroid-network-monitor-11901.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pcapdroid-network-monitor-11901.html
</guid><description>
PCAPdroid is a privacy-friendly open source application that allows you to monitor, analyze and block connections made by other applications in your device. It also allows you to export PCAP traffic dumps, extract metadata, and more! PCAPdroid simulates VPN to capture network traffic without rooting. It does not use a remote VPN server. All data is processed locally on the device.
PCAPdroid Features
	- Logs and audits connections made by users and system applications
	- Extract SNI,...
</description></item></channel></rss>