<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 09:20:00 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 09:20:00 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download DoNotSpy11 Pro 1.3.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 02 Nov 2025 22:30:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-donotspy11-pro-10596.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-donotspy11-pro-10596.html
</guid><description>
DoNotSpy11 Pro is the professional successor to DoNotSpy10, the world's first anti-spy tool for Windows 10. Its simple user interface allows you to manage explains how Windows 10, Windows 11, Microsoft Edge, and Microsoft Office respect your privacy.
DoNotSpy11 gives you the opportunity to easily manage what you want to share and what not. While many of the settings represent what you can configure using Settings and many other apps, there are also adjustments that aren't easily...
</description></item><item><title>Download Simple Cutting Software X 2025.11.02</title><pubDate> Sun, 02 Nov 2025 22:29:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-simple-cutting-software-x-12810.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-simple-cutting-software-x-12810.html
</guid><description>
Simple Cutting Software X is a lightweight and practical program that helps you maximize the potential of a material, be it wood, metal, glass or other. It gives you the best cutting options for the parts you need, while minimizing waste.
Key Features
	2D Cutter Optimization: The cuts are made from one side to the other of the material. This feature is useful for glass, wood, tempered glass, etc.
	Adjustable blade thickness: For diamond glass cutting, the blade thickness is 0, but for...
</description></item><item><title>Download Album TD 4.9.0.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 02 Nov 2025 22:28:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-album-td-3968.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-album-td-3968.html
</guid><description>
Album TD has the full name is "Album Turbo Design" can help you design a wedding album album family photo album, with friends, etc.; any theme album with the great entertainment in just a few seconds. Album TD is equipped with fishing features from Album DS design software album for Photoshop, a new tool has been developed: Album Turbo Design. All the power to pull and drop-at services, album design, tools design new of, we will immediately create layouts for both page count and paging...
</description></item><item><title>Download XYplorer (32 Bit) 27.20.0200</title><pubDate> Sun, 02 Nov 2025 22:28:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-portable-12066.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-portable-12066.html
</guid><description>
XYplorer Portable is a file management software application that provides a comprehensive set of features for organizing and managing files and folders on your computer. This is a portable version of XYplorer that you can run directly from a portable storage device, such as a USB drive, without installation.
XYplorer Portable Features
	File Management: XYplorer Portable provides a two-window interface, allowing you to view and work with two folders at the same time. It provides easy...
</description></item><item><title>Download Nobe OmniScope 1.10.168</title><pubDate> Sun, 02 Nov 2025 22:27:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nobe-omniscope-10985.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nobe-omniscope-10985.html
</guid><description>
Nobe OmniScope is a powerful and flexible video monitoring and analysis tool used by professionals in the film, television and post-production industries. It provides a comprehensive set of features and tools for monitoring, analyzing, and editing video footage. Nobe OmniScope is equipped with many powerful features to help classify colors easily. GPU acceleration, HDR support, StreamDeck. Use the benefits of GPU acceleration and monitor your images in real time with virtually no...
</description></item><item><title>Download dbForge Studio for SQL Server Enterprise 2025.2.91</title><pubDate> Sun, 02 Nov 2025 22:26:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbforge-studio-for-sql-server-4710.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbforge-studio-for-sql-server-4710.html
</guid><description>
dbForge Studio 2019 for SQL Server is the program that will help the developer SQL management database, change database version control in the source control system downloads, speed up routine tasks, as well as perform the change database complicated.
A handy tool to analyze the status of the index SQL and troubleshoot issues with fragmentation index. dbForge Studio 2019 for SQL Server allows you to quickly collect statistical data fragmentation index and the current database needs...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft Office Pro Plus - Online Installer 3.3.8</title><pubDate> Sun, 02 Nov 2025 22:26:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-office-professional-plus-x86-x64-online-installer-7661.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-office-professional-plus-x86-x64-online-installer-7661.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft Office 2021 Professional Plus x86-x64 - Online Installer is a small script that helps users to download and install Microsoft Office 2021 Professional Plus including all updates directly from Microsoft CDN Server.
The version of Office 2021 downloaded and installed on your computer will include the following programs: Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Outlook, OneNote, Publisher, Access, Visio, Project, ProofingTools, OneDrive Desktop.
Usage:
Unzip the downloaded ZIP Archive...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cutting Optimization Pro 5.18.16</title><pubDate> Sun, 02 Nov 2025 22:25:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cutting-optimization-pro-6573.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cutting-optimization-pro-6573.html
</guid><description>
Cutting Optimization Pro is a cutting software used to obtain the optimal cut layout for one-dimensional (1D) and two-dimensional (2D) pieces. The software also allows you to define and process complex products, such as desks, tables, cabinets, cabinets, bookshelves... Cutting Optimization Pro can be used to cut rectangular panels made of glass, wood, metal, plastic or any other material used in industrial applications.
Features of Cutting Optimization Pro
	Optimize 1D and 2D in the...
</description></item><item><title>Download High-Logic FontCreator Professional 15.0.0.3035</title><pubDate> Sun, 02 Nov 2025 22:24:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-high-logic-fontcreator-professional-1533.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-high-logic-fontcreator-professional-1533.html
</guid><description>
High-Logic FontCreator Professional allows you to create and edit TrueType fonts and OpenType. It has the powerful drawing tools that typographers and graphic designers require, and an intuitive interface that allows beginners to become productive immediately.
When you create or open a font, FontCreator displays an overview of all available characters. You can only add the characters missing, or select an existing character, and modify its appearance. You can import (scanned) signature...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaMonkey Gold 2024.2.0.3174 RC-1</title><pubDate> Sun, 02 Nov 2025 22:24:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediamonkey-gold-231.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediamonkey-gold-231.html
</guid><description>
MediaMonkey Gold is music manager and music player multimedia for the music collection and iPod users. MediaMonkey lists the audio file of you as CD, OGG, WMA, MPC, FLAC, APE, WAV and MP3 and includes the edit smart card and an automatic file and folder to arrange your music library.
MediaMonkey Gold also has CD ripper, CD / DVD Burner, and audio converter for saving music, and manual or editor list automatically to create mixed music.
Features MediaMonkey Gold
	Automatically find...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mercuriall Audio Ampbox 1.7.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 02 Nov 2025 22:23:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mercuriall-audio-ampbox-8841.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mercuriall-audio-ampbox-8841.html
</guid><description>
Mercuriall Audio Ampbox is a software-based guitar amplifier emulation that uses advanced digital signal processing algorithms to reproduce sound and feel of classical guitar amplifiers. It can be used as a standalone plugin in a digital audio workstation (DAW) or as a standalone application for live performances or rehearsals.
This software includes a wide range of amplifier models, including classic models such as the Marshall JCM800, Fender Twin Reverb and Mesa Boogie Dual Rectifier....
</description></item><item><title>Download dbForge Studio for PostgreSQL Professional 2025.2.91</title><pubDate> Sun, 02 Nov 2025 22:23:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbforge-studio-for-postgresql-enterprise-11213.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbforge-studio-for-postgresql-enterprise-11213.html
</guid><description>
dbForge Studio for PostgreSQL Enterprise is a GUI client and popular tool for managing and developing PostgreSQL databases. This PostgreSQL IDE allows users to create, develop and execute queries, edit and adapt code according to their requirements in a convenient and user-friendly interface.
Main features:
SQL Development
	Save your time and improve code quality when creating and editing queries with the following features
	PostgreSQL code completion
	Code format
	SQL Check SQL...
</description></item><item><title>Download dbForge SQL Complete Enterprise 2025.2.91</title><pubDate> Sun, 02 Nov 2025 22:22:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbforge-sql-complete-pro-7827.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbforge-sql-complete-pro-7827.html
</guid><description>
dbForge SQL Complete Pro is an advanced solution for SQL database development, management and administration. Available as an add-in for Visual Studio and SSMS, this tool provides great autocompletion.Write, beautify, refactor your SQL code and give your productivity a huge boost with features included in SQL Complete.
dbForge SQL Complete Pro provides a wide range of code completion features that save users from having to memorize long and complex object names, column names, SQL...
</description></item><item><title>Download Syncovery Premium 11.10.1.121</title><pubDate> Sun, 02 Nov 2025 22:22:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncovery-pro-enterprise-232.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncovery-pro-enterprise-232.html
</guid><description>
Syncovery Pro Enterprise is a great application used to back up data and to synchronize personal computers, servers, laptops, notepads and storage online. The software comes with support for FTP and secure FTP servers, SSH, WebDAV, Amazon S3, http, update the part file, ZIP compression, data encryption, and schedule automatic backups.
Syncovery Pro Enterprise have the ability to freely select files and folders across the whole folder hierarchy in tree view and supports email...
</description></item><item><title>Download Display Driver Uninstaller (DDU) 18.1.3.8</title><pubDate> Sun, 02 Nov 2025 21:01:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-display-driver-uninstaller-1999.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-display-driver-uninstaller-1999.html
</guid><description>
Display Driver Uninstaller (DDU) help to easily completely remove the packages and drivers graphics cards AMD, NVIDIA and Intel from your system without leaving any rest whatsoever. Display Driver Uninstaller will automatically detect your current GPU and allows you to delete drivers, registry and files related only by the click of a button. It will also prevent Windows automatically re-install drivers when you reboot your computer, leaving you a drivers graphics common until you install...
</description></item><item><title>Download HFS: HTTP File Server (version 3) 0.57.26</title><pubDate> Sun, 02 Nov 2025 19:38:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hfs-http-file-server-11851.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hfs-http-file-server-11851.html
</guid><description>
HFS is a web file server to run on your computer. Share a folder or even a file thanks to the virtual file system. Essentially, this application turns your computer into an HTTP server and all users who want to connect and download files can do so by loading a simple website in their browser. HFS includes many configuration settings, so you can basically change each part of the application, starting with how users download files and ending with the appearance of the created website.
HFS...
</description></item><item><title>Download iDefender 5.2.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 02 Nov 2025 19:33:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idefender-13959.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idefender-13959.html
</guid><description>
iDefender is an advanced security solution designed for the home, providing both a High-Performance Intrusion Prevention System (HIPS) and Real-Time Endpoint Detection and Response (EDR). This integrated system protects against potential threats, ensuring the safety and integrity of your devices by proactively monitoring and responding to suspicious activity.
Why iDefender?
Ransomware Prevention
	Detects and blocks ransomware in real time to protect important files from malicious...
</description></item><item><title>Download Windows 11 Pro 25H2 v26200.6899 NoTPM Multilingual Preactivated</title><pubDate> Sun, 02 Nov 2025 19:31:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-11-6618.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-11-6618.html
</guid><description>
Windows 11 is officially leaked to a developer version. Previously, when Windows 10 was released, Microsoft once stated that Windows 10 would be the last version of Windows for users. Clearly, with the arrival of Windows 11, Microsoft needed a major reason to reverse its previous claims and still remove Windows 10 by introducing some new operating systems.
About the interface of Windows 11 is quite similar to Windows 10X (a version of Windows 10 has stopped growing). The logo image of...
</description></item><item><title>Download ImgDrive 2.2.5</title><pubDate> Sun, 02 Nov 2025 19:30:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-imgdrive-7453.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-imgdrive-7453.html
</guid><description>
ImgDrive is an application for users who need a simple, reliable drive emulator that allows them to mount disk image files saved in various formats . It is easy to use and does your job well, as it sits in the system tray and is integrated into the Windows context menu.
Features of ImgDrive
	One-click mounting of ISO, CUE, NRG, MDS/MDF, CCD, ISZ images
	Runs on 32-bit and 64-bit versions of Windows from 2000 to Windows 10/11.
	Mount APE, FLAC, M4A, WAV, WavPack, TTA files as AUDIO CD...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mocha Pro for Adobe 2025.5 v12.5.3</title><pubDate> Sun, 02 Nov 2025 19:30:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mocha-pro-1029.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mocha-pro-1029.html
</guid><description>
Mocha Pro 2019 is the tool for visual effects and postproduction. Tool Tracking and VFX and is plugins for Adobe. Mocha is the artist and editor effects appreciate about the unique ability of his to reduce the time using keyframing related to VFX and premium finishing.
Mocha Pro 2019
Mocha Pro 2019 features track and remove objects that are GPU acceleratedtools, rotoscoping, advanced, stable, solved 3D camera, supports stereo 360 / VR, etc. Using Mocha AE CC in Adobe After Effects? See...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mocha Pro Standalone 2025.5 v12.5.3</title><pubDate> Sun, 02 Nov 2025 19:30:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mocha-pro-standalone-4302.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mocha-pro-standalone-4302.html
</guid><description>
Mocha Pro Standalone is the tracking tool flat the world's most powerful for VFX and postproduction. With the tracking feature and remove objects that are GPU accelerated, mask advanced with snapshot feature edge, stable, corrective lens, the 3D camera, supports stereo 360 / VR, v. v. Mocha Pro Standalone is a plugin for Adobe Premiere Pro &amp;amp; After Effects, servers Avid Media Composer &amp;amp; OFX as Flame, Nuke, Fusion, HitFilm, and VEGAS Pro.
Mocha Pro Standalone 2020
New features in...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mocha Pro for OFX 2025.5 v12.5.3</title><pubDate> Sun, 02 Nov 2025 19:27:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mocha-pro-for-ofx-4303.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mocha-pro-for-ofx-4303.html
</guid><description>
Mocha Pro for OFX is the tracking tool flat the world's most powerful for VFX and postproduction. With the tracking feature and remove objects that are GPU accelerated, mask advanced with snapshot feature edge, stable, corrective lens, the 3D camera, supports stereo 360 / VR, v. v. Mocha Pro for OFX is a plugin for Adobe Premiere Pro &amp;amp; After Effects, servers Avid Media Composer &amp;amp; OFX as Flame, Nuke, Fusion, HitFilm, and VEGAS Pro.
Mocha Pro for OFX 2020
New features in version...
</description></item><item><title>Download Boris FX Mocha Pro for AVX 2025.5 v12.5.3</title><pubDate> Sun, 02 Nov 2025 19:27:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-boris-fx-mocha-pro-for-avx-13995.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-boris-fx-mocha-pro-for-avx-13995.html
</guid><description>
Boris FX Mocha Pro for AVX is the industry-leading version of the plane tracking and visual effects software, designed to work as a plugin supporting AVX (Avid Video Extensions) servers such as Avid Media Composer. Mocha Pro integrates advanced plane tracking, rotoscoping, 3D camera resolution, object removal, image stabilization, and masking tools into supported hosts, including AVX-based editing software.
Key points about Boris FX Mocha Pro for AVX:
	This is part of the Boris FX...
</description></item><item><title>Download Daemon Tools Lite 12.3.0.2363</title><pubDate> Sun, 02 Nov 2025 19:26:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-daemon-tools-lite-3391.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-daemon-tools-lite-3391.html
</guid><description>
DAEMON Tools Lite is based on two key features, simulation of virtual disks and building the file disk image as iso. DAEMON Tools Lite can emulate up to 4 virtual drives, DVD, CD or Blu-ray on your computer. The virtual units will be present in your system the same as the unit. After you select the virtual drive you want, you will choose a disc image (nrg, iso, mdf, bin, cue, etc.) that you want to mount. Visit My Computer at the device have The mobile storage and you will find the disk...
</description></item><item><title>Download Derivative TouchDesigner Pro 2025.31550</title><pubDate> Sun, 02 Nov 2025 19:24:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-derivative-touchdesigner-pro-3916.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-derivative-touchdesigner-pro-3916.html
</guid><description>
Derivative TouchDesigner Pro is a development platform visual equip you with the tools you need to create the project real-time stunning user experience and rich. Whether you are creating the system, media interaction, project architecture, photos, live music, or simply rapid-prototyping creative impulses your latest Derivative TouchDesigner Pro is platform can do it all.
Derivative TouchDesigner Pro - creation Support project, application
Derivative TouchDesigner Pro works well with...
</description></item></channel></rss>