<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 10:07:02 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 10:07:02 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download StartAllBack 3.9.16.5314</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 01:47:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-startallback-6857.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-startallback-6857.html
</guid><description>
With the official release of Windows 11, chances are that most of you want to try it out. As the name suggests, StartAllBack is a small, lightweight tool that can help you enjoy the power of the new operating system while keeping the look and feel, especially because main work area, desktop of Windows 7, Windows 10 as taskbars and start menu styles.
StartAllBack is specially designed for Windows 11 and will not work on any older operating systems. If you want to get the start menu back...
</description></item><item><title>Download XYplorer 27.20.0000</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 01:47:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-533.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-533.html
</guid><description>
XYplorer - File Manager for Windows is software that supports users to manage files on the Window quickly and to arrange the folder tidy. XYplorer features tabbed browsing, search, files, powerful, preview, flexible, highly customizable interface, dual frame options and a variety of unique ways to automate effective tasks often repeat. It's fast, lightweight, and portable.
Features XYplorer
	XYplorer is a file manager mobile. It does not require any settings, store all configuration...
</description></item><item><title>Download TreeSize Professional 9.6.1.2153</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 01:46:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-treesize-professional-390.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-treesize-professional-390.html
</guid><description>
TreeSize Pro is a software to manage hard disk space powerfully and flexibly for Windows 2003/2008 / XP / Vista / 7/8/10. TreeSize will find out which directory the largest on your drives and recover megabytes on disk. TreeSize Professional shows you the size, allocated and wasted space, number of files, 3D charts, last accessed date, file owner and permissions, the speed NTFS compression and much more information for several folders or drives you choose. It also lets you search drives,...
</description></item><item><title>Download BitTorrent PRO 7.11.0.47223</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 01:45:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bittorrent-pro-190.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bittorrent-pro-190.html
</guid><description>
BitTorrent PRO supports users to share files via p2p peer-to-peer network protocol, and allows you to download torrent data quickly and safely, without requiring What other software must you use? Using this tool, users can download many different types of data, manage bandwidth effectively, and can download many files at the same time, even large files.
In addition, the feature of this network is a very high jump speed, which can be achieved by the initial method of releasing files from...
</description></item><item><title>Download Atlantis Word Processor 5.0.0.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 01:44:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-atlantis-word-processor-585.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-atlantis-word-processor-585.html
</guid><description>
Atlantis Word Processor is a word processor app with features format, standard text, autocorrect, and spell check.  Atlantis is a word processor in accordance with most of the tasks handled daily text. The interface is very easy to use and offers the toolbars, hotkeys and sound effects thanh can customize (can turn off). It includes a clip library for quick access to the text or images used regular preview, font format and many other features aimed at improving the process of your...
</description></item><item><title>Download MobiKin Assistant for iOS 3.6.14</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 01:44:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mobikin-assistant-for-ios-4865.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mobikin-assistant-for-ios-4865.html
</guid><description>
MobiKin Assistant for iOS is software assistant the world's most powerful apps for iPad users, iPhone and iPod, MobiKin Assistant for iOS allows users to transfer, backup and manage all content on your device just by a simple click. In case of losing data if your iPhone is stolen or accidentally damaged or you just want to share the movies on your iDevice with your friends in other ways you should regularly backup the files on iPhone, iPad or iPod to iTunes . However, there are still many...
</description></item><item><title>Download XtraTools Pro 25.9.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 01:42:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xtratools-pro-7168.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xtratools-pro-7168.html
</guid><description>
XtraTools Pro is a universal tool for MS Windows system optimization that takes care of all aspects of your computer like optimizing the registry and removing unnecessary program to establish network connection and increase RAM speed. It is a compact tool with an intuitive interface that gives you complete control over the boot process, memory monitoring and a huge set of system settings that control your computer. The current version of the software provides the following tools: Folder...
</description></item><item><title>Download Coolmuster Android Assistant 6.0.89</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 01:42:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-android-assistant-226.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-android-assistant-226.html
</guid><description>
Coolmuster Android Assistant is a lightweight application that allows you to export the data important from your mobile device to your computer for safekeeping just in few clicks.
Coolmuster Android Assistant allows you to browse a number of types of data on your mobile device, you, namely the apps, contacts, SMS, music, photos, videos , and books. In case you can't preview the contents of the desired part, then you can fix this minor inconvenience by access to the child folder of...
</description></item><item><title>Download ArmorTools Professional / Home 25.9.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 01:42:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-armortools-7726.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-armortools-7726.html
</guid><description>
ArmorTools is a set of tools that extend the capabilities of the MS Windows operating system in the field of security and protection of user confidential information. ArmorTools allows you to create secure virtual disks encrypted with AES128/AES256 algorithms, encrypting files and folder contents using any file as a password.
ArmorTools erases the user's work traces on the computer, deletes the history of accessing websites, deletes confidential information without the possibility of...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinTools.one Professional / Home 25.9.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 01:41:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wintoolsone-10808.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wintoolsone-10808.html
</guid><description>
WinTools.one is a program designed to help both regular and advanced users as well as computer engineers fine-tune the MS Windows operating system. It allows you to increase the performance of the operating system, maintain its performance at a high level, fix operating system errors, free up space on the computer's hard drive and control the operation of installed programs. In addition, the program allows you to store and protect your secret and confidential information, as well as work...
</description></item><item><title>Download Coolmuster iOS Assistant 4.6.16</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 01:41:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-ios-assistant-2476.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-ios-assistant-2476.html
</guid><description>
You want to backup data from iPhone / iPad / iPod to computer? You want to import a file from your computer to your iOS device? You want to restore backup on your iDevices? You want to have full control over the data stored on your iDevices? This iOS Assistant pro integrates all these features in a and sure is the best manager for your iOS device.
Coolmuster iOS Assistant - backup for IOS devices
Coolmuster iOS Assistant is a whole program feature allows you to freely backup contacts,...
</description></item><item><title>Download AccdbMerge 1.35.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 01:40:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-accdbmerge-12716.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-accdbmerge-12716.html
</guid><description>
AccdbMerge is a reliable program that allows you to quickly combine information and structure from multiple Microsoft Access database files, in two projects. The application can perform advanced data segregation, to avoid duplicate entries. Furthermore, the program provides support for differential comparison of batch data.
AccdbMerge Features
	The software can open password-protected files and compare them in two parallel projects. You can save settings, in case you often work with...
</description></item><item><title>Download Intel Graphics Driver for Windows 10 / 11 32.0.101.7076</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 00:53:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intel-graphics-driver-for-windows-10-5954.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intel-graphics-driver-for-windows-10-5954.html
</guid><description>
Intel Graphics Driver for Windows 10 supports Intel ' s latest 8th-generation Core processor, introducing the Intel ® UHD graphics, with the ability to immerve in the top 4K UHD entertainment from your laptop for a maximum of 10 hours. Along with some security fixes, this driver also optimised the system's inactivity to reduce power consumption.
Look at the complete new interface of gameplay.intel.com, where you will find the proposed game settings for many of your favorite PC games....
</description></item><item><title>Download Stellar Data Recovery Pro 12.3.0.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 00:49:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stellar-phoenix-windows-data-recovery-professional-3312.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stellar-phoenix-windows-data-recovery-professional-3312.html
</guid><description>
Stellar Phoenix Windows Data Recovery Professional is an application that reliable and comprehensive, allowing you to recover quickly and easily the files lost or deleted from internal hard drive or any media outside any other. The program provides with an intuitive interface and no clutter, help you easily get back lost data without modifying the original structure.
Stellar Phoenix Windows Data Recovery Professional - Recover lost data
Stellar Phoenix Windows Data Recovery...
</description></item><item><title>Download Media Player Classic Home Cinema 2.5.3.10</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 00:48:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-media-player-classic-home-cinema-2839.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-media-player-classic-home-cinema-2839.html
</guid><description>
Media Player Classic Home Cinema is a multimedia compact for Microsoft Windows 32 bit and 64 bit. MPC mimics the interface of Windows Media Player 6.4, but provides most options and features available in the modern means. Media Player Classic Home Cinema for free 100% no advertising, so you can directly access content and enjoy media playback without being distracted.
With Media Player Classic Home, you can now change the design a multimedia of the custom toolbar. There is a range to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Abelssoft YouTube Song Downloader Plus 2025 v25.10</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 00:47:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-abelssoft-youtube-song-downloader-plus-111.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-abelssoft-youtube-song-downloader-plus-111.html
</guid><description>
Abelssoft YouTube Song Downloader Plus 2018.18.17 Program YouTube Song Downloader Plus will help you search the music and video files from YouTube, after you can download them at. To search for music you just need to enter song name in the required field and you will get results, then you can download all videos and audio files. The program can search the entire album, this function will help to find individual songs from separate albums, because of this we specify the name of the artist...
</description></item><item><title>Download Net Monitor for Employees Professional 6.4.9</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 00:46:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-network-lookout-net-monitor-for-employees-professional-2098.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-network-lookout-net-monitor-for-employees-professional-2098.html
</guid><description>
Network LookOut Net Monitor for Employees Professional is a software platform to help manage user activity, gives the ability to inspect and control computer activities, as well as record activity on the screen as AVI file. Net Monitor for Employees Professional allows access from remote computers. This feature proved particularly useful when you want to see the activity of each user on the computer, or assist them perform the work on the computer with the mouse manipulation or the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Stellar Toolkit for Data Recovery 12.3.0.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 00:46:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stellar-toolkit-for-data-recovery-3330.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stellar-toolkit-for-data-recovery-3330.html
</guid><description>
Stellar Toolkit for Data Recovery is recovery software lost data or can't access, can restore the file buffer is not full or corrupt, and the Windows operating system, Mac and Linux. Sometimes the data on the hard drive can be deleted due to a system error or malfunction. In such cases, use a recovery software can strongly increase the possibility of data recovery and save your important data from the risk of permanently deleted.
Stellar Toolkit for Data Recovery - recover lost...
</description></item><item><title>Download NTLite Business 2025.8.10552</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 00:45:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ntlite-enterprise-1282.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ntlite-enterprise-1282.html
</guid><description>
NTLite Enterprise is software that is configuration Windows and advanced customization tools optimal can modify the settings for existing Windows or an image yet to be deployed. NTLite allows you to remove Windows components that you do not want or do not need to install. In addition, you can configure and integrate, speed up the process of deploying Windows and installed all for next time.
NTLite Enterprise - Customizable and optimized window
Easily integrate application installers,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Simio Enterprise Edition 19.280.48282</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 00:45:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-simio-enterprise-edition-12383.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-simio-enterprise-edition-12383.html
</guid><description>
In 2009, Simio released a comprehensive, agile simulation platform that represents evolutionary fourth-generation design — built from the ground up to be completely object-oriented, data-generated , data-driven, and highly adaptable — critical innovations to overcome the barriers that hindered previous generations. Returning to the present, the Simio development team continues to build on this initial architecture, enhancing Simio's capabilities.
The Simio discrete event simulation...
</description></item><item><title>Download Distant Desktop 4.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 00:45:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-distant-desktop-8490.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-distant-desktop-8490.html
</guid><description>
Distant Desktop is free software that allows you to control your computer from any device anywhere. Only 2 computers need to have Distant Desktop software installed and one of them needs to provide a unique ID and password to establish a remote desktop connection.
Distant Desktop allows remote control of your computer through your mouse and keyboard. Multiple connections can be made at the same time. This applies to both the managing party and the controlled party. You can perform file...
</description></item><item><title>Download HE - Hardware Read and Write Utility 1.25.09.22</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 00:44:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-he-hardware-read-and-write-utility-4287.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-he-hardware-read-and-write-utility-4287.html
</guid><description>
HE - Hardware Read and Write Utility is a powerful utility intended for hardware engineer, engineer, BIOS developer, driver, engineer, QA engineers, performance test engineers, diagnostic, etc., this utility access almost all the computer hardware, including PCI (PCI Express), index / Data, PCI, memory, index memory / Data space I / O, Index I / O / Data, Super I / O, DIMM SPD, CPU The registers MSR, screen, SMART, physical area of the hard drive identification data, ATA, dump tables ACPI...
</description></item><item><title>Download KILHO ImageConverter 1.5.4</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 00:44:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kilho-imageconverter-12520.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kilho-imageconverter-12520.html
</guid><description>
ImageConverter is designed for ease of use, making it accessible to everyone, regardless of technical expertise. To get started, drag and drop the image you want onto the user interface. Once uploaded, you can explore different configuration options to suit your needs. These settings allow you to customize the output format, adjust resolution, and apply any necessary filters or enhancements. You can efficiently convert your images to your desired specifications in just a few...
</description></item><item><title>Download Driver Magician 6.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 00:44:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-driver-magician-lite-117.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-driver-magician-lite-117.html
</guid><description>
Driver Magician: The program automatically marks non-standard drivers (not included with Windows), allowing you to quickly find drivers that have been added by devices such as printers, the web orange etc ... Improve driver backup and restore performance
The application Driver Magician also backs up all the drivers in the machine for restoration in case of malfunction or reinstallation. All the drivers for the devices are gathered in an exe self-installer file and only need to run this...
</description></item><item><title>Download Stellar Data Recovery Technician 12.3.0.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 00:43:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stellar-data-recovery-technician-3561.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stellar-data-recovery-technician-3561.html
</guid><description>
Stellar Data Recovery Technician is a other version helps you to recover lost data like files, photos, videos, emails and many other things from hard drive Windows storage media and RAID arrays. Technicians data recovery of Stellar smart detection parameters RAID key and rebuild the RAID virtual to recover data from the RAID 0 array, RAID 5 and RAID 6 faulty or damaged.
Software Stellar Data Recovery Technician provides advanced functions for recovering data from servers, RAID 0, 5 and 6...
</description></item></channel></rss>