<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 17:39:46 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 17:39:46 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Office Tool Plus 10.28.29.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 18:03:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-tool-plus-3664.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-tool-plus-3664.html
</guid><description>
Office Tool Plus based on the Office deployment tool from Microsoft. You can customize configuration files installation and install Office of to install Office without Internet. Configure install Office, as well as customize the product C2R have installed, such as add and remove components, language packs, etc.
Office Tool Plus - Download and install Office
The characteristics of Office Tool Plus
	1. Configure install Office, as well as customize the product C2R have installed, such...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft Activation Scripts 3.8</title><pubDate> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 18:01:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-activation-scripts-5390.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-activation-scripts-5390.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft Activation Scripts is an open source Windows and Office activation tool that features online HWID, Ohook, KMS38 and KMS activation methods, along with advanced troubleshooting functionality.
Activation methods
			Trigger type
			Supported products
			Activation time
			HWID
			Windows 10-11
			Permanent
			Ohook
			Office
			Permanent
			KMS38
			Windows 10-11, Server
			Until 2038
			Online KMS
			Windows / Office
			180 days (with...
</description></item><item><title>Download PIDKey Lite 1.64.4 b51</title><pubDate> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 18:00:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pidkey-lite-2693.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pidkey-lite-2693.html
</guid><description>
PIDKey Lite is a program intended to show the renovation and preservation in the database of the product information to check "validity" of the key Microsoft from the famous program we or is Ratiborus and VAMT. Program PIDKey LiteIt is the successor of the PIDKey. and I got out of it the idea the best program (allows you To add new keyboard with two methods additional mode key).
The program has a number of configuration integration, but you can also create custom profiles by themselves....
</description></item><item><title>Download GoodSync Enterprise 12.9.15.5</title><pubDate> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 18:00:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-goodsync-enterprise-163.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-goodsync-enterprise-163.html
</guid><description>
GoodSync Enterprise is a software that saves files and files easily and is reliable. It automatically analyts, synchronize and backup your email, family photos, contacts, MP3, financial documentation and other important files-between desktop computers, laptops, servers, external drives and Windows Mobile devices as well as remotely via FTP , SFTP, WebDAV and more. The GoodSync synchronized software combines bulletproof reliability with an extremely easy interface to compare, synchronize...
</description></item><item><title>Download IObit Software Updater Pro 8.2.0.11</title><pubDate> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 17:59:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iobit-software-updater-pro-2234.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iobit-software-updater-pro-2234.html
</guid><description>
IObit Software Updater Pro software is useful for those who don't download apps for Windows 10 from the store company, virtually all software was installed will not be updated automatically. The web browser will naturally inform you about a new version, software security of you will also be automatically updated, just like Windows, but almost all other apps will quietly operate in the normal mode and you will never know that the update was available, if you can't run itself.
IObit...
</description></item><item><title>Download Rhinoceros 8.25.25314.11001</title><pubDate> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 17:58:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rhinoceros-179.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rhinoceros-179.html
</guid><description>
Rhinoceros is design software 3D easy to learn, easy to use and has range of application in various industries. Rhinoceros (or Rhino, Rhino3D) is a graphics software CAD and 3D developed by Robert McNeel &amp;amp; Associates, a private company established in the year 1980. Rhinoceros is developed according to the algorithm NURBS mathematical model, algorithm, focus on the correct presentation of curves and surfaces mathematics in computer graphics (in contrast to the application polygon...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Master Collection 2025 v10</title><pubDate> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 17:58:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-master-collection-0001-8036.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-master-collection-0001-8036.html
</guid><description>
You may already know that Adobe Master Collection 2025 does not officially exist and Adobe has never released it. But now that it's here, we also need to give thanks to m0nkrus and PainteR (who put a lot of effort into creating it). Adobe Master Collection 2025 is a collection of applications from the Creative Cloud 2025 line, united by a multilingual installer with the ability to choose the installation path and interface language of installed programs. In terms of functionality,...
</description></item><item><title>Download UpdatePack7R2 25.11.11</title><pubDate> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 17:56:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-updatepack7r2-6614.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-updatepack7r2-6614.html
</guid><description>
UpdatePack7R2 is software that allows you to update a working system and integrate software updates in the distribution. Can be installed on any version of Windows 7 and Server 2008 R2, any digit and any language. Includes updates for all versions of Internet Explorer, all critical, recommended, and security updates.
How to use UpdatePack7R2 software:
	The system must have at least 10 GB of free space on the hard drive and preferably no less than 1 GB of free RAM.
	Key / Reboot to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Viber for PC 26.6.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 17:55:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-viber-2406.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-viber-2406.html
</guid><description>
Viber is a software of instant messaging, based on VoIP protocols, multi-platform due to the Viber Media development for smart phones used to send sms and make calls over the internet. Along with text messaging, users can exchange images, video and audio.
Viber - software news message, chat online
This is a program that is quite popular is mainly designed for mobile phones, but now we are talking about the version for Windows, so immediately. It will allow you to send messages to other...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Downloader 9.18.3</title><pubDate> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 17:55:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html
</guid><description>
YTD Youtube Downloader is an application that reliable and intuitive, allowing you to quickly download YouTube videos and save them to your computer. You can also convert the media files to the format desired video or extract audio streams and save separately. YTD Youtube Downloader lets you save your favorite clips of yourself from Youtube, Facebook, Vimeo and Dailymotion to your desktop. The software supports URLS from many web site hosting, multimedia and allows you to download desired...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Creative Master Collection 2025-2026 v10.11.2025 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 17:54:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-001-adobe-creative-cloud-collection-8035.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-001-adobe-creative-cloud-collection-8035.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Creative Cloud Collection 2023 - 2025 is a collection of applications from the Creative Cloud 2023, 2024, 2025 family and several firmware versions combined by a single installer with path selection settings and languages of installed programs. In terms of functionality, everything is very similar to the well-proven Adobe Master Collection CS6 in the past. Only here has the installer interface changed, the current package includes significantly more programs than the Creative Suite...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDF Architect Pro + OCR 9.1.77.23081</title><pubDate> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 17:51:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-architect-pro-ocr-6381.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-architect-pro-ocr-6381.html
</guid><description>
PDF Architect  is professional software that provides PDF creation and editing features according to your needs. Our PDF editor keeps you up to date with forward-looking features. Take complete control of your PDF files with our PDF editor. Modify text, images, and pages, and convert PDF to Word and Excel and more.
It has many advanced options and features for customizing, securing, and collaborating PDF files. All necessary features are included in this for better user experience. This...
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 7.4.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 17:51:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-11-7760.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-11-7760.html
</guid><description>
TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 is a program that allows users to discover hidden settings in Windows 11. This application is specially designed for Windows 11, groups many registry settings and distribute them from the easy and secure user interface. With TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 you can move the Windows taskbar to the top and resize the taskbar by editing the registry value. With any application that modifies the registry, we recommend that you have a backup copy...
</description></item><item><title>Download UltraSearch Professional 4.8.5.1185</title><pubDate> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 17:51:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ultrasearch-professional-10252.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ultrasearch-professional-10252.html
</guid><description>
UltraSearch Professional is the professional version that helps you find your files and documents on all connected hard drives and network drives. Search by file type, document content, or file properties. Take back your valuable time and let UltraSearch do the searching for you.
UltraSearch Professional does not maintain an index stored on your hard disk. It achieves speed by working directly on the Master File Table (MFT) of NTFS partitions. So it even identifies NTFS hardlinks. That...
</description></item><item><title>Download Moho Pro 14.4 Build 20251110</title><pubDate> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 17:50:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-smith-micro-moho-pro-4596.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-smith-micro-moho-pro-4596.html
</guid><description>
Smith Micro Moho Pro is film program of Anime Studio. Moho helps turn ideas and rich imagination of the film as lively as life. Moho is there 2 version is Moho Debut and Moho Pro, offers users tools cartoon from beginning to end. With display technology in 2D, beautifully combined with the custom made film base, anyone can learn to make films with Moho Animation Software.
Modern interface
With an intuitive interface and 1 number of powerful features such as Smart Bones Smart Warp,...
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 7.4.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 17:50:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-10-7759.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-10-7759.html
</guid><description>
TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 is a utility that allows users to discover hidden settings in Windows 10. This application is specially designed for Windows 10, groups many registry settings and provide them from an easy and secure user interface. With TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 you can move the Windows taskbar to the top and resize the taskbar by editing the registry value. With any application that modifies the registry, we recommend that you have a backup copy to...
</description></item><item><title>Download XYplorer (32 Bit) 27.20.0300</title><pubDate> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 17:49:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-portable-12066.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-portable-12066.html
</guid><description>
XYplorer Portable is a file management software application that provides a comprehensive set of features for organizing and managing files and folders on your computer. This is a portable version of XYplorer that you can run directly from a portable storage device, such as a USB drive, without installation.
XYplorer Portable Features
	File Management: XYplorer Portable provides a two-window interface, allowing you to view and work with two folders at the same time. It provides easy...
</description></item><item><title>Download Google Chrome 142.0.7444.163</title><pubDate> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 17:49:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-chrome-1012.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-chrome-1012.html
</guid><description>
Google Chrome web browser is the most used today. Support surf the web, listen to music, watch movies, play web game effective no jerky lag with the internet connection stable. When you are surfing the web or performing an important task, whether it is operation big or small, work or entertainment, then Chrome has the smart features and the speed you need to make, create and explore on the net.
The latest version of Google Chrome is the third 114. But we are providing for users Google...
</description></item><item><title>Download Causality 4.0.27</title><pubDate> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 17:48:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-causality-6895.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-causality-6895.html
</guid><description>
Causality is a new kind of writing app where you develop your stories visually, giving you an amazing overview of your stories. Friend. Causality works with your story the way it looks in your mind, but with the ability to visualize a much larger structure.
Causality supports writing in over 100 languages, checks spells in multiple languages ​​simultaneously, and comes with a gigabyte of fonts for identical rendering on all platforms. With Causality, it's easy to write screenplays...
</description></item><item><title>Download SQL Backup Master 8.0.1016 All Editions</title><pubDate> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 17:48:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sql-backup-master-6687.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sql-backup-master-6687.html
</guid><description>
SQL Backup Master backup your SQL Server database into any popular cloud hosting service such as Dropbox, OneDrive, Amazon S3, Microsoft Azure, Box and Google Drive. It can also backup the database to the FTP server-or a directory on your local machine, network server or storage device.
The backup of your SQL Server database to the cloud will not be complex or expensive. SQL Backup Master is born by providing an easy way to download copies of your database to one or more of the most...
</description></item><item><title>Download Easy System Utility Pro 1.1.50</title><pubDate> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 17:47:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easy-system-utility-pro-12380.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easy-system-utility-pro-12380.html
</guid><description>
Easy System Utility Pro is a powerful, all-in-one program designed for Windows 10 and 11 users. This versatile tool should be your primary choice to improve your computing experience ! This is the complete version with additional and enhanced features. It will help you easily determine your computer's hardware specifications with a system overview. You can view the operating system, CPU model, GPU, Memory, Motherboard, Network and even drivers.
It also supports launching programs,...
</description></item><item><title>Download UltraSearch 4.8.5.1185</title><pubDate> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 17:46:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ultrasearch-5751.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ultrasearch-5751.html
</guid><description>
UltraSearch finds files and folders on local NTFS drives and provides results in seconds. UltraSearch does not maintain an index stored on your hard disk, but achieves its speed by working directly on the Main File Table (MFT) of an NTFS partition. UltraSearch even identifies NTFS hard links. Just enter a filename or template like * .exe and see the first result while you're still typing.
Features of UltraSearch
	Additional information such as file size and file date (last changed,...
</description></item><item><title>Download yt-dlp 2025.11.12</title><pubDate> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 17:46:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-dlp-6802.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-dlp-6802.html
</guid><description>
yt-dlp is a youtube-dl branch based on youtube-dlc currently not working. The main focus of this project is the addition of new features and patches while still updating the original project.
</description></item><item><title>Download Ultimate Power Assistant 1.1.23</title><pubDate> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 17:46:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ultimate-power-assistant-12372.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ultimate-power-assistant-12372.html
</guid><description>
Ultimate Power Assistant provides you with an efficient and easy way to manage your computer's power settings and tasks. With this tool, you can schedule and apply various power options in Windows.
Main features
	Shut down when download completes: Turn off your computer after your favorite game launcher or web browser completes the download. You no longer have to leave your PC running for hours wasting electricity!
	Change Power Plan when certain programs are detected: Launch a...
</description></item><item><title>Download Artweaver Plus 8.1.0.3438</title><pubDate> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 17:45:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-artweaver-plus-1324.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-artweaver-plus-1324.html
</guid><description>
Artweaver Plus is a software graphics editor with many functions fundamental to advanced and supports many different formats. Artweaver Plus works with image files in formats BMP, GIF, JPEG, JPG, JPE, PCX, PNG, TGA, VDA, ICB, VST, TIF, TIFF and AWD. Out of the possibilities of it, you can do outstanding work with layers, import and export graphic in different formats.
Artweaver Plus - editing software graphics
Artweaver Plus owner interface very similar to Photoshop , so users very...
</description></item></channel></rss>