<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 20:04:38 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 20:04:38 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download R-Drive Image 7.3 Build 7309</title><pubDate> Mon, 18 Aug 2025 17:29:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-drive-image-1971.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-drive-image-1971.html
</guid><description>
R-Drive Image is a powerful utility provides create a file disk image for backup purposes, or copy. File disk image contains the exact copy each and every byte of hard drive, partition or logical disk and can be created with various levels compression without stopping Windows os and therefore without interrupting your work. The image file this drive can then be stored in many places, including various removable media as different as a CD-R (W) / DVD, Iomega Zip or Jazz, etc.
R-Drive...
</description></item><item><title>Download Foxit PDF Editor Pro 14.0.0.33046 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Mon, 18 Aug 2025 17:28:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-foxit-pdf-editor-pro-13375.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-foxit-pdf-editor-pro-13375.html
</guid><description>
Foxit PDF Editor Pro is a professional PDF editing software designed for personal and business users who need advanced capabilities to create, edit, secure and manage PDF documents. This Foxit software can combine, split or repackage multiple PDF files. Documents can be merged or split based on page numbers, page layout or bookmarks. Additionally, this Suite can batch convert existing documents into one or more PDF files.
Features of Foxit PDF Editor Pro 
Advanced PDF editing with...
</description></item><item><title>Download XRECODE3 1.170</title><pubDate> Mon, 18 Aug 2025 17:27:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xrecode-iii-2915.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xrecode-iii-2915.html
</guid><description>
"Xrecode II" is the switch and grab the audio allows you to convert from mp2, mp3, ac3, aiff, wma, amr, ogg, ape, flac, cue, mpc, wv, tak, mid, cue, m4b, tta, wav, dts , wav (rf64), m4a, mp4, ra, shn, rm, avi, aac, mpg, vob, mka, mkv, flv, Mov, swf, ofr, divx, wmv, spx, mp3, m4v, 3gp, m2v, 3g2, m4v, m2ts, ts, adts, tak, xm, mod, it, s3m, alac, umx, mtm, mlp to m4a, ape, flac, mp4 (using NeroAAC), raw, ogg, wav, wav (rf64) , wma, mpc, WavPack, mp2, ofr, Speex, ac3, tak, aiff, snd, Shorten...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ventoy 1.1.06 + LiveCD</title><pubDate> Mon, 18 Aug 2025 17:27:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ventoy-4578.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ventoy-4578.html
</guid><description>
Ventoy is an open source tool for creating bootable USB drives for ISO files. With ventoy, you don't need to format the disk multiple times, you just need to copy the iso file to the USB drive and boot it. You can copy multiple iso files at once and ventoy will give you a boot menu to select them.
Features of Ventoy
100% Open Source
Simple to Use
Fast (limited only by iso file copy speed)
Boot directly from iso file, no extraction required
Legacy + UEFI supported in the same...
</description></item><item><title>Download OneCommander Pro 3.99.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 18 Aug 2025 17:26:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-one-commander-4232.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-one-commander-4232.html
</guid><description>
One Commander is a file manager for Microsoft Windows with function improved user interface and navigation experience, system file and manipulating the files. Utilities use the tree view to sort the folder, subfolders, and files your, make sure that the current location of you always clear. It supports multiple tabs, allowing you to easily switch between them and access the folder you need.
One Commander - a filemanager for Windows
Depending on the format of the files, some files can...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Downloader 9.15.8</title><pubDate> Mon, 18 Aug 2025 17:25:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html
</guid><description>
YTD Youtube Downloader is an application that reliable and intuitive, allowing you to quickly download YouTube videos and save them to your computer. You can also convert the media files to the format desired video or extract audio streams and save separately. YTD Youtube Downloader lets you save your favorite clips of yourself from Youtube, Facebook, Vimeo and Dailymotion to your desktop. The software supports URLS from many web site hosting, multimedia and allows you to download desired...
</description></item><item><title>Download R-Drive Image BootCD 7.3 Build 7309</title><pubDate> Mon, 18 Aug 2025 17:25:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-drive-image-bootcd-4878.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-drive-image-bootcd-4878.html
</guid><description>
R-Drive Image BootCD is a powerful utility provides create a file disk image for backup purposes, or copy. File disk image contains the exact copy each and every byte of hard drive, partition or logical disk and can be created with various levels compression without stopping Windows os and therefore without interrupting your work. The image file this drive can then be stored in many places, including various removable media as different as a CD-R (W) / DVD, Iomega Zip or Jazz,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Smadav Pro 2025 v15.5</title><pubDate> Mon, 18 Aug 2025 17:24:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-smadav-pro-2443.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-smadav-pro-2443.html
</guid><description>
Smadav is an antivirus powerful virus for Windows operating system. Like any program anti-virus any other, this program will provide insurance on your system in order to prevent attacks and security threats. In addition to detecting viruses and malware like worms, Trojans, advertising, spammers, ransomware, etc., this program has good ability to protect and detect all type of virus Autorun. These viruses are often found in flash memory and storage media, mobile. You attach and copy the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Syncovery Premium 11.7.0.85</title><pubDate> Mon, 18 Aug 2025 17:24:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncovery-pro-enterprise-232.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncovery-pro-enterprise-232.html
</guid><description>
Syncovery Pro Enterprise is a great application used to back up data and to synchronize personal computers, servers, laptops, notepads and storage online. The software comes with support for FTP and secure FTP servers, SSH, WebDAV, Amazon S3, http, update the part file, ZIP compression, data encryption, and schedule automatic backups.
Syncovery Pro Enterprise have the ability to freely select files and folders across the whole folder hierarchy in tree view and supports email...
</description></item><item><title>Download RevisionFX Effections Plus 25.08 for After Effects</title><pubDate> Mon, 18 Aug 2025 17:23:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-revisionfx-effections-plus-4842.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-revisionfx-effections-plus-4842.html
</guid><description>
RevisionFX Effections Plus is a collection of effects, footage comes. Twixtor is used to return more slowly to 160 times higher than real-time. DEFlicker is designed to smooth out the flicker and artifact unpleasant when recording high speed video or timelapse. Here is your solution for high frame rate and timelapse footage there are problems. Noise reduction using spatial filters sensitive new features, along with the method the optical line based on time.
The features of RevisionFX...
</description></item><item><title>Download Luxion KeyShot Studio Enteprise 2025.2.1 v14.1.1.5</title><pubDate> Mon, 18 Aug 2025 17:23:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-luxion-keyshot-enteprise-10602.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-luxion-keyshot-enteprise-10602.html
</guid><description>
Luxion KeyShot Enteprise is a popular computer program used for 3D visualization and visualization. It is designed primarily to display 3D models, making them look as realistic as possible. KeyShot is commonly used in a variety of industries, including product design, automotive design, architecture, and more.
Overall, KeyShot is known for its ease of use and ability to produce high-quality, realistic renderings with minimal setup and configuration. This is a valuable tool for designers...
</description></item><item><title>Download TypeButler 1.13.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 18 Aug 2025 17:22:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-typebutler-7056.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-typebutler-7056.html
</guid><description>
TypeButler helps you type frequently used documents, from single words to entire sentences, paragraphs, emails, and more. This not only reduces the time required for text entry, but also eliminates the risk of typos. You can arrange your text blocks in a clear menu structure and select them with one click. TypeButler can input texts into any program, it can simulate complex keystrokes, and it can replace entered texts on the fly.
It can also be used to replace keystrokes with any other...
</description></item><item><title>Download OCCT 14.2.6.99</title><pubDate> Mon, 18 Aug 2025 17:21:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-occt-perestroika-1680.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-occt-perestroika-1680.html
</guid><description>
OCCT is a free application designed to benchmark and overclock system components. Test tool OverClock includes 4 different tests to assess the stability of your computer. CPU and CPU: Linpack to test the processor, GPU: 3D to check stability of the graphics processor and power supply combination of CPU: Linpack and GPU: 3D to download power of you up to the maximum.
OCCT - Measuring system components
The features of OCCT
	Support is enabled for a maximum of 16 cores.
	All the tests...
</description></item><item><title>Download TripAdvisor Extractor Pro 2.4.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 18 Aug 2025 17:20:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tripadvisor-extractor-pro-12427.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tripadvisor-extractor-pro-12427.html
</guid><description>
TripAdvisor is a popular online platform that provides reviews, recommendations, and information on travel-related content. It was founded in 2000 and has since become one of the largest travel websites in the world. TripAdvisor provides user-generated content such as reviews, ratings, and photos for hotels, restaurants, attractions, and other travel-related businesses. Travelers can use the platform to research destinations, plan trips, and make reservations.
How to use TripAdvisor...
</description></item><item><title>Download USB Device Tree Viewer 4.6.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 18 Aug 2025 16:51:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-usb-device-tree-viewer-3286.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-usb-device-tree-viewer-3286.html
</guid><description>
USB Device Tree Viewer provides detailed information for all the ports and USB hub on the computer in the format tree. If a device is connected to a port, it also provides detailed information for the properties of the device and connection. USB Device Tree Viewer analyze your system configuration and display details about the controller server is connected, such as the manufacturer, drivers, bus types, list, location, devices, drive letters, COM ports, and debugging and statistics bus...
</description></item><item><title>Download DVDFab 13.0.4.7</title><pubDate> Mon, 18 Aug 2025 16:48:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dvdfab-67.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dvdfab-67.html
</guid><description>
DVDFab All-In-One is a multi-purpose combo of nearly all powerful DVDFab products-DVD replication, Ripper DVD, Blu-ray Ripper, Blu-ray Ripper, Copy UHD, Blu-ray to DVD, DVD to Blu-ray Transaction, DVD Creator, Blu-ray Creator, video conversion, Cinavia DVD removal, Windows DVD removal, DRM elimination for Apple, Screen Recorder and Editor for iOS, Hi-Fi Sound and File Transfer. It provides a complete solution to all of your DVD/Blu-ray/video problems and the perfect execution.
DvDFab -...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cent Browser 5.2.1168.76</title><pubDate> Mon, 18 Aug 2025 16:48:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cent-browser-3301.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cent-browser-3301.html
</guid><description>
Cents Browser is the improved version of web browser Chrome popular integrate countless features, including download the lazy, the tab bar can scroll, optimize memory automatically, mouse gestures and more options the other tab. Application small and efficient, this will significantly improve the browsing experience of your website and make it safer and more comfortable.
Cent Browser - web browser improvements new
This web browser based on the code and tools of Google Chrome and offers...
</description></item><item><title>Download Autodesk AutoCAD 2026.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 18 Aug 2025 16:47:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-autodesk-autocad-2025-0002-4077.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-autodesk-autocad-2025-0002-4077.html
</guid><description>
Autodesk AutoCAD design software is computer-aided (CAD) which the architects, engineers and construction professionals rely on to create the 2D and 3D drawings accurately. Autodesk AutoCAD will allow you to design and shape the world around you using the powerful features and flexibility of it. Speed documentation, share ideas seamlessly, and explore ideas more intuitively in 3D. With thousands of add-ons available, AutoCAD offers maximum flexibility, is customized for the specific needs...
</description></item><item><title>Download Autodesk AutoCAD LT 2026.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 18 Aug 2025 16:46:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-autodesk-autocad-lt-0001-7351.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-autodesk-autocad-lt-0001-7351.html
</guid><description>
AutoCAD LT 2024 is designed for the development and detailing of 2D drawings. The program automates most of the phases of the project. A complete set of 2D commands allows you to create drawings, modify them, and publish working documents for projects. can easily transfer files to other professionals. Additionally, you can customize the program's user interface to fit your needs.
Features of AutoCAD LT
	Create and edit 2D drawings.
	Annotate drawings with text, dimensions, paths, and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Agisoft Metashape Professional 2.2.2 Build 20976</title><pubDate> Mon, 18 Aug 2025 16:45:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-agisoft-metashape-professional-1731.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-agisoft-metashape-professional-1731.html
</guid><description>
Agisoft Metashape (formerly PhotoScan) is a software product independently perform image processing and digital data creation, 3D space used in GIS applications, material cultural heritage and the production visual effects as well as the indirect measurement of the different subjects scale. Technical digital photography is deployed wisely is applied with the method of computer vision led to the system processor, smart auto, on the one hand, can be managed by a new person in the field of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Aescripts BRAW Studio 3.3.9</title><pubDate> Mon, 18 Aug 2025 16:45:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aescripts-braw-studio-6395.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aescripts-braw-studio-6395.html
</guid><description>
Aescripts BRAW Studio  includes established plugins, including brand new .braw format that will be imported into Adobe CC (Premiere Pro, Media Encoder and After Effects). In Premiere Pro, you can load the Blackmagic RAW parameters in our new BRAW Studio Power Settings Panel. This panel provides durability properties and useful utilities, such as editing NTSC timecode and importing your footage metadata (Dashboard UI is provided at Window - &amp;amp; gt menu. ; Extensions). On After Effects,...
</description></item><item><title>Download G-Business Extractor 7.6.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 18 Aug 2025 16:44:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-g-business-extractor-10863.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-g-business-extractor-10863.html
</guid><description>
Google Maps is the source where you can find millions of business leads sorted by category and location.
You can search by target keywords in your location. This software will search and find business information such as website, email address, phone number, fax, etc. G-Business Extractor is a powerful tool that helps you find business leads from Google Maps. This is the best Google Maps Scraper tool that can extract data from the most important business categories.
Features of...
</description></item><item><title>Download SeekFast 5.6 Build 2</title><pubDate> Mon, 18 Aug 2025 16:43:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-seekfast-7524.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-seekfast-7524.html
</guid><description>
SeekFast has the ability to quickly search for specific text in all documents on your computer. SeekFast then sorts the results in a way that makes it easy to find the text you're looking for, see its context, and open the file that contains it. All you have to do is select a folder to search for and enter search words or phrases - you'll get all the sentences they appear in within seconds. This is especially useful if you need to find something quickly.
SeekFast uses state-of-the-art...
</description></item><item><title>Download Private Windows Script (PrivWindoze) 5.6.6</title><pubDate> Mon, 18 Aug 2025 16:38:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-private-windows-script-12878.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-private-windows-script-12878.html
</guid><description>
Are you concerned about your personal information sent to others? Or do you feel that your Windows settings have many programs that you never use? Private Windows Script (or Privwindoze) provides a comprehensive anti -remote monitoring set designed to enhance your privacy when using Windows operating system.
The main features
	End the positive process. All unnecessary processes are turned off while the scanning program. A small white list is maintained.
	Clean up the positive runonce....
</description></item><item><title>Download Easy System Utility Pro 1.1.48</title><pubDate> Mon, 18 Aug 2025 16:36:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easy-system-utility-pro-12380.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easy-system-utility-pro-12380.html
</guid><description>
Easy System Utility Pro is a powerful, all-in-one program designed for Windows 10 and 11 users. This versatile tool should be your primary choice to improve your computing experience ! This is the complete version with additional and enhanced features. It will help you easily determine your computer's hardware specifications with a system overview. You can view the operating system, CPU model, GPU, Memory, Motherboard, Network and even drivers.
It also supports launching programs,...
</description></item></channel></rss>