<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 15:37:24 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 15:37:24 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download FxSound (FxSound Enhancer Premium) 1.2.4 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 17:32:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fxsound-enhancer-premium-2013.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fxsound-enhancer-premium-2013.html
</guid><description>
FxSound Enhancer Premium formerly DFX Audio Enhance, is accessories multimedia software most popular in the world with over 46 million downloads worldwide. FxSound enhances the sound of most of the music content and online video is live streaming on the Web, including the streaming service, YouTube, Pandora, Spotify and Apple Music. FxSound Enhancer Premium also implemented enhanced real-time audio on the player PC multimedia most popular include iTunes, Windows Media Player, Winamp and...
</description></item><item><title>Download OCCT 15.0.11.99</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 17:31:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-occt-perestroika-1680.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-occt-perestroika-1680.html
</guid><description>
OCCT is a free application designed to benchmark and overclock system components. Test tool OverClock includes 4 different tests to assess the stability of your computer. CPU and CPU: Linpack to test the processor, GPU: 3D to check stability of the graphics processor and power supply combination of CPU: Linpack and GPU: 3D to download power of you up to the maximum.
OCCT - Measuring system components
The features of OCCT
	Support is enabled for a maximum of 16 cores.
	All the tests...
</description></item><item><title>Download Irix HDR Pro 2.3.55</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 17:29:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-irix-hdr-pro-10653.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-irix-hdr-pro-10653.html
</guid><description>
Irix HDR Pro is an AI-powered photo editing application for Windows, it is available on Microsoft Store. This program has tons of professional HDR photo editing features including Sky Replacement, Face Sculpting &amp;amp; body, over 200 presets &amp;amp; AI powered tool' and is a Photo Editor in the category of photo &amp;amp; Graphics. It delivers true-to-life HDR photo editing, providing one-click edits for a full-scale professional editing toolkit.
Features of Irix HDR Pro
	Sky Replacement...
</description></item><item><title>Download PrivaZer Pro Donors 4.0.115</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 17:29:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-privazer-donors-198.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-privazer-donors-198.html
</guid><description>
PrivaZer Donors  cleans and removes filth traces from the system. Intensive cleaning of unwanted traces of what you've done, viewed, downloaded, deleted, etc. Take ownership of your security and freedom - Free up disk space. Keep your PC snug and secure !!!
With one click, PrivaZer can safely clean: Internet browsers, Index.dat, Cookies, Tor Cookies, Flash Cookies, Silverlight Cookies, DOM Storing, IndexedDB, AppCache Registry, RAM, Pagefile.sys and Hiberfil.sys files.  PrivaZer  can...
</description></item><item><title>Download FxSound Pro 1.2.4 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 17:29:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fxsound-5966.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fxsound-5966.html
</guid><description>
FxSound Pro is a professional software that helps to enhance the quality of sound, volume, depth, and sound on your PC. FxSound brings you a great sound just with a downloadable download. After using FxSound, you will know if it is for you or not. Most people do n' t know what they ' re missing in their sound until they try their software/sound hardware better. It ' s hard to convey if you do n' t really experience yourself.
Reason to use FxSound Pro:
	The perfect sound on every...
</description></item><item><title>Download Quick Access Popup 12.1.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 17:28:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quick-access-popup-984.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quick-access-popup-984.html
</guid><description>
Quick Access Popup  ( QAP ) is a software that provides quick access to files, files, windows applications and is  shortcut manager , mouse and keyboard.  Quick Access Popup  helps you quickly move between FILE, DOCUMENT, APPS in Windows Explorer or file dialog to quickly launch applications, documents or web pages at once 
To launch the pop-up menu, click the  QAP  icon in the Notifications area, press the Middle mouse button, or press Windows + W (these triggers can be changed under...
</description></item><item><title>Download DiskMax 7.29</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 17:27:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-diskmax-5940.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-diskmax-5940.html
</guid><description>
Using DiskMax to periodically make a robust drive cleaner and optimize performance to keep your PC healthy. After using DiskMax, you will notice that your system will work better, the apps will start faster, the files will open faster and the games will run better. Just run DiskMax over time to keep your system steady.
Even if you are an advanced user, DiskMax will be useful to you because it automate all the tasks needed to keep your system clean and quickly, helping you enjoy the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Irix HDR Classic Pro 2.3.55</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 17:27:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-irix-hdr-classic-pro-10652.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-irix-hdr-classic-pro-10652.html
</guid><description>
Irix HDR Classic Pro is an AI-powered photo editor that delivers true-to-life HDR photo editing, providing one-click edits to the editing toolkit professional at full scale with a highly cognitive user interface (UI).
Main features:
	Sky replacement (SkyXpress): replaces the sky and imports weather. Import custom skies and merge, blend, and integrate with your images for a natural look with AI Edge Detect.
	Presets &amp;amp; Filters: 200+ social media optimized presets with just one tap...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube Downloader 3.9.18 (0112)</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 17:27:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube Downloader  is a dedicated software that helps users  downloading youtube videos  Favorites on PC for offline viewing. With MediaHuman YouTube  Downloader  you can download videos from youtube website to your computer with  fast speed , with special software development technology that automatically receives videos from Websites, in addition to the ability to download videos from software websites, can convert downloaded video formats to various formats for the purpose...
</description></item><item><title>Download HFS: HTTP File Server (version 3) 0.57.27</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 17:26:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hfs-http-file-server-11851.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hfs-http-file-server-11851.html
</guid><description>
HFS is a web file server to run on your computer. Share a folder or even a file thanks to the virtual file system. Essentially, this application turns your computer into an HTTP server and all users who want to connect and download files can do so by loading a simple website in their browser. HFS includes many configuration settings, so you can basically change each part of the application, starting with how users download files and ending with the appearance of the created website.
HFS...
</description></item><item><title>Download ExpanDrive 2025.11.21</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 17:26:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-expandrive-609.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-expandrive-609.html
</guid><description>
ExpanDrive is software sync cloud storage strong support BackBlaze B2, Google Team Drive, SMB / CIFS and new interface and easy user search file version, share links and much more.  ExpanDrive mapped network drives for macOS and Micosoft Windows connect with all the provide major cloud storage such as Dropbox, Google Drive, Google Team Drive, Amazon Drive, Box, OneDrive, OneDrive for Business, Sharepoint, Openstack Swift , BackBlaze B2, Amazon S3 or SFTP servers, FTP or WebDAV on your own...
</description></item><item><title>Download Outline Client VPN 1.17.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 17:25:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-outline-client-vpn-7913.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-outline-client-vpn-7913.html
</guid><description>
Outline Client VPN is a simple, easy-to-use application that allows you to share access to a VPN with anyone on your network. It provides greater control over a user's online anonymity. It is a free service that allows users to create their own virtual private network, allowing them to share access with anyone on their network.
Outline Client VPN uses services from DigitalOcean, Google Cloud Platform, and Amazon Lightsail. These options are intended to make the process simpler, you can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Lyric Video Studio 1.3.82</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 17:25:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lyric-video-studio-13581.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lyric-video-studio-13581.html
</guid><description>
Lyric Video Studio is a powerful, feature-rich video editor specifically designed to create lyric videos, music videos, and visualizers with ease. It integrates simple and effective text tools along with generative AI capabilities to streamline the video creation process. Whether you're a musician launching a killer new track, a content creator, or just love playing with visuals, this app lets you sync your lyrics to your music in just a few clicks. Enter lyrics, drag to sync and you're...
</description></item><item><title>Download Omidsoft Red Burner 18.44</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 17:24:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-red-burner-10119.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-red-burner-10119.html
</guid><description>
Red Burner is a lightweight burning software based on Blue Burner with full functionality to work with ISO/CUE images and drives. Start the move to a lightweight, yet powerful, and time-saving standalone optical disc burner with the simplest user interface and fastest possible burning algorithm.
Features of Red Burner
	Fastest possible CD/DVD/BD burning algorithm
	Standard, dual-layer and high-capacity media recording
	Browse ISO/CUE images via internal image browser
	Writable M-Disc,...
</description></item><item><title>Download PC Timer 18.44</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 17:24:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pc-timer-7519.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pc-timer-7519.html
</guid><description>
PC Timer is a simple tool to automatically shut down, log out, restart or lock your PC based on your scheduled time. A handy feature of the app is its ability to prevent unauthorized cancellation of a scheduled task. To do so, PC Timer .NET allows you to set a password that the user must provide to cancel the operation.
The advantage of the application is its simplicity, small footprint on the system and the fact that it does not require installation. Thanks to the ability to set tasks...
</description></item><item><title>Download Bitwig Studio 6.0 Beta 7</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 17:23:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bitwig-studio-3626.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bitwig-studio-3626.html
</guid><description>
Find new standard in the process of individual work. Bitwig Studio excite you good control over his music, give you access to all features of your production. Streamline course creation of you and quickly develop your ideas into the songs, compositions and music full.
Bitwig Studio - Create your own music
Arrange and record, perform and improvise, or do all at the same time. Choose among the many records displayed. Design your sound with the equipment container commitment. Mixing the...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter 3.9.18 (0112)</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 17:23:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-to-mp3-converter-1744.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-to-mp3-converter-1744.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter is the software support download youtube video and convert video to mp3 format fast and most simple. MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter allows you download and convert videos from YouTube and other websites to MP3 format by pasting the YouTube URL into the application. When you paste the URL, the program will display thumbnails for videos and you have the option to customize the title information, artist and album before you begin the process of...
</description></item><item><title>Download SSD Booster .NET 18.44</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 17:22:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ssd-booster-net-7375.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ssd-booster-net-7375.html
</guid><description>
SSD Booster .NET is our perfect tool to optimize and adjust Windows for the SSD drive to increase performance and maintain the highest performance for your SSD. In addition, the app comes with the system information tab for information about the hardware and operating system of your machine. To check your specifications, move to the Introduction and find the System Information button.
Features of SSD Booster .NET
	The perfect tool to optimize and adjust Windows for the SSD drive to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft Safety Scanner 1.441.782.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 17:22:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-safety-scanner-4512.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-safety-scanner-4512.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft Safety Scanner is a scanning tool designed to find and remove malware from a Windows computer. Just download and run the scan to find malware and try to reverse the changes made by the threat identified. Microsoft Safety Scanner has the ability to remove virus, spyware and files other dangers on your computer, Microsoft Safety Scanner completes scanning tasks in just a few minutes, while the computer is moderate stress during handling.
In other words, no real time protection...
</description></item><item><title>Download eM Client Pro 10.3.4324</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 17:21:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-em-client-pro-953.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-em-client-pro-953.html
</guid><description>
eM Client Pro is an email app full features with modern interface. eM Client offers calendar, tasks, contacts and chat. Software is best Email app for windows today. eM Client supports all major services including Gmail, Exchange, iCloud and Outlook.com. You can find more information in the server part on our website.
eM Client Pro - the best email App for windows
eM Client is very simple , can automatically set everything up for most of the services. It is also effective to import...
</description></item><item><title>Download SEO Checker 10.4</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 17:21:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-seo-checker-2514.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-seo-checker-2514.html
</guid><description>
SEO Checker (A product of genuine VOVSoft) is a tool to analyze all type of web site or personal web page. The software works in many different ways, it can help you discover the content that you have specifically chosen to analyze from suitable site. As the authors write, the program, as this program allows you to plan for your SEO strategy by providing information about the function of it, you will get a set of keyword analysis and tracking the reverse link.
SEO Checker - Support SEO...
</description></item><item><title>Download Windhawk 1.7.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 17:20:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windhawk-10622.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windhawk-10622.html
</guid><description>
Windhawk aims to make customizing Windows programs easier. It allows installing and configuring mods (custom modules) in just a few clicks. For developers, it provides a convenient platform to develop and share such mods.
Another benefit for users is that each mod is just a text code file. This makes it easy to review what the mod actually does, unlike an executable which is difficult to verify. And that doesn't affect the user experience – installing a mod takes just a few clicks,...
</description></item><item><title>Download EarthTime 6.30.17</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 17:20:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-earthtime-185.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-earthtime-185.html
</guid><description>
EarthTime is software that displays the time and date local time of any place in the world. This application has database integration good for 3000 city, users can manually add, download at EarthTime if you want to. EarthTime allows you to install for the time zone and current local time.EarthTime displays the Earth according to the view night and day, you can view the map in full screen mode.
EarthTime
The feature on EarthTime
	EarthTime allows users to interact with visualization...
</description></item><item><title>Download Memory Cleaner 3.00</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 17:19:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-memory-cleaner-6016.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-memory-cleaner-6016.html
</guid><description>
Memory Cleaner uses multiple functionality that has been integrated in Windows to release memory without affecting your system. You can also access the functions of Memory Cleaner right from your systray without having to open the program. The cleanup processes are all silent and the only time you will see the alert showing the amount of RAM is restored in the short period.
Memory Cleaner also cuts the work of the process, deleting the system cache, which monitors the use of RAM and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Quicken WillMaker &amp;amp; Trust 26.2.3130</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 17:19:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quicken-willmaker-trust-4277.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quicken-willmaker-trust-4277.html
</guid><description>
Quicken WillMaker &amp;amp; Trust is the easiest way to create a package of your estate, whether you beginner or you want to update the sort earlier. This powerful software guides you throughout the process from beginning to end, provide you with practical information and legal that you need to take the best decision for you and your family. Quicken WillMaker &amp;amp; Trust is software write wills original, created and regularly updated by the experts of Nolo. Updates free legal will continue the...
</description></item></channel></rss>