<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 15:39:28 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 15:39:28 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download USB Device Tree Viewer 4.6.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:54:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-usb-device-tree-viewer-3286.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-usb-device-tree-viewer-3286.html
</guid><description>
USB Device Tree Viewer provides detailed information for all the ports and USB hub on the computer in the format tree. If a device is connected to a port, it also provides detailed information for the properties of the device and connection. USB Device Tree Viewer analyze your system configuration and display details about the controller server is connected, such as the manufacturer, drivers, bus types, list, location, devices, drive letters, COM ports, and debugging and statistics bus...
</description></item><item><title>Download Free Audio Editor 1.1.43.903 Premium</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:54:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dvdvideosoft-free-audio-editor-7852.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dvdvideosoft-free-audio-editor-7852.html
</guid><description>
Free Audio Editor is an easy-to-use audio editing tool whose main function is to remove unwanted audio parts and split audio files. The interface of the program is intuitive and simple. It displays the waveform of the audio files making it possible for users of any level to edit it visually.
The program includes many special sound effects, capable of working on many different audio formats such as MP3, OGG, WMA, ACC, M4A, FLAC… Free Audio Editor will display the sounds according to...
</description></item><item><title>Download PrintFab Pro XL 3.0.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:53:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-printfab-pro-xl-4083.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-printfab-pro-xl-4083.html
</guid><description>
PrintFab Pro XL software is targeted to advanced users and will allow for the prints, neutral balance. Of course, you can also affect the brightness of the color, adjust contrast, etc. using the option of different controls. PrintFab Pro XL allows you to print on any means accurate color possible - and even arbitrary use of special inks from the manufacturer side Tuesday. This is done for people by measuring color inexpensive (the 14.95 EUR) by service PrintFab or measurement technology of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Zortam Mp3 Media Studio Pro 33.25</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:53:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zortam-mp3-media-studio-pro-135.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zortam-mp3-media-studio-pro-135.html
</guid><description>
Zortam Mp3 Media Studio Pro brings you rich processing tools music includes extract and convert music from CD to Mp3 format, edit, music cards, music download....You can also create discs CD high-quality music, with Zortam Mp3 Media Studio search music files duplicated to remove them from the system, rename music files, switch back and forth between formats.
Zortam Mp3 Media Studio Pro is rated as perfect software in the processing of the MP3 files on the computer. First of all, you can...
</description></item><item><title>Download EverNote 10.154.1.51289</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:52:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-evernote-3261.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-evernote-3261.html
</guid><description>
EverNote is the all in one tool allows you to track notes, todo items, memos, outlines, excerpts, websites, ideas and other things and automatically synchronize them between multiple computers and mobile devices (iPhone, Android, etc.). You can choose to sort their notes into categories, password protect them, export them to XML and more. EverNote supports a number of pattern notes allow you to add to-do list, spreadsheet like Excel to calculate costs (automatic sum), notes, phone, contact...
</description></item><item><title>Download Daum PotPlayer 1.7.22611</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:52:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-daum-potplayer-1015.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-daum-potplayer-1015.html
</guid><description>
Daum PotPlayer is a multimedia player has almost all the functions and interface similar, but improved markedly with KMP. Software Daum PotPlayer Stable have the special feature is the high quality playback, support for all video formats and audio modern and the presence of video codecs DXVA integration. Has a modern design, easy to install, have the ability to assign and change the hot keys, record sound to play, display subtitles, connect the plug-in DSP that allows visual display when...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinZip Pro 29.0.16416</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:51:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winzip-pro-263.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winzip-pro-263.html
</guid><description>
WinZip Pro is a Windows utility Zip most popular in the world to compress files share files, coding files and backup data. WinZip helps you to save time, save space and improve productivity. Moreover, you can instantly compress files to conserve storage space, send email swifter and reducing time to upload / download files. Zip documents, spreadsheets, PDFS, presentations, you name it! You can quickly compress and decompress files to save storage space, speed up e-mail transmission and...
</description></item><item><title>Download DeskSoft EarthView 7.13.9</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:51:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desksoft-earthview-184.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desksoft-earthview-184.html
</guid><description>
With software DeskSoft EarthView you can easily create wallpapers to your computer or select screen saver of your favorite. the program can change day and night, the clouds will also change according to weather conditions current on one or another part of the earth, you can see the lights of the city.
Features of DeskSoft EarthView can be interesting, because of DeskSoft EarthView support for day and night, you can view atmospheric phenomena, light city can see, the cloud is displayed,...
</description></item><item><title>Download UniFab 3.0.2.7</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:50:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-unifab-10377.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-unifab-10377.html
</guid><description>
UniFab is software to efficiently convert, compress and edit more than 1000 video formats for playback on any device without losing quality. Enlarge video/audio to 1080p/DTS 7.1 and upgrade video to HDR10 or Dolby Vision with AI Enhancer. UniFab Pro provides the best AI-powered zoom tool that allows you to enlarge videos from low resolutions, such as 360p, 480p and 720p, to 1080p without losing any quality. Clearer and sharper image details will bring you an exceptional viewing...
</description></item><item><title>Download Scooter Beyond Compare 5.1.5.31310</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:50:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-scooter-beyond-compare-2649.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-scooter-beyond-compare-2649.html
</guid><description>
Scooter Beyond Compare is a powerful tool to compare quickly and easily the files and folders. This program provides you with a full report on work done so you can compare the complete data on the file, folder, folder with speed and file size, very fast and incredible, time changes on the file as well as the compared bytes Do byte this information. With the strong command of this program, you can merge the changes, synchronize files, create a report to record.
Scooter Beyond Compare -...
</description></item><item><title>Download MusConv 4.10.415 Lifetime</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:49:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html
</guid><description>
MusConv transfers playlists, albums, followed artists and liked songs across a variety of services – Spotify, Apple Music, Amazon Music, YouTube, YouTube Music, iTunes, Deezer, Tidal, SoundCloud, Pandora and more 125 music services!
Features of MusConv Ultimate
	Transfer playlists, albums, followed artists and liked tracks between over 125 music servicesManage playlists (Delete, Merge, Split, Copy...)
	More than 125 music services supported
	Access DAILY updated music charts on...
</description></item><item><title>Download Device Cleanup Tool 1.5.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:49:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-device-cleanup-tool-6911.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-device-cleanup-tool-6911.html
</guid><description>
Device Cleanup Tool is a free tool that allows you to see what devices are attached to your computer like USB, Modem, CDROM, NET,.. and it allows you to choose easily and delete multiple device entries at once. It also tells you when the device was last used to help you ensure the right ones are discarded.
Before using the Device Cleanup Tool software, you need to run it as an administrator so that you can erase the devices connected to the computer without errors. Device Cleanup Tool...
</description></item><item><title>Download StaxRip 2.50.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:49:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-staxrip-2930.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-staxrip-2930.html
</guid><description>
StaxRip app is a comprehensive and powerful, allowing you to convert all video files DVB, DVD, or DV video into a variety of file formats. The program is open Source, meaning completely free to download and use. StaxRip can support many video formats such as x264, MPEG-4, DivX, XviD, MPEG-2 and many other formats. The format sounds different also be supported, including MP2 / MPA, AAC, WAV, Ogg Vorbis, MP3, AC3, DTS and other formats. Moreover, the program also supports a variety of...
</description></item><item><title>Download DBF Viewer 2000 v8.81</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:48:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbf-viewer-2000-7869.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbf-viewer-2000-7869.html
</guid><description>
DBF Viewer 2000 is a fast, efficient solution for viewing and editing all types of DBF files. It can handle files from dBase, Visual dBase, Foxpro, Visual FoxPro and Clipper, just to name a few, with performance that easily rivals expensive professional database utilities. DBF Viewer 2000 is extremely fast, does any task, just one simple query and cleanup copy to export data at lightning speed.
With DBF Editor's simple, dynamically generated visual dialogs, you can easily view the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ashisoft Duplicate Photos Finder Pro 2.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:48:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashisoft-duplicate-photos-finder-pro-11097.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashisoft-duplicate-photos-finder-pro-11097.html
</guid><description>
Ashisoft Duplicate Photos Finder Pro is software that removes duplicate photos and organizes your photo collection and frees up your precious disk space. Find similarities in different images like people and list them even if they are rotated, flipped, resized or edited. It supports over 60 photo formats, including RAW, HEIC/HEIF, JPG, PNG, GIF, and more, which means it won't miss a single duplicate photo.
Why is finding duplicate images useful?
	People who maintain large collections...
</description></item><item><title>Download BAT to EXE Converter 4.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:47:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bat-to-exe-converter-1585.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bat-to-exe-converter-1585.html
</guid><description>
BAT to EXE Converter is a powerful tool designed to create the file .EXE from the format .BAT. The app's interface is a standard window layout is not complicated. You can download Batch file using the browser file or method 'drag and drop'. BAT to EXE Converter allows you to configure a number of options before you convert the file .BAT into the executable, including manipulation with behavior of the .EXE by inserting a command line argument.
BAT to EXE Converter - Create file EXE from...
</description></item><item><title>Download Audiority Complete Effects Bundle 2025.9.9</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:41:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-audiority-effects-plugin-bundle-2071.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-audiority-effects-plugin-bundle-2071.html
</guid><description>
Audiority Plugins Bundle is a collection of sound effects and virtual instruments developed by Audiority, an Italian software company specializing in sound design and tools. music production. This package includes many plugins that cover various aspects of music production, such as synthesizers, guitar amplifier simulation, delay effects, reverb, and more.
included effects
	Deleight v1.4.1 — Multi Tap Stereo Delay with cross feedback
	Echoes T7E mkII v2.2.2 — *Binson® Echorec®...
</description></item><item><title>Download Atlantis Word Processor 4.4.6.7</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:40:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-atlantis-word-processor-585.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-atlantis-word-processor-585.html
</guid><description>
Atlantis Word Processor is a word processor app with features format, standard text, autocorrect, and spell check.  Atlantis is a word processor in accordance with most of the tasks handled daily text. The interface is very easy to use and offers the toolbars, hotkeys and sound effects thanh can customize (can turn off). It includes a clip library for quick access to the text or images used regular preview, font format and many other features aimed at improving the process of your...
</description></item><item><title>Download ClassicDesktopClock 5.11</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:40:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-classicdesktopclock-3986.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-classicdesktopclock-3986.html
</guid><description>
ClassicDesktopClock is a simple clock, and can customize allow you to see the current time on the computer to your desk. The program provides a number of topics that will help you change the look just by a click of the mouse. In addition, you can set the clock anywhere you want on your screen. ClassicDesktopClock comes with a variety of features and rich options, such as transparency, the ability to show or hide the second hand, some themes, multiple language support, portability, etc.,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Gillmeister Automatic PDF Processor 1.41.13</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:39:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gillmeister-automatic-pdf-processor-9026.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gillmeister-automatic-pdf-processor-9026.html
</guid><description>
Gillmeister Automatic PDF Processor is a software tool that allows users to automate various tasks related to PDF files. This software can be used to process large number of PDF files at once, saving time and effort for users who need to perform repetitive tasks.
Features of Gillmeister Automatic PDF Processor
	Track any number of folders: Inspect incoming PDFs and apply individual rules
	Archive PDF files in a structured way: Automatically rename PDF files and save them in...
</description></item><item><title>Download DriverStore Explorer 0.12.118</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:39:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-driverstore-explorer-2892.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-driverstore-explorer-2892.html
</guid><description>
DriverStore Explorer RAPR is software for dealing with drivers Windows more easily. The supported operations include enumeration, adding driver package (stage), add and install, delete and delete force from the store drivers.
DriverStore Explorer - drivers
The features of the DriverStore Explorer
	Listed / Listed all the packages are held in the store current drivers.
	Export the list as CSV.
	Added package drivers catalog drivers (called staging)
	Install &amp;amp; Add driver package...
</description></item><item><title>Download Blue Cat Audio 2025.9</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:38:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blue-cat-audio-751.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blue-cat-audio-751.html
</guid><description>
Blue Cat Audio develops and distributes the app and the plug-in real-time audio for PC and Mac platforms, focuses on sound analysis, feedback, image accuracy and flexibility. Check out our software and convert audio workstation digital of a processing environment sounds professional.
Blue Cat Audio - Plugins audio standard
The products Plugins inside Blue Cat Audio
Blue Cat's Axiom v1.1.2
Blue Cat's Destructor v1.4.1
Blue Cat's DP Meter Pro v4.1.0
Blue Cat's Dynamics v4.2.0
Blue Cat's...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaPortal 2.5 / 1.38.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:38:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediaportal-2627.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediaportal-2627.html
</guid><description>
MediaPortal is a media player and open source software project, digital video recorders, are often considered as an alternative solution for Windows Media Center. MediaPortal is a media center, it is open source after launch, not only can view the different video formats, but also view photos in a convenient form.
MediaPortal is written on the website of the developer, as a Microsoft Windows application, this program can be called safely is a project quite unique on the network, because...
</description></item><item><title>Download Awesome Miner Ultimate 11.2.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:37:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-awesome-miner-9041.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-awesome-miner-9041.html
</guid><description>
Awesome Miner is a software application designed to manage and monitor cryptocurrency mining operations. It supports a wide variety of mining hardware, including ASICs and GPUs, and can be used to manage mining for a variety of cryptocurrencies, including Bitcoin, Ethereum, and Litecoin.
Powerful tool to manage and monitor cryptocurrency mining activities. With support for a wide variety of mining hardware and cryptocurrencies, mobile apps, and customizable alerting and performance...
</description></item><item><title>Download Trellix Stinger (McAfee Stinger) 13.0.0.455</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:36:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mcafee-stinger-202.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mcafee-stinger-202.html
</guid><description>
McAfee Stinger is a free utility that functions to scan, check and remove the hazards and obstacles as virus or malware for Windows, whether they are hiding deep into the system.
In addition, due to the ability to search for the correct folder, or the data at risk contains viruses to scan instead you have to remove a long time waiting for antivirus software to scan all system on your computer. Thus speed of work of the McAfee Stinger faster and somewhat more accurate.
Themselves McAfee...
</description></item></channel></rss>