<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 21:33:10 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 21:33:10 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download foobar2000 2.25.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Sep 2025 00:24:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-foobar2000-1812.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-foobar2000-1812.html
</guid><description>
foobar2000 is the media player for media formats MP3, WAV, OGG and other formats multimedia other. It has no bells and whistles, however, under the hood, the program offers quite many features, including format, title and layout of the interface can be customized, convert WAV, Equalizer, Resampler, note cards, MP3, playlists, music album, CD, drag / drop and more. It also includes all the standard features like shuffle, random play, etc.
foobar2000 - The media player
foobar2000 running...
</description></item><item><title>Download Intel Graphics Driver for Windows 10 / 11 32.0.101.7029</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Sep 2025 00:22:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intel-graphics-driver-for-windows-10-5954.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intel-graphics-driver-for-windows-10-5954.html
</guid><description>
Intel Graphics Driver for Windows 10 supports Intel ' s latest 8th-generation Core processor, introducing the Intel ® UHD graphics, with the ability to immerve in the top 4K UHD entertainment from your laptop for a maximum of 10 hours. Along with some security fixes, this driver also optimised the system's inactivity to reduce power consumption.
Look at the complete new interface of gameplay.intel.com, where you will find the proposed game settings for many of your favorite PC games....
</description></item><item><title>Download AOMEI Partition Assistant Professional 10.9 + Technician + Unlimited + Server</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Sep 2025 00:20:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aomei-partition-assistant-281.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aomei-partition-assistant-281.html
</guid><description>
AOMEI Partition Assistant is partition software hard disk all in one easy to use, offers many features partition manager free. AOMEI Partition Assistant to ensure the full features to create, resize, move, copy, delete, delete, align, format, merge, split partitions.
AOMEI Partition Assistant
AOMEI Partition Manager enables you to expand the available space on hard disk quickly for improve the capacity for the root partition. The instructions move smart can easily support you move the...
</description></item><item><title>Download EaseUS Fixo Technician 3.8.5 Build 20250905</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Sep 2025 00:19:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-fixo-9814.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-fixo-9814.html
</guid><description>
Video is corrupted or inaccessible after power failure and sudden blackout, whole system crash, update failure, wrong file handling or some other reason? EaseUS Fixo allows you to repair many different video file formats including MOV, MP4, M2TS, MKV, MTS, 3GP, etc. easier no matter how broken it is.
It can intelligently and intelligently repair damaged and damaged photos from computers or other external storage devices such as USB flash drives, memory cards, SD cards, digital cameras...
</description></item><item><title>Download Opera One 122.0.5643.17</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Sep 2025 00:19:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-972.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-972.html
</guid><description>
Opera is a fast, safe, configurable and compliant intranet web browser, which includes both the reader and the application. The Opera browser supports web browsing, listening to music, watching high speed movies, you can open many tabs on the Opera without affecting your browsing speed. Opera now supports almost all devices and operating systems such as windows, IOS, Android, linux, MacOS ...
Opera is a beautiful interface and many interesting features, operating on both PCs and mobile,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Acrobat Pro DC 2025.001.20693 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Sep 2025 00:13:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-001en-adobe-acrobat-pro-458.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-001en-adobe-acrobat-pro-458.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Acrobat Pro DC is a comprehensive software that helps you create and edit the PDF&amp;nbsp;document, or create form, sign, protect PDF, connect, split PDF, export PDF to various formats. The Acrobat Pro DC is the latest version of Adobe with improvements in the interface with the polished ribbon bar and the ability to create and handle pdf files as well as its male versions.
The highlight of the Acrobat Pro DC is probably the ability to connect, store documents on the cloud, you can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Minimal Firewall 2.1.5</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Sep 2025 00:05:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minimal-firewall-13877.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minimal-firewall-13877.html
</guid><description>
Minimal Firewall works in conjunction with Windows Firewall to block all unknown connections by default, prompting you to create application-based rules to mitigate malware, telemetry, and data leaks. Completely eliminate applications that call home without your knowledge. Minimal Firewall provides a more secure and integrated approach by interacting directly with the native Windows Firewall, eliminating the need for risky system modifications.
Core Features
	Lockdown Mode: The core...
</description></item><item><title>Download AnyDesk 9.6.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Sep 2025 00:04:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anydesk-1321.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anydesk-1321.html
</guid><description>
AnyDesk is software computer control remote, easy connection with remote computer management and manipulation on the computer. After installing the AnyDesk up 2 the computer then you can easily use the software to provide technical support for a friend or family member or you have access to your computer while you away from home or office.
AnyDesk - control your computer remotely
The process of using very simple software, want to allow access to his computer, only need to provide for...
</description></item><item><title>Download EF AutoSync 25.10</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Sep 2025 00:04:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ef-autosync-3206.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ef-autosync-3206.html
</guid><description>
EF AutoSync is a practical tool to synchronize data automatically between PC and other components such as USB flash drive, external drive, another computer, etc.
Easy to use software done for you activities such as archiving, mirroring, data backup, update, takes you out of work.
EF AutoSync - synchronizes data
The integration of the plugin file system side Tuesday outside in the form of WFX support a variety of devices.
The following languages are included in the package: English,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ant Download Manager Pro 2.15.10.91278</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 23:00:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ant-download-manager-pro-137.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ant-download-manager-pro-137.html
</guid><description>
Ant Download Manager Pro is software support download has the same features as IDM, even it has many prominent features, more user friendly more and have speed download data incredible. Ant Download Manager is a Internet content downloader quickly with support download at video! Function: fully Integrated with the web browsers most popular: Internet Explorer 8+, Mozilla Firefox 32 +, Google Chrome 31+ and the copies of them (Pale Moon, Opera, Vivaldi, Slimjet, ComodoDragon, etc.). you...
</description></item><item><title>Download AB Download Manager 1.6.12</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 23:00:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ab-download-manager-12399.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ab-download-manager-12399.html
</guid><description>
With this application, you can easily download files from anywhere. Enjoy fast, free downloads with seamless browser extension support. It is built to be a desktop application that allows you to manage and organize your downloads better than before.
AB Download Manager features
	Simple and modern UI: Simple UI and dark mode by default
	Faster download speeds: Download files using multiple connections to increase your download speed by up to 500%
	Download Queue: Create and manage your...
</description></item><item><title>Download Draftable Desktop 25.9.100</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 22:59:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-draftable-desktop-3749.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-draftable-desktop-3749.html
</guid><description>
Draftable Desktop is comparison tool documents the fastest. Compare over 300 pages in a few seconds. Draftable Desktop 2.0 is now available - faster and stronger than ever! See all the changes in your documents, locally and online. Take your work to the next level. Compare secret and private do not use the internet and your documents never leave your computer. Specifically, Draftable Desktop compatible with .xls, .xlsx, .xlsxm. With Office 2013, 2016 or 365, you can compare text in...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ashampoo WinOptimizer 28.00.14</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 22:59:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-winoptimizer-870.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-winoptimizer-870.html
</guid><description>
Ashampoo WinOptimizer is a software cleanup, optimize and protect your PC. It frees up disk space, fix errors on computer. WinOptimizer has overcome the shortcomings of Windows and give you a system faster, leaner and leaner. Many features automated features make setting it up a problem is only a few clicks of the mouse most simple.
Ashampoo WinOptimizer - Clean optimize PC
Ashampoo WinOptimizer provides instant access to your system, you can look and feel the way that best suits you....
</description></item><item><title>Download Ashampoo UnInstaller 16.00.02</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 22:58:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-uninstaller-247.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-uninstaller-247.html
</guid><description>
When you remove a program, but maybe some files will not be completely deleted, it will remain on your computer in hidden mode, thus causing your computer to slow down and not optimize. . But not with Ashampoo UnInstaller. Ashampoo UnInstaller is a powerful program uninstaller to completely remove unnecessary software, free up your drive, speed up your computer.
In addition, with Ashampoo UnInstaller you can also manage fonts, clean the registry, possibly, have support for defragmenting...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Acrobat Reader DC 2025.001.20693</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 22:58:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-acrobat-reader-3707.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-acrobat-reader-3707.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Acrobat Reader DC is a system of application software and Web services developed by Adobe Systems to view, create, manipulate, print and manage PDF files. With Adobe Acrobat Reader DC, you can create, export, edit, and track PDF files from anywhere - and maintain connection with the recent set of files on all your devices.
Adobe Acrobat Reader current DC is connected with Adobe Document Cloud - help working on the computers and mobile devices becomes easier than ever before. This is...
</description></item><item><title>Download ColorPicker Max 6.8.0.2509</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 22:57:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-colorpicker-7039.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-colorpicker-7039.html
</guid><description>
ColorPicker is a modern color picker for developers available on Windows. This is the next major evolution of the existing ColorPicker 2 software, released in 2020.
ColorPicker allows you to choose a color from your monitor, or you can choose it manually; it will then save the color history so you can go back and review the selected colors. ColorPicker can also randomize a color for you if you want. Then the color can be converted to another (RGB, HEX, HSL, HSV, CMYK). It has a sleek...
</description></item><item><title>Download Stardock Windowblinds 11.07</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 22:56:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stardock-windowblinds-1562.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stardock-windowblinds-1562.html
</guid><description>
Stardock Windowblinds is software customizable editing, computer interface such as the taskbar, window frames and control buttons,... Stardock Windowblinds enables users to customize the theme interface desktop called skins to personalize the interface of the computer to their desk.
Stardock Windowblinds - Customize the Windows interface
The functions and features of Stardock Windowblinds
Visualization
	Choose from the many interfaces available in WindowBlinds or choose from among...
</description></item><item><title>Download DroidKit 2.3.7.20250911</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 22:56:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-droidkit-6578.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-droidkit-6578.html
</guid><description>
DroidKit is data recovery software for your mobile device, it will quickly scan your phone memory and save photos, WhatsApp chats and files, messages Messages, contacts and more essential data up to 13 categories, covering almost everything you need every day. All Android phones and tablets are supported. Without rooting your device. No tech skills required. No need to wait many days. You can get back what you've lost with just a few simple clicks, instantly.
Besides, DroidKit also has...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ghostery for Firefox 10.5.9 + Chrome / Opera / Edge</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 22:55:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ghostery-for-firefox-320.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ghostery-for-firefox-320.html
</guid><description>
Ghostery for Firefox is a browser add-on for Firefox allows you to see what kind of technical track is used by the current website, including tags, error web, pixels and beacons. Ghostery also gives you the hints to learn about the objects that are "of interest" to you includes the privacy policy useful links other.
Ghostery for Firefox comes with the option to block any elements of this, including ads, cookies, tracking, analysis, social extensions and more. You can select the items to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Windows Movie Maker 2025 v10.0.0.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 22:54:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-movie-maker-4542.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-movie-maker-4542.html
</guid><description>
Windows Movie Maker is a video editing app that allows you to transform images, audio files and short clips into full movies. It accepts all types of media, including photos from digital cameras, flash cards, mobile phone and DVD. With this helpful program, it's easy to sort and select the photos and videos you want to use in the next film of his. You can also add text, transitions, effects, etc. change as much as you want or let Windows Movie Maker do it for you.
Windows Movie Maker -...
</description></item><item><title>Download Photo Supreme 2025.3.3.8094</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 22:54:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photo-supreme-430.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photo-supreme-430.html
</guid><description>
Photo Supreme is a software product management professional pictures of idimager. With Photo Supreme you can arrange, manage back stock photo archive of yourself and share them with you here and relatives easily via Email or Facebook. Photo Supreme provides users method to sort images effective, logical, as well as edit and share your photos with friends and relatives in the family. Especially the Photo Supreme allows to work with multiple image formats and support mounting support,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Kindle for PC 2.8.70980</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 22:54:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kindle-for-pc-6655.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kindle-for-pc-6655.html
</guid><description>
Kindle for PC is a handy and handy application that you can use to read a Kindle book with a computer without a Kindle device. To use it, you need to have an Amazon account registered, as the app will prompt you to log in as soon as the startup starts. Simple interface, which allows you to browse through your book library and manage your collections.
Features of Kindle for PC
	The navigation is so easy, because the entry can help you move to the desired chapter and you can use the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Red Gate SmartAssembly Professional 8.3.8.6565</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 22:53:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-red-gate-smartassembly-1593.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-red-gate-smartassembly-1593.html
</guid><description>
Red Gate SmartAssembly is a tool that helps protect your application against reverse engineering or modifications prevent side Tuesday access to source code. This comprehensive solution protects the data card of you and more likely to report errors. This program makes files difficult can disassemble and injection code does not use, to help engineer can reverse and understand the core structure of the code. With your smartphone, you will have many features to tamper with the code as the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Lesspain Kyno Premium 1.9.0.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 22:52:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lesspain-kyno-premium-3732.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lesspain-kyno-premium-3732.html
</guid><description>
Lesspain Kyno Premium is an app for managing multi-media smart allows you to manage, sift and transfer the code means for free adjustment according to the process of your work. Preview, check and arrange your photos from all your cameras quickly on set or in post, even in a group. Quickly find and organize the media files on the drive reduce load or stored your. Immediate use without training or studying the documentation.
Lesspain Kyno Premium - multimedia Manager
Browse videos...
</description></item><item><title>Download Windows Video Editor Pro 2025 v10.0.0.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 22:51:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-video-editor-6420.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-video-editor-6420.html
</guid><description>
Windows Video Editor is the 2021 editing tool collection that has everything you need to edit your video file. You can easily Cut, Crop, Rotate, Split, Trim or Join your videos. You can add Effects, Text, Animations, Watermarks, Subtitles, Music to your videos. You can adjust video speed, brightness, contrast, saturation or anything else of your videos. You can do almost everything to edit your videos! And You can edit videos in batch!
Features of Windows Video Editor
	With Windows...
</description></item></channel></rss>