<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 18:05:36 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 18:05:36 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download EaseUS PDF Editor Pro 6.3.2.5 Build 02022026</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 19:12:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-pdf-editor-pro-7123.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-pdf-editor-pro-7123.html
</guid><description>
EaseUS PDF Editor Pro is an all-in-one PDF reader and generator that allows you to modify PDF files easily. With the help of this program, you can create and edit PDF files from many common files including images and Microsoft Office documents. Speaking of editing, it allows you to insert, delete, reorder, extract or crop a PDF file as you want. In addition, you can insert footers and headers or add page numbers to the PDF instantly.
Features of EaseUS PDF Editor Pro:
	Convert PDF...
</description></item><item><title>Download Edraw Max Ultimate 15.1.3.1475</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 19:12:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-edraw-max-1121.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-edraw-max-1121.html
</guid><description>
Edraw Max is software draw professional looking diagrams help simplify creating diagrams, organization charts, network diagrams, business presentations, building plans, mind mapping, illustration, science, fashion designs, UML diagrams , workflows, program structure diagrams, web design diagrams, electrical engineering, directional maps, diagrams, databases, and more.
Edraw Max - Draw professional looking diagrams
EdrawSoft Edraw Max use software mapping best suits what you know and...
</description></item><item><title>Download WonderFox DVD Video Converter 31.3</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 19:11:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wonderfox-dvd-video-converter-189.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wonderfox-dvd-video-converter-189.html
</guid><description>
WonderFox DVD Video Converter is a software to convert Video DVD to the Video format the other with fast speed. Convenient program to convert the popular video formats and movie DVD, download WonderFox DVD Video Converter below. You can create videos that will be optimized for viewing on mobile devices. There is a simple video editor, it will allow you to add effects, crop photos, and etc.
WonderFox DVD Video Converter
WonderFox DVD Video Converter support rip DVD and videos to various...
</description></item><item><title>Download Freemake Video Converter Gold 5.0.0.34</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 19:10:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-freemake-video-converter-gold-167.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-freemake-video-converter-gold-167.html
</guid><description>
Freemake Video Converter Gold is a software to help convert tail high quality videos with many different formats on many devices. Freemake Video Converter - convert video to AVI, MP4, WMV, MKV, 3GP, DVD, MP3, iPad, iPhone, PSP, Android phone. Video to MP3 just with one click! Rip and burn DVD. Convert YouTube to MP4, AVI, etc. with Freemake! Results guaranteed. Freemake Video Converter has fast conversion speed, guarantee the output quality,support create HTML5 videos have the embed code...
</description></item><item><title>Download WebMinds Hard Drive Optimizer 1.9.0.12</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 19:10:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hard-drive-optimizer-7835.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hard-drive-optimizer-7835.html
</guid><description>
Hard Drive Optimizer is a software that optimizes your hard drive, with it you will quickly recover free disk space! The job of this program is to find the biggest files on your hard drive and delete the ones you don't need easily.
Features of Hard Drive Optimizer
	Hard Drive Optimizer provides the fastest and easiest way to free up your hard drive and free up precious space.
	Scan your hard drive or any folder on your computer for large files that are eating up disk space.
	Review...
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow QR Code Maker 4.1.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 19:09:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qr-code-maker-9760.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qr-code-maker-9760.html
</guid><description>
QR Code Maker is a simple app to generate QR Code for text, link, email, Whatsapp, SMS, Call and Wifi. With QR Codes, you have complete flexibility, because only a short URL points to the encrypted content. So you can modify the links or stored files without having to generate and reprint the Codes. This will save resources and allow you to respond to any campaign changes as quickly as possible.
Features of QR Code Maker
	Generate QR Code for Text, Link, Email, Whatsapp, SMS, Call and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Diffchecker 6.7.8</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 19:09:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-diffchecker-5025.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-diffchecker-5025.html
</guid><description>
Diffchecker is a application compare text, images and powerful file to desktop of your. Available for Windows, macOS. Compare text files, documents, PDF. Compare photos, graphics. Because Diffchecker Desktop running entirely on your computer, so it does not have to communicate with our servers to create your difference. This means that there is no other way in addition you can view your sensitive data, you.
Diffchecker Desktop run offline, that means you can use it anytime, anywhere and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Visual Studio Code 1.109.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 16:27:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-visual-studio-code-3182.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-visual-studio-code-3182.html
</guid><description>
Visual Studio Code is the encryption tool of Microsoft has met most of the needs of the developer. Environment this encoding was introduced to compete with other products such as Sublime and Nodepad ++ . Microsoft, in its new product, has not been released in many years, has provided many features in a simple environment. In addition to the familiar with a dozen programming languages, the syntax and get to know coding language as soon as be encrypted and allows for syntax highlighting, it...
</description></item><item><title>Download Light Image Resizer 7.5.1.147</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 16:26:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-light-image-resizer-945.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-light-image-resizer-945.html
</guid><description>
Light Image Resizer or also known as VSO Image Resizer. This is a software support thumbnail resolution images or move images in your hard drive. Light Image Resizer helps people store photos and digital images on their PC and who want to resize, compress, convert, create copies, import or organize photos. Light Image Resizer is integrated into Windows Explorer, right-click on your pictures and start working on your photos.
Light Image Resizer - miniature high-resolution photos and sort...
</description></item><item><title>Download CyberLink PhotoDirector Ultra 2026 v17.1.1330.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 16:25:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-photodirector-ultra-129.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-photodirector-ultra-129.html
</guid><description>
Cyberlink PhotoDirector Ultra is known to be photo editing tools and videos with the effect is extremely rich, help you to change the style for the individual images or the videos of his favorite. This software integrated the 3D engine helps to speed up Video processing, which allows accessing the repository effect online and extract the Videos into the movies 3D Bru-ray, 3D AVCHD.
Cyberlink PhotoDirector Ultra to offer users a more professional tool to handle their images, remove...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sysinternals Suite 2026.2.4</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 16:25:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sysinternals-suite-1447.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sysinternals-suite-1447.html
</guid><description>
Sysinternals Suite is a software monitoring and control system helps to find and fix errors most impressive. The software includes more than seventy utilities aimed at overcoming the problem related to managing files and disks, network problems and security, as well as information about processes and systems. Because of this very rich, the analysis of each ministry will take a significant period of time and therefore, we decided to focus on the most popular.
Sysinternals Suite - Set of...
</description></item><item><title>Download RapidRAW 1.4.12</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 16:24:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rapidraw-13957.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rapidraw-13957.html
</guid><description>
RapidRAW is a modern, high-performance, open-source RAW photo editor, designed to deliver a fast and clean editing experience with a lightweight footprint (under 30MB). Built with performance and usability in mind, the software is aimed at photographers who want a simple, efficient, and fun workflow without compromising performance.
Key Features
	GPU-accelerated processing: Uses a custom WGSL shader to process all image adjustments on the GPU, allowing for smooth, responsive editing...
</description></item><item><title>Download O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Premium 22.4.1206</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 16:23:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-diskimage-server-4547.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-diskimage-server-4547.html
</guid><description>
O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Server is software that is specially designed for use in enterprise environments, the software allows users to backup all the files you want and keep them safe from any incident or disaster computer. O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Server comes with a variety of easy to use utility that allows users to backup entire partitions of the specific files from their PC, as well as recover the version previous data of them, all from a simple interface.
O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Server - data...
</description></item><item><title>Download UWPSpy 1.5</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 16:23:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-uwpspy-10357.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-uwpspy-10357.html
</guid><description>
UWPSpy is a testing tool for UWP and WinUI 3 applications. Seamlessly view and manipulate UI elements and their properties in real time.
It allows users to observe how changes affect the structure and functionality of their UWP app. This is beneficial for helping with user interface design tasks during application development. When you select specific properties, the associated elements will be highlighted and any changes will update in real time.
How to use:
	Run UWPSpy.exe and...
</description></item><item><title>Download VectorStyler 1.3.009</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 16:22:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vectorstyler-7917.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vectorstyler-7917.html
</guid><description>
VectorStyler provides a complete set of drawing, design and illustration tools needed for modern design. Create illustrations, logos, icons, drawings, typography, vector art for screen, print and web. With many new features, VectorStyler redefines and extends the tools available to illustrators and designers, improving the creation of complex illustrations and designs.
Shape effects can be used to adjust the shape of objects, create different distortions, or add detail to shapes. Shape...
</description></item><item><title>Download PlayerFab (Ultra HD Player) 7.0.5.5</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 16:22:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dvdfab-player-ultra-68.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dvdfab-player-ultra-68.html
</guid><description>
PlayerFab (DVDFab Player Ultra) is one of the best 4K UHD media players. The software plays DVD, Blu-ray, 4K Ultra HD Blu-ray and also supports online video. It supports native navigation menus, along with HDR10, and supports high-resolution audio output. PlayerFab supports watching videos of a variety of popular streaming platforms such as Amazon, Netflix, Tubi, Peacock, and more.
Video streaming in FHD 1080p video quality and high quality EAC3 audio quality is the prerequisite and...
</description></item><item><title>Download lessmsi 2.11.9</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 16:22:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lessmsi-12392.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lessmsi-12392.html
</guid><description>
Lessmsi (Less MSIerables) is a free and portable application that allows users to view and extract the contents of MSI files.
How does it work? Files with the .msi extension are not as widely used as their .exe cousins, but both contain programs for Windows. The main difference between them is that the latter does not always come with an installer, while it comes standard with the former. However, there will be cases where you just need to view or want to extract specific content from...
</description></item><item><title>Download Trillian 6.6 Build 11</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 16:21:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-trillian-2638.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-trillian-2638.html
</guid><description>
Trillian is the chat help you sign in to more the registered name of a certain service or you can log on at the same time many services in a working window. It integrates multiple services such as Yahoo! MSN, IRC, AIM and ICQ. In addition, you can manage Email accounts, Facebook and Twitter friends - all in just one application.
Login is easy; just click on the network or the appropriate website and log in as normal. Trillian requires access your data (accepted) and post to friends...
</description></item><item><title>Download Free YouTube Download 4.5.5.204 Premium</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 16:21:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-download-1177.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-download-1177.html
</guid><description>
Free YouTube Download Premium is the most popular application to download videos from YouTube. The program was released in 2006 and regularly updated since then. Use the program to download and convert YouTube videos to view offline anytime.
Free YouTube Download - added Support to download youtube
Download more videos! Save whole playlists and YouTube channels, videos from a playlist individually (history, video be favorite, favourites, Watch later), videos from many different...
</description></item><item><title>Download WindowManager 10.25</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 16:20:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desksoft-windowmanager-573.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desksoft-windowmanager-573.html
</guid><description>
WindowManager is a software by DeskSoft dedicated to providing software utilities for windows. DeskSoft WindowManager is the window manager window to ensure your windows are placed exactly where you want. Software will help you to help you improve your work flow by remembering and restoring the position and size of the program and your window. The processing window can completely customize and you can set the special rules for the windows favorite or used most often.
WindowManager send...
</description></item><item><title>Download EmEditor Pro 26.0.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 16:19:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-emeditor-pro-69.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-emeditor-pro-69.html
</guid><description>
EmEditor Pro - the professional version of editor text powerful for programmers, web developers and ordinary users with illumination of syntax and Unicode support. The features of the editor such as search and replace in files using regular expressions, automatic code detect, bookmark link and address email, block selection mode, configure the button bar, menu, font and elements color. With each language you can set separate configuration.
EmEditor Pro - text Editor professional
The...
</description></item><item><title>Download Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium 4.5.5.204</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 16:19:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-to-mp3-converter-premium-844.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-to-mp3-converter-premium-844.html
</guid><description>
Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium version is a software used to convert YouTube to MP3, extract audio from playlists YouTube, show listings, charts, video responses, channels, favorites of the user. With Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium, you can download and convert playlists, channels, stream original tv series and get them into iTunes at the same time.
Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium - convert YouTube to MP3
Features Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium from the...
</description></item><item><title>Download VCap Downloader Pro 0.1.44.6930</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 16:18:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vcap-downloader-pro-8474.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vcap-downloader-pro-8474.html
</guid><description>
VCap Downloader Pro (VCapDL) is a popular piece of software that allows you to record video and audio from websites on the internet. The interface of the software is similar to a normal browser, making it easy for users to get used to and work with this software. User just need to copy video url from favorite browser and convert it to VCap Downloader Pro. It will capture the video and make the quality available for download. You can also extract the audio track from any video and convert...
</description></item><item><title>Download Universal USB Installer 2.0.3.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 16:18:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-universal-usb-installer-3140.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-universal-usb-installer-3140.html
</guid><description>
Universal USB Installer is a software to create a USB Linux that will give you the ability to choose from a large selection of Linux distributions to create bootable USB Flash Drives. the software is intuitive and easy to use, allowing you to simply choose a distribution Live Linux, your flash drive and the ISO file and make USB drive bootable with just a single mouse click. When the task finishes, you will get USB Flash Drive ready to accommodate Linux distributions have chosen. This...
</description></item><item><title>Download Unicodia 3.0.9</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 16:17:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-unicodia-8521.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-unicodia-8521.html
</guid><description>
Unicodia is free, open source software that can be used as an alternative character map for your Windows machine. The interface contains everything you need, allowing you to easily cycle through all the available ASCII symbols and copy them to the clipboard. Uncicodia is a great alternative to your standard Unicode characters and is filled with symbols/characters that make it useful for a number of different uses.
Features of Unicodia
	In Windows 10/11 — all characters of Unicode 15...
</description></item></channel></rss>