<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 20:15:21 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 20:15:21 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download BandiView Pro (Honeyview) 7.25</title><pubDate> Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:22:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-honeyview-4871.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-honeyview-4871.html
</guid><description>
HoneyView is an image viewer, comic book archive support with formats such as zip, cbz, rar....and support the photo format display, such as JPG, GIF, TIFF, PNG,... can see the photos automatically change after a period of time, adjust the time from 1 to 90 seconds and the options like repeat or random. In addition, support photo editing basics like rotate, add effects, zoom and pan or zoom display frame.
Features of HoneyView
	Operating system supported: Windows XP / Vista / 7/8 /...
</description></item><item><title>Download XYplorer 28.20.0000</title><pubDate> Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:22:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-533.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-533.html
</guid><description>
XYplorer - File Manager for Windows is software that supports users to manage files on the Window quickly and to arrange the folder tidy. XYplorer features tabbed browsing, search, files, powerful, preview, flexible, highly customizable interface, dual frame options and a variety of unique ways to automate effective tasks often repeat. It's fast, lightweight, and portable.
Features XYplorer
	XYplorer is a file manager mobile. It does not require any settings, store all configuration...
</description></item><item><title>Download Folder Guard Professional 26.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:21:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-folder-guard-professional-1314.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-folder-guard-professional-1314.html
</guid><description>
Folder Guard Professional (The most professional) software includes password computer folder to help you control access to files, folders and the Windows resource. Folder Guard to lock files and folders, your personal password to stop other users from peeking into your records.  You can even completely hide the private folder of his from almost all the apps and the folders that will be hidden until you enter the valid password. You can also protect files sensitive system from modification...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ableton Live Suite 12.3.5</title><pubDate> Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:20:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ableton-live-suite-663.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ableton-live-suite-663.html
</guid><description>
Ableton Live Suite is professional software to create, edit, music with effects, instruments, audio and all creative. Ableton Live Suite is the software fast, flexible and flexibility to create and perform music. Move freely between the musical elements and play with ideas, that don't stop the music and do not break the flow of your sound.
Features, Ableton Live Suite
	Meet Wavetable, Echo, Drum Buss and Pedal: the new equipment means new sounds, colorful can with the instruments and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Display Driver Uninstaller (DDU) 18.1.4.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:20:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-display-driver-uninstaller-1999.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-display-driver-uninstaller-1999.html
</guid><description>
Display Driver Uninstaller (DDU) help to easily completely remove the packages and drivers graphics cards AMD, NVIDIA and Intel from your system without leaving any rest whatsoever. Display Driver Uninstaller will automatically detect your current GPU and allows you to delete drivers, registry and files related only by the click of a button. It will also prevent Windows automatically re-install drivers when you reboot your computer, leaving you a drivers graphics common until you install...
</description></item><item><title>Download QOwnNotes 26.1.12</title><pubDate> Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:19:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qownnotes-3178.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qownnotes-3178.html
</guid><description>
QOwnNotes is notes bookmark file simple text (GPL) open source application for GNU / Linux , Mac OS X and Windows of Patrizio Bekerle ( pbek on GitHub and IRC) (optional) activity along with the notes application of ownCloud or Nextcloud. QOwnNote store your notes as plain text files and can be synchronized with synchronization function file of ownCloud / Nextcloud. You can also use other apps like Syncthing or Dropbox . Just write out your thoughts as they appear, and edit them if...
</description></item><item><title>Download UPDF 2.1.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:19:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-updf-14160.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-updf-14160.html
</guid><description>
UPDF for Windows is easy-to-use PDF software for Windows! Enjoy powerful editing tools for text, images, links, and more in your PDFs. Customize backgrounds, watermarks, and page sizes as easily as in Word. AI-powered PDF editor and manager that offers a wide range of features including editing, annotating, converting, OCR (Optical Character Recognition), organizing, protecting, sharing, printing, summarizing, translating, and interpreting PDF files.
Features of UPDF
Analyze PDFs with...
</description></item><item><title>Download AutoDWG DWGSee Pro 2027 v6.61</title><pubDate> Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:19:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-autodwg-dwgsee-pro-3589.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-autodwg-dwgsee-pro-3589.html
</guid><description>
AutoDWG DWGSee Pro is a software compact and lightweight to display and print the files DWG / DXF / DWF. This small program supports the file CAD AutoCAD R2.5 until 2017 and really display any type of file CAD how. AutoDWG DWGSee Pro provides a comprehensive solution for displaying, measuring, and in the design of AutoCAD to create, especially for those who do not have system strong and need to show quick file CAD of heavy duty software such as AutoCAD. To open. This program offers users...
</description></item><item><title>Download VidMasta 29.9</title><pubDate> Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:18:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vidmasta-6803.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vidmasta-6803.html
</guid><description>
VidMasta is a free and open source online movie downloading and viewing software. It allows you to easily watch or download movie/TV titles in any format with just a few clicks. VidMasta gives full control over downloading, searching, reading about, previewing and watching any movie or TV show title currently being shared online.
In addition, VidMasta provides you with solid anonymity through automatic filtering of untrusted IPs, the use of proxies and encryption, as well as the "Best...
</description></item><item><title>Download RapidRAW 1.4.10</title><pubDate> Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:18:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rapidraw-13957.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rapidraw-13957.html
</guid><description>
RapidRAW is a modern, high-performance, open-source RAW photo editor, designed to deliver a fast and clean editing experience with a lightweight footprint (under 30MB). Built with performance and usability in mind, the software is aimed at photographers who want a simple, efficient, and fun workflow without compromising performance.
Key Features
	GPU-accelerated processing: Uses a custom WGSL shader to process all image adjustments on the GPU, allowing for smooth, responsive editing...
</description></item><item><title>Download TidyWindow 4.2.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:17:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tidywindow-14454.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tidywindow-14454.html
</guid><description>
TidyWindow is a Windows desktop assistant that automates developer PC setup, cleanup, diagnostics, software package installation, registry tweaking, and driver updates—powered by a WPF interface and robust PowerShell 7 automation capabilities in the background.
Key Features
	Essentials Repair Center (docs/essentials.md): Queues selected automation tasks Filter for network, Defender, printing, and Windows Update issues. Each task supports preview run, sequential execution, restore...
</description></item><item><title>Download AssistMyTeam PDF Editor 7.2.300.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:16:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-assistmyteam-pdf-editor-14175.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-assistmyteam-pdf-editor-14175.html
</guid><description>
The AssistMyTeam PDF Editor add-on integrates your Windows Explorer with a PDF editor, organizer, splitter, merger, file extractor, and even a viewer with instant one-click operation.
What sets this application apart from most other bloated, complex commercial PDF applications is its relative ease of use and efficiency with a simple, minimalistic, yet intuitive and unobtrusive interface – just right-click on the file in the browser window and perform the operation of your choice on your...
</description></item><item><title>Download MakeMKV 1.18.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:14:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-makemkv-3126.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-makemkv-3126.html
</guid><description>
MakeMKV is the solution a click of your mouse to convert video that you own into free format and the patent can be found everywhere. MakeMKV is a format converter, otherwise called "transcoder". It converts the video clips from disc proprietary (and usually encrypted) into a set of files MKV, keeping most information but not changing it in any way. MKV format can store more music / video with all the meta information and retention programs. There are many the player can playback files MKV...
</description></item><item><title>Download Advanced Installer Architect 23.4.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:13:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-installer-128.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-installer-128.html
</guid><description>
Advanced Installer is a Windows utility designed to help you build the package Windows Installer in a working environment clean and intuitive.
Although it has many parameters dedicated but the user interface is very simple and gives users the ability to create new projects by selecting the type, namely installer (for example: application Visual Studio or .NET, pack 32/64-bit mixture), Java , updates, support, mobile devices, and other things.
Advanced Installer - An environment for...
</description></item><item><title>Download AnyTrans for iOS 8.9.14.20260126</title><pubDate> Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:07:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anytrans-for-ios-755.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anytrans-for-ios-755.html
</guid><description>
AnyTrans for iOS is content manager essential fully managed iPhone, Android and content of your cloud. Including all mobile devices, all cloud drives from your iPhone, iPad, iPod touch to phones and tablets. From local disk to cloud storage. AnyTrans has protected them all, providing you convenient management for all data and your files, regardless of whether they are stored where.
AnyTrans is the one stop solution to meet all the management needs of your data. For the first time, you can...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Downloader 10.1.8</title><pubDate> Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:00:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html
</guid><description>
YTD Youtube Downloader is an application that reliable and intuitive, allowing you to quickly download YouTube videos and save them to your computer. You can also convert the media files to the format desired video or extract audio streams and save separately. YTD Youtube Downloader lets you save your favorite clips of yourself from Youtube, Facebook, Vimeo and Dailymotion to your desktop. The software supports URLS from many web site hosting, multimedia and allows you to download desired...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Saver Pro 10.13.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:00:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-saver-6830.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-saver-6830.html
</guid><description>
YT Saver is a software that supports downloading Video, Audio, Playlist from 10,000+ websites, Convert Video to MP4, MOV, AAC, WAV and more. YT Saver is a powerful downloader that allows you to save video and audio for free. The output format of the high-speed converter is high-quality MP4, MP3. Fully compatible with iPhone, iPad, iTunes, iMovie, Android Phone and more.
Supported Input Formats:
	Video: MP4, M4V, 3GP, MPEG, DAT, AVI, ASF, WMV, VOB, MKV, FLV, 3GS, 3G2, F4V, WEBM, TS,...
</description></item><item><title>Download ExamXML Pro 5.58 Build 1097</title><pubDate> Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:59:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-examxml-pro-2482.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-examxml-pro-2482.html
</guid><description>
ExamXML Pro is a tool to distinguish XML powerful, intuitive and easy to use for Windows. It is specially developed for comparing and merging XML files in an intelligent way. It offers features best-in-class to distinguish ExamXML with the tools to distinguish XML other. Unique to ExamXML is its ability to ignore the elements match the condition the user-defined. In addition to the comparison of normal text, ExamXML adds ability to compare numbers in numeric format and dates in date / time...
</description></item><item><title>Download PureBasic 6.30 LTS</title><pubDate> Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:59:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-purebasic-7857.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-purebasic-7857.html
</guid><description>
PureBasic is a modern, cross-platform environment for developing and debugging programs and games in BASIC, allowing you to create applications for the Windows platform, Linux, MacOS X and AmigaOS for Intel/AMD x86 and x64 processors, as well as for ARM 32 and ARM 64. The environment includes a cross-platform library containing more than 1800 functions. Their description can be found in the help (press F1 when PureBasic is running) or in the online help. Among them are functions for...
</description></item><item><title>Download Godot Game Engine 4.6</title><pubDate> Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:58:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-godot-engine-10493.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-godot-engine-10493.html
</guid><description>
Godot Engine is a feature-rich, cross-platform game engine for creating 2D and 3D games from a unified interface. It provides a comprehensive set of common tools so users can focus on game creation without having to reinvent the wheel. Games can be exported with a single click to several platforms, including major desktop platforms (Linux, macOS, Windows), mobile platforms (Android, iOS), as well as Web-based platform and dashboard.
Supported platforms:
Godot Engine, used to create...
</description></item><item><title>Download AOM Total Bundle 1.18.9</title><pubDate> Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:57:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aom-total-bundle-8859.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aom-total-bundle-8859.html
</guid><description>
A.O.M Total Bundle is a set of powerful plugins that can be used for a variety of audio processing tasks. The plugins are designed to be transparent and of high quality, with a focus on achieving professional results without creating unwanted artifacts or distortions. This package is great for mixing and mastering engineers, sound designers, and producers looking for a comprehensive set of tools for audio processing and manipulation.
Features of A.O.M Total Bundle
	Invisible Limiter:...
</description></item><item><title>Download iDownerGo 10.13.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:57:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idownergo-12439.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idownergo-12439.html
</guid><description>
iDownerGo is the best tool that allows users to download videos, music and playlists from more than 10,000 streaming sites. It can easily convert videos to MP4, MOV, MKV, 3GP, AAC, WAV, FLAC and other formats on PC and Mac. With this amazing program, users can enjoy their favorite media content without restrictions.
iDownerGo Features
	Download any video up to 8K resolution
	Download 1080p videos online from over 10,000 popular streaming sites easily.
	Save any video in various...
</description></item><item><title>Download Karaosoft KJ/DJ File Manager 4.0.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:56:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kj-file-manager-2378.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kj-file-manager-2378.html
</guid><description>
KJ File Manager is a program that will allow you to easily manage the audio and video files in karaoke format, you can now record MP3 tags ID and edit metadata information, done all in batch mode.
Easily manage files karaoke, video and audio of you and fixes title easily with batch editing powerful. Support the format name standard most popular. Automatic fix for underscores and capitalization, swap title and artist, shift, split, and replace field data on multiple files at once,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Karaosoft Karma 2026.1.26</title><pubDate> Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:55:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-karma-2379.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-karma-2379.html
</guid><description>
Karma is an enhancement program that helps you tune, karaoke can view the text of the files sound different. At first glance, after launch, the layout may seem complicated, unclear where to start. You can customize the display prompts to understand the function of each parameter is highlighted integrated.
Management program your karaoke a easy way. Search no need to click, drag and drop feature and many other unique features designed to bring you the easiest management for the program...
</description></item><item><title>Download PPTube 10.13.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:55:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pptube-12556.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pptube-12556.html
</guid><description>
PPTube Video Downloader allows you to download HD videos easily, from 720p, 1080p, 2K, 4K and 8K. You can save multiple videos at the same time. Just copy multiple video URLs from various websites and paste them into PPTube Downloader, then you can download multiple videos in seconds.
In addition, you can download HD videos from Instagram, TikTok, Facebook, Apple Music, Vimeo, adult websites, etc. and convert them to MP4, MP3, MOV, AAC and more than 20 other output formats. PPTube...
</description></item></channel></rss>