<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 10:23:51 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 10:23:51 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download lessmsi 2.11.10</title><pubDate> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 00:26:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lessmsi-12392.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lessmsi-12392.html
</guid><description>
Lessmsi (Less MSIerables) is a free and portable application that allows users to view and extract the contents of MSI files.
How does it work? Files with the .msi extension are not as widely used as their .exe cousins, but both contain programs for Windows. The main difference between them is that the latter does not always come with an installer, while it comes standard with the former. However, there will be cases where you just need to view or want to extract specific content from...
</description></item><item><title>Download RepairKit 1.3.8</title><pubDate> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 00:26:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-repairkit-11968.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-repairkit-11968.html
</guid><description>
RepairKit is an all-in-one Java-based Windows repair and maintenance toolkit. RepairKit aims to provide a package that provides users with a dedicated system repair tool as well as quick access to some operating system features and some other PC maintenance software that comes with it. it.
If you want to keep your PC running smoothly and want to do it conveniently, RepairKit offers a simple and effective solution for that, with an automatic repair/cleanup module , as well as access to...
</description></item><item><title>Download GeoGebra 6.0.915</title><pubDate> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 20:20:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-geogebra-992.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-geogebra-992.html
</guid><description>
GeoGebra is software the mathematics on the computer for you to solve problems more quickly and accurately data problem given. GeoGebra supports connect geometry, algebra and elements of mathematics other in an interactive way and tight. Besides, GeoGebra also allows users to directly enter and manipulate mathematical equations and coordinates, and make use of the points, vector, lines, triangles, cones..
GeoGebra - graph the function
GeoGebra is designed for math classes in junior...
</description></item><item><title>Download VidMasta 30.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 19:17:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vidmasta-6803.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vidmasta-6803.html
</guid><description>
VidMasta is a free and open source online movie downloading and viewing software. It allows you to easily watch or download movie/TV titles in any format with just a few clicks. VidMasta gives full control over downloading, searching, reading about, previewing and watching any movie or TV show title currently being shared online.
In addition, VidMasta provides you with solid anonymity through automatic filtering of untrusted IPs, the use of proxies and encryption, as well as the "Best...
</description></item><item><title>Download ExifTool 13.50</title><pubDate> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 19:17:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-exiftool-1685.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-exiftool-1685.html
</guid><description>
ExifTool is a library of Perl platform-independent plus a command line application for reading, writing, and editing meta information in various file types. ExifTool supports many metadata formats including EXIF , GPS , IPTC , XMP , JFIF , GeoTIFF , ICC Profile , Photoshop IRB , FlashPix , AFCP and ID3 , as well as notes of the manufacturer of many digital cameras by Canon , Casio , DJI , FLIR , FujiFilm , GE , GoPro , HP , JVC / Victor , Kodak , Leaf , Minolta / Konica-Minolta , Motorola...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Acrobat Pro DC 2025.001.21184 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 19:13:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-001en-adobe-acrobat-pro-458.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-001en-adobe-acrobat-pro-458.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Acrobat Pro DC is a comprehensive software that helps you create and edit the PDF&amp;nbsp;document, or create form, sign, protect PDF, connect, split PDF, export PDF to various formats. The Acrobat Pro DC is the latest version of Adobe with improvements in the interface with the polished ribbon bar and the ability to create and handle pdf files as well as its male versions.
The highlight of the Acrobat Pro DC is probably the ability to connect, store documents on the cloud, you can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Autodesk 3ds Max 2026.3.2 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 19:11:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-autodesk-3ds-max-0001-1273.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-autodesk-3ds-max-0001-1273.html
</guid><description>
Autodesk 3ds Max 2024 provides a tool powerful, integrated three-dimensional modeling, animation, rendering, and synthesis to work with speed and efficiency. Autodesk 3ds Max provides innovative methods to build and texture models, accumulated data, forming character and creating high quality images. Application for three-dimensional environments, animated, rendered, and combined Autodesk 3ds Max is designed for professionals graphics and computer animation, who developed computer games,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wise Care 365 Pro 7.3.5.722</title><pubDate> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 19:10:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wise-care-365-pro-106.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wise-care-365-pro-106.html
</guid><description>
Wise Care 365 pro is a package of utilities registry, disk, and other systems important for your PC. Easy to use and effective, Wise Care 365 is the best solution to improve the performance of your computer. Get Wise Care 365 and your computer will never run slow again!
Wise Care 365 pro is what?
Wise Care 365 Pro
	Check PC a clicks
	Pc cleaning &amp;amp; speed up
	Inventory hardware
	Protecting your privacy
	Protect real-time system
	Silent mode
	Boot speed faster
	Freeing up disk...
</description></item><item><title>Download TubeDownload Pro 7.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 19:06:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubedownload-pro-12035.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubedownload-pro-12035.html
</guid><description>
TubeDownload Pro is a professional Windows application for downloading your favorite videos from YouTube and hundreds of other video sites. TubeDownload Pro can increase download speed up to 500% or even more.
Features of TubeDownload Pro
	Download your favorite videos from YouTube and hundreds of other video sites.
	Increase download speed up to 500% or even more.
	Download 720p, 1080p, 2K, 4K and 8K HD videos from YouTube.
	Download entire playlists in just a few clicks.
	Download...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT-DL 12.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 19:05:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-dl-5876.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-dl-5876.html
</guid><description>
YT-DL is a small program to download videos from YouTube and other video sites. Our goal is to make the program as simple as its name.
The features of YT-DL
	Download the video from YouTube and other video sites
	Increase download speed up to 400%
	Download multiple videos at the same time
	Pause and continue to download at any time
	Preview video content while downloading
</description></item><item><title>Download GetWindowText 5.29</title><pubDate> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 19:05:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-getwindowtext-2844.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-getwindowtext-2844.html
</guid><description>
GetWindowText is a program that is small and portable that you can read text on windows. It can be read almost all the texts, e.g. from edit, Static, groupbox - controls, etc. this Program also supports directory trees (SysTreeView32), combo box and list view (SysListView32) to read the entire content. When you release the mouse button, the reading will end.
GetWindowText - Read the text on windows
"GetWindowText" no need to be installed and can be executed easily from the desktop....
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Geek YTDL Pro 12.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 19:04:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-geek-ytdl-pro-9895.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-geek-ytdl-pro-9895.html
</guid><description>
YT Geek YTDL Pro is software that helps users easily download videos from YouTube and hundreds of other video sites. It is very easy to use, just paste the video URL and you can download the video while keeping the original quality. Not only videos on Youtube, users can download any video from social networking sites like Facebook, Vimeo, Myspace video,...
Features of YT Geek YTDL Pro
	Download videos from YouTube and other video sites.
	Increase download speed up to 400%.
	Download...
</description></item><item><title>Download Calibre 9.2.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 17:22:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-calibre-1669.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-calibre-1669.html
</guid><description>
Calibre  is an eBook library management application that allows you to manage your eBook collection, convert eBooks between different formats, Sync with popular e-reading devices and read your e-books with included viewer. You can sort books by author, title, date and other details, download meta information and book covers, add personalized tags and comments, and view your images in the cover display.
Collection of essential tools for adding metadata editing books or managing your...
</description></item><item><title>Download Gilisoft Watermark Remover 9.0.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 17:21:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-watermark-remover-12261.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-watermark-remover-12261.html
</guid><description>
Gilisoft Watermark Remover provides comprehensive solutions to remove watermarks from different types of media. It offers both options to remove watermarks from images and videos. This can be really helpful for people who need to edit or clean up their visual content.
Do you have any specific needs for removing watermarks from images or videos? Maybe you're working on a project or have some personal photos you want to improve. Either way, it's good to have these tools available. Inpaint...
</description></item><item><title>Download AllMapSoft Google Maps Downloader 8.887</title><pubDate> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 17:21:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-google-maps-downloader-2796.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-google-maps-downloader-2796.html
</guid><description>
AllMapSoft Google Maps Downloader is a reliable application aimed at downloading maps from Google at high speed. The result is a set of small images can be combined in a larger map. This can serve in a large variety of projects, from creating a tile map to presentations and tutorials.
Google Maps Downloader successfully fulfills both of those conditions, providing simple means to quickly grab maps at the resolution satisfactory. In addition, it is extremely easy to use and integrated a...
</description></item><item><title>Download ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro 15.26.0207</title><pubDate> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 17:20:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-videotube-downloader-pro-1276.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-videotube-downloader-pro-1276.html
</guid><description>
ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro is the professional version support download videos and playlists from YouTube, videos from Dailymotion, BBC iPlayer, ITV Player, ABC,  FOX,CBS.com Vimeo, Prosieben, Metacafe, Blip.tv CBC.ca many more video sites. After the video is downloaded, you can convert them to the formats compatible with iPad, iPhone, iPod, MPEG-4, H. 264, MP3, AC3.
ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro - Download videos on Youtube
This is one of the software download the most...
</description></item><item><title>Download Worksheet Crafter Premium Edition 2025.2.10.385 + Premium Content Pack</title><pubDate> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 17:20:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-worksheet-crafter-premium-edition-3922.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-worksheet-crafter-premium-edition-3922.html
</guid><description>
Worksheet Crafter Premium Edition helps you to create the form of teaching, worksheet and quiz grade perfect for elementary school students &amp;amp; your special in just a few clicks. Create a spreadsheet of your own in a few clicks. It is interesting to use, tested by 1000 teacher, and as familiar as Microsoft Word. Moreover, Worksheet Crafter Premium Edition has improved the ability to use the equation editor by adding support undo / redo for better editing. In addition, when choosing a...
</description></item><item><title>Download 3D Youtube Downloader 1.26.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 17:20:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-3d-youtube-downloader-1631.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-3d-youtube-downloader-1631.html
</guid><description>
3D Youtube Downloader is application support users to download the videos from Youtube website with great quality. The advantage of this software is the ability to download the videos in 3D, make the download process is fully automated and the download speed is extremely fast. In addition to Youtube, this tool also allows to download videos from many other sites, so users can own any favorite videos yet. 3D Youtube Downloader is a downloads simple but powerful from Youtube, Vimeo,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Intel Extreme Tuning Utility 10.0.1.35</title><pubDate> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 17:19:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intel-extreme-tuning-utility-2664.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intel-extreme-tuning-utility-2664.html
</guid><description>
Intel Extreme Tune Utility (Intel XTU) is a software performance tuning Windows-based simple for beginners and enthusiasts who have the experience to overclocking, monitoring, and stressed system. The software interface shows a set of strong capabilities common in most of the platforms passion along with the special new feature available on Intel® processor and new Motherboard Intel®. Intel Extreme Tune Utility is a great tool to overclock!
Intel Extreme Tuning Utility - overclock,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Any Video Downloader Pro 10.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 17:18:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-video-downloader-pro-3731.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-video-downloader-pro-3731.html
</guid><description>
Any Video Downloader Pro is software support you can download video HD 720p, 1080p, 2K, 4K and 8K from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion, Vimeo, Metacafe and thousands of video sharing sites, other. It is a tool to speed up multi-threading can speed up your download faster up to 5 times. This helpful program support download at the same time. Any Video Downloader Pro lets you download multiple videos at the same time. Moreover, it allows you to pause and resume downloads if you need more...
</description></item><item><title>Download iTubeGo YouTube Downloader 10.14.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 17:18:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-itubego-youtube-downloader-3681.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-itubego-youtube-downloader-3681.html
</guid><description>
iTubeGo YouTube Downloader  is the best way to download live video from 1000+ streaming sites. iTubeGo YouTube Downloader is a powerful download tool that allows you to save video and audio for free. The output format of high speed converter is high quality MP4, MP3. Fully compatible with iPhone, iPad, iTunes, iMovie, Android Phone and more.
iTubeGo YouTube Downloader - Solution for downloading high quality Youtube video 
Features of iTubeGo YouTube Downloader
	Download videos from...
</description></item><item><title>Download VectorStyler 1.3.010</title><pubDate> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 17:17:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vectorstyler-7917.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vectorstyler-7917.html
</guid><description>
VectorStyler provides a complete set of drawing, design and illustration tools needed for modern design. Create illustrations, logos, icons, drawings, typography, vector art for screen, print and web. With many new features, VectorStyler redefines and extends the tools available to illustrators and designers, improving the creation of complex illustrations and designs.
Shape effects can be used to adjust the shape of objects, create different distortions, or add detail to shapes. Shape...
</description></item><item><title>Download ChrisPC Free VPN Connection 4.26.0207</title><pubDate> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 17:17:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-free-vpn-connection-2887.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-free-vpn-connection-2887.html
</guid><description>
ChrisPC Free VPN Connection software allows you to create VPN connection (virtual private network) to the server for free from the United States, Germany, Canada, France, Germany, Russia, Singapore, the Netherlands. This will help you to unblock your favorite sites to watch free TV and on-demand television when living abroad, travelling, on business or vacation. In addition, here is the solution to overcome the limited area for the popular websites: Google, YouTube, Facebook, Instagram,...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Downloader 10.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 17:14:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html
</guid><description>
YTD Youtube Downloader is an application that reliable and intuitive, allowing you to quickly download YouTube videos and save them to your computer. You can also convert the media files to the format desired video or extract audio streams and save separately. YTD Youtube Downloader lets you save your favorite clips of yourself from Youtube, Facebook, Vimeo and Dailymotion to your desktop. The software supports URLS from many web site hosting, multimedia and allows you to download desired...
</description></item><item><title>Download AllMapSoft Universal Maps Downloader 10.235</title><pubDate> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 17:14:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-universal-maps-downloader-736.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-universal-maps-downloader-736.html
</guid><description>
AllMapSoft Universal Maps Downloader is software download map images on the computer for offline viewing support many types such as Google Maps, Yahoo maps, Bing maps, OpenStreet Maps, Yandex Maps, Ovi Maps, MapQuest Maps. All the downloaded photos will be saved on disk. You can view downloaded maps by Maps Viewer Or you can combine them into one big bmp, or jpg file tif by Maps Combiner, and also you can export all the tiles into a database format MBTiles.
AllMapSoft Universal Maps...
</description></item></channel></rss>