<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 13:38:33 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 13:38:33 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download X-plore File Manager 4.44.05</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Sep 2025 16:30:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-x-plore-file-manager-8781.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-x-plore-file-manager-8781.html
</guid><description>
X-plore File Manager is a file management application for Android devices that allows users to browse, manage and organize files and folders on the device's storage as well as on network storage services and clouds. Developed by Lonely Cat Games, X-plore File Manager offers a number of advanced features, making it a popular choice among users who need a powerful and flexible file management solution.
Features of X-plore File Manager
	Two-pane tree view
	Root, FTP, SMB1 / SMB2, Sqlite,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Pulsar Music Player Pro 1.13.7 build 284</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Sep 2025 16:30:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pulsar-music-player-pro-9602.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pulsar-music-player-pro-9602.html
</guid><description>
Pulsar Music Player has long been one of the best music players on Android. It is an ad-free offline audio player. Its beautiful user interface matches every detail of material design principles. Pulsar contains almost every feature needed to satisfy all your musical needs, including: seamless playback, lyrics display, interlacing, playback speed adjustment, tag editing, Last recording .fm, Chromecast, voice command, Android Auto, equalizer, music visualizer, equalizer, ReplayGain, sleep...
</description></item><item><title>Download radio.net PRIME 5.17.5.1-app build 100069</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Sep 2025 16:30:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-radionet-prime-8335.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-radionet-prime-8335.html
</guid><description>
radio.net PRIME is a mobile application that allows users to listen to a variety of radio stations on their Android devices. This app provides access to more than 30,000 radio stations around the world, including local and international stations in a variety of genres and formats.
Features of radio.net PRIME
	Access to more than 30,000 radio stations around the world
	Supports multiple genres and formats, including news, music, sports, and chat
	Option to create a list of favorite...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaMonkey 2.1.0.1274</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Sep 2025 16:29:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-mediamonkey-8211.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-mediamonkey-8211.html
</guid><description>
MediaMonkey APK is a media player and management application for Android devices. MediaMonkey lets you organize and play music, podcasts, and audiobooks on your device. It supports multiple audio formats and has a built-in equalizer, sleep timer, and customizable interface.
MediaMonkey can also sync your music library with other devices, including Windows and Mac computers, and allows you to create playlists and play music on a variety of devices. This app is a great way to organize and...
</description></item><item><title>Download SnapTube for Android 7.46.1.74675101</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Sep 2025 16:29:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-snaptube-youtube-downloader-hd-video-8351.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-snaptube-youtube-downloader-hd-video-8351.html
</guid><description>
SnapTube is a mobile application that allows users to download videos from various platforms, such as YouTube, Vimeo, and Dailymotion. It provides video resolution in multiple formats 144p, 720p, 1080p HD, 2K HD, 4K HD and audio formats MP3 and M4A. With Snaptube, users can search for content across all their platforms without using multiple apps.
Features of SnapTube for Android
Download in multiple resolutions
	MP4 videos are available in resolutions: choose small 360 pixels or...
</description></item><item><title>Download 3C All-in-One Toolbox 3.1.1a</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Sep 2025 16:29:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-3c-all-in-one-toolbox-8399.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-3c-all-in-one-toolbox-8399.html
</guid><description>
3C All-in-One Toolbox combines many features into one giant toolbox with a modern and easy-to-use interface. All the tools you need to monitor, control and fine-tune all your Android devices. This app uses the Accessibility service to help you stop the app on non-rooted devices but will never collect any information.
Features of 3C All-in-One Toolbox
	Device Manager offers very powerful configurations, task scheduling, and device watchdogs that you can find to optimize performance and...
</description></item><item><title>Download AppKiller: close apps 4.1.4</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Sep 2025 16:28:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-appkiller-close-apps-11977.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-appkiller-close-apps-11977.html
</guid><description>
AppKiller: close apps allows users to quickly and effectively kill background applications that are consuming system resources, such as RAM and CPU, which can help improve overall speed and performance. device responsiveness. By freeing up system resources, users can also see increased battery life because their devices are no longer consuming power on unnecessary background processes. This can be especially beneficial for users who use their devices throughout the day and need to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Duolingo: language lessons 6.46.3</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Sep 2025 16:28:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-duolingo-language-lessons-8265.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-duolingo-language-lessons-8265.html
</guid><description>
Duolingo is a popular language learning app that offers interactive lessons to help users learn new languages. This application offers many languages for you to choose from, including Spanish, French, German, Italian, Portuguese, Chinese, Japanese and many more.
This app offers an gamified learning experience with interactive lessons, exercises, and quizzes designed to help users learn new words, phrases, and grammar rules. This app is designed to be easy to use and suitable for people...
</description></item><item><title>Download SD Maid 2/SE - System Cleaner 1.5.0-beta0</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Sep 2025 16:28:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sd-maid-2se-system-cleaner-10472.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sd-maid-2se-system-cleaner-10472.html
</guid><description>
SD Maid 2/SE - System Cleaner is a reliable helper for your Android, keeping the device clean &amp;amp; orderly. SD Maid SE has optional features that use the AccessibilityService API to automate tedious actions. Using the AccessibilityService API, SD Maid SE can click buttons for you to perform cross-app operations, for example, clear cache. SD Maid SE does not use the AccessibilityService API to collect information.
No one is perfect and neither is Android
	Apps you deleted will leave...
</description></item><item><title>Download Compass Pro 1.6.11</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Sep 2025 16:27:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-compass-pro-10926.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-compass-pro-10926.html
</guid><description>
Stay informed about your north, direction (azimuth) and location.
The main advantages of our Compass application
	Beautiful and modern material design style.
	Status bar notifications - know your direction and location when using other apps.
	Colorful themes - personalize the look of your compass.
	Unique feature "course scale". Allows you to mark your preferred azimuth and define the return direction.
	Supported compass scale units: degrees, mil and grad.
	Easy to use.
	Displays word...
</description></item><item><title>Download Omnia Music Player 1.8.2 build 137</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Sep 2025 16:27:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-omnia-music-player-10217.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-omnia-music-player-10217.html
</guid><description>
Omnia Music Player is a powerful music player for Android. It is an ad-free offline audio player. Its beautiful user interface matches every detail of material design principles. Omnia Music Player supports almost all audio formats, including mp3, ape, aac, flac, opus, ogg, wav, etc. It has a high-resolution output engine with the best sound quality and a 10-band equalizer, in a small footprint, under 5 MB.
Omnia Music Player contains almost every necessary feature to satisfy all your...
</description></item><item><title>Download Square Home 3.3.9</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Sep 2025 16:27:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-square-home-8744.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-square-home-8744.html
</guid><description>
Square Home is an Android launcher app that allows users to customize their Android device's home screen with various themes, layouts, and widgets. Square Home is the best launcher with Windows 10 metro UI. Easy to use, simple, beautiful and powerful for any phone, tablet and TV box.
	This app uses Device Administrator permissions. If your Android version is lower than 9.0, you should grant permission to perform the launcher's "screen lock" action.
	This app only uses the Accessibility...
</description></item><item><title>Download Digital Compass 17.2 build 172</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Sep 2025 16:27:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-digital-compass-13590.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-digital-compass-13590.html
</guid><description>
This app is a smart compass with high accuracy and a great tool for outdoor activities. This compass app allows you to easily determine the direction you are facing. This app is built using the device's gyroscope, accelerometer, magnetometer, gravity sensor to determine the direction. Make sure your device has an accelerometer and magnetometer sensor or it will not work.
Features
	Show current location (longitude, latitude, address)
	Show altitude
	Show magnetic field strength
	Show...
</description></item><item><title>Download Auto Text: Schedule Messages 5.8.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Sep 2025 16:26:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-auto-text-auto-send-message-8447.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-auto-text-auto-send-message-8447.html
</guid><description>
Auto Text: Auto send WA &amp;amp; SMS is a feature or application that allows users to automatically send pre-written text messages at a specific time or in response to a request. specific activation. This feature can be useful in many situations, such as sending reminders, sending messages to loved ones at a specific time, or sending messages in response to certain events, such as calls to or location-based triggers.
Auto Text features: Auto send WA &amp;amp; SMS
	Automatically send happy...
</description></item><item><title>Download ASICS Runkeeper - Run Tracker 16.12</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Sep 2025 16:26:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-asics-runkeeper-run-tracker-8334.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-asics-runkeeper-run-tracker-8334.html
</guid><description>
Join a community that helps people escape difficulties and stick with running forever! Track your workouts, set goals, sweat, and see your progress. Whether you're trying to track a 5K goal or train for a marathon, use the GPS app trusted by 50 million users and counting.
ASICS Runkeeper - Run Tracker is a mobile application that allows users to track running and fitness activities on their Android devices. The app uses GPS to track the user's distance, pace, and running time as well as...
</description></item><item><title>Download Acode - code editor | FOSS 1.11.6 build 965</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Sep 2025 16:25:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-acode-code-editor-foss-8264.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-acode-code-editor-foss-8264.html
</guid><description>
Acode is a free and open source code editing application for Android devices. It allows users to edit and code on their mobile devices and supports multiple programming languages ​​and file formats. This is a useful tool for programmers and developers who need to work with code on the go or away from their primary development environment.
You can use this editor to edit HTML, JavaScript, text. You can create a website, run it in your browser, and view errors or logs in the console....
</description></item><item><title>Download KX Music Player Pro 2.5.4</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Sep 2025 16:25:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kx-music-player-pro-10124.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kx-music-player-pro-10124.html
</guid><description>
KX Music Player Pro is a professional music player and intuitive Equalizer to improve the sound quality of your music. Whichever sound effect you want, just slide your finger! Simple, useful and innovative controls. The most professional music player designed for music enthusiasts! Uses professional audio decoding technology to play music perfectly, providing high-fidelity playback. And, the most professional creative Equalizer helps you tailor your own exclusive music.
Supported...
</description></item><item><title>Download Audiomack: Music Downloader 7.4.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Sep 2025 16:24:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-audiomack-music-downloader-11192.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-audiomack-music-downloader-11192.html
</guid><description>
Stream and download the best new trending music (full tracks offline data-free) and listen to your local MP3s!&amp;nbsp;Browse music from the best artists in top categories like Hip-Hop, Rap, R&amp;amp;B, EDM, Afropop, and Reggae on the Audiomack music app. Download songs and listen offline, without using your data, or listen to your personal MP3 collection! Audiomack provides download access and unlimited streaming to the newest and hottest tracks, right at your fingertips. Our music download...
</description></item><item><title>Download Screen Recorder - XRecorder 2.4.4.6</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Sep 2025 16:24:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-screen-recorder-xrecorder-13293.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-screen-recorder-xrecorder-13293.html
</guid><description>
Screen Recorder &amp;amp; Video Recorder - XRecorder helps you record smooth &amp;amp; clear screen videos, screenshots in the easiest way. Just tap the floating ball, you can record HD tutorial videos, video calls and undownloadable videos. And you will never miss live game shows and important moments again.
TOP FEATURES:
	Screenshot to capture clear Screenshots
	Record Games on your phone
	Record internal audio without noise (Android 10 and above ONLY)
	Live stream YouTube &amp;amp; RTMP:...
</description></item><item><title>Download BeSoccer - Soccer Live Score 5.6.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Sep 2025 16:24:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-besoccer-soccer-live-score-8800.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-besoccer-soccer-live-score-8800.html
</guid><description>
All the football in the world at the click of a button. BeSoccer is the best live soccer app with soccer news, results and statistics. We cover over 10,000 competitions: you'll be able to follow all the matches live, receive goal notifications, line-ups, news, signings and today's televised matches . Explore the best database in the world of football with all the statistics about your team, favorite players around the world, comparisons, team form and the latest transfer rumours.&amp;lt;...
</description></item><item><title>Download Drivvo - car management 8.6.7</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Sep 2025 16:24:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-drivvo-car-management-8614.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-drivvo-car-management-8614.html
</guid><description>
Drivvo is a car management app that helps users track and manage expenses related to their vehicles. It provides a platform to record and analyze fuel consumption, maintenance costs and other expenses, making it easier to budget and manage car-related expenses.
Save Money: Manage fuel consumption and economic costs, car maintenance costs and service costs of your car, motorcycle, bus or truck.
Control Finances: Track average KM/liter, monthly costs, average per day, fuel,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Bluelight Filter for Eye Care 6.4.11</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Sep 2025 16:23:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-bluelight-filter-for-eye-care-8192.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-bluelight-filter-for-eye-care-8192.html
</guid><description>
Blue light from smartphones or tablets causes eye strain and makes it difficult to sleep at night. This app adjusts your screen color to reduce blue light and relax your eyes, helping you sleep better.
Features of Blue Light Filter for Eye Care
	Free screen filter app to protect your eyes
	Screen filter with natural colors
	Easy operation
	Turn on or off quickly and easily
	Automatic start
	Eye care on your smartphone or tablet
	This app works on most smartphones like Samsung Galaxy,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Guardian Feast: Cook &amp;amp; Explore 1.0.0.517</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Sep 2025 16:23:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-guardian-feast-cook-explore-13455.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-guardian-feast-cook-explore-13455.html
</guid><description>
With over 6,000 recipes to choose from, find unique flavors, explore different cuisines and expand your repertoire of regular dishes, with a 14-day free trial of the Feast app. Or if you're already a Guardian subscriber, log in to see if Feast is part of your subscription.
The Feast app is packed with daily inspiration from our world-class chefs – including Meera Sodha, Yotam Ottolenghi, Benjamina Ebuehi, Nigel Slater, Rachel Roddy and many more. Our food editors carefully curate the...
</description></item><item><title>Download MIUI-ify: Custom Notifications 1.10.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Sep 2025 16:23:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-miui-ify-custom-notifications-11202.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-miui-ify-custom-notifications-11202.html
</guid><description>
MIUI-ify feels smooth, fast and natural MIUI 12 style quick settings and notification panel at the bottom of the screen, allowing you to toggle settings like WiFi, Bluetooth, Flash and more Other settings, as well as adding shortcuts to apps and websites in the control panel too!
What is the difference between MIUI-ify and Bottom Quick Settings? The main difference can be seen in the Play Store screenshots. MIUI-ify is cleaner, easier to use and MIUI style. Quick settings at the bottom...
</description></item><item><title>Download Meteoblue weather &amp;amp; maps vCirrus Uncinus 2.12.00</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Sep 2025 16:22:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-meteoblue-weather-maps-vcirrus-uncinus-10132.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-meteoblue-weather-maps-vcirrus-uncinus-10132.html
</guid><description>
Meteoblue displays highly accurate weather forecasts combined with a beautiful, simple and easy-to-use design. The weather forecast for any place on Earth can be requested easily and comfortably.
Features of Meteoblue vCirrus Uncinus Weather &amp;amp; Maps
	Weather forecast for any point on land or sea.
	Location search with over 6 million locations: search for a location name, postal code or coordinates, or let the app find your current location using the GPS module.
	3 different widgets...
</description></item></channel></rss>