<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 15:45:50 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 15:45:50 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download PDF-XChange Editor Plus 10.8.1.406</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 17:56:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-xchange-editor-plus-645.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-xchange-editor-plus-645.html
</guid><description>
PDF-XChange Editor Plus is the editor, PDF viewer, compact, fast with many features, add-ons, professional. When using the PDF-XChange Editor Plus, easy for users to create, view, edit, annotate, OCR and digital signing PDF files, plus much more.
PDF-XChange Editor is a PDF editing full-featured. With the help of it, you can edit, fix, add, or delete text easily. Graphics can also be moved, resized or removed.
Features PDF-XChange Editor Plus
Edit documents
	Use a variety of editing...
</description></item><item><title>Download Topaz Photo Pro 1.1.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 17:55:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-photo-ai-8105.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-photo-ai-8105.html
</guid><description>
What is Topaz Photo AI?
Topaz Photo AI is a professional software that automatically adjusts for your image quality needs. Simply import images into Topaz Photo AI and it will use specially trained AI models to first detect unique details, clarity, and resolution issues before applying the intelligently adjusts to maximize your image quality.
For users experienced with Topaz Labs image quality applications, it combines the functionality of DeNoise AI, Sharpen AI and Gigapixel AI into...
</description></item><item><title>Download NoMachine 9.3.7</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 17:55:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nomachine-5939.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nomachine-5939.html
</guid><description>
NoMachine is a fast-use remote desktop computer that allows you to quickly access any computer in the world. Move from your desktop to any of the NoMachine support computers at the speed of light. In just a few clicks, you can approach any computer in the world and start working with it as if it were right in front of you.
NoMachine can turn your computer into your personal cloud. Bring what 's important when you arrive, whether it' s at home or at the office. Whatever your desktop and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Vivaldi Browser 7.7.3851.66</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 17:54:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vivaldi-159.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vivaldi-159.html
</guid><description>
Vivaldi is a browser designed for users who have power and offer the option to customize high. You can choose the location of the tabs and the address bar, put the hotkeys for the common tasks and many other features. Also, Vivaldi also provides a number of improvements such as Tab Stacks to group multiple open tabs into a tab, leads to interface less cluttered. Can notes and added a screenshot of a web page while browsing, storing an attachment, and add the URL to easily sort and locate...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDF-XChange Pro 10.8.1.406</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 17:53:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-xchange-editor-pro-3422.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-xchange-editor-pro-3422.html
</guid><description>
PDF-XChange Editor Pro is an application to manipulate and create PDF versatile, offering a wide range of useful features and powerful will help you to easily work with PDF files. This application is very flexible and allows you to easily create and modify PDF files. PDF-XChange Editor Pro provides a powerful set of tools and flexibility to work with PDF files, such as editor PDF-XChange new, utilities series, OFFice2PDF and the Addin tool Bar allows you to easily convert multiple file...
</description></item><item><title>Download Google Chrome 143.0.7499.170</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 17:53:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-chrome-1012.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-chrome-1012.html
</guid><description>
Google Chrome web browser is the most used today. Support surf the web, listen to music, watch movies, play web game effective no jerky lag with the internet connection stable. When you are surfing the web or performing an important task, whether it is operation big or small, work or entertainment, then Chrome has the smart features and the speed you need to make, create and explore on the net.
The latest version of Google Chrome is the third 114. But we are providing for users Google...
</description></item><item><title>Download reaConverter Pro 8.0.172</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 17:52:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html
</guid><description>
reaConverter Pro is software image processing feature with batch conversion and image editing periodically becomes simple. eaConverter also provide command line utilities allow you to process images automatically, thus helping you shorten the time for other work.
reaConverter Pro integrated powerful tool of Uber with many great features. It provides advanced solutions to process and adjust images. Management of the conversion process the base image with the latest version of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Scooter Beyond Compare 5.1.7.31736</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 17:52:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-scooter-beyond-compare-2649.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-scooter-beyond-compare-2649.html
</guid><description>
Scooter Beyond Compare is a powerful tool to compare quickly and easily the files and folders. This program provides you with a full report on work done so you can compare the complete data on the file, folder, folder with speed and file size, very fast and incredible, time changes on the file as well as the compared bytes Do byte this information. With the strong command of this program, you can merge the changes, synchronize files, create a report to record.
Scooter Beyond Compare -...
</description></item><item><title>Download CapCut PC 7.7.0.3143 / 7.8.0.3909 Beta 2</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 17:51:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capcut-pc-9995.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capcut-pc-9995.html
</guid><description>
CapCut PC is a simple video editing tool that you can freely use anywhere. You can create videos on your browser, desktop and laptop, or on your phone. Versatile editing, magical AI tools, team collaboration, and built-in assets. Create videos in a whole new way.
You can edit videos based on editing the timeline, in the process you can add different elements and effects to the video to give the best effect to your work. It is a simple and intuitive set of editing tools and effects that...
</description></item><item><title>Download KDEnlive 25.12.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 17:50:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kdenlive-3288.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kdenlive-3288.html
</guid><description>
Kdenlive is a video editor open source. The project was started in about 2003. Kdenlive is built on the Qt libraries and the KDE Frameworks. Most of the video processing is done by the MLT Framework, based on many open-source projects other as FFmpeg , frei0r , Movit, ladspa, sox, etc.
KDEnlive - video editing quickly
Our software is designed to meet most needs, from basic video editing to professional work. Kdenlive allows you to use and arrange a number of music and video, each can...
</description></item><item><title>Download MusConv 4.10.440 Lifetime</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 17:50:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html
</guid><description>
MusConv transfers playlists, albums, followed artists and liked songs across a variety of services – Spotify, Apple Music, Amazon Music, YouTube, YouTube Music, iTunes, Deezer, Tidal, SoundCloud, Pandora and more 125 music services!
Features of MusConv Ultimate
	Transfer playlists, albums, followed artists and liked tracks between over 125 music servicesManage playlists (Delete, Merge, Split, Copy...)
	More than 125 music services supported
	Access DAILY updated music charts on...
</description></item><item><title>Download VoiceBot Pro 3.9.9</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 17:45:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-voicebot-pro-4924.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-voicebot-pro-4924.html
</guid><description>
VoiceBot Pro is professional software allows you to dictate in his voice. With VoiceBot Pro the command to send the action to the game and your application. Use your voice to type keyboard shortcuts, click and move the mouse and execute the macro, and scripting. Control the game with your favorite voice recognition enhancement of VoiceBot Pro. Binding voice commands for actions in-game and perform the action, simple or complex, in one word.
The features of VoiceBot Pro
	Fully...
</description></item><item><title>Download Bitwig Studio 6.0 Beta 10</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 17:45:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bitwig-studio-3626.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bitwig-studio-3626.html
</guid><description>
Find new standard in the process of individual work. Bitwig Studio excite you good control over his music, give you access to all features of your production. Streamline course creation of you and quickly develop your ideas into the songs, compositions and music full.
Bitwig Studio - Create your own music
Arrange and record, perform and improvise, or do all at the same time. Choose among the many records displayed. Design your sound with the equipment container commitment. Mixing the...
</description></item><item><title>Download eM Client Pro 10.4.4209</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 17:44:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-em-client-pro-953.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-em-client-pro-953.html
</guid><description>
eM Client Pro is an email app full features with modern interface. eM Client offers calendar, tasks, contacts and chat. Software is best Email app for windows today. eM Client supports all major services including Gmail, Exchange, iCloud and Outlook.com. You can find more information in the server part on our website.
eM Client Pro - the best email App for windows
eM Client is very simple , can automatically set everything up for most of the services. It is also effective to import...
</description></item><item><title>Download Run-Command 6.33</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 17:44:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-run-command-1816.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-run-command-1816.html
</guid><description>
Run-Command is an alternative to Windows dialog Run standard. Dialog Run-Command looks similar to the Windows dialog but offers the button "Run as Administrator" convenient, as well as the option to save and schedule the Run command on your menu Favorites for quick access in the future.
You may not know, this Command works more or less like command line interface a line. In the Gnome , the command Run is used to run applications through the command terminal. It can be accessed by pressing...
</description></item><item><title>Download Bitvise SSH Client 9.53</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 17:43:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bitvise-ssh-client-2845.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bitvise-ssh-client-2845.html
</guid><description>
Bitvise SSH Client is a SSH terminal, tunneling and file transfer application SFTP for free with the command line interface and graphics. It supports all versions desktop and server of Windows! Bitvise SSH Client for free use! Bitvise SSH Client is an application multipurpose, fast and powerful in the transmission of the advanced file helps users control and manage the terminal remotely in a flexible manner. Bitvise SSH Client intensive support for establishing the secure connection...
</description></item><item><title>Download DisplayFusion Pro 12.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 17:43:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-displayfusion-pro-1576.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-displayfusion-pro-1576.html
</guid><description>
DisplayFusion Pro is software that support open computer dual screen with good performance and smooth operation the most. With DisplayFusion Pro, you can add a taskbar to every monitor acts and looks just like the Windows taskbar. Or take advantage of background image support multi-screen, advanced Integrated Flickr to search for images and the hot key manager window can be fully customized. Here are just a few of the many things that DisplayFusion can do.
DisplayFusion Pro - open...
</description></item><item><title>Download TrayStatus Pro 5.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 17:37:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-traystatus-pro-1597.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-traystatus-pro-1597.html
</guid><description>
TrayStatus Pro is professional software to help display the status of the keys Caps Lock, Num Lock, Scroll Lock, Kana, Alt, Ctrl, Shift in the system tray. In addition, the software TrayStatus this Pro also displays CPU, memory or operation of the hard drive or use performance counters to track things like the queue length, disk, network activity, requires IIS and more.
TrayStatus Pro - Show keyboard status and parameters of the computer
The features and functions TrayStatus...
</description></item><item><title>Download FileSeek Pro 7.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 17:30:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fileseek-pro-2237.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fileseek-pro-2237.html
</guid><description>
FileSeek  is a powerful program to quickly search for files on your computer. The developers write that their tool uses multi-threading technology to search for, thus ensuring high speed. You can set a number of search queries, as this has a system of tabs (only in Pro version), open how much you need and search. FileSeek can operate with text and regular expressions to search files, allows you get search results the most accurate side in the desired folder or specific files. If there are...
</description></item><item><title>Download Awesome Miner Ultimate 11.3.3</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 17:29:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-awesome-miner-9041.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-awesome-miner-9041.html
</guid><description>
Awesome Miner is a software application designed to manage and monitor cryptocurrency mining operations. It supports a wide variety of mining hardware, including ASICs and GPUs, and can be used to manage mining for a variety of cryptocurrencies, including Bitcoin, Ethereum, and Litecoin.
Powerful tool to manage and monitor cryptocurrency mining activities. With support for a wide variety of mining hardware and cryptocurrencies, mobile apps, and customizable alerting and performance...
</description></item><item><title>Download LogFusion Pro 7.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 17:29:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-logfusion-pro-5024.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-logfusion-pro-5024.html
</guid><description>
LogFusion Pro is a monitoring tool powerful diary helps to analyze your logs easy. Take advantage of features Filter text and Filter text of LogFusion to quickly filter your log and only show the relevant lines you are looking for. Use features custom Columns to parse LogFusion and split your logs into separate columns for easier reading. Like the program 'tail' in the popular Linux / Unix, LogFusion can also auto-scroll and always show you the latest line in the log file of you in real...
</description></item><item><title>Download Advanced CSV Converter 7.87</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 17:28:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-csv-converter-4508.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-csv-converter-4508.html
</guid><description>
Advanced CSV Converter is a conversion tool CSV to DBF, Excel (XLS, XLSX), TXT, HTML, PRG, XML, SQL, RTF. To convert a file, the program provides an interface controlled by the wizard, guides you step by step conversion. Use the wizard, you select file input, select the format and destination folder. If necessary, you can set the filter switch according to the example and select columns you want to exclude from the process. When the conversion process is started, the program will extract...
</description></item><item><title>Download Flyby11 2.3.833</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 17:28:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-flyby11-12467.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-flyby11-12467.html
</guid><description>
Flyby11 is a simple patcher that removes annoying restrictions that prevent you from installing Windows 11 (24H2) on unsupported hardware. Do you have an old PC? No TPM, Secure Boot or your processor is not supported? Flyby11 allows you to install Windows 11 24H2. There are no complicated steps. Just run the tool and you'll be running Windows 11 on your outdated machine in no time.
Technical overview
Flyby11 takes advantage of a feature of the Windows 11 setup process that uses the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Flyoobe 2.3.833</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 17:28:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oobelux-13956.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oobelux-13956.html
</guid><description>
Flyoobe was born out of the frustration many users felt with the Windows 11 setup experience. Whether it was the mandatory online account, the endless "Next, next, next..." screens, or the incomplete configuration options when you finally reached the desktop, the current setup lacked focus on what users really wanted.
Why choose Flyoobe?
	Simplifies the Windows 11 setup process right out of the box.
	Allows easy local account creation without need to hunt for hidden options.
	Includes...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft Edge 143.0.3650.96</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 17:27:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-edge-3940.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-edge-3940.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft Edge is web browser developed specifically for Windows operating system 10 alternatives to Internet Explorer is the default browser on Windows. Browser Microsoft Edge built-in assistant Cortana brings content and website based on the user's preferences, there are also system utilities quite extensive help you to customize according to individual. Microsoft Edge has the similarity with Google Chrome quite large, except the target is marked more of the interface and the rounded...
</description></item></channel></rss>