<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 05:31:54 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 05:31:54 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Media Player Classic Home Cinema 2.5.4</title><pubDate> Thu, 02 Oct 2025 03:57:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-media-player-classic-home-cinema-2839.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-media-player-classic-home-cinema-2839.html
</guid><description>
Media Player Classic Home Cinema is a multimedia compact for Microsoft Windows 32 bit and 64 bit. MPC mimics the interface of Windows Media Player 6.4, but provides most options and features available in the modern means. Media Player Classic Home Cinema for free 100% no advertising, so you can directly access content and enjoy media playback without being distracted.
With Media Player Classic Home, you can now change the design a multimedia of the custom toolbar. There is a range to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Fort Firewall 3.19.8</title><pubDate> Thu, 02 Oct 2025 03:56:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fort-firewall-6439.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fort-firewall-6439.html
</guid><description>
Fort Firewall is a network security system that monitors and controls network traffic and goes based on predefined security rules. A firewall often establishes a barrier between a trusted internal network and untrusted external networks, such as the Internet.
Features of Fort Firewall
	Filter by network address, application group
	Support of representative characters in the name path name
	Application group speed limit
	Access Traffic Statistics
	Display bandwidth
	Based on the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Acrobat Pro DC 2025.001.20756 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Thu, 02 Oct 2025 03:52:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-001en-adobe-acrobat-pro-458.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-001en-adobe-acrobat-pro-458.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Acrobat Pro DC is a comprehensive software that helps you create and edit the PDF&amp;nbsp;document, or create form, sign, protect PDF, connect, split PDF, export PDF to various formats. The Acrobat Pro DC is the latest version of Adobe with improvements in the interface with the polished ribbon bar and the ability to create and handle pdf files as well as its male versions.
The highlight of the Acrobat Pro DC is probably the ability to connect, store documents on the cloud, you can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Reuschtools CopyWin 4.69</title><pubDate> Thu, 02 Oct 2025 03:50:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reuschtools-copywin-14136.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reuschtools-copywin-14136.html
</guid><description>
Reuschtools CopyWin is a versatile program designed to copy the contents of your Windows drive, including all files and programs, to another drive, USB or MicroSD card. This is especially useful for upgrading or replacing storage hardware, as it simplifies the migration process. The tool does not require installation; it can be used by running the executable file, but requires administrative rights to operate. CopyWin also offers features like incremental backups after the initial backup,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Illustrator 2025 v29.8.2 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Thu, 02 Oct 2025 03:50:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-illustrator-0018-749.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-illustrator-0018-749.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Illustrator is a powerful vector graphics editor developed by Adobe Inc., first released in 1987. It is primarily used by graphic designers, illustrators, and artists to create high-quality illustrations, logos, icons, and digital artwork. Unlike raster graphics editors like Adobe Photoshop, which manipulate images pixel by pixel, Illustrator uses mathematical formulas to create vector graphics. This allows designs to be scaled infinitely without losing quality, making it ideal for...
</description></item><item><title>Download FakeDriveCheck 4.69</title><pubDate> Thu, 02 Oct 2025 03:49:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fakedrivecheck-11322.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fakedrivecheck-11322.html
</guid><description>
FakeDriveCheck is a simple utility you can run to verify if your USB stick or MicroSD card is fake. It's easy to get and use, making it a good choice for anyone skeptical about the authenticity of their external storage.
FakeDriveCheck Features
	Existing files will not be destroyed while the USB drive is verified.
	Super fast verification.
	No need to unplug and plug in.
	Hot Plug: FakeDriveCheck detects USB drives
	inserted after FakeDriveCheck is started.
</description></item><item><title>Download Calibre 8.12.0 + Portable</title><pubDate> Thu, 02 Oct 2025 03:48:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-calibre-1669.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-calibre-1669.html
</guid><description>
Calibre  is an eBook library management application that allows you to manage your eBook collection, convert eBooks between different formats, Sync with popular e-reading devices and read your e-books with included viewer. You can sort books by author, title, date and other details, download meta information and book covers, add personalized tags and comments, and view your images in the cover display.
Collection of essential tools for adding metadata editing books or managing your...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft Office 2021-2024 Professional Plus VL (64-bit) 2509 Build 19231.20156 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Thu, 02 Oct 2025 03:47:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-office-2021-6670.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-office-2021-6670.html
</guid><description>
Since the end of February 2021, Microsoft has announced two new versions of Office 2021 including: Office 2021 and Office LTSC. Reportedly, Office 2021 is the next version of Office 2019, promising to bring users a better experience in the new Word, Excel or PowerPoint tools.
With each office user, the Microsoft Office toolkit is essential and indispensable software in the job. Microsoft Office has undergone numerous editions from Office 2010, 2013, 2016, 2019 to Microsoft 365 developed...
</description></item><item><title>Download DBF Converter 7.63</title><pubDate> Thu, 02 Oct 2025 03:40:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbf-converter-6362.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbf-converter-6362.html
</guid><description>
DBF Converter is a common solution for all your DBF format conversion needs. Whenever you need to extract data from the DBF file to CSV, XLS, XLSX, SQL or pure text, the software will provide a simple way to do this with minimal effort.
Features of DBF Converter
	Work with DBF Converter is easy. You specify a DBF file or a directory with DBF files that you want to convert, select the fields and filter out the records you need. Then, just a click to DBF Converter to turn the source...
</description></item><item><title>Download Aquaforest Autobahn DX 6.0.2509.24</title><pubDate> Thu, 02 Oct 2025 03:38:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aquaforest-autobahn-dx-12791.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aquaforest-autobahn-dx-12791.html
</guid><description>
Aquaforest Autobahn DX is a fast, high-volume batch OCR and PDF conversion solution to searchable PDFs for Windows servers. Process thousands of documents at once or create workflows to automatically convert and OCR new documents. It is used by many businesses globally for large and batch projects.
	Test your SharePoint library to find out the percentage of non-searchable and fully searchable files.
	Accurate and reliable processing with AI-powered OCR.
	Powerful capabilities and the...
</description></item><item><title>Download FileLocator Pro 2022 Build 3536</title><pubDate> Thu, 02 Oct 2025 03:35:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-filelocator-pro-1056.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-filelocator-pro-1056.html
</guid><description>
FileLocator Pro is software manage files and search function the file quickly the software and data. FileLocator Pro helps you find things quickly. The unique feature of it allows the extraction of information in all file formats the most obscure.
FileLocator Pro - file Manager
The features of FileLocator Pro
	Search algorithm based on the C ++ multi-threading for ultra-fast
	Search for network drive by mapped drive or UNC paths
	Support regular expressions for file name and...
</description></item><item><title>Download IK Multimedia Tonex Max 1.10.4</title><pubDate> Thu, 02 Oct 2025 03:35:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ik-multimedia-tonex-max-7877.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ik-multimedia-tonex-max-7877.html
</guid><description>
TONEX software uses groundbreaking AI Machine Modeling technology to let you model the sound of any amp, cabinet, or combo and turn it into a plug-in, all with precision sounds are almost indistinguishable from reality. You can instantly play up to the more than 1,000 already available Melody Models along with browsing, performing, and downloading more and more Melody Models available on TONEX in ToneNET.
Features of IK Multimedia Tonex Max
	Modeled tone generator, player,...
</description></item><item><title>Download dbForge Studio for PostgreSQL Professional 2025.2.37</title><pubDate> Thu, 02 Oct 2025 03:34:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbforge-studio-for-postgresql-enterprise-11213.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbforge-studio-for-postgresql-enterprise-11213.html
</guid><description>
dbForge Studio for PostgreSQL Enterprise is a GUI client and popular tool for managing and developing PostgreSQL databases. This PostgreSQL IDE allows users to create, develop and execute queries, edit and adapt code according to their requirements in a convenient and user-friendly interface.
Main features:
SQL Development
	Save your time and improve code quality when creating and editing queries with the following features
	PostgreSQL code completion
	Code format
	SQL Check SQL...
</description></item><item><title>Download Dont Sleep 9.89</title><pubDate> Thu, 02 Oct 2025 03:34:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dont-sleep-89.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dont-sleep-89.html
</guid><description>
Don't Sleep allows you can set the date and custom time that you want to reactivate the feature manager usual sources or you can set a countdown fast to pause the power management in X hours.
Can temporarily disable the protection of your screen or off your computer at a certain time.
The main features of the Dont Sleep:
- Optimal power supply for computer
- Installation time power source according to
- Prevent computer reboot
Content update Dont Sleep 5.66:
The official website...
</description></item><item><title>Download Boris FX Particle Illusion Pro 2025.5 v18.5.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 02 Oct 2025 03:33:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-boris-fx-particle-illusion-pro-11486.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-boris-fx-particle-illusion-pro-11486.html
</guid><description>
Boris FX Particle Illusion Pro is powerful visual effects software developed by Boris FX, a leading developer of VFX, compositing, titling and workflow tools. Workflow for the film, television and video editing industries. Particle Illusion Pro is an enhanced version of Particle Illusion software, providing advanced features and capabilities to create stunning particle effects.
Features of Boris FX Particle Illusion Pro
	Advanced particle effects: Particle Illusion Pro allows users to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Privacy Eraser Free 6.23.0 Build 5378</title><pubDate> Thu, 02 Oct 2025 03:27:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-privacy-eraser-free-9160.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-privacy-eraser-free-9160.html
</guid><description>
Privacy Eraser is a software tool that helps protect user privacy by securely erasing or deleting unwanted data from their computer or device. This tool is designed to delete browsing history, cookies, cache, temporary files and other sensitive information that may be stored on the computer.
Privacy Eraser can be used to clear browsing history of popular web browsers such as Google Chrome, Mozilla Firefox and Microsoft Edge. It can also clear the history and cache of other applications,...
</description></item><item><title>Download AnkhTech Windows 11 Pro 25H2 Build 26200.6584 (Lite / Super Lite)</title><pubDate> Thu, 02 Oct 2025 00:46:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ankh-tech-windows-11-pro-10550.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ankh-tech-windows-11-pro-10550.html
</guid><description>
Ankh Tech Windows 11 Pro has been introduced as 1 of the best Modified Windows 11 Pro 23h2 ISO with Multi-Function/Multi-Purpose Boot. It is available in 5 Installation Languages and the ability to install multiple languages (in settings). Looks original and Microsoft original, but Performance, speed and stability.
WinPE Multi-Function Boot
	Powerful multi-function start with professional programs to help you
	Taskbar Displays when you move the mouse pointer down the screen
	All...
</description></item><item><title>Download Steinberg SpectraLayers Pro 12.0.30</title><pubDate> Thu, 02 Oct 2025 00:44:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-steinberg-spectralayers-pro-2045.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-steinberg-spectralayers-pro-2045.html
</guid><description>
Steinberg SpectraLayers Pro is a new approach to audio editing, with the new concept to change the way you work. The first time you can directly edit the data spectrum, open to the world advanced audio and the use of innovative enhancements to the traditional techniques. With SpectraLayers Pro you will visualise sound in new ways incredible, including 3D. Work with the distribution like them is the music. Integration of this capability into your DAW and other tools. And all in a familiar...
</description></item><item><title>Download AI Image Upscaler Pro 1.1.4</title><pubDate> Thu, 02 Oct 2025 00:43:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ai-image-upscaler-pro-14203.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ai-image-upscaler-pro-14203.html
</guid><description>
Tired of blurry, low-resolution images? Enlarge your photos and increase their resolution with AI Image Upscaler Pro, the ultimate computer tool that enhances your photos with the power of artificial intelligence. Whether you need to enlarge a photo for print, improve the quality of a photo for a professional project, or simply restore a memorable photo, our app delivers great results right on your PC.
Powered by advanced Real-ESRGAN AI models, AI Image Upscaler Pro is more than just a...
</description></item><item><title>Download Static Equipment Generator (SEG) 6.07</title><pubDate> Thu, 02 Oct 2025 00:31:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-static-equipment-generator-seg-14202.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-static-equipment-generator-seg-14202.html
</guid><description>
Static Equipment Generator (SEG) is an advanced software tool designed to simplify the modeling and detailed design process for static equipment used in the oil, gas, petrochemical, and related industries. Static Equipment Generator (SEG) is a standalone software application that runs on the Autodesk® Inventor® platform. Using Inventor's powerful CAD modeling and design capabilities to create detailed 3D models and manufacturing drawings for static equipment, SEG provides engineers and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Acrobat Reader DC 2025.001.20756</title><pubDate> Wed, 01 Oct 2025 23:50:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-acrobat-reader-3707.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-acrobat-reader-3707.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Acrobat Reader DC is a system of application software and Web services developed by Adobe Systems to view, create, manipulate, print and manage PDF files. With Adobe Acrobat Reader DC, you can create, export, edit, and track PDF files from anywhere - and maintain connection with the recent set of files on all your devices.
Adobe Acrobat Reader current DC is connected with Adobe Document Cloud - help working on the computers and mobile devices becomes easier than ever before. This is...
</description></item><item><title>Download anyPDF 1.4.3.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 01 Oct 2025 23:47:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anypdf-11943.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anypdf-11943.html
</guid><description>
AnyPDF is an integrated PDF viewer and manager as it facilitates viewing and editing of PDF files in a user-friendly manner where users can merge multiple documents, protect and compress important data, etc. This program aims to be a more or less general tool for PDF workflow. That said, it doesn't necessarily specialize in anything specific as it has a number of uses related to working with PDF files.
Features of anyPDF
	User-friendly user interface
	Convert from JPG to...
</description></item><item><title>Download VueScan Pro 9.8.48</title><pubDate> Wed, 01 Oct 2025 23:47:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vuescan-pro-75.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vuescan-pro-75.html
</guid><description>
VueScan Pro l  is one of the software  Scan quality pictures  First and appeared quite soon,  VueScan Pro  always asserted its No. 1 position on the technology pages, awards as well as user reviews. Through many versions, VueScan Pro 9 is greatly improved in terms of interface and features. Supporting most popular image formats today, this software will help you scan images quickly, easy to use and high quality output. With the color balance mode, you won't have to worry about blurring the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Textadept 12.9</title><pubDate> Wed, 01 Oct 2025 23:46:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-textadept-2878.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-textadept-2878.html
</guid><description>
Textadept is a text editor multi-platform, fast, minimalist, and can expand significantly. The user interface of Textadept is sleek and simple. Optimized non-stop for speed and minimalism over the years, the editor consists of less than 2000 lines of C code and less than 4000 lines of code.
Textadept - source code editor
Textadept runs on Windows, Mac OSX, Linux and BSD. It also has a the top-end version, ideal for work on the remote machine. Textadept is an editor, ideal for...
</description></item><item><title>Download CyberLink PhotoDirector Ultra 2026 v17.0.0922.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 01 Oct 2025 23:46:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-photodirector-ultra-129.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-photodirector-ultra-129.html
</guid><description>
Cyberlink PhotoDirector Ultra is known to be photo editing tools and videos with the effect is extremely rich, help you to change the style for the individual images or the videos of his favorite. This software integrated the 3D engine helps to speed up Video processing, which allows accessing the repository effect online and extract the Videos into the movies 3D Bru-ray, 3D AVCHD.
Cyberlink PhotoDirector Ultra to offer users a more professional tool to handle their images, remove...
</description></item></channel></rss>