<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 19:58:40 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 19:58:40 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download iTop Easy Desktop 3.2.1.147</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Sep 2025 17:48:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-itop-easy-desktop-7879.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-itop-easy-desktop-7879.html
</guid><description>
iTop Easy Desktop is a lightweight and easy-to-use desktop manager that organizes desktop icons, files and folders according to your rules, helping you Freed from the tedious arrangement of icons on the screen. It provides various practical features including but not limited to grouping desktop items, awakening live search, and quickly accessing icons and files even across multiple desktop sites. desktop.
Untidy desktop If you're not one to diligently organize your Windows desktop icons...
</description></item><item><title>Download Godot Game Engine 4.5</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Sep 2025 17:47:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-godot-engine-10493.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-godot-engine-10493.html
</guid><description>
Godot Engine is a feature-rich, cross-platform game engine for creating 2D and 3D games from a unified interface. It provides a comprehensive set of common tools so users can focus on game creation without having to reinvent the wheel. Games can be exported with a single click to several platforms, including major desktop platforms (Linux, macOS, Windows), mobile platforms (Android, iOS), as well as Web-based platform and dashboard.
Supported platforms:
Godot Engine, used to create...
</description></item><item><title>Download AB Download Manager 1.6.13</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Sep 2025 17:46:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ab-download-manager-12399.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ab-download-manager-12399.html
</guid><description>
With this application, you can easily download files from anywhere. Enjoy fast, free downloads with seamless browser extension support. It is built to be a desktop application that allows you to manage and organize your downloads better than before.
AB Download Manager features
	Simple and modern UI: Simple UI and dark mode by default
	Faster download speeds: Download files using multiple connections to increase your download speed by up to 500%
	Download Queue: Create and manage your...
</description></item><item><title>Download Q-Dir 12.34</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Sep 2025 17:45:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-q-dir-348.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-q-dir-348.html
</guid><description>
Q-Dir is software to manage the entire file and folder on the computer, allowing to see file in same time 4 different positions (viewport quadro) while still maintaining all the standard features of the Explorer.
It also provides a variety of management features, additional files included the filter file color-coding, layouts and columns can be customized, quick access to file and folder favorites and more.
Other features of Q-Dir , including directory listings (.txt, .doc .html .csv),...
</description></item><item><title>Download AIDA64 Extreme / Engineer 8.00.8000</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Sep 2025 17:44:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aida64-1297.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aida64-1297.html
</guid><description>
AIDA64 is a powerful tool to identify and test virtually all components of personal computers running operating systems Windows.  AIDA64 give you detailed information on all hardware and software, in addition, with the integrated modules for testing and calibration can be checked more for each subsystem PC individually. Display detailed information about all hardware and software is installed on your system.
AIDA64 Extreme/Engineer
Features AIDA64
	Level information about motherboard...
</description></item><item><title>Download IObit Software Updater Pro 8.1.0.10</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Sep 2025 17:43:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iobit-software-updater-pro-2234.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iobit-software-updater-pro-2234.html
</guid><description>
IObit Software Updater Pro software is useful for those who don't download apps for Windows 10 from the store company, virtually all software was installed will not be updated automatically. The web browser will naturally inform you about a new version, software security of you will also be automatically updated, just like Windows, but almost all other apps will quietly operate in the normal mode and you will never know that the update was available, if you can't run itself.
IObit...
</description></item><item><title>Download iTunes 12.13.8.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Sep 2025 17:43:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-itunes-2639.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-itunes-2639.html
</guid><description>
iTunes or is a multimedia library management application mobile developed by Apple. Software this each is play, download and arrange the audio and video multimedia on the personal computer according to the operating system OS X and Microsoft Windows.
iTunes allows you to browse and purchase music, videos, and apps from the Apple Store. iTunes allows you to browse the repository online music iTunes from where you can search for songs, browse genres and then download songs, music videos or...
</description></item><item><title>Download Stretchly 1.18.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Sep 2025 17:42:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stretchly-1877.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stretchly-1877.html
</guid><description>
Stretchly is a reminder application break time automatically remind you to take breaks while you are working on your computer. By default, the program runs in the system tray and display the window prompts and press the bell for 20 seconds violation just after 10 minutes and take a 5 minute break every 30 minutes. You can customize the duration of the stay as well as the time between the times, to violate or ignore them if you like.
Stretchly - software automatic reminders
Stretchly is...
</description></item><item><title>Download AOMEI Backupper Pro / Technician / Server 8.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Sep 2025 17:42:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aomei-backupper-pro-98.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aomei-backupper-pro-98.html
</guid><description>
AOMEI Backupper pro is a software backup and recovery professional, easy to use. Fully protect your computer from data loss. It allows you to backup an entire PC and Server, provides one-click backup your system partition or your disk and execute it in a few minutes. This software also can explore the created image and restore it on hard drive if your data gets lost or corrupted. In addition, you can create the recovery disk the ability to boot to recover his data after a system crash and...
</description></item><item><title>Download By Click Downloader 2.4.24</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Sep 2025 17:41:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-by-click-premium-193.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-by-click-premium-193.html
</guid><description>
YouTube By Click Premium is a high quality powerful video downloader including YouTube downloader, YouTube Converter, YouTube Chrome Downloader, Facebook Video Downloader, Downloader Vimeo, Dailymotion Downloader and supports many other video sites.
YouTube By Click
YouTube By Click Features
	YouTube by Click can download and convert files to MP3, MP4, FLV, AVI, WMV, 3GP, WAV and WEBM formats.
	Download all supported qualities, including HD.
	YouTube By Click downloads entire YouTube...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDF24 PDF Creator 11.28.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Sep 2025 17:41:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf24-pdf-creator-926.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf24-pdf-creator-926.html
</guid><description>
PDF24 PDF Creator is a printer driver application that lets you convert any document or image can be printed into PDF format. With any application that supports printing any user can also create a PDF file of the document through the virtual printer PDF24. Virtual printer can also save the file under format image files other than PDF such as PNG, JPEG, BMP, TIFF, and PSD. After printing, a help section of the program that pops up allows the user to view, save, send, edit that...
</description></item><item><title>Download SoundSwitch 6.14.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Sep 2025 17:40:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-soundswitch-2910.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-soundswitch-2910.html
</guid><description>
SoundSwitch is a handy simple and light, give you the ability to switch between the playback equipment different is connected with your PC just by using the hot keys. The program can be configured in just few simple steps and quickly. Just right-click on the icon in your system tray and table settings will be open. You can choose the hot key and select which device you want to control just by few mouse clicks. The application will run smoothly in the background, allowing you to quickly...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mozilla Firefox 143.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Sep 2025 17:40:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-firefox-quantum-501.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-firefox-quantum-501.html
</guid><description>
Firefox Quantum is a web browser independently provide the tabbed browsing combined with numerous handy features like pop-up blocker, Bookmarks, direct (integrated RSS), password manager, and more. Functionality can be extended with dozens of plugins available for free (extensions).
Firefox Quantum are interface completely new, beautiful, neat, minimalistic and delicate, eats less RAM to 30% compared with the old version and solve the condition consuming capacity
Firefox can import all...
</description></item><item><title>Download DVDFab 13.0.4.8</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Sep 2025 17:39:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dvdfab-67.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dvdfab-67.html
</guid><description>
DVDFab All-In-One is a multi-purpose combo of nearly all powerful DVDFab products-DVD replication, Ripper DVD, Blu-ray Ripper, Blu-ray Ripper, Copy UHD, Blu-ray to DVD, DVD to Blu-ray Transaction, DVD Creator, Blu-ray Creator, video conversion, Cinavia DVD removal, Windows DVD removal, DRM elimination for Apple, Screen Recorder and Editor for iOS, Hi-Fi Sound and File Transfer. It provides a complete solution to all of your DVD/Blu-ray/video problems and the perfect execution.
DvDFab -...
</description></item><item><title>Download Worksheet Crafter Premium Edition 2025.1.12.461 + Premium Content Pack</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Sep 2025 17:39:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-worksheet-crafter-premium-edition-3922.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-worksheet-crafter-premium-edition-3922.html
</guid><description>
Worksheet Crafter Premium Edition helps you to create the form of teaching, worksheet and quiz grade perfect for elementary school students &amp;amp; your special in just a few clicks. Create a spreadsheet of your own in a few clicks. It is interesting to use, tested by 1000 teacher, and as familiar as Microsoft Word. Moreover, Worksheet Crafter Premium Edition has improved the ability to use the equation editor by adding support undo / redo for better editing. In addition, when choosing a...
</description></item><item><title>Download PhotoDiva 6.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Sep 2025 17:38:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photodiva-3652.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photodiva-3652.html
</guid><description>
PhotoDiva is tool support, photo editing, photo help photos of you are absolutely not blurred, blurry image. With PhotoDiva you will get the beautiful portrait the eyes quickly by using the effects by a click of the mouse to make the drastic changes. Whether you need a boost of color or a full face of makeup, software this portrait brings great results automatically.
PhotoDiva - enhanced image quality
PhotoDiva is an easy to master, even when there is no photo editing experience...
</description></item><item><title>Download AIDA64 Business / Network Audit 8.00.8000</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Sep 2025 17:38:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aida64-business-5689.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aida64-business-5689.html
</guid><description>
AIDA64 Business can gather a very detailed arsenal of hardware and software from Windows clients connected to the corporate network. Since it supports command line switching, inventory creation can be fully automated, while reports collected from a PC can be saved in open formats ready for further processing. , as well as into SQL databases. Changes between network test snapshots taken at different times can be tracked in the built-in change manager. It can notify network administrators in...
</description></item><item><title>Download CoolUtils PDF Combine Pro 4.2.0.151/102</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Sep 2025 17:37:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-pdf-combine-pro-580.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-pdf-combine-pro-580.html
</guid><description>
CoolUtils PDF Combine Pro  is software that helps you combine  PDF, DOC, TXT, DOCX, HTML, XLS, images  h (TIFF, JPEG, PNG) and  email  as a  PDF  file. With PDF Combine Pro it is easier than ever to combine documents into one PDF file. Now you don't have to use some programs and converters to get a PDF. Everything for PDF Combine Pro to do for you.
Office, fax, email files - get combined PDF in seconds for personal use, commercial needs, electronic discovery, or manufacturing.  PDF...
</description></item><item><title>Download KLS Backup Professional 2025 v14.0.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Sep 2025 17:36:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kls-backup-professional-2951.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kls-backup-professional-2951.html
</guid><description>
KLS Backup Professional is a tool to backup and synchronize powerful allows you to backup or synchronize your information with the local drive and network, cloud storage, media, CD and DVD, WebDAV and FTP server. The backup documents can be stored uncompressed or compressed in Zip format or 7z basic. Backup KLS can backup: files or folders from the local disk, database, network locations or cloud storage, the mailbox data and other specific program (profile). Management in turn can...
</description></item><item><title>Download MusConv 4.10.419 Lifetime</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Sep 2025 17:36:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html
</guid><description>
MusConv transfers playlists, albums, followed artists and liked songs across a variety of services – Spotify, Apple Music, Amazon Music, YouTube, YouTube Music, iTunes, Deezer, Tidal, SoundCloud, Pandora and more 125 music services!
Features of MusConv Ultimate
	Transfer playlists, albums, followed artists and liked tracks between over 125 music servicesManage playlists (Delete, Merge, Split, Copy...)
	More than 125 music services supported
	Access DAILY updated music charts on...
</description></item><item><title>Download AOMEI Backupper WinPE 8.0 Technician Plus</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Sep 2025 17:36:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aomei-backupper-sever-99.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aomei-backupper-sever-99.html
</guid><description>
AOMEI Backupper server is a software backup and recovery professional, easy to use. It allows you to backup, secure Server, providing one-click backup your system partition or your disk and execute it in a few minutes. This software also can explore the created image and restore it on hard drive if your data gets lost or corrupted.
AOMEI Backupper sever what ?
AOMEI Backupper sever - backup data recovery sever
√ AOMEI Backupper sever also allows you to copy partitions or disk. The...
</description></item><item><title>Download Atlantis Word Processor 5.0.0.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Sep 2025 17:34:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-atlantis-word-processor-585.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-atlantis-word-processor-585.html
</guid><description>
Atlantis Word Processor is a word processor app with features format, standard text, autocorrect, and spell check.  Atlantis is a word processor in accordance with most of the tasks handled daily text. The interface is very easy to use and offers the toolbars, hotkeys and sound effects thanh can customize (can turn off). It includes a clip library for quick access to the text or images used regular preview, font format and many other features aimed at improving the process of your...
</description></item><item><title>Download Bitwig Studio 6.0 Beta 3</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Sep 2025 17:28:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bitwig-studio-3626.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bitwig-studio-3626.html
</guid><description>
Find new standard in the process of individual work. Bitwig Studio excite you good control over his music, give you access to all features of your production. Streamline course creation of you and quickly develop your ideas into the songs, compositions and music full.
Bitwig Studio - Create your own music
Arrange and record, perform and improvise, or do all at the same time. Choose among the many records displayed. Design your sound with the equipment container commitment. Mixing the...
</description></item><item><title>Download App Builder 2025.33</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Sep 2025 17:26:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-app-builder-241.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-app-builder-241.html
</guid><description>
App Builder is a software application developer to help create and design apps, HTML5, web app, web app PWA on both platforms mobile and desktop. App Builder is professional software supports users to create the program HTML5 without writing code. It is very easy to use, suitable with all users who lack of professional knowledge in the field of programming and application design.
App Builder brings to 22 different themes that users can use to design for your app. You can choose 1 or a...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cloanto Amiga Forever Plus Edition 11.1.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Sep 2025 17:26:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cloanto-amiga-forever-plus-edition-4743.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cloanto-amiga-forever-plus-edition-4743.html
</guid><description>
Cloanto Amiga Forever Plus Edition is the emulator, preservation and support of official Amiga of Cloanto, a software developer Commodore / Amiga brought to you from the 1980s. The different editions of Amiga Forever blend high-quality software and original content with the video great top to record the time and let you experience firsthand the history, culture, challenges and passion behind the Amiga.
The features of Cloanto Amiga Forever Plus Edition
	Interface player revolutionary...
</description></item></channel></rss>