<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 03:33:40 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 03:33:40 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download ChrisPC Free VPN Connection 4.25.1220</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Dec 2025 00:45:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-free-vpn-connection-2887.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-free-vpn-connection-2887.html
</guid><description>
ChrisPC Free VPN Connection software allows you to create VPN connection (virtual private network) to the server for free from the United States, Germany, Canada, France, Germany, Russia, Singapore, the Netherlands. This will help you to unblock your favorite sites to watch free TV and on-demand television when living abroad, travelling, on business or vacation. In addition, here is the solution to overcome the limited area for the popular websites: Google, YouTube, Facebook, Instagram,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Easy Duplicate Finder 7.36.0.78</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Dec 2025 00:42:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easy-duplicate-finder-2768.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easy-duplicate-finder-2768.html
</guid><description>
Easy Duplicate Finder is software to find and remove files duplicate on the computer. With this tool, you can restore gigabyte of capacity, make your computer faster and arrange your files. Manage duplicate files with Easy Duplicate Finder™ on your computer or Mac fast, simple and fun.
Easy Duplicate Finder has powerful features that will help you to find and delete the photos, documents, MP3, videos, emails and many more. It is fast to the incredible, accurate and easy to use. Just...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Downloader 10.0.11</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Dec 2025 00:42:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html
</guid><description>
YTD Youtube Downloader is an application that reliable and intuitive, allowing you to quickly download YouTube videos and save them to your computer. You can also convert the media files to the format desired video or extract audio streams and save separately. YTD Youtube Downloader lets you save your favorite clips of yourself from Youtube, Facebook, Vimeo and Dailymotion to your desktop. The software supports URLS from many web site hosting, multimedia and allows you to download desired...
</description></item><item><title>Download ClipboardFusion Pro 6.3</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Dec 2025 00:41:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-clipboardfusion-pro-894.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-clipboardfusion-pro-894.html
</guid><description>
ClipboardFusion Pro is the software easy to delete the text format to the clipboard, replace clipboard text or run powerful macro on the clipboard contents. In addition, you can sync your clipboard with other computers and mobile devices. The clipboard text is copied to the clipboard to be pasted into different applications without formatting. It can be done automatically or with a HotKey custom.
ClipboardFusion Pro - Remove, replace clipboard text
The main features of ClipboardFusion...
</description></item><item><title>Download Gilisoft Total Repair 11.3.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Dec 2025 00:41:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-total-repair-12836.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-total-repair-12836.html
</guid><description>
Total Repair Toolkit is an all-in-one system maintenance tool that integrates smart diagnosis, in-depth repair, and performance optimization. It has a one-click smart repair engine that can automatically resolve over 500 common problems such as system lag, game crashes, and file corruption. Meanwhile, it provides a professional manual repair module to meet advanced requirements.
Gilisoft Total Repair Features
	Application error repair based on a large DLL library
	In-depth diagnosis...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Photoshop 2026 v27.2.0.15 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Dec 2025 00:40:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-0010-adobe-photoshop-737.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-0010-adobe-photoshop-737.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Photoshop is a powerful raster graphics editor developed by Adobe Systems, primarily used for image editing, photo editing, and graphic design. Currently,&amp;nbsp;Adobe Photoshop 2025 is considered a graphic design software, creating and enhancing images, illustrations, and 3D artwork. In addition, it also supports website and mobile app design, video editing, real-life painting simulation, and more.
Adobe Photoshop 2025 - Graphic design
When it comes to Adobe Photoshop, it is...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tiny11 25H2 Build 26200.7462 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Dec 2025 00:39:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tiny11-8649.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tiny11-8649.html
</guid><description>
Tiny11 is a compact Windows operating system based on Windows 11 Pro 22H2, Tiny11 has everything you need for a comfortable, hassle-free computing experience. cumbersome and messy like a standard Windows installation. The operating system requires only 8GB of disk space and 2GB of RAM, and requires no TPM (Trusted Platform Module) and Secure Boot support.
The main goal of Tiny11 is to extend the reach of systems that can access Windows 11. The custom edition can run on any system...
</description></item><item><title>Download SUPERAntiSpyware Pro X 10.0.1282</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Dec 2025 00:38:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-superantispyware-pro-396.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-superantispyware-pro-396.html
</guid><description>
SUPER AntiSpyware Pro is a part mễm perfect provides the function of remove Spyware and Adware, Malware, Trojans, KeyLoggers, Dialers, Hi-Jackers from your computer. Besides the main task is prevent Spyware, SUPERAntiSpyware Pro also helps you to scan virus quickly, system restore and operate the computer fast, stable.
Main features SUPER AntiSpyware Pro
Detect and remove malicious threats:
	Prevent malware, spyware, adware, trojan, worm, ransomware, Hijackers, Parasites, Rootkits,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Clean Space Pro 2025 v716</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Dec 2025 00:37:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-clean-space-pro-545.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-clean-space-pro-545.html
</guid><description>
Clean Space Pro is the professional software remove junk files from the system to release the hard drive and improve computer performance. From time to time when using computer files as buffers, temporary files of various programs, files, internet cookies, internet browsing history, diary, file index.dat, registry entries and even the Windows will gradually increase, occupy wise space your hard drive and make the computer suffer from stagnation. The best solution is to use the Clean Space...
</description></item><item><title>Download Futuremark PCMark Pro 10 v2.3.2909</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Dec 2025 00:37:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-futuremark-pcmark-pro-1275.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-futuremark-pcmark-pro-1275.html
</guid><description>
Futuremark PCMark 10 Professional Edition is a suite of comprehensive test includes multiple tasks to be performed in the work environment modern. With the option of running quick, extended and customized in accordance with your needs, PCMark 10 is a standard PC complete for modern office and is the ideal choice for organizations that buy PC with big volume.
Futuremark PCMark Pro
PCMark 10 easy to install and run, no need for complex configuration. Running the benchmark itself and you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Prevent Restore Pro 2025 v116</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Dec 2025 00:35:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-prevent-restore-pro-1473.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-prevent-restore-pro-1473.html
</guid><description>
Prevent Restore Pro is software prevent restore files deleted in any drive: external hard drives and hard drives mounted in hard drive, SSD, Flash drives, except CD-ROM and CD-RW. The software uses many security algorithms can be used to get data.Our program includes some of the most reliable and accepted as standard.
Prevent Restore Pro - Prevent restore files deleted
The features of Prevent Restore Pro
Mode to clean up quickly
	In this mode, the program will not overwrite the free...
</description></item><item><title>Download TubeDownload Pro 7.0.9</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Dec 2025 00:35:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubedownload-pro-12035.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubedownload-pro-12035.html
</guid><description>
TubeDownload Pro is a professional Windows application for downloading your favorite videos from YouTube and hundreds of other video sites. TubeDownload Pro can increase download speed up to 500% or even more.
Features of TubeDownload Pro
	Download your favorite videos from YouTube and hundreds of other video sites.
	Increase download speed up to 500% or even more.
	Download 720p, 1080p, 2K, 4K and 8K HD videos from YouTube.
	Download entire playlists in just a few clicks.
	Download...
</description></item><item><title>Download MultiAlarm 1.4.1 + Portable</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Dec 2025 17:00:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-multialarm-12745.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-multialarm-12745.html
</guid><description>
MultiAlarm is a multi-timer and alarm setup tool with system tray, desktop widget, and RGB light notification on the keyboard. Each alarm can be configured for up to 24 hours, making them ideal for a variety of tasks that require constant reminders. Users can conveniently stop, restart, and reconfigure these alarms at any time, providing flexibility based on changing schedules or needs. Additionally, timed alarms are permanently stored in the system memory until you decide to delete...
</description></item><item><title>Download Executor 2.2.0.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Dec 2025 16:59:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-executor-271.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-executor-271.html
</guid><description>
Executor for windows is a software alternative premium customization features for the Windows "Run" and "Search Programs". When you press WIN + Z and provides the search results instant, as-you-type for any keywords you enter. By default, Executor will index all the Desktop and Start Menu and you can easily expand the search range by adding the folder location additional.
Executor for windows
The program comes with a list of commands built in which you can use to quickly access many...
</description></item><item><title>Download Screenpresso Pro 2.1.41</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Dec 2025 16:56:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-screenpresso-pro-1362.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-screenpresso-pro-1362.html
</guid><description>
Screenpresso Pro is a program easy to take great photos on your screen! Screenpresso blocked Print Screen key and screen capture the best in a few seconds. Allows you to capture windows and screen area, roll the part of the screen, edit the images obtained, add effects, resize a group of images, send screenshots by email and post them to Web resources.
Screenpresso Pro - Shooting the computer screen
Features of Screenpresso Pro
	Take the window and screen area. Take a partial screen...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare PDFelement Pro 12.1.3.3909</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Dec 2025 16:55:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-pdfelement-pro-105.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-pdfelement-pro-105.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare PDFelement Pro support users to convert PDF to office documents for easier use, modify in every situation. Is one of the software conversion material is rated best today, integrated with many features. We recommend that you should use experience software many useful features this.
Wondershare PDFelement Pro - conversion Fie PDF more features, multi-language
Wondershare PDFelement Pro what?
Convert PDF into Word, Excel, PowerPoint...
• Convert PDF and protected PDF into...
</description></item><item><title>Download JRiver Media Center 35.0.31</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Dec 2025 16:55:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jriver-media-center-110.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jriver-media-center-110.html
</guid><description>
JRiver Media Center can help you strictly manage all your files media and enjoy them in a completely new way. Launching the application for the first time, users will be immediately impressed with the intuitive and eye-catching interface with many interesting features to explore. Most people who have used JRiver Media Center evaluate that the software interface design is youthful and modern.
The software for arranging cover art of music files is also extremely neat, especially Insert...
</description></item><item><title>Download Astute Graphics Plug-ins Elite Bundle 4.4.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Dec 2025 16:54:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-astute-graphics-plug-ins-elite-bundle-5523.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-astute-graphics-plug-ins-elite-bundle-5523.html
</guid><description>
Astute Graphics Plug-ins Elite Bundle is a set of graphics editing tools for Adobe Illustrator. It includes many unique tools like Phantasm, VectorScribe, WidthScribe and many others. Get the complete set of plug-ins and transform your workflow in Illustrator. Add speed, ease, and precision with all our plug-ins and become the Astute Graphics Plug-in Elite Package!
Astute Graphics Plug-ins Elite Bundle Features:
	Correct alignment + selection
	Sketching visual vector
	Instantly...
</description></item><item><title>Download VectorStyler 1.3.004</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Dec 2025 16:54:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vectorstyler-7917.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vectorstyler-7917.html
</guid><description>
VectorStyler provides a complete set of drawing, design and illustration tools needed for modern design. Create illustrations, logos, icons, drawings, typography, vector art for screen, print and web. With many new features, VectorStyler redefines and extends the tools available to illustrators and designers, improving the creation of complex illustrations and designs.
Shape effects can be used to adjust the shape of objects, create different distortions, or add detail to shapes. Shape...
</description></item><item><title>Download ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro 15.25.1219</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Dec 2025 16:54:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-videotube-downloader-pro-1276.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-videotube-downloader-pro-1276.html
</guid><description>
ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro is the professional version support download videos and playlists from YouTube, videos from Dailymotion, BBC iPlayer, ITV Player, ABC,  FOX,CBS.com Vimeo, Prosieben, Metacafe, Blip.tv CBC.ca many more video sites. After the video is downloaded, you can convert them to the formats compatible with iPad, iPhone, iPod, MPEG-4, H. 264, MP3, AC3.
ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro - Download videos on Youtube
This is one of the software download the most...
</description></item><item><title>Download AB Download Manager 1.8.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Dec 2025 16:53:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ab-download-manager-12399.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ab-download-manager-12399.html
</guid><description>
With this application, you can easily download files from anywhere. Enjoy fast, free downloads with seamless browser extension support. It is built to be a desktop application that allows you to manage and organize your downloads better than before.
AB Download Manager features
	Simple and modern UI: Simple UI and dark mode by default
	Faster download speeds: Download files using multiple connections to increase your download speed by up to 500%
	Download Queue: Create and manage your...
</description></item><item><title>Download HitmanPro.Alert 3.21.1 Build 2033</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Dec 2025 16:53:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hitmanpro-alert-112.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hitmanpro-alert-112.html
</guid><description>
HitmanPro is a lightweight application that can monitor your browser activity and detect the hidden threats may include security systems. Tool HitmanPro is built specifically to add an additional layer of security for system of you, to protect you whenever you shop on the Internet , or perform banking activities online. It offers computer protection in real time against the exploitation of software, download at in drive, encryption software, online fraud and identity...
</description></item><item><title>Download Geekbench AI Corporate 1.6.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Dec 2025 16:52:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-geekbench-ai-corporate-12385.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-geekbench-ai-corporate-12385.html
</guid><description>
Geekbench AI is a cross-platform AI benchmark that uses real-world machine learning tasks to evaluate the performance of AI workloads. Geekbench AI measures your CPU, GPU, and NPU to determine whether your device is ready for today's and tomorrow's advanced machine learning applications.
Evaluating real-world AI performance:
Real-world AI performance
	Geekbench AI runs ten AI workloads, each with three different types of data, giving you a multidimensional picture of on-device AI...
</description></item><item><title>Download AntiPlagiarism.NET 4.153</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Dec 2025 16:52:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-antiplagiarismnet-2457.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-antiplagiarismnet-2457.html
</guid><description>
AntiPlagiarism NET is software to check the originality of some given text, most people find a section of text on the Internet, often the search engines quickly put out the answer to this question. Sometimes the results can be wrong, because not all results are accurate, a hundred percent. Fortunately, there are other solutions to the problem, for example, AntiPlagiarism.NET it can help you determine the originality of some given text. Application to operate correctly, you need to install...
</description></item><item><title>Download Metatogger 7.7.0.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Dec 2025 16:51:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-metatogger-62.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-metatogger-62.html
</guid><description>
Metatogger enables you to tag, rename and arrange the files Ogg Vorbis, FLAC, Speex and MP3 your. It allows you to rename files based on the existing cards of them and also follow the links folder of them (useful if the folder path of your contains artist name, and album are related).
Interface work modern
The interface of the utility is clean and intuitive. Import the audio track into the workspace is done by using the browser files, folder view, or the method of "drag and drop"; you...
</description></item></channel></rss>