<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 15:37:20 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 15:37:20 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download MetaProducts Offline Explorer Enterprise 8.8.0.5004</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Sep 2025 18:08:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-metaproducts-offline-explorer-enterprise-2653.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-metaproducts-offline-explorer-enterprise-2653.html
</guid><description>
MetaProducts Offline Explorer Enterprise is one of the most powerful programs to download both individual files and whole website. It works with HTTP, FTP and HTTPS. After download website to your hard drive, you can see it without need to connect to the Internet, and the download page will be much faster, because the Internet can sometimes work is slow, simply can different error.
MetaProducts Offline Explorer Enterprise is the leading application in the industry about storage and ing...
</description></item><item><title>Download Parted Magic 2025.09.18</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Sep 2025 18:01:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-parted-magic-2298.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-parted-magic-2298.html
</guid><description>
Powerful tools for home or Office! - Parted Magic is a solution to manage hard disk complete. PartedMagic has the tools to complete the job. With The edit partitions, you can resize, copy, and move partitions. You can grow or shrink your C: drive. Create space for the new operating system. Attempt data rescue from lost partitions.
A pack of very powerful utility has been updated is very useful to work with partitions of your hard disk based on the disk boot Linux. Please note that you can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Minimal Firewall 2.2.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Sep 2025 18:01:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minimal-firewall-13877.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minimal-firewall-13877.html
</guid><description>
Minimal Firewall works in conjunction with Windows Firewall to block all unknown connections by default, prompting you to create application-based rules to mitigate malware, telemetry, and data leaks. Completely eliminate applications that call home without your knowledge. Minimal Firewall provides a more secure and integrated approach by interacting directly with the native Windows Firewall, eliminating the need for risky system modifications.
Core Features
	Lockdown Mode: The core...
</description></item><item><title>Download Muziza YouTube Downloader Converter 8.15</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Sep 2025 17:56:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-muziza-youtube-downloader-converter-3972.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-muziza-youtube-downloader-converter-3972.html
</guid><description>
Muziza YouTube Downloader Converter is a tool to create conditions for an attractive interface and many features to help you to download video clips from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion, Instagram and other sites. Muziza YouTube Downloader Converter can also download the video UHD 8K, 5K, 4K, QHD 2K, HD 1080p and 720p from YouTube. The app allows you download only audio stream from YouTube and save as MP3. You don't need to download the entire video file.
Muziza YouTube Downloader...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tomabo MP4 Downloader Pro 5.8</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Sep 2025 17:55:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tomabo-mp4-downloader-pro-3602.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tomabo-mp4-downloader-pro-3602.html
</guid><description>
Tomabo MP4 Downloader Pro is the app designed exclusively for Windows users to help them download videos from the Internet. In addition, it also increase download speeds by up to 500%, or even more. Tomabo MP4 Downloader Pro, interface design, simple, well-organized, beautifully. Here, users can view a list of videos has download with gravatar, URL, quality, duration and size of them. Software allows download video series at the same time, at the same time, support create a list of clips...
</description></item><item><title>Download RizomUV Real &amp;amp; Virtual Space 2025.0.101</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Sep 2025 17:55:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rizomuv-real-virtual-space-1537.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rizomuv-real-virtual-space-1537.html
</guid><description>
RizomUV Real &amp;amp; Virtual Space known as Unold3D ago, is the perfect software to design a package or build texture laser. RizomUV Real Space includes all the features of RizomUV Virtual Space, but use ultraviolet rays to build and control the UV maps to the flat version over of your model will take all the size of it. This program allows you to get the mesh is not perpendicular three-dimensional, not even lasts for a few seconds. Mesh felt is produced with real size and get delivered in...
</description></item><item><title>Download Monkeys Audio 11.50</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Sep 2025 17:55:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-monkeys-audio-949.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-monkeys-audio-949.html
</guid><description>
Monkey\'s Audio is software that compresses digital music without loss of quality. Supports high quality WAV files and CD ripping. Monkeys Audio will compress .wav tracks into .ape files to reduce their size without loss of sound quality, decompress .ape, convert files, check file integrity and manage tags.
Unlike traditional methods like MP3 and OGG, which permanently remove quality to save space, Monkey\'s Audio only creates perfect copies with the same sound quality as the originals....
</description></item><item><title>Download Opera GX (Gaming Browser) 122.0.5643.52</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Sep 2025 17:54:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-gx-3170.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-gx-3170.html
</guid><description>
Opera GX is a special version of the Opera browser is built to complement gamers avid. Browser this game comes with the unique features to help users make maximum use of both the game and their browser. Opera GX is built specifically to support the game. This browser includes the unique features to help users have the best experience when gaming and surfing the web.
Opera GX - special browser for gamers
GX Control allows you to set a limit on the level of use RAM, CPU and network where...
</description></item><item><title>Download 4KSoftware 4K Downloader 5.18</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Sep 2025 17:53:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-downloader-3858.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-downloader-3858.html
</guid><description>
4K Downloader is a Windows application small but powerful to download and convert video in 4K and 8K Ultra HD from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion and thousands of other video-based websites. It speeds up your download by up to 5 times. Consider that most smart phones, TVS, computers, and tablets all support the high definition format, don't be surprised when many users want to enjoy quality content on their device. 4K Downloader is a lightweight software designed to help you grab videos...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sante PACS Server PG 4.2.5</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Sep 2025 17:53:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sante-pacs-server-pg-7540.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sante-pacs-server-pg-7540.html
</guid><description>
Sante PACS Server PG is an HTTP server (web) for DICOM files and a recorder and In CD/DVD with high performance and reliability. It provides connectivity with all the DICOM (CT, MR, US, CR, NM, XA, MG, DX, etc.). The review of the DICOM image can be done with the Sante PACS Viewer.
Integrated web servers can be used as a free cloud server for DICOM files!
</description></item><item><title>Download Social Media Downloader 7.8</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Sep 2025 17:49:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-socialmediaapps-facebook-video-downloader-3742.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-socialmediaapps-facebook-video-downloader-3742.html
</guid><description>
SocialVideo Downloader (formerly SocialMediaApps Facebook Video Downloader) is a Windows application to download and convert your favorite videos from Facebook and hundreds of other video sharing sites. It increases your loading speed by up to 500%, or even more! The application has a simple and intuitive user interface, its main functions and features are quite obvious to anyone. , regardless of prior experience with similar purpose tools.
&amp;nbsp;
SocialVideo Downloader
The main...
</description></item><item><title>Download ESEDatabaseView 1.79</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Sep 2025 17:49:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-esedatabaseview-6555.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-esedatabaseview-6555.html
</guid><description>
ESEDatabaseView is a simple utility that reads and displays data stored inside the Extensible Storage Engine database (ESE) (also known as 'Jet Blue' or .edb files). It displays a list of all the tables that are in the open database file, allowing you to select the desired table to view and then when you select a table, it displays all the records found in the selected table. ESEDatabaseView also allows you to easily select one or more records, then export them to a comma...
</description></item><item><title>Download FanCtrl 1.7.6</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Sep 2025 17:48:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fanctrl-5779.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fanctrl-5779.html
</guid><description>
FanCtrl is software that allows you to automatically control the fan speed on your PC. FanCtrl is easy to use, although the app is best for high-end users. You can cause damage to your computer due to overheating or conflict with other processors or other monitoring software. As an independent developed application, not all motherboards are or may be supported.
The application is well positioned and is located in the system tray with the name of the motherboard, every fan and control...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sante PACS Server 4.2.5</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Sep 2025 17:48:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sante-pacs-server-7541.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sante-pacs-server-7541.html
</guid><description>
Sante PACS Server is an HTTP (web) server for DICOM files and a CD/DVD Burn and Print server that offers high performance and reliability at an affordable price. It provides connectivity to all DICOM methods (CT, MR, US, CR, NM, XA, MG, DX, etc.). Reviewing of DICOM images can be done using the Sante PACS Viewer (the system's built-in, full-featured DICOM Viewer). The built-in web server can be used as a free cloud server for DICOM files!
Tools of Sante PACS Server
	The Migration Tool...
</description></item><item><title>Download PentaLogix CAMMaster Designer 11.24.60</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Sep 2025 17:47:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pentalogix-cammaster-designer-13705.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pentalogix-cammaster-designer-13705.html
</guid><description>
CAMMaster Designer is the CAM software of choice for designers for their most demanding jobs. Experience the industry's best CAD companion to get your work done. Panelization is easy with all the features included in this package. Netlist and DRC extraction set the industry standard.
Highlights
	Contour-based netlist extraction
	Advanced DFM inspection
	Automatic aperture conversion
	Layer comparison
	Network conversion
	Automatic conversion from draw to flash
	Solder mask...
</description></item><item><title>Download FanControl v240</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Sep 2025 17:47:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fancontrol-5749.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fancontrol-5749.html
</guid><description>
FanControl is a highly customizable fan control software for Windows. Stay in control of every aspect of your PC's GPU and CPU fan with the help of this highly customizable fan control app.
Features of FanControl
	Save, edit and load multiple configurations
	Multiple temperature sources (CPU, GPU, motherboard, hard drive, ".sensor" files)
	Custom fan curve
	Fine tune fan control response with steps,% start,% stop, response time and delay
	Mix different curves and sensors...
</description></item><item><title>Download Multi Commander 15.6 Build 3119</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Sep 2025 17:46:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-multi-commander-2038.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-multi-commander-2038.html
</guid><description>
Multi Commander is a file manager, multi tab and is an alternative to the Windows Explorer standard. It uses the table layout control dual very popular and effective. Multi Commander has everything you need in daily work with files to increase speed and efficiency.
Multi Commander - file Manager
Multi Commander has all the standard features that any manager files would have, such as copy, move, rename, view. But the strong point of Multi Command is the special feature allows you to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Kaslaan AImage Tools 1.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Sep 2025 15:00:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kaslaan-aimage-tools-14162.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kaslaan-aimage-tools-14162.html
</guid><description>
Here's a new app from KaslaanSoft called Kaslaan AI Image Tools. It brings together AI-based image processing tools in one place. Currently, it includes a background removal tool and an enhancement tool. Let's start with the background removal tool. You can process a single image or, for batch processing, select a folder containing multiple images. In the model selection section, choose the model that best suits your photo or photos.
The output background can be transparent or solid,...
</description></item><item><title>Download S&amp;amp;P Global QUE$TOR 2025 Q1</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Sep 2025 14:52:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sp-global-quetor-14161.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sp-global-quetor-14161.html
</guid><description>
QUE$TOR provides concept screening, optimization, and detailed CAPEX/OPEX cost estimation for oil and gas. The QUE$TOR suite includes the QUE$TOR Offshore, QUE$TOR Onshore, and QUE$TOR LNG Regasification modules. With a comprehensive cost database with multiple attributes, technologies, and equipment, cost estimating engineers, financial analysts, executives, and M&amp;amp;A analysts.
Use this software to
	Accurately model oil and gas costs and production;
	Schedule development;
	Save...
</description></item><item><title>Download Eusing Cleaner 6.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Sep 2025 23:35:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-eusing-cleaner-2912.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-eusing-cleaner-2912.html
</guid><description>
Eusing Cleaner app is free to use system optimization and cleaning tools right to privacy. It level for you to explore and delete the old file in your system, the registry files null, delete your internet history, provides added support to clean the history for over 150 programs of side Tuesday. You can select the items that you want cleaned and also specify cookies should not be deleted. With just a click of the mouse, Eusing Cleaner can clear the memory auto-completion, cookies, the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Secret Disk Pro 2025 v313</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Sep 2025 23:34:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secret-disk-pro-933.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secret-disk-pro-933.html
</guid><description>
Secret Disk Pro 4 is a software to create a virtual disk can be hidden and password protected to keep your data private and safe. You can store any file and folder on the disk. Disc secret works like a hard disk typically, and is compatible with any any other program that you have installed. You can have more than one disk secret, and you can also choose disk letter.
Secret Disk Pro 4 - Create and secure drive
Secret Disk does not encrypt any files, it just limits access to your files...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare Repairit 6.5.15.9</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Sep 2025 23:33:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-recoverit-video-repair-3889.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-recoverit-video-repair-3889.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare Recoverit Video Repair is a reliable application that helps you fix the broken video, Wondershare Recoverit Video Repair supports file formats MP4, MOV, M4V, M2TS, MKV, MTS, 3GP, AVI and FLV is corrupt and broken. Great service we provide. It fixes the video that there is corruption in the process of shooting, when done, file transfer, while editing, convert.
Wondershare Recoverit Video Repair - video repair broken
Features of Wondershare Recoverit Video Repair
	Repair...
</description></item><item><title>Download Foxit PDF Editor Pro 2025.2.0.33046 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Sep 2025 23:33:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-foxit-pdf-editor-pro-162.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-foxit-pdf-editor-pro-162.html
</guid><description>
Foxit PDF Editor Pro (formerly Foxit PhantomPDF Business) is a PDF toolkit dedicated to the creation of professional PDF documents and forms. You can do that for tasks such as personal document development, working group collaboration, company model design. Manufacturing the company's collateral, completing the agreements, applying the signature number or document storage.
Foxit PDF Editor Pro is the perfect solution for family/family offices, small and medium enterprises and large...
</description></item><item><title>Download Memtest86 Pro 11.5 Build 1000</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Sep 2025 23:32:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-memtest86-pro-725.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-memtest86-pro-725.html
</guid><description>
Memtest86 Pro is software check free RAM memory in your computer to detect the latent fault inside the memory. Anyone know RAM is very important part of the computer. If RAM is error that does not fix soon will greatly affect your computer. Therefore, the Memtest86 Pro is the software necessary for the system of your computer.
Memtest86 Pro - Check memory RAM
Features of Memtest86 Pro
	13 algorithm to check RAM different
	Support RAM DDR4 (and DDR2 &amp;amp; DDR3)
	XMP - configuration...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mocha Pro for Adobe 2025.5 v12.5.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Sep 2025 23:31:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mocha-pro-1029.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mocha-pro-1029.html
</guid><description>
Mocha Pro 2019 is the tool for visual effects and postproduction. Tool Tracking and VFX and is plugins for Adobe. Mocha is the artist and editor effects appreciate about the unique ability of his to reduce the time using keyframing related to VFX and premium finishing.
Mocha Pro 2019
Mocha Pro 2019 features track and remove objects that are GPU acceleratedtools, rotoscoping, advanced, stable, solved 3D camera, supports stereo 360 / VR, etc. Using Mocha AE CC in Adobe After Effects? See...
</description></item></channel></rss>