<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 03:44:05 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 03:44:05 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Hypersnap 9.7.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 23:31:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hypersnap-764.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hypersnap-764.html
</guid><description>
Hypersnap is a software screen capture from Windows screen and capture text (TextSnap) from places can't copy normal text. HyperSnap combines the power of screen capture app class with utility image editing advanced is packaged in a easy to use tool! It's perfect for capturing images that you want to put into the help system, online tutorials, manuals, training guides, presentations, marketing materials, website, email, and more. Use HyperSnap to quickly share a picture perfect...
</description></item><item><title>Download Allavsoft Video Downloader Converter 3.28.8.9526</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 23:30:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allavsoft-video-downloader-converter-248.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allavsoft-video-downloader-converter-248.html
</guid><description>
Allavsoft Video Downloader Converter software supports download movies, music videos, playlist, sport videos from video sharing website for free like Facebook, Youtube and over 100 video sharing sites.
Allavsoft is many users favorite thanks to the combined features simultaneous transmission of multiple videos and speed limit download video. Besides, the program also supports pause and resume data transmission, to help you interfere with the process of transmitting download data to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Free YouTube Download 4.5.4.130 Premium</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 23:30:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-download-1177.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-download-1177.html
</guid><description>
Free YouTube Download Premium is the most popular application to download videos from YouTube. The program was released in 2006 and regularly updated since then. Use the program to download and convert YouTube videos to view offline anytime.
Free YouTube Download - added Support to download youtube
Download more videos! Save whole playlists and YouTube channels, videos from a playlist individually (history, video be favorite, favourites, Watch later), videos from many different...
</description></item><item><title>Download Coolutils Total Excel Converter 7.1.0.107</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 23:29:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-total-excel-converter-849.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-total-excel-converter-849.html
</guid><description>
Coolutils Total Excel Converter is software that converts Excel documents to other formats like ODS, XML, SQL, WK2, WKS WAB, DBF, TEX and DIF for you to use. In addition, the software also supports converting Excel files into file DOC, DOCX, PDF, HTML, Access, TXT, ODT, ODS, XML, SQL, CSV, Lotus, DBF, TEX, DIFF, SYLK and LaTeX.
Coolutils Total Excel Converter - batch convert Excel
Total Excel Converter has a perfect layout and tight. When the conversion is finished you will get an...
</description></item><item><title>Download Calibre 9.1.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 23:29:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-calibre-1669.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-calibre-1669.html
</guid><description>
Calibre  is an eBook library management application that allows you to manage your eBook collection, convert eBooks between different formats, Sync with popular e-reading devices and read your e-books with included viewer. You can sort books by author, title, date and other details, download meta information and book covers, add personalized tags and comments, and view your images in the cover display.
Collection of essential tools for adding metadata editing books or managing your...
</description></item><item><title>Download O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro 22.1.242 / Server</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 23:29:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-diskimage-pro-218.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-diskimage-pro-218.html
</guid><description>
O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro is software backup data comprehensive and effective is provided to protect the data of the computer system, it creates images for individual drives or the entire system that still does not affect your system.
O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro allows the user to backup the entire computer or drive, the and files whenever you want even while the computer is being used. Or can use O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro to create a copy chinh sac of computer disk drives, can be used instead of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Photomatix Pro 7.1.4 RC 1</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 23:28:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photomatix-pro-2535.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photomatix-pro-2535.html
</guid><description>
Photomatix Pro is software to help merge the photos were taken at the level of different exposures into a HDR image only for see all the details, highlights and shadows, with the option to automatically align the photo handheld, removing ghosts, and reducing noise and chromatic aberration. Then, the picture is mixed can be adjusted by a variety of options and settings to get the look that users want from the results look natural by using fusion to photos, graphics, super real or surreal...
</description></item><item><title>Download Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium 4.5.4.130</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 23:28:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-to-mp3-converter-premium-844.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-to-mp3-converter-premium-844.html
</guid><description>
Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium version is a software used to convert YouTube to MP3, extract audio from playlists YouTube, show listings, charts, video responses, channels, favorites of the user. With Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium, you can download and convert playlists, channels, stream original tv series and get them into iTunes at the same time.
Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium - convert YouTube to MP3
Features Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium from the...
</description></item><item><title>Download DISMTools 0.7.2 Update 1</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 23:27:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dismtools-12200.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dismtools-12200.html
</guid><description>
Inspired by Visual Studio, DISMTools is a user interface for DISM that allows you to manage Windows Imaging (WIM) files and much more. You can use it to uninstall apps, add driver or tool packages, etc.
DISM: This is a tool used to maintain and repair Windows images. This includes Windows Recovery Environment, Windows Setup, and Windows PE (WinPE). You can also use DISM to repair Windows images locally on your computer.
DISMTools: This is a user-friendly interface that allows you to...
</description></item><item><title>Download TidyWindow 4.5.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 23:26:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tidywindow-14454.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tidywindow-14454.html
</guid><description>
TidyWindow is a Windows desktop assistant that automates developer PC setup, cleanup, diagnostics, software package installation, registry tweaking, and driver updates—powered by a WPF interface and robust PowerShell 7 automation capabilities in the background.
Key Features
	Essentials Repair Center (docs/essentials.md): Queues selected automation tasks Filter for network, Defender, printing, and Windows Update issues. Each task supports preview run, sequential execution, restore...
</description></item><item><title>Download Song List Generator 6.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 23:26:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-song-list-generator-2376.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-song-list-generator-2376.html
</guid><description>
Song List Generator is software that support you to create song books professional from files MP3, karaoke, or video of you in just a few clicks. This tool is very useful for DJ, KJ or anyone storing their music on hard drive and want to have the song professionally without the hassle in maintaining the database.
The list of songs just read the music files right from your hard drive and create a song book can print, cut and chopped in any way you want (by artist, title, DiscID,...
</description></item><item><title>Download XL-Connector 3.6.43.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 23:25:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xl-connector-12415.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xl-connector-12415.html
</guid><description>
XL-Connector is a popular plugin that securely integrates Excel and Salesforce to export, import, refresh and transform data seamlessly with ultra-fast api connection. It provides Salesforce administrators with a comprehensive toolbox that easily performs data and metadata management activities in a familiar Excel environment.
Features
Export from Salesforce to Excel
	Get data from existing Salesforce reports or build your own SOQL queries directly into Excel.
Import data into...
</description></item><item><title>Download CoolUtils Total Doc Converter 5.1.0.371/143</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 23:25:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-total-doc-converter-84.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-total-doc-converter-84.html
</guid><description>
CoolUtils Total Doc Converter Program that will allow you to document conversion DOC to others, the list can be viewed on the official website or you can watch carefully the screenshot, I think the question would no longer can download CoolUtils Total Doc Converter below. There is batch processing,in general, everything is convenient, I hope you like it.
Total Doc Converter is conversion tools text comprehensive and multi-featured, very necessary when storing or printing the text. It also...
</description></item><item><title>Download Coder Technologies Coder 2.28.9</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 23:24:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coder-oss-enterprise-8726.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coder-oss-enterprise-8726.html
</guid><description>
Coder OSS Enterprise is a development platform that provides a complete cloud-based solution for software development, testing and deployment. It is designed to simplify the software development process by providing developers with a collaborative and streamlined environment.
Coder offloads development from local workstations to your on-premises infrastructure and public cloud. Boost developer productivity with powerful server resources and instant integration. Keep the code and data...
</description></item><item><title>Download Karaosoft KJ/DJ File Manager 4.0.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 23:24:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kj-file-manager-2378.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kj-file-manager-2378.html
</guid><description>
KJ File Manager is a program that will allow you to easily manage the audio and video files in karaoke format, you can now record MP3 tags ID and edit metadata information, done all in batch mode.
Easily manage files karaoke, video and audio of you and fixes title easily with batch editing powerful. Support the format name standard most popular. Automatic fix for underscores and capitalization, swap title and artist, shift, split, and replace field data on multiple files at once,...
</description></item><item><title>Download AnyDesk 9.6.9</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 18:20:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anydesk-1321.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anydesk-1321.html
</guid><description>
AnyDesk is software computer control remote, easy connection with remote computer management and manipulation on the computer. After installing the AnyDesk up 2 the computer then you can easily use the software to provide technical support for a friend or family member or you have access to your computer while you away from home or office.
AnyDesk - control your computer remotely
The process of using very simple software, want to allow access to his computer, only need to provide for...
</description></item><item><title>Download PrivaZer Pro Donors 4.0.117</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 18:19:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-privazer-donors-198.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-privazer-donors-198.html
</guid><description>
PrivaZer Donors  cleans and removes filth traces from the system. Intensive cleaning of unwanted traces of what you've done, viewed, downloaded, deleted, etc. Take ownership of your security and freedom - Free up disk space. Keep your PC snug and secure !!!
With one click, PrivaZer can safely clean: Internet browsers, Index.dat, Cookies, Tor Cookies, Flash Cookies, Silverlight Cookies, DOM Storing, IndexedDB, AppCache Registry, RAM, Pagefile.sys and Hiberfil.sys files.  PrivaZer  can...
</description></item><item><title>Download EndNote 2025.3.1 Build 19926</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 18:18:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-endnote-4237.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-endnote-4237.html
</guid><description>
EndNote X9 as a researcher, you constantly carry the different roles, addressing the competing demands on your time and coordinate not only the activities of the own in study published that all your collaborators on the whole and on the whole world. EndNote X9 is software management reference not only frees you from the tedious work in collecting and managing research material and format folder manually but also help you easy and more controlled in coordination with colleagues.
EndNote...
</description></item><item><title>Download AI FaceSwap 2.6.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 18:18:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ai-faceswap-11511.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ai-faceswap-11511.html
</guid><description>
AI FaceSwap uses artificial intelligence (AI) algorithms to swap faces between two or more people in an image or camera. This technology leverages deep learning techniques, especially convolutional neural networks (CNN), to accurately detect and manipulate facial features.
The algorithm identifies important facial landmarks such as eyes, nose, mouth, etc. to understand the structure and orientation of each face. The faces are then aligned to ensure that the corresponding facial features...
</description></item><item><title>Download JRiver Media Center 35.0.40</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 18:16:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jriver-media-center-110.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jriver-media-center-110.html
</guid><description>
JRiver Media Center can help you strictly manage all your files media and enjoy them in a completely new way. Launching the application for the first time, users will be immediately impressed with the intuitive and eye-catching interface with many interesting features to explore. Most people who have used JRiver Media Center evaluate that the software interface design is youthful and modern.
The software for arranging cover art of music files is also extremely neat, especially Insert...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tiny11 25H2 Build 26200.7627 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 18:15:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tiny11-8649.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tiny11-8649.html
</guid><description>
Tiny11 is a compact Windows operating system based on Windows 11 Pro 22H2, Tiny11 has everything you need for a comfortable, hassle-free computing experience. cumbersome and messy like a standard Windows installation. The operating system requires only 8GB of disk space and 2GB of RAM, and requires no TPM (Trusted Platform Module) and Secure Boot support.
The main goal of Tiny11 is to extend the reach of systems that can access Windows 11. The custom edition can run on any system...
</description></item><item><title>Download By Click Downloader 2.4.29</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 18:15:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-by-click-premium-193.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-by-click-premium-193.html
</guid><description>
YouTube By Click Premium is a high quality powerful video downloader including YouTube downloader, YouTube Converter, YouTube Chrome Downloader, Facebook Video Downloader, Downloader Vimeo, Dailymotion Downloader and supports many other video sites.
YouTube By Click
YouTube By Click Features
	YouTube by Click can download and convert files to MP3, MP4, FLV, AVI, WMV, 3GP, WAV and WEBM formats.
	Download all supported qualities, including HD.
	YouTube By Click downloads entire YouTube...
</description></item><item><title>Download Revive Faces 2.0.12</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 18:14:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-revive-faces-13762.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-revive-faces-13762.html
</guid><description>
Have you ever looked at an old photo or video and wished you could see those faces clearly again? Time, blurriness, and pixels shouldn't steal the smiles, glances, or stories of the people you love. With Revive Faces, our breakthrough AI-powered restoration software, blurry, smudged, and pixelated faces can now shine with stunning clarity—as if they were taken yesterday.
Why Restore Faces?
	See the unseen again – Our advanced AI not only sharpens images, but also recreates lost...
</description></item><item><title>Download Active UNDELETE Ultimate 26.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 18:14:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-active-undelete-ultimate-2716.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-active-undelete-ultimate-2716.html
</guid><description>
Active Undelete is recovery software powerful data to help you recover the deleted files and restore partitions deleted. The Pro version of the software Active Undelete has the advanced features like recovery volume / partition has been deleted, the editing part volume boot and the possibility to modify the partition rollback. Package contains the files ISO image that you can use to create CD / DVD / USB that can boot to launch the computer can't execute. If your system does not boot and...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube Downloader 3.9.18 (3001)</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 18:14:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube Downloader  is a dedicated software that helps users  downloading youtube videos  Favorites on PC for offline viewing. With MediaHuman YouTube  Downloader  you can download videos from youtube website to your computer with  fast speed , with special software development technology that automatically receives videos from Websites, in addition to the ability to download videos from software websites, can convert downloaded video formats to various formats for the purpose...
</description></item></channel></rss>