<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 23:47:13 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 23:47:13 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download XnViewMP 1.9.7</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Dec 2025 23:44:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xnview-mp-1074.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xnview-mp-1074.html
</guid><description>
XnViewMP "XnView MP" is the enhanced version of XnView Classic. This is the view and convert images multi-platform powerful, compatible with more than 500 image formats, different today. XnView MP easily export images to about 70 file format is different. Similar to XnConvert, XnView MP also features integrated switch at the same time batch file to help you process photos faster. XnView is another version of the photo viewer but with the ability to support formats more limited.
XnView...
</description></item><item><title>Download BluffTitler Ultimate 16.8.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Dec 2025 23:44:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bluffTitler-ultimate-39.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bluffTitler-ultimate-39.html
</guid><description>
Create 3D titles brilliant for your video with BluffTitler Ultimate. You want to impress your friends and clients with 3D titles interesting? But don't want to spend a fortune on 3D animation, as well as professional software video titling?
BluffTitler is the easiest way to add animated text, 3D spectacular for photos and videos of you! Other 3D programs always seemed too hard to learn and too expensive to justify. But thanks to BluffTitler, I can finally create all the wonderful...
</description></item><item><title>Download VideoProc Converter AI 8.6</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Dec 2025 23:43:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-videoproc-2473.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-videoproc-2473.html
</guid><description>
VideoProc (an improved version of WinX HD Video Converter Deluxe) - processing software the most powerful video designed to edit, cut, crop, merge, adjust, convert and compress (4K) video with full Hardware Acceleration. Is the heir to be improved a lot, VideoProc integrated conversion / compression video UHD, the download at videos (YouTube) with the video editor, gives you the power to control optimal for every video file much music, SD, HD and 4K on your PC. With technology hardware...
</description></item><item><title>Download Google Chrome 143.0.7499.41</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Dec 2025 23:43:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-chrome-1012.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-chrome-1012.html
</guid><description>
Google Chrome web browser is the most used today. Support surf the web, listen to music, watch movies, play web game effective no jerky lag with the internet connection stable. When you are surfing the web or performing an important task, whether it is operation big or small, work or entertainment, then Chrome has the smart features and the speed you need to make, create and explore on the net.
The latest version of Google Chrome is the third 114. But we are providing for users Google...
</description></item><item><title>Download Atlantis Word Processor 5.0.0.12</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Dec 2025 23:42:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-atlantis-word-processor-585.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-atlantis-word-processor-585.html
</guid><description>
Atlantis Word Processor is a word processor app with features format, standard text, autocorrect, and spell check.  Atlantis is a word processor in accordance with most of the tasks handled daily text. The interface is very easy to use and offers the toolbars, hotkeys and sound effects thanh can customize (can turn off). It includes a clip library for quick access to the text or images used regular preview, font format and many other features aimed at improving the process of your...
</description></item><item><title>Download PMAS - PowerShell Multi Activation System 8.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Dec 2025 23:42:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-powershell-tsf-activation-13584.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-powershell-tsf-activation-13584.html
</guid><description>
This advanced PowerShell script is a flexible and modular solution designed for licensing Windows and Office products. It runs a custom .NET library called LibTSforge.dll directly from memory to license Office. It can work in GUI mode or silent mode.
Features
	License management for both Windows and Office products
	Generate product keys with the help of LibTSforge.dll
	User-friendly graphical options with Out-GridView
	Compatible with KMS, MAK, RETAIL, OEM, AVMA license types
	In...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Acrobat Pro DC 2025.001.20982 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Dec 2025 23:41:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-001en-adobe-acrobat-pro-458.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-001en-adobe-acrobat-pro-458.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Acrobat Pro DC is a comprehensive software that helps you create and edit the PDF&amp;nbsp;document, or create form, sign, protect PDF, connect, split PDF, export PDF to various formats. The Acrobat Pro DC is the latest version of Adobe with improvements in the interface with the polished ribbon bar and the ability to create and handle pdf files as well as its male versions.
The highlight of the Acrobat Pro DC is probably the ability to connect, store documents on the cloud, you can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Able2Extract Professional 21.0.1.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Dec 2025 23:40:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-able2extract-professional-3133.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-able2extract-professional-3133.html
</guid><description>
Able2Extract Professional is a PDF conversion only on the market to help increase efficiency, productivity PDF of you on Windows. Convert PDF format to Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Publisher, AutoCAD and CSV. Get photo create perfect PDF with the optional enhanced security and quickly modify text and page PDF. Fill in, edit and create the PDF form can be filled right in the Able2Extract or insert the order number on long PDF documents. All the tasks are performed in a user interface smooth...
</description></item><item><title>Download Replay Media Catcher 2026.1.1.32</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Dec 2025 23:39:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-replay-media-catcher-1560.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-replay-media-catcher-1560.html
</guid><description>
Replay Media Catcher is a tool to convert and download videos best today and support downloads, audio / MP3, or recording. Replay Media Catcher using technology download enhanced to record video, and MP3 files with playback speed up to 10 times. Integrates with iTunes, DropBox, Google Drive or SkyDrive for automatically copying files to your phone or tablet, Apple or Android your.
Replay Media Catcher - convert and download video
Software Replay Media Catcher software is download at...
</description></item><item><title>Download Zoom Player Max 22.0 RC3</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Dec 2025 23:38:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zoom-player-max-104.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zoom-player-max-104.html
</guid><description>
Zoom Player MAX help you to see the film on DVD, Blu-ray, Flash movies and HD format with high quality and the ability to display subtitles in English very well. The advantage of software is that takes up very little system resources to play the movie with quick speed, change the wallpaper options while viewing movies.
Zoom Player MAX is the movies, browse high-quality photos on the computer with the advantages such as compact size, quick start, built-in codec. The application supports...
</description></item><item><title>Download VovSoft Website Watcher 2.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Dec 2025 23:37:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-website-watcher-10719.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-website-watcher-10719.html
</guid><description>
VovSoft Website Watcher is a powerful and user-friendly website monitoring tool, suitable for both beginners and advanced users. The software allows users to monitor many different types of websites, including RSS/Atom feeds. It provides notifications about changes on competitors' websites, price adjustments, product availability, updates to favorite websites, modifications to the user's home page, and more. The tool runs as a client on the user's computer, ensuring full control over the...
</description></item><item><title>Download FileLocator Pro 2022 Build 3542</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Dec 2025 23:37:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-filelocator-pro-1056.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-filelocator-pro-1056.html
</guid><description>
FileLocator Pro is software manage files and search function the file quickly the software and data. FileLocator Pro helps you find things quickly. The unique feature of it allows the extraction of information in all file formats the most obscure.
FileLocator Pro - file Manager
The features of FileLocator Pro
	Search algorithm based on the C ++ multi-threading for ultra-fast
	Search for network drive by mapped drive or UNC paths
	Support regular expressions for file name and...
</description></item><item><title>Download DBF Converter 7.69</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Dec 2025 23:36:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbf-converter-6362.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbf-converter-6362.html
</guid><description>
DBF Converter is a common solution for all your DBF format conversion needs. Whenever you need to extract data from the DBF file to CSV, XLS, XLSX, SQL or pure text, the software will provide a simple way to do this with minimal effort.
Features of DBF Converter
	Work with DBF Converter is easy. You specify a DBF file or a directory with DBF files that you want to convert, select the fields and filter out the records you need. Then, just a click to DBF Converter to turn the source...
</description></item><item><title>Download Exacoustics GHOST 1.1.10</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Dec 2025 23:36:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-exacoustics-ghost-13879.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-exacoustics-ghost-13879.html
</guid><description>
Exacoustics GHOST is a powerful and innovative synthesis plugin that uniquely combines Wavetable synthesis and Frequency Modulation (FM) synthesis into one integrated instrument. Released in August 2024 by Brisbane-based developer Exacoustics, the plugin quickly gained attention for its fresh approach and deep sound design capabilities.
Key Features:
	Hybrid Synthesis Engine: Combines the flexibility of wavetable oscillators with the complexity and richness of FM synthesis.
	Six...
</description></item><item><title>Download Super Grate 1.5.1.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Dec 2025 23:34:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-super-grate-11261.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-super-grate-11261.html
</guid><description>
Super Grate is a Windows User Profile backup and migration utility. With GUI (Graphical User Interface) supports Microsoft's USMT (User State Migration Utility) in performing remote migrations over a network connection.
Super Grate Features
	Easy to tweak, easy to configure. Help Super Grate work efficiently by changing one of the many configurable settings.
	Are all your computers connected to an Active Directory domain? Super Grate will be able to perform Migration &amp;amp; Backup over...
</description></item><item><title>Download CapCut PC 7.5.0.3053 / 7.6.0.3120 Beta 8</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Dec 2025 23:29:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capcut-pc-9995.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capcut-pc-9995.html
</guid><description>
CapCut PC is a simple video editing tool that you can freely use anywhere. You can create videos on your browser, desktop and laptop, or on your phone. Versatile editing, magical AI tools, team collaboration, and built-in assets. Create videos in a whole new way.
You can edit videos based on editing the timeline, in the process you can add different elements and effects to the video to give the best effect to your work. It is a simple and intuitive set of editing tools and effects that...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cubase Pro 15.0.6</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Dec 2025 22:42:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-steinberg-cubase-pro-3528.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-steinberg-cubase-pro-3528.html
</guid><description>
Steinberg Cubase Pro - The highest and most professional from the publisher Steinberg. Current program Steinberg Cubase Pro is priced near$ 600. But we will provide versions completely free for you. Can you might also like more simple versions, you can download version Cubase Elements at our website.
Steinberg Cubase Pro - music Production professional
Steinberg Cubase Pro is one of the pack music creation software, the most powerful in the world. With a variety of tools, unparalleled...
</description></item><item><title>Download Winaero Tweaker 1.64.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Dec 2025 22:41:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winaero-tweaker-1063.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winaero-tweaker-1063.html
</guid><description>
Winaero Tweaker is a customization tool is provided for windows for you to change the default settings, and personalization Windows liking. The program includes the tweaks for all version of operating system from Windows 7 to Windows 10. Winaero Tweaker automatically detect OS version of Windows you're running and show the custom and custom custom. Software can be installed as a mobile app so that you can carry with you when you move from this computer to another computer.
Winaero...
</description></item><item><title>Download Steinberg Nuendo 14.0.41</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Dec 2025 22:39:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-steinberg-nuendo-7928.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-steinberg-nuendo-7928.html
</guid><description>
As the most advanced audio post-production solution available, Nuendo is the choice of professionals in the motion picture, television, game and immersive sound industries. all around the world. Since its initial release, Nuendo has been an important tool in creating the soundtracks for many well-known works, productions and settings.
Regular updates with new features, workflow improvements, and additional, user-requested functions mean that the Nuendo is constantly exceeding the...
</description></item><item><title>Download LastPass Password Manager 5.3.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Dec 2025 22:39:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lastpass-269.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lastpass-269.html
</guid><description>
LastPass is a free software to help manage passwords allows you to store all the login information of your site in a warehouse password cross-platform compatibility only. Instead of remember the user name and personal password, you only need to remember the main password to open the lock the password of his safe.
LastPass
LastPass can automatically fill in the login box for all the account website is your hosting. Whenever you log into a website has stored your vault, the program will...
</description></item><item><title>Download Xreveal 2.8.8</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Dec 2025 22:38:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xreveal-7252.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xreveal-7252.html
</guid><description>
Xreveal is an application similar to AnyDVD. This is an interactive research and purpose project. Xreveal does NOT contain any decryption key, it is based solely on the official public AACS specification. You need the decryption key or key database to make it work.
Features of Xreveal
	Remove Blu-ray AACS 1.0 protection
	Remove Blu-ray AACS 2.0 (UHD) protection
	Remove BD+ protection
	Remove BDAV Protection
	Remove DVD CSS protection
	Remove CPRM Protection
	Remove CPPM...
</description></item><item><title>Download Radiant Photo 2.2.0.818 + Addon Pack</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Dec 2025 22:38:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-radiant-photo-8319.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-radiant-photo-8319.html
</guid><description>
Radiant Photo is a photo editing software that allows users to edit, enhance and organize their digital photos. It provides many tools to adjust color, brightness, contrast, saturation, and other image properties, as well as features to crop, rotate, and resize images.
Radiant Photo also includes many filters and effects that can be applied to photos to change their appearance. Additionally, it also allows users to organize their photos by creating albums, tagging photos, and searching...
</description></item><item><title>Download Private Windows Script (PrivWindoze) 5.8.4</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Dec 2025 22:37:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-private-windows-script-12878.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-private-windows-script-12878.html
</guid><description>
Are you concerned about your personal information sent to others? Or do you feel that your Windows settings have many programs that you never use? Private Windows Script (or Privwindoze) provides a comprehensive anti -remote monitoring set designed to enhance your privacy when using Windows operating system.
The main features
	End the positive process. All unnecessary processes are turned off while the scanning program. A small white list is maintained.
	Clean up the positive runonce....
</description></item><item><title>Download Kingston SSD Manager 1.5.6.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Dec 2025 22:37:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kingston-ssd-manager-2810.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kingston-ssd-manager-2810.html
</guid><description>
Kingston SSD Manager is an application that gives users the ability to track and manage the various aspects of solid state drives Kingston® his.
Kingston SSD Manager - track, manage, drive SSD
&amp;nbsp;
The feature of Kingston SSD Manager
	Monitor the status and use of drive
	View the identification information drives, such as model name, serial number, firmware version and other related information
	Using The technology Self-monitoring analysis and report (SMART), and the detailed...
</description></item><item><title>Download Macrium Reflect Workstation / Server / Server Plus 10.0.8750</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Dec 2025 22:36:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-macrium-reflect-1444.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-macrium-reflect-1444.html
</guid><description>
Macrium Reflect is software backup and recovery files, image files, with big improvements in speed, simplicity and strength. The software we provide taiwebs.com 've included 3 version is Macrium Reflect Workstation / Server / Server Plus. Whole our focus is to help organizations protect critical data and business systems, without fuss and budget breaking.
Macrium Reflect - backup and restore files
The function of Macrium Reflect
	Backup tool new: image gradually increases and...
</description></item></channel></rss>