<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 01:39:55 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 01:39:55 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Perfectly Clear WorkBench 4.8.0.2857</title><pubDate> Fri, 03 Oct 2025 19:37:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfectly-clear-workbench-6892.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfectly-clear-workbench-6892.html
</guid><description>
Perfectly Clear Workbench is an application that uses image editing libraries Perfectly Clear by Athentech and is provided to demonstrate the capabilities of the Perfectly Clear processing libraries, which recognize faces and allow quick export of processing settings for use.
One of the key features in Workbench is the ability to "export to API" when saving a Preset. This allows you to make image edits in Workbench and adjust the settings to suit your editing style and needs. You can...
</description></item><item><title>Download AVS Video ReMaker 8.1.3.4</title><pubDate> Fri, 03 Oct 2025 19:37:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs-video-remaker-1196.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs-video-remaker-1196.html
</guid><description>
AVS Video ReMaker is software that support quick editing of video files without reducing the video quality. Detection algorithm scenes used in AVS Video ReMaker will save time when processing video images and split it into the set. So, no need to preview every frame of the video file to find the transitions manually. With the help of AVS Video ReMaker, you can delete the unwanted parts and TV commercials from video files or file format DVD, recorded by various cameras, various video...
</description></item><item><title>Download CyberLink PowerDirector Ultimate 2026 v24.0.1001.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 03 Oct 2025 19:36:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-powerdirector-ultimate-425.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-powerdirector-ultimate-425.html
</guid><description>
CyberLink PowerDirector Ultimate is software editor, edit video and make movies on the computer from a variety of templates are made available, complete with effects, transitions, animations, and music. CyberLink PowerDirector 17 is a combination of video editing software with advanced video editing features powerful. Cblowing need to add your clips into the time line and click on 'Production'!
The tool design video in CyberLink PowerDirector have the ability to customize helps you...
</description></item><item><title>Download StartAllBack 3.9.16.5316</title><pubDate> Fri, 03 Oct 2025 19:36:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-startallback-6857.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-startallback-6857.html
</guid><description>
With the official release of Windows 11, chances are that most of you want to try it out. As the name suggests, StartAllBack is a small, lightweight tool that can help you enjoy the power of the new operating system while keeping the look and feel, especially because main work area, desktop of Windows 7, Windows 10 as taskbars and start menu styles.
StartAllBack is specially designed for Windows 11 and will not work on any older operating systems. If you want to get the start menu back...
</description></item><item><title>Download Windows 11 Pro + Office 2024 25H2 v26200.6584 NoTPM Multilingual Preactivated</title><pubDate> Fri, 03 Oct 2025 19:35:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-11-pro-incl-office-7292.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-11-pro-incl-office-7292.html
</guid><description>
Windows 11 Pro is a Microsoft operating system announced in 2021, part of the Windows NT family of operating systems. Windows 11 was released to the general public on October 5, 2021 as a free upgrade through Windows Update for eligible Windows 10 devices.
This Windows 11 Pro Premium is created from the original Microsoft installer and is integrated with the latest update in 2022. By skipping TPM 2.0 for computers Windows 11 cannot be installed and it is also Comes with the office...
</description></item><item><title>Download Stardock Start11 2.5.5.4</title><pubDate> Fri, 03 Oct 2025 19:34:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stardock-start11-7029.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stardock-start11-7029.html
</guid><description>
Start11 is an application capable of customizing the Start Menu and Taskbar on Windows 11 and Windows 10. This is an application that allows users to customize Windows 11 to suit their preferences. his personal. Start11 will help you bring the new Start Menu of Windows 11 to Windows 10. And vice versa, Start11 also helps you to bring the Start Menu of Windows 10 to Windows 11.
Start11 also helps users bring some functions of Windows 10 to Windows 11 through customizing the Taskbar such...
</description></item><item><title>Download AI Video Upscaler Pro 1.2.4</title><pubDate> Fri, 03 Oct 2025 19:34:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ai-video-upscaler-pro-14184.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ai-video-upscaler-pro-14184.html
</guid><description>
Break new life into your old or low-resolution videos with AI Video Upscaler Pro. This powerful and private desktop application uses advanced artificial intelligence to enhance and upscale your video files, bringing incredible new levels of detail and clarity. Designed with privacy at its core, AI Video Upscaler Pro works 100% offline after a one-time setup. Your video files will never be uploaded to the cloud or shared with anyone, ensuring your content stays under your control on your...
</description></item><item><title>Download dslrBooth Photo Booth Software Pro 7.49.1.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 03 Oct 2025 19:33:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dslrbooth-photo-booth-software-666.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dslrbooth-photo-booth-software-666.html
</guid><description>
Photo Booth Software is a software to create, list and combine the images back together in the same theme as travel, haloween. Created by the professional photographer for the operator photo booth at all skill levels, photo booth software dslrBooth built from scratch with the sole purpose of running the photo booth. The software uses the latest technology to provide you and your guests, high quality prints and the ability to share photos and GIF on the means of social media including...
</description></item><item><title>Download Telestream Wirecast Pro 16.5.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 03 Oct 2025 19:33:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-telestream-wirecast-pro-739.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-telestream-wirecast-pro-739.html
</guid><description>
Telestream Wirecast Pro is software to broadcast live video, turn your computer into a tv studio directly. Live streaming with just your webcam or connect multiple cameras, scoreboard, graphics, and guests from far away. Wirecast makes it easy to stream great-looking live and pre-recorded video to Facebook Live, YouTube, Twitter, Periscope and many more.
Telestream Wirecast Pro - live broadcast
Wirecast is used everywhere to transmit online your program to OTT and the social platform....
</description></item><item><title>Download Antidote 12 v2.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 03 Oct 2025 19:32:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-antidote-8032.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-antidote-8032.html
</guid><description>
Antidote is a multi-resource platform, very useful for anyone writing in English or French. Antidote's debugger flags a wide variety of errors: from capitalization and verb agreement to commas and unwanted redundancies. Once your spelling and grammar are correct, correct typographical and stylistic errors, including repetition of words and boring verbs. Never before has software given you such power to perfect your writing.
The error correction tool analyzes your text and highlights any...
</description></item><item><title>Download AVS Audio Editor 11.1.3.4</title><pubDate> Fri, 03 Oct 2025 19:31:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs-audio-editor-1194.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs-audio-editor-1194.html
</guid><description>
AVS Audio Editor is editor audio professional allows you to edit, record and encode music. The program has more than 20 effects and filters built in, including delay, flanger, chorus, reverb, filters to remove irritating sounds such as "vuvuzelas", new sound effects, strange, unique.
AVS Audio Editor - audio editing
Features of AVS Audio Editor
Save to all major formats
	Edit and save audio files into MP3, FLAC, WAV, M4A, WMA, AAC, MP2, AMR, OGG and other files with the help of AVS...
</description></item><item><title>Download Reg Organizer 9.86</title><pubDate> Fri, 03 Oct 2025 19:31:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reg-organizer-1595.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reg-organizer-1595.html
</guid><description>
Reg Organizer is a software to scan and clean your registry windows register errors and help optimize performance computer system. Reg Organizer is a software subscription, professional, and professional, and any way that the Windows registry are necessary and therefore, the overall performance of Windows improves, there is this software.
Reg Organizer - registry Cleaning and pc optimization
The main features of Reg Organizer
	Cleaning the registry of the lock is not valid and not...
</description></item><item><title>Download Modbus Poll 12.0.0.2448</title><pubDate> Fri, 03 Oct 2025 19:30:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-modbus-poll-3852.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-modbus-poll-3852.html
</guid><description>
Modbus Poll is the simulator the Modbus is designed primarily to help developers device Modbus or others want to test and simulate the Modbus protocol. With the multiple document interface you can monitor a number of slave Modbus and / or the zone data at the same time. For each window you simply specify the ID slave, Modbus, function, address, size, and proportion of poll. You can read and write registers and coils from any window. If you want to change a register, just double-click the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Rufus 4.11 + Portable</title><pubDate> Fri, 03 Oct 2025 19:30:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rufus-2442.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rufus-2442.html
</guid><description>
Rufus support create a USB install Windows operating system like installing from a Windows installation disc often. Rufus offers to users the features from simple to lift the cap fit the needs as well as the ability of many objects. Rufus also has useful functions such as automatic identification, USB, display information about the connected USB.
A new version of a small program has been released that allows you to create and format the USB flash drive that can boot, it also can operate...
</description></item><item><title>Download Files Inspector Pro 4.40</title><pubDate> Fri, 03 Oct 2025 19:29:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-files-inspector-pro-2289.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-files-inspector-pro-2289.html
</guid><description>
Files Inspector is a software that allows you to analyze the data on the hard drive and delete the file obsolete, since it frees up space and improve performance of the system. Despite the fact that the hard drives are becoming cheaper and more voluminous, you have a place to store a large number of files are not really necessary in most cases, due to the repetition and simple data is outdated. If not maintained properly, you can fill the space trash and clean up will eventually become a...
</description></item><item><title>Download Pepakura Designer 6.1.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 03 Oct 2025 19:28:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pepakura-designer-748.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pepakura-designer-748.html
</guid><description>
Pepakura Designer is software to create 2D models, 3D quick, easy and developed in Japan. Pepakura Designer helps easily design the template paper craft by importing data 3D model. No special knowledge is required to model papercraft. All you have to do is prepare the 3D model. You can use some software 3DCG released from other developers to make the 3D models for unfolding.
Pepakura Designer - Create model 2D 3D
Pepakura Designer to create the form of 2D images that you can share it...
</description></item><item><title>Download AVS Video Editor 11.1.3.4</title><pubDate> Fri, 03 Oct 2025 19:28:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs-video-editor-426.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs-video-editor-426.html
</guid><description>
AVS Video Editor is software professional video editing for windows with full features useful, easy-to-use.  When using AVS Video Editor you can record a video, to impose various effects, create and burn DVD, export movies to various video formats, convert video to iPod, PSP, mobile phones and the other portable device.
Features AVS Video Editor
Format support
	AVS Video Editor supports all major video formats. Edit and save the video file in the codec AVI, VOB, MP4, DVD, WMV, 3GP,...
</description></item><item><title>Download VideoPad Video Editor Pro 17.45 Beta</title><pubDate> Fri, 03 Oct 2025 19:27:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-videopad-video-editor-pro-268.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-videopad-video-editor-pro-268.html
</guid><description>
VideoPad Video Editor Pro is software edit video from any camcorder, DV camcorder, VHS player or webcam for best quality. The interface of this utility is divided into several parts (for example: list of multi-media, Effects, transitions, Files, Clips, video track, audio track, overlay), which makes everything seem difficult to operate. You can capture videos from camcorder or other devices like webcam or capture card TV and after you have added files and sequence clips to the queue, you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sublime Merge 2 Build 2112</title><pubDate> Fri, 03 Oct 2025 19:27:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sublime-merge-3957.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sublime-merge-3957.html
</guid><description>
Sublime Merge is the name of the application software and of course very useful for the programmer. In fact, the software in front of you is a text editor and the code light on the mass, and of course is strong. When using this software, you can view and edit multiple page text and his code at the same time and edit and complete them. User interface with great editing tools will give you experience coding very interesting.
Sublime Merge - source Editor and write the Code
Software...
</description></item><item><title>Download MusConv 4.10.423 Lifetime</title><pubDate> Fri, 03 Oct 2025 19:26:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html
</guid><description>
MusConv transfers playlists, albums, followed artists and liked songs across a variety of services – Spotify, Apple Music, Amazon Music, YouTube, YouTube Music, iTunes, Deezer, Tidal, SoundCloud, Pandora and more 125 music services!
Features of MusConv Ultimate
	Transfer playlists, albums, followed artists and liked tracks between over 125 music servicesManage playlists (Delete, Merge, Split, Copy...)
	More than 125 music services supported
	Access DAILY updated music charts on...
</description></item><item><title>Download Omidsoft Red Burner 18.28</title><pubDate> Fri, 03 Oct 2025 19:26:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-red-burner-10119.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-red-burner-10119.html
</guid><description>
Red Burner is a lightweight burning software based on Blue Burner with full functionality to work with ISO/CUE images and drives. Start the move to a lightweight, yet powerful, and time-saving standalone optical disc burner with the simplest user interface and fastest possible burning algorithm.
Features of Red Burner
	Fastest possible CD/DVD/BD burning algorithm
	Standard, dual-layer and high-capacity media recording
	Browse ISO/CUE images via internal image browser
	Writable M-Disc,...
</description></item><item><title>Download FontViewOK 9.11</title><pubDate> Fri, 03 Oct 2025 19:25:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fontviewok-1337.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fontviewok-1337.html
</guid><description>
FontViewOK is a simple tool that helps show your location and can install any fonts in list of it. To view (display) the font is not installed on Windows, you can also thanks to the help of Font View OK. Launch FontViewOK on the program screen, click the select folder Button From. Then just select the category to which the display font.
FontViewOK - Support install fonts
Many users install available font on Windows operating system of them and want tocompare the font visually on...
</description></item><item><title>Download XRECODE3 1.172</title><pubDate> Fri, 03 Oct 2025 19:25:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xrecode-iii-2915.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xrecode-iii-2915.html
</guid><description>
"Xrecode II" is the switch and grab the audio allows you to convert from mp2, mp3, ac3, aiff, wma, amr, ogg, ape, flac, cue, mpc, wv, tak, mid, cue, m4b, tta, wav, dts , wav (rf64), m4a, mp4, ra, shn, rm, avi, aac, mpg, vob, mka, mkv, flv, Mov, swf, ofr, divx, wmv, spx, mp3, m4v, 3gp, m2v, 3g2, m4v, m2ts, ts, adts, tak, xm, mod, it, s3m, alac, umx, mtm, mlp to m4a, ape, flac, mp4 (using NeroAAC), raw, ogg, wav, wav (rf64) , wma, mpc, WavPack, mp2, ofr, Speex, ac3, tak, aiff, snd, Shorten...
</description></item><item><title>Download Directory Opus Pro 13.18.6 Beta</title><pubDate> Fri, 03 Oct 2025 19:24:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-opus-pro-779.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-opus-pro-779.html
</guid><description>
Directory Opus Pro is a software replacement for Explorer with traditional strength and function more than any manager other files. Directory Opus Pro full support for high DPI screen (for example 4K and 5K) with the rename dialog is redesigned, with new features. Besides being a recording macro only allows you to perform mass renaming complex that don't need regular expressions. In addition, Directory Opus Pro also enhances the ability to script.Better handling of renaming recursive and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Source Insight 4.00.0148</title><pubDate> Fri, 03 Oct 2025 19:24:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-source-insight-2185.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-source-insight-2185.html
</guid><description>
Source Insight is an editor, programming-oriented strong project, browse the code and the analysis help you understand the code in when you work and plan. Source insight has built-in analysis for C / C ++, C #, Java, Objective-C, and much more. Source Insight is a powerful program created to give you a browser, as well as tools to view and edit the source code for the application is written in the programming language different. Everyone knows that the analysis and processing of the source...
</description></item></channel></rss>