<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 13:47:26 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 13:47:26 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download ImageMagick 7.1.2-2</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 16:12:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-imagemagick-1319.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-imagemagick-1319.html
</guid><description>
ImageMagick is software image processing command line to create, edit, compose, or convert bitmap images. ImageMagick is completely free for users and you easily download it on taiwebs.com. Typical functions most of software is able to read and write images in many formats (over 100) including DPX, EXR, GIF, JPEG, JPEG-2000, PDF, PhotoCD, PNG, Postcript, SVG, and TIFF.
ImageMagick - image Processing
The Windows version of ImageMagick is installed. Just click on the appropriate version...
</description></item><item><title>Download RapidRAW 1.3.10</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 16:09:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rapidraw-13957.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rapidraw-13957.html
</guid><description>
RapidRAW is a modern, high-performance, open-source RAW photo editor, designed to deliver a fast and clean editing experience with a lightweight footprint (under 30MB). Built with performance and usability in mind, the software is aimed at photographers who want a simple, efficient, and fun workflow without compromising performance.
Key Features
	GPU-accelerated processing: Uses a custom WGSL shader to process all image adjustments on the GPU, allowing for smooth, responsive editing...
</description></item><item><title>Download UniGetUI 3.3.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 16:09:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-unigetui-12209.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-unigetui-12209.html
</guid><description>
UniGetUI (formerly WingetUI) is a graphical user interface for WinGet (and other package managers), a command-line package manager for Windows 10 and Windows 11 such as Winget, Scoop, Chocolatey, Pip, NPM, .NET Tool and PowerShell Gallery. It allows users to install, update and uninstall software from the package manager easily. Additionally, it provides features like backup, restore, group and update your packages and receive notifications about new updates.
With this program, you can...
</description></item><item><title>Download C64 Forever Plus Edition 11.1.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 16:07:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-c64-forever-plus-edition-2307.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-c64-forever-plus-edition-2307.html
</guid><description>
C64 Forever is the program is an emulator of Commodore strong, even comes with a set of rich game. Of course, video games have come a long way and so can you and you need more than a lifetime to undergo computer toys alone, not to mention game machines. If you, like me, are nostalgic and want to undergo these difficulties, neurological examination, patience and everything else, you need the emulator for this.
C64 Forever Plus Edition - The emulator game
External application suitable...
</description></item><item><title>Download Photo Pos Pro Premium 4.16 Build 46</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 16:07:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photo-pos-pro-premium-672.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photo-pos-pro-premium-672.html
</guid><description>
Photo Pos Pro Premium is the photo editing most popular worldwide in the areas of image enhancement and image editing and in the field of design of computer graphics. Version 3 has the photo editing features for free and premium, you can perform various tasks from the basic tasks of simple to complex tasks or can edit existing images, create new works based on existing images, create new works from scratch and more.
Software Photo Pos Pro Premium is packed with adjustments and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Balabolka 2.15.0.903</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 16:06:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-balaboka-142.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-balaboka-142.html
</guid><description>
Balabolka is a text-to-speech (TTS) program. It can read text on your screen in a human-like voice. You can use Balabolka to listen to text from a variety of file formats, convert text to spoken audio files, and adjust speech parameters such as speed and pitch. It is often used for accessibility purposes, helping people who have difficulty reading or multi-tasking by listening to text while doing other activities. Balabolka supports multiple languages and uses different TTS engines,...
</description></item><item><title>Download MassTube 2026 v21.0.0.157 Ultra</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 16:06:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-masstube-plus-461.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-masstube-plus-461.html
</guid><description>
MassTube Plus is a small utility used to download the favorite videos of you on youtube on your computer. This is a software compact, has a simple design with few options to download videos fastest. The you complete peace of mind because the software is easy to use, built exclusively for a single goal: to retrieve the video file from YouTube, so it doesn't pack the other useful features such as search engine integrated and a download audio file.
MassTube can work with multiple output...
</description></item><item><title>Download Directory Opus Pro 13.18</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 16:05:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-opus-pro-779.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-opus-pro-779.html
</guid><description>
Directory Opus Pro is a software replacement for Explorer with traditional strength and function more than any manager other files. Directory Opus Pro full support for high DPI screen (for example 4K and 5K) with the rename dialog is redesigned, with new features. Besides being a recording macro only allows you to perform mass renaming complex that don't need regular expressions. In addition, Directory Opus Pro also enhances the ability to script.Better handling of renaming recursive and...
</description></item><item><title>Download WindowTop Pro 5.28.3</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 16:05:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windowtop-6955.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windowtop-6955.html
</guid><description>
WindowTop is a program that pins windows on Desktop, in other words it sets the window to float above all other program windows, creating transparency for the windows. that window via a dedicated slider, which supports adjusting transparency, changing the color of application windows or similar programs with the dark theme of the Windows 10 operating system, creating contrast and reducing tension straight, painful for the eyes.
Features of WindowTop
	Put window on top
	Set window to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wing FTP Server Corporate 8.0.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 16:05:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wing-ftp-server-corporate-2752.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wing-ftp-server-corporate-2752.html
</guid><description>
Wing FTP Server Corporate is a highly functional, easy and safe can be used in the operating system Windows, Linux, Mac and Solaris are used. The software supports a number of file transfer protocol such as FTP, HTTP, FTPS, HTTPS and SFTP. Wing FTP Server provides web-based interface to manage the server at any time. You can also get performance server and the online and even send email notifications about various events happening on the server.
Management server multi-function
Wing FTP...
</description></item><item><title>Download Helium Music Manager Premium 17.4.494</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 16:04:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-helium-music-manager-premium-164.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-helium-music-manager-premium-164.html
</guid><description>
Helium Music Manager is a music manager that can rip, tag, play, browse, search, rename, burn and synchronize your music with the mobile. You can control your music collection with Helium Music Manager. Stop using time looking for the file on your computer or looking through CDS, vinyl records and tapes - instead, simply enjoy and explore your music! Helium Music Manager can replace the ripper, the player, tag editor and related software to audio your other.
Helium Music Manager...
</description></item><item><title>Download Duplicate &amp;amp; Same Files Searcher 10.7.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 16:04:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-duplicate-same-files-searcher-1758.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-duplicate-same-files-searcher-1758.html
</guid><description>
Duplicate &amp;amp; Same Files Searcher is the duplicate search allows you to search for files similar or identical on your computer and help you delete to free up disk space.The interface of the app Duplicate &amp;amp; Same Files Searcher user-friendly. So, you can immediately start the search by setting the destination drive.
Duplicate &amp;amp; Same Files Searcher - Find duplicate files
With software you can include and exclude file types, set file size, minimum and maximum, just find the link...
</description></item><item><title>Download Syncovery Premium 11.7.4.89</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 15:59:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncovery-pro-enterprise-232.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncovery-pro-enterprise-232.html
</guid><description>
Syncovery Pro Enterprise is a great application used to back up data and to synchronize personal computers, servers, laptops, notepads and storage online. The software comes with support for FTP and secure FTP servers, SSH, WebDAV, Amazon S3, http, update the part file, ZIP compression, data encryption, and schedule automatic backups.
Syncovery Pro Enterprise have the ability to freely select files and folders across the whole folder hierarchy in tree view and supports email...
</description></item><item><title>Download Find.Same.Images.OK 5.78</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 15:59:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-find-same-images-ok-113.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-find-same-images-ok-113.html
</guid><description>
Find.Same.Images.OK lets find the images identical or similar in the folder of you, even if they were to rotate, change size or change.
Just select one or more folders that you want the program to scan and it will return a list of all the duplicate images or very similar, as indicated by the percent the same and the preview is built.Then, you can select images from the list and then copy, move or delete them.
Find.Same.Images.OK
In addition, there are other options smart option allows...
</description></item><item><title>Download Automize Enterprise 13.16</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 15:58:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hitek-software-automize-enterprise-7647.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hitek-software-automize-enterprise-7647.html
</guid><description>
Automize Enterprise is a suite of automation software to improve your productivity and save you time. It allows you to schedule tasks, execute tasks as well as other software programs and applications without requiring any programming or scripting knowledge. It creates advanced automation solutions using Automation tasks in combination with variables, folder/file monitors, and task sequences for your Windows.
For advanced users, you can develop scripts to reduce repetitive, laborious...
</description></item><item><title>Download Devious Machines Complete Effects Bundle 2025.8.25</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 15:58:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-devious-machines-complete-effects-bundle-13867.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-devious-machines-complete-effects-bundle-13867.html
</guid><description>
Devious Machines Complete Effects Bundle is a comprehensive audio effects plugin suite designed for music producers, sound designers, and mixing/mastering engineers. This plugin suite includes the full range of Devious Machines flagship plugins, providing a powerful and versatile set of tools for creative audio processing and professional audio processing.
Key components of the package:
	Infiltrator 2: A powerful multi-effects engine for complex sound design and rhythmic...
</description></item><item><title>Download Output Portal Presets 2025.8</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 15:57:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-output-portal-presets-12234.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-output-portal-presets-12234.html
</guid><description>
With PORTAL, particle synthesis takes your sound to the next level. Easily change any audio input – VST, drums, vocals, live guitar, you name it – in a new and musical way. Infinite ideas in seconds, Enjoy detailed effects that can play around the music you create to turn one idea into infinite others.
Main features
	Over 250 presets for instant play
	Round XY controller linked with detailed parameters
	Powerful time manipulation tool
	Synchronous particle delay
	tempo Pitch...
</description></item><item><title>Download JaSFTP 13.16</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 15:57:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hitek-software-jasftp-7648.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hitek-software-jasftp-7648.html
</guid><description>
JaSFTP is a secure FTP client (SFTP) designed with automation in mind, so you don't have to waste time with interactive file transfers for Windows. It has a simple user interface that helps you to transfer files interactively, but the goal is to help you create advanced SFTP tasks that can be scheduled automatically or run manually.
With JaSFTP you can easily automate SFTP to/from your local network or internet server. Schedule SFTP for files between your PC and the server; and...
</description></item><item><title>Download QOwnNotes 25.8.7</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 15:57:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qownnotes-3178.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qownnotes-3178.html
</guid><description>
QOwnNotes is notes bookmark file simple text (GPL) open source application for GNU / Linux , Mac OS X and Windows of Patrizio Bekerle ( pbek on GitHub and IRC) (optional) activity along with the notes application of ownCloud or Nextcloud. QOwnNote store your notes as plain text files and can be synchronized with synchronization function file of ownCloud / Nextcloud. You can also use other apps like Syncthing or Dropbox . Just write out your thoughts as they appear, and edit them if...
</description></item><item><title>Download Hitek Software AutoKrypt 13.16</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 15:56:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hitek-software-autokrypt-9549.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hitek-software-autokrypt-9549.html
</guid><description>
Hitek Software AutoKrypt is software that automatically encrypts or decrypts files and folders on a schedule. Encryption methods include password-based, secret key, public and private key, OpenPGP password, OpenPGP public and private key.
Features of Hitek Software AutoKrypt
	Encryption profiles allow you to quickly add encryption and decryption profiles. These files can be used in encryption or decryption tasks.
	Encryption allows you to encrypt files or an entire folder and its...
</description></item><item><title>Download Hitek Software AbleFTP 13.16</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 15:52:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hitek-software-ableftp-9548.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hitek-software-ableftp-9548.html
</guid><description>
Hitek Software AbleFTP  is designed with automation in mind, so you don't have to spend time transferring files interactively. The simple user interface helps you to transfer files interactively, but the Goal is to help you create advanced FTP tasks that can be scheduled automatically or run manually. Automate FTP to/from your local network or internet server. Schedule FTP for files between your PC and the server; and automatically rename files based on the current month, day, or time as...
</description></item><item><title>Download AutoSmith Openings Builder 1.0.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 13:02:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-autosmith-openings-builder-14104.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-autosmith-openings-builder-14104.html
</guid><description>
Introducing Openings Builder — the ultimate Autodesk® Revit® add-on designed to transform the way your team manages MEP coordination and structural openings. No more tedious manual opening placement or error-prone workflows. Openings Builder helps engineers, architects, and BIM professionals streamline the coordination process with precision, speed, and confidence.
Why Choose Openings Builder?
In every MEP project, coordinating wall penetrations for pipes, ducts, and cable trays is...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mohan Klein MidiRemap 1.1.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 12:55:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mohan-klein-midiremap-14103.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mohan-klein-midiremap-14103.html
</guid><description>
Mohan Klein MidiRemap is a dedicated MIDI plugin designed to convert MIDI drum data between different drum libraries, allowing musicians, producers, and sound engineers to easily adapt grooves or drum performances for use with different virtual drum instruments.
Key features include:
	MIDI Note Mapping: Instantly convert your MIDI notes to new note values ​​to match the format of the target drum library.
	Install Library presets: Comes with built-in presets for major drum...
</description></item><item><title>Download NetSpeedTray 1.1.5 + Portable</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 01:27:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-netspeedtray-14068.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-netspeedtray-14068.html
</guid><description>
NetSpeedTray is a lightweight, open source network monitor for Windows that displays upload/download speeds directly on the Taskbar with a native look and feel.
Designed to blend seamlessly with Windows 10/11 user interface. Includes intelligent detection of light and dark themes on the taskbar to ensure text is always visible. Sits quietly in the system tray without hogging resources. Features "Dynamic Update Rate" that automatically reduces update frequency when the network is idle to...
</description></item><item><title>Download DirPrintOK 7.44</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 01:26:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dirprintok-2073.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dirprintok-2073.html
</guid><description>
DirPrintOK allows you to print and save the contents of the folder and / or entire folder structures. You can browse the directory with Explorer-like interface and arbitrary filter folder contents by file extensions or matching the wildcard. You can also right-click to exclude files or folders selected from the printed version.
&amp;nbsp;
Folder contents can be grouped by path, date, size or file extension and you can customize the data columns to be included in the printed book. Very easy...
</description></item></channel></rss>