<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 19:58:13 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 19:58:13 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Perfectly Clear WorkBench 4.8.0.2853</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Sep 2025 17:43:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfectly-clear-workbench-6892.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfectly-clear-workbench-6892.html
</guid><description>
Perfectly Clear Workbench is an application that uses image editing libraries Perfectly Clear by Athentech and is provided to demonstrate the capabilities of the Perfectly Clear processing libraries, which recognize faces and allow quick export of processing settings for use.
One of the key features in Workbench is the ability to "export to API" when saving a Preset. This allows you to make image edits in Workbench and adjust the settings to suit your editing style and needs. You can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Free YouTube Download 4.4.39.919 Premium</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Sep 2025 17:42:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-download-1177.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-download-1177.html
</guid><description>
Free YouTube Download Premium is the most popular application to download videos from YouTube. The program was released in 2006 and regularly updated since then. Use the program to download and convert YouTube videos to view offline anytime.
Free YouTube Download - added Support to download youtube
Download more videos! Save whole playlists and YouTube channels, videos from a playlist individually (history, video be favorite, favourites, Watch later), videos from many different...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe After Effects 2025 v25.5.0 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Sep 2025 17:42:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-after-effects-0001-2793.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-after-effects-0001-2793.html
</guid><description>
Adobe After Effects is a powerful digital visual effects, motion graphics, and compositing application developed by Adobe Inc. The software is widely used in the film, television, and video game industries to animate and enhance video content.
After Effects allows users to create stunning motion graphics and visual effects by animating text, images, and video clips. Its capabilities include keying, tracking, compositing, and basic audio editing, making it a versatile tool for...
</description></item><item><title>Download Soda PDF Desktop Pro 14.0.518.23083</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Sep 2025 17:41:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-soda-pdf-home-808.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-soda-pdf-home-808.html
</guid><description>
Soda PDF Pro  is intuitive PDF software that helps you to easily process and create PDF files from more than 300 different formats. Soda PDF is built to help you power through any PDF task. Convert to a wide range of file types. Edit the content of your document. Create custom forms. Annotate your files. Send and track contracts for electronic signatures.
Soda PDF Pro: Create PDF file
Features of Soda PDF Pro
	Read your PDFs and digital publications in 3D with unique page-turning...
</description></item><item><title>Download Q-Dir 12.35</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Sep 2025 17:40:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-q-dir-348.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-q-dir-348.html
</guid><description>
Q-Dir is software to manage the entire file and folder on the computer, allowing to see file in same time 4 different positions (viewport quadro) while still maintaining all the standard features of the Explorer.
It also provides a variety of management features, additional files included the filter file color-coding, layouts and columns can be customized, quick access to file and folder favorites and more.
Other features of Q-Dir , including directory listings (.txt, .doc .html .csv),...
</description></item><item><title>Download EndNote 2025.1 Build 19456</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Sep 2025 17:40:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-endnote-4237.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-endnote-4237.html
</guid><description>
EndNote X9 as a researcher, you constantly carry the different roles, addressing the competing demands on your time and coordinate not only the activities of the own in study published that all your collaborators on the whole and on the whole world. EndNote X9 is software management reference not only frees you from the tedious work in collecting and managing research material and format folder manually but also help you easy and more controlled in coordination with colleagues.
EndNote...
</description></item><item><title>Download PilotEdit Pro 20.3.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Sep 2025 17:39:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pilotedit-979.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pilotedit-979.html
</guid><description>
PilotEdit is software edit the textfile to help you execute scripts, extract strings and edit large files. PilotEdit is the editing file will help you search and replace multi-line text, edit files, FTP or even download and upload files and folders FTP. With edit file PilotEdit becomes easier.
PilotEdit - edit text files
PilotEdit is a hex-editor and advanced text support opening files larger than 4GB. It provides syntax to customize and highlight keywords, advanced search and replace...
</description></item><item><title>Download Quick CPU Pro 5.2.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Sep 2025 17:39:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quick-cpu-pro-13622.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quick-cpu-pro-13622.html
</guid><description>
Quick CPU Pro is a powerful CPU monitoring and performance tuning application designed for both Intel® and AMD® processors. This application provides real-time visibility and control over key system parameters such as CPU temperature, power, voltage, frequency, core utilization, core stall status, efficiency, voltage, current, and power management features.
The application also includes customizable power plan controls, turbo power limit configuration, core performance ratios, and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium 4.4.39.919</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Sep 2025 17:39:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-to-mp3-converter-premium-844.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-to-mp3-converter-premium-844.html
</guid><description>
Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium version is a software used to convert YouTube to MP3, extract audio from playlists YouTube, show listings, charts, video responses, channels, favorites of the user. With Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium, you can download and convert playlists, channels, stream original tv series and get them into iTunes at the same time.
Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium - convert YouTube to MP3
Features Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium from the...
</description></item><item><title>Download O&amp;amp;O Defrag Pro 30.0.1057</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Sep 2025 17:38:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-o-o-defrag-pro-149.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-o-o-defrag-pro-149.html
</guid><description>
O&amp;amp;O Defrag Pro is the professional software has the ability to defragment the hard disk and can work with the file system different from FAT / 32 to NTFS / 5, and support for the different arrays Volume / Stripe Sets. You can also set the schedule which O &amp;amp; O Defrag will be booted and perform a number of manipulation certain. Regular defragmentation of the disk partition optimized performance of your computer. The user interface is very easy to use. It has a ribbon bar displays all...
</description></item><item><title>Download O&amp;amp;O Defrag Server 30.0.1057</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Sep 2025 17:38:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-defrag-server-2521.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-defrag-server-2521.html
</guid><description>
O&amp;amp;O Defrag Server professional software has the ability to defragment the hard disk and can work with the file system different from FAT / 32 to NTFS / 5, and support for the different arrays Volume / Stripe Sets. You can also set the schedule which O &amp;amp; O Defrag will be booted and perform a number of manipulation certain. Regular defragmentation of the disk partition optimized performance of your computer. The user interface is very easy to use. It has a ribbon bar displays all the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Xreveal 2.8.5</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Sep 2025 17:17:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xreveal-7252.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xreveal-7252.html
</guid><description>
Xreveal is an application similar to AnyDVD. This is an interactive research and purpose project. Xreveal does NOT contain any decryption key, it is based solely on the official public AACS specification. You need the decryption key or key database to make it work.
Features of Xreveal
	Remove Blu-ray AACS 1.0 protection
	Remove Blu-ray AACS 2.0 (UHD) protection
	Remove BD+ protection
	Remove BDAV Protection
	Remove DVD CSS protection
	Remove CPRM Protection
	Remove CPPM...
</description></item><item><title>Download FL Studio Producer Edition 25.1.6 Build 4997 All Plugins</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Sep 2025 16:59:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-image-line-fl-studio-488.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-image-line-fl-studio-488.html
</guid><description>
Image Line FL Studio is software that provides an environment to produce and create music, open architecture, full-featured for computer. Image Line FL Studio owner, audio workstation digital this has everything you need in one package to compose, arrange, record, edit, mix and master music in professional quality.
With user interface graphics based on the music player FL Studio 20 is the fastest way to create any style of music with a kits and kits studio complete. The plugins, sounds...
</description></item><item><title>Download Remote Desktop Manager Enterprise 2025.2.29</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Sep 2025 16:58:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-remote-desktop-manager-enterprise-242.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-remote-desktop-manager-enterprise-242.html
</guid><description>
Remote Desktop Manager Enterprise software is the complete management of remote connections and virtual machines from a single location, at the same time access support data online and cloud storage. Remote Desktop Manager supports multiple types of connections, not only connections for the protocol connect remote computer Remote Desktop Protocol (RDP).
Remote Desktop Manager easily add, edit, delete, share, organize and find your remote connection of you quickly. Compatible with...
</description></item><item><title>Download Imagine 2.2.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Sep 2025 16:58:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-imagine-7369.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-imagine-7369.html
</guid><description>
Imagine is an application that allows you to view images and animations in a variety of formats, including JPG, BMP, PNG and GIF. With Imagine you can view file properties and EXIF ​​information, copy, move, delete and rename images. Additionally, you can also flip, resize and rotate them, swap colors, set transparency levels, import, export, and edit palettes, and change color depth.
Features of Imagine
	View and save image/animation files at lightning speed
	Multiple...
</description></item><item><title>Download Markdown Monster 3.9.9.3</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Sep 2025 16:58:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-markdown-monster-2640.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-markdown-monster-2640.html
</guid><description>
Markdown Monster is the edit and view Markdown allows you to edit Markdown by syntax highlighting and fast text input. Live preview can collapse, synchronized allows you to see the output of when you enter. You can easily embed images, links, emoticons and code in text form or by using the support UI lightness of we to simplify many operations. You can also paste and drag images directly into the editor.
Markdown Monster is a solution comprehensive software designed to solve almost any...
</description></item><item><title>Download CFTurbo 2025 R2.1.120 + CFTurbo FEA v2025 R2.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Sep 2025 16:57:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cfturbo-3713.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cfturbo-3713.html
</guid><description>
CFTurbo is a powerful program but easy to use software for pump design can help you design pumps from scratch or redesign the rotor is there. Simply tell it the flow rate, head, RPM and any vortex before (optional) and CFTurbo which will automatically generate a pump design. Then you have the option to go back and change any detail of design with the guidance of CFTurbo. Easy but flexible, this approach to pump design saves you time and still lets you get exactly the pump design you...
</description></item><item><title>Download iTop VPN 7.0.0.6652</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Sep 2025 16:56:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-itop-vpn-5733.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-itop-vpn-5733.html
</guid><description>
iTop VPN is software that encrypts your Internet traffic and hides your IP address from hackers and trackers, protecting your privacy and security. Just click the Connect button, we will choose the fastest and most stable server for you. You can change different Network Solutions according to your needs. Safeguard mode gives you higher security protection, Game Mode offers unlimited bandwidth and speed, so you can stream your favorite movies and TV shows at High definition and enjoy the...
</description></item><item><title>Download GraphPad Prism 10.6.1.892</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Sep 2025 16:56:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-graphpad-prism-3726.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-graphpad-prism-3726.html
</guid><description>
GraphPad Prism is one of the software products statistics released by a private company whose name is GraphPad. This software has the ability to draw all the chart types 3D and also be used to solve the statistical problems. In general, this software is designed to solve the problems of science and commerce. GraphPad Prism provides users the ability to solve statistical problems difficult and most difficult with the right speed.
GraphPad Prism - software statistics
Although GraphPad...
</description></item><item><title>Download Google Chrome 140.0.7339.208</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Sep 2025 16:55:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-chrome-1012.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-chrome-1012.html
</guid><description>
Google Chrome web browser is the most used today. Support surf the web, listen to music, watch movies, play web game effective no jerky lag with the internet connection stable. When you are surfing the web or performing an important task, whether it is operation big or small, work or entertainment, then Chrome has the smart features and the speed you need to make, create and explore on the net.
The latest version of Google Chrome is the third 114. But we are providing for users Google...
</description></item><item><title>Download NxFilter 4.7.3.7</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Sep 2025 16:55:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nxfilter-50.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nxfilter-50.html
</guid><description>
NxFilter is a server filter DNS have the ability to filter Internet traffic based on domain names and content types. In addition, it can use check package DNS to protect your network from malware and botnet activity.
NxFilter is installed on a single computer, where it acts as a proxy server, DNS. To route Internet traffic through NxFilter, you will need to change the DNS settings on all the machines that you want to protect to use the IP address of the individual NxFilter (instead of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Network LookOut Administrator Pro 5.3.7</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Sep 2025 16:54:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-network-lookout-administrator-pro-1414.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-network-lookout-administrator-pro-1414.html
</guid><description>
Network LookOut Administrator Pro is application software to control the screen of the computer on the network to help full the right to monitor your computer remotely. Network LookOut Administrator use the most appropriate for LAN network, the benefits that it brought back really great, you can control the computer remotely using the mouse and keyboard , without the need to use these tools other troubles. When employees get into trouble, you only have to help from far away that still...
</description></item><item><title>Download lessmsi 2.9.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Sep 2025 16:54:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lessmsi-12392.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lessmsi-12392.html
</guid><description>
Lessmsi (Less MSIerables) is a free and portable application that allows users to view and extract the contents of MSI files.
How does it work? Files with the .msi extension are not as widely used as their .exe cousins, but both contain programs for Windows. The main difference between them is that the latter does not always come with an installer, while it comes standard with the former. However, there will be cases where you just need to view or want to extract specific content from...
</description></item><item><title>Download MassTube 2026 v21.0.2.166 Ultra</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Sep 2025 16:53:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-masstube-plus-461.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-masstube-plus-461.html
</guid><description>
MassTube Plus is a small utility used to download the favorite videos of you on youtube on your computer. This is a software compact, has a simple design with few options to download videos fastest. The you complete peace of mind because the software is easy to use, built exclusively for a single goal: to retrieve the video file from YouTube, so it doesn't pack the other useful features such as search engine integrated and a download audio file.
MassTube can work with multiple output...
</description></item><item><title>Download Syncovery Premium 11.8.2.102</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Sep 2025 16:53:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncovery-pro-enterprise-232.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncovery-pro-enterprise-232.html
</guid><description>
Syncovery Pro Enterprise is a great application used to back up data and to synchronize personal computers, servers, laptops, notepads and storage online. The software comes with support for FTP and secure FTP servers, SSH, WebDAV, Amazon S3, http, update the part file, ZIP compression, data encryption, and schedule automatic backups.
Syncovery Pro Enterprise have the ability to freely select files and folders across the whole folder hierarchy in tree view and supports email...
</description></item></channel></rss>