<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 20:07:44 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 20:07:44 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 7.5.6</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Dec 2025 19:20:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-11-7760.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-11-7760.html
</guid><description>
TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 is a program that allows users to discover hidden settings in Windows 11. This application is specially designed for Windows 11, groups many registry settings and distribute them from the easy and secure user interface. With TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 you can move the Windows taskbar to the top and resize the taskbar by editing the registry value. With any application that modifies the registry, we recommend that you have a backup copy...
</description></item><item><title>Download Total Commander 11.56 Extended 25.12 Full / Lite</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Dec 2025 19:20:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-total-commander-it-edition-7090.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-total-commander-it-edition-7090.html
</guid><description>
Total Commander is the most popular file manager with all necessary functions for both casual users and IT professionals. Total Commander will help you manage, change data, computer files allowing you to best manage your data. Total Commander tool has two parallel opening windows that allow you to move and copy data from one folder to another easily.
In addition to all the tools dedicated to file managers, Total Commander also contains very convenient viewers for multimedia and graphic...
</description></item><item><title>Download AITextTune 1.4.9.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Dec 2025 19:19:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aitexttune-12973.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aitexttune-12973.html
</guid><description>
AITextTune is an AI-powered tool designed to enhance and refine text content. It offers features such as improving clarity and coherence, generating summaries, and translating text into multiple languages. Users can easily adjust their writing style from formal to creative. This tool is very flexible and can be used on many different software and platforms.
AITextTune Features
	WRITE PERFECTLY: Improve the clarity and coherence of your writing! Create summaries and...
</description></item><item><title>Download SoftMaker FlexiPDF Professional 2025.416.1204</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Dec 2025 19:18:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-softmaker-flexipdf-professional-1513.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-softmaker-flexipdf-professional-1513.html
</guid><description>
SoftMaker FlexiPDF Professional is the perfect software to edit and create pdf files. With this program, you can easily open any pdf file in environment task simple and easy. Change the text you want. Change the color of text and paragraphs. Like software Word, you can create a section of text or italics. Can you are not satisfied with the font of the pdf, you can open the file and save it with the font you want to pdf. In addition to text, you can add forms, graphics, photos, comments,...
</description></item><item><title>Download XYplorer 28.10.0000</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Dec 2025 19:18:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-533.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-533.html
</guid><description>
XYplorer - File Manager for Windows is software that supports users to manage files on the Window quickly and to arrange the folder tidy. XYplorer features tabbed browsing, search, files, powerful, preview, flexible, highly customizable interface, dual frame options and a variety of unique ways to automate effective tasks often repeat. It's fast, lightweight, and portable.
Features XYplorer
	XYplorer is a file manager mobile. It does not require any settings, store all configuration...
</description></item><item><title>Download Office Timeline Plus 13.15.00.00 Expert / Pro / Pro+ Edition</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Dec 2025 19:17:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-timeline-2106.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-timeline-2106.html
</guid><description>
Office Timeline is an add-on very useful and powerful software for Microsoft PowerPoint. With add-ons, you can create PowerPoint documents look more beautiful. With add-ons, you can add the time Line on the project by yourself. Application time for the composition and different segments of the document, your PowerPoint will not only increase the beauty for your work, but also for customers and your manager. The people who created this product is also believe that add-ons this is the only...
</description></item><item><title>Download Bitsum Process Lasso Pro 17.0.0.132</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Dec 2025 19:16:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bitsum-process-lasso-pro-289.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bitsum-process-lasso-pro-289.html
</guid><description>
Bitsum Process Lasso Pro is software compact statistics and troubleshoot computer systems, such as crashes by control CPU. Technological process Lassos ProBalance (process balance) adjust the smart priority of running programs so that the process works poorly or too active will not affect the ability to use your computer!
Software Process Lasso to help manage the program or application will be managed and controlled to not have the ability to monopolize the CPU. Process Lasso also...
</description></item><item><title>Download Any Video Downloader Pro 10.0.5</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Dec 2025 19:16:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-video-downloader-pro-3731.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-video-downloader-pro-3731.html
</guid><description>
Any Video Downloader Pro is software support you can download video HD 720p, 1080p, 2K, 4K and 8K from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion, Vimeo, Metacafe and thousands of video sharing sites, other. It is a tool to speed up multi-threading can speed up your download faster up to 5 times. This helpful program support download at the same time. Any Video Downloader Pro lets you download multiple videos at the same time. Moreover, it allows you to pause and resume downloads if you need more...
</description></item><item><title>Download MSAct++ 2.11</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Dec 2025 19:15:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-msact-plus-plus-258.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-msact-plus-plus-258.html
</guid><description>
MSAct++ is compact software with features activate windows and office license quickly with click simple. Program for install key and activate Windows 7-10 and Office 2010-2016. If the key installed allows the activation through the network, through the Internet, product will be activated automatically, if this does not happen and the lock is not key - code is issued to transfer the M $ Activation Center to activate by phone. Unlike MSAct in the program MSAct Plus has the ability to create...
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 7.5.6</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Dec 2025 19:14:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-10-7759.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-10-7759.html
</guid><description>
TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 is a utility that allows users to discover hidden settings in Windows 10. This application is specially designed for Windows 10, groups many registry settings and provide them from an easy and secure user interface. With TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 you can move the Windows taskbar to the top and resize the taskbar by editing the registry value. With any application that modifies the registry, we recommend that you have a backup copy to...
</description></item><item><title>Download MedCalc 23.4.5</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Dec 2025 19:14:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-medcalc-1536.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-medcalc-1536.html
</guid><description>
MedCalc is a statistical software for biomedical research can analyze many performance curve system with a set of rich functionality, chart types and advanced module. MedCalc was designed to meet the needs and requirements of the study nature and aims to analyze the statistical calculations of the project. This software provides the tools and means essential to analyze the characteristic curve of the system (ROC), drawing data and perform the statistical calculations.
MedCalc -...
</description></item><item><title>Download PhoneRescue for iOS 4.3.1.20251211</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Dec 2025 19:13:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-phonerescue-for-ios-2851.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-phonerescue-for-ios-2851.html
</guid><description>
PhoneRescue for iOS is the solution to restore lost data of iOS devices such as iPhone, iPad with the ability to work quickly find back all the data on the device such as music, videos, photos, call logs, contacts, or even sms. With PhoneRescue is that you don't need to connect iPhone device with the computer directly, the software works through the index and account, now you can completely assured when using data on the iPhone, by all user's data are lost, you can restore back...
</description></item><item><title>Download Aidfile Recovery Software Professional 3.7.9.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Dec 2025 19:12:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aidfile-recovery-software-professional-4316.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aidfile-recovery-software-professional-4316.html
</guid><description>
Aidfile Recovery Software Professional is a software small but powerful will assist you to recover files lost, deleted or damaged. It is ideal to restore data such as videos, files, office, images, folders and many other things. Professional tool this will help you to perform full scan and in-depth hard drive and partition, USB drive, memory card or removable media , to fully restore your data. This software can restore the data file from the file system partition FAT32, NTFS and ExFAT,...
</description></item><item><title>Download ASCOMP Easy Slideshow Professional 2.001</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Dec 2025 19:12:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ascomp-easy-slideshow-professional-13811.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ascomp-easy-slideshow-professional-13811.html
</guid><description>
ASCOMP Easy Slideshow Professional is a user-friendly Windows software designed to quickly create stunning slideshow videos from your photos. Ideal for both beginners and professionals, the software offers an intuitive drag-and-drop interface for arranging images, setting display durations, and adding individual subtitles or captions for personalization.
Key features include:
	Over 200 built-in transition effects such as soft fades, dynamic zooms, and creative animations for changing...
</description></item><item><title>Download TexSender Pro 8.9.9</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Dec 2025 19:11:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-texsender-pro-9550.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-texsender-pro-9550.html
</guid><description>
TexSender Pro is a software designed for those who want to send Telegram messages directly from their PC in a simple and efficient way. TexSender requires no API and uses Telegram Web technology to automate various activities like sending messages, adding members to your group, etc. This is more and more popular.
Features of TexSender Pro
	Create and send personalized messages to Telegram contacts or user lists (list of phone numbers or usernames). Messages can be sent with alternate...
</description></item><item><title>Download Chaos Enscape 4.14.0.668</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Dec 2025 18:06:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-enscape-3d-4125.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-enscape-3d-4125.html
</guid><description>
Enscape 3D is the tool support simulation 3D for the software Revit, SketchUp, Rhino, ArchiCAD. With real-time technology of Enscape 3D your project is displayed in the form of walk-3D is fully displayed, can be navigated and explored from every angle, at every moment of the day. With direct link between Enscape 3D and CAD programs, you can track all updates for his plan immediately. More Enscape to your work to give yourself more time to create and innovate. Enscape 3D offers many options...
</description></item><item><title>Download Q-Dir 12.43</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Dec 2025 18:05:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-q-dir-348.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-q-dir-348.html
</guid><description>
Q-Dir is software to manage the entire file and folder on the computer, allowing to see file in same time 4 different positions (viewport quadro) while still maintaining all the standard features of the Explorer.
It also provides a variety of management features, additional files included the filter file color-coding, layouts and columns can be customized, quick access to file and folder favorites and more.
Other features of Q-Dir , including directory listings (.txt, .doc .html .csv),...
</description></item><item><title>Download Chaos V-Ray 7.2.2 Build 7.20.02 for SketchUp 2021 - 2026</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Dec 2025 18:04:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chao-vray-for-sketchup-3936.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chao-vray-for-sketchup-3936.html
</guid><description>
V-Ray Next for SketchUp is the tool of Chaos Group for Windows PC, this is a lighting tool and as a professional for architects &amp;amp; designers.V-Ray Next for SketchUp allows you to export everything and everything - from the design models to the 3D scene details most of you. Use V-Ray for SketchUp, you can also have access to over 600 documents actual photo, drag and drop. V-Ray Next for SketchUp is very easy to use and brings great results. You can use it to create everything - from 3D...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDQ Inventory 19.6.21.0 Enterprise</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Dec 2025 18:03:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdq-inventory-1468.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdq-inventory-1468.html
</guid><description>
PDQ Inventory is a software application to manage your system. This software will be able to manage your system by scanning the Windows operating system of you to provide information hardware, software, and configuration for the Windows operating system in your your tools. The tools available in this software helps you can scan the computer correctly.
In addition, the software PDQ Inventory can give you very detailed information. This software application is one of the management...
</description></item><item><title>Download Chaos V-Ray 7.2.2 Build 7.20.02 for Rhinoceros 7-9</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Dec 2025 18:03:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-v-ray-next-for-rhino-1285.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-v-ray-next-for-rhino-1285.html
</guid><description>
V-Ray Next For Rhino is an extension a very powerful and handy for Rhino can be used to improve the process output. V-Ray Next allows you to achieve much achievement in Rhino than ever. It's faster to showcase your designs in the best light of them. And a variety of new tools to help manage and display the sight of you much easier.
V-Ray Next For Rhino
V-Ray Next in for Rhino comes with some speed on the table. Optimize performance, speed up the production up to 50% off. The shader...
</description></item><item><title>Download O&amp;amp;O SafeErase Pro 20.1.577</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Dec 2025 18:02:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-safeerase-pro-294.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-safeerase-pro-294.html
</guid><description>
O&amp;amp;O SafeErase Pro is software that helps you to delete sensitive data securely with safeguards against misuse of data. With O&amp;amp;O SafeErase Pro you can be sure that no data is put into the wrong hands. O&amp;amp;O SafeErase provides reliable solution to securely delete files sensitive security and provide you with data protection optimization. With O&amp;amp;O SafeErase even hackers and spyware data can't restore the deleted files of your safety.
&amp;nbsp;O&amp;amp;O SafeErase is the solution...
</description></item><item><title>Download Visual Studio Code 1.107.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Dec 2025 18:01:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-visual-studio-code-3182.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-visual-studio-code-3182.html
</guid><description>
Visual Studio Code is the encryption tool of Microsoft has met most of the needs of the developer. Environment this encoding was introduced to compete with other products such as Sublime and Nodepad ++ . Microsoft, in its new product, has not been released in many years, has provided many features in a simple environment. In addition to the familiar with a dozen programming languages, the syntax and get to know coding language as soon as be encrypted and allows for syntax highlighting, it...
</description></item><item><title>Download Chaos Vantage 3.1.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Dec 2025 18:01:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chaos-vantage-6178.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chaos-vantage-6178.html
</guid><description>
Explore and interact with enough 3D detail in real time. Chaos Vantage is even more outstanding than the V-Ray even though you ' re using the V-Ray version. Artists and designers only need to pull and drop their V-Ray (.vrscene) scenes to discover them immediately in real time-without taking the time to optimize the geometry, opening up the UV package. When in Vantage, the user has the freedom to define and recall views and scenes, create a role in the role and communicate better than...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDQ Deploy 19.6.21.0 Enterprise</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Dec 2025 18:00:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdq-deploy-1469.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdq-deploy-1469.html
</guid><description>
PDQ Deploy Enterprise is an application to keep the Windows PC and the programs installed on it. Software PDQ Deploy helps you to connect multiple patch or a windows app (.exe, .msi) with multiple operating systems. The deployment software can be install, delete, run script, reboot, copy the file, sliding mode, send messages, etc.
PDQ Deploy Enterprise
Features of PDQ Deploy Enterprise
	Send notifications (alerts) via email
	Run the script as popular as .vbs, .reg .bat and .ps1
	Run...
</description></item><item><title>Download VectorStyler 1.3.002</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Dec 2025 18:00:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vectorstyler-7917.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vectorstyler-7917.html
</guid><description>
VectorStyler provides a complete set of drawing, design and illustration tools needed for modern design. Create illustrations, logos, icons, drawings, typography, vector art for screen, print and web. With many new features, VectorStyler redefines and extends the tools available to illustrators and designers, improving the creation of complex illustrations and designs.
Shape effects can be used to adjust the shape of objects, create different distortions, or add detail to shapes. Shape...
</description></item></channel></rss>