<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 10:09:05 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 10:09:05 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Eusing Cleaner 6.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Sep 2025 23:35:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-eusing-cleaner-2912.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-eusing-cleaner-2912.html
</guid><description>
Eusing Cleaner app is free to use system optimization and cleaning tools right to privacy. It level for you to explore and delete the old file in your system, the registry files null, delete your internet history, provides added support to clean the history for over 150 programs of side Tuesday. You can select the items that you want cleaned and also specify cookies should not be deleted. With just a click of the mouse, Eusing Cleaner can clear the memory auto-completion, cookies, the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Secret Disk Pro 2025 v313</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Sep 2025 23:34:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secret-disk-pro-933.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secret-disk-pro-933.html
</guid><description>
Secret Disk Pro 4 is a software to create a virtual disk can be hidden and password protected to keep your data private and safe. You can store any file and folder on the disk. Disc secret works like a hard disk typically, and is compatible with any any other program that you have installed. You can have more than one disk secret, and you can also choose disk letter.
Secret Disk Pro 4 - Create and secure drive
Secret Disk does not encrypt any files, it just limits access to your files...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare Repairit 6.5.15.9</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Sep 2025 23:33:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-recoverit-video-repair-3889.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-recoverit-video-repair-3889.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare Recoverit Video Repair is a reliable application that helps you fix the broken video, Wondershare Recoverit Video Repair supports file formats MP4, MOV, M4V, M2TS, MKV, MTS, 3GP, AVI and FLV is corrupt and broken. Great service we provide. It fixes the video that there is corruption in the process of shooting, when done, file transfer, while editing, convert.
Wondershare Recoverit Video Repair - video repair broken
Features of Wondershare Recoverit Video Repair
	Repair...
</description></item><item><title>Download Foxit PDF Editor Pro 2025.2.0.33046 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Sep 2025 23:33:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-foxit-pdf-editor-pro-162.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-foxit-pdf-editor-pro-162.html
</guid><description>
Foxit PDF Editor Pro (formerly Foxit PhantomPDF Business) is a PDF toolkit dedicated to the creation of professional PDF documents and forms. You can do that for tasks such as personal document development, working group collaboration, company model design. Manufacturing the company's collateral, completing the agreements, applying the signature number or document storage.
Foxit PDF Editor Pro is the perfect solution for family/family offices, small and medium enterprises and large...
</description></item><item><title>Download Memtest86 Pro 11.5 Build 1000</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Sep 2025 23:32:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-memtest86-pro-725.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-memtest86-pro-725.html
</guid><description>
Memtest86 Pro is software check free RAM memory in your computer to detect the latent fault inside the memory. Anyone know RAM is very important part of the computer. If RAM is error that does not fix soon will greatly affect your computer. Therefore, the Memtest86 Pro is the software necessary for the system of your computer.
Memtest86 Pro - Check memory RAM
Features of Memtest86 Pro
	13 algorithm to check RAM different
	Support RAM DDR4 (and DDR2 &amp;amp; DDR3)
	XMP - configuration...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mocha Pro for Adobe 2025.5 v12.5.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Sep 2025 23:31:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mocha-pro-1029.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mocha-pro-1029.html
</guid><description>
Mocha Pro 2019 is the tool for visual effects and postproduction. Tool Tracking and VFX and is plugins for Adobe. Mocha is the artist and editor effects appreciate about the unique ability of his to reduce the time using keyframing related to VFX and premium finishing.
Mocha Pro 2019
Mocha Pro 2019 features track and remove objects that are GPU acceleratedtools, rotoscoping, advanced, stable, solved 3D camera, supports stereo 360 / VR, etc. Using Mocha AE CC in Adobe After Effects? See...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mocha Pro for OFX 2025.5 v12.5.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Sep 2025 23:31:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mocha-pro-for-ofx-4303.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mocha-pro-for-ofx-4303.html
</guid><description>
Mocha Pro for OFX is the tracking tool flat the world's most powerful for VFX and postproduction. With the tracking feature and remove objects that are GPU accelerated, mask advanced with snapshot feature edge, stable, corrective lens, the 3D camera, supports stereo 360 / VR, v. v. Mocha Pro for OFX is a plugin for Adobe Premiere Pro &amp;amp; After Effects, servers Avid Media Composer &amp;amp; OFX as Flame, Nuke, Fusion, HitFilm, and VEGAS Pro.
Mocha Pro for OFX 2020
New features in version...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mocha Pro Standalone 2025.5 v12.5.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Sep 2025 23:31:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mocha-pro-standalone-4302.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mocha-pro-standalone-4302.html
</guid><description>
Mocha Pro Standalone is the tracking tool flat the world's most powerful for VFX and postproduction. With the tracking feature and remove objects that are GPU accelerated, mask advanced with snapshot feature edge, stable, corrective lens, the 3D camera, supports stereo 360 / VR, v. v. Mocha Pro Standalone is a plugin for Adobe Premiere Pro &amp;amp; After Effects, servers Avid Media Composer &amp;amp; OFX as Flame, Nuke, Fusion, HitFilm, and VEGAS Pro.
Mocha Pro Standalone 2020
New features in...
</description></item><item><title>Download AnkhTech Toolbox 3.2.0.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Sep 2025 23:30:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ankhtech-toolbox-10197.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ankhtech-toolbox-10197.html
</guid><description>
AnkhTech Toolbox is a compact toolkit used to install necessary programs in just a few clicks, Activate your Microsoft Windows or Microsoft Office. With the Simple interface, all you have to do is write the option number you want and press Enter Full Automatically Downloads and installs a simple tool that runs on any Microsoft Windows without any requirements Works on x32 and x64 without any problems.
Programs Section Contains most of the Software used (Activated and Free) Runtime...
</description></item><item><title>Download Boris FX Mocha Pro for AVX 2025.5 v12.5.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Sep 2025 23:29:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-boris-fx-mocha-pro-for-avx-13995.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-boris-fx-mocha-pro-for-avx-13995.html
</guid><description>
Boris FX Mocha Pro for AVX is the industry-leading version of the plane tracking and visual effects software, designed to work as a plugin supporting AVX (Avid Video Extensions) servers such as Avid Media Composer. Mocha Pro integrates advanced plane tracking, rotoscoping, 3D camera resolution, object removal, image stabilization, and masking tools into supported hosts, including AVX-based editing software.
Key points about Boris FX Mocha Pro for AVX:
	This is part of the Boris FX...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Downloader 9.17.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Sep 2025 23:28:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html
</guid><description>
YTD Youtube Downloader is an application that reliable and intuitive, allowing you to quickly download YouTube videos and save them to your computer. You can also convert the media files to the format desired video or extract audio streams and save separately. YTD Youtube Downloader lets you save your favorite clips of yourself from Youtube, Facebook, Vimeo and Dailymotion to your desktop. The software supports URLS from many web site hosting, multimedia and allows you to download desired...
</description></item><item><title>Download Boris FX SynthEyes Pro 2025.5.1 Build 3399</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Sep 2025 23:27:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syntheyes-pro-9914.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syntheyes-pro-9914.html
</guid><description>
Syntheyes Pro is a standalone application optimized for camera, object, geometry and plane tracking, stabilization and motion capture, with high performance, huge feature list, output to many applications. Use SynthEyes to insert creatures, fix shaky photos, virtual backgrounds, object removal, stereoscopic production, 360° VR, architecture preview, accident reconstruction, product placement, face and body capture, and more.
Features of Syntheyes Pro
	SynthEyes has been supporting...
</description></item><item><title>Download Boris FX Particle Illusion Pro 2025.5 v18.5.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Sep 2025 23:27:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-boris-fx-particle-illusion-pro-11486.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-boris-fx-particle-illusion-pro-11486.html
</guid><description>
Boris FX Particle Illusion Pro is powerful visual effects software developed by Boris FX, a leading developer of VFX, compositing, titling and workflow tools. Workflow for the film, television and video editing industries. Particle Illusion Pro is an enhanced version of Particle Illusion software, providing advanced features and capabilities to create stunning particle effects.
Features of Boris FX Particle Illusion Pro
	Advanced particle effects: Particle Illusion Pro allows users to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Boris FX CrumplePop Pro 2025.5.0 (AAX/VST3)</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Sep 2025 23:26:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-boris-fx-crumplepop-complete-9687.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-boris-fx-crumplepop-complete-9687.html
</guid><description>
Boris FX CrumplePop Complete is a complete set of audio plugin tools to make your sound the best with advanced AI technology. Never before has dealing with common audio problems like background noise, echoes, traffic, wind, and more. as well as enhancing the sound quality to achieve professional results has never been easier. The CrumplePop audio tools are easy to use if you're a beginner, and powerful enough to meet the daily needs of audio professionals.
Features of Boris FX...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinCHM Pro 5.551</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Sep 2025 23:24:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winchm-pro-1059.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winchm-pro-1059.html
</guid><description>
WinCHM Pro full name Softany WinCHM Pro is a drafting tools help create HTML help, professional, and good-looking (CHM), help, Web, PDF manual and Word documents. With this powerful tool you can not only create a chm from scratch, but also convert a set of HTML files existing files CHM. You can open CHM existing and edit the file chm. create CHM file.
WinCHM Pro - Drafting help CHM
WinCHM Pro offers you a tool to handle the complete text and the attributes may be configured for images,...
</description></item><item><title>Download FileLocator Pro 2022 Build 3532</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Sep 2025 23:24:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-filelocator-pro-1056.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-filelocator-pro-1056.html
</guid><description>
FileLocator Pro is software manage files and search function the file quickly the software and data. FileLocator Pro helps you find things quickly. The unique feature of it allows the extraction of information in all file formats the most obscure.
FileLocator Pro - file Manager
The features of FileLocator Pro
	Search algorithm based on the C ++ multi-threading for ultra-fast
	Search for network drive by mapped drive or UNC paths
	Support regular expressions for file name and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Vivaldi Browser 7.6.3797.52</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Sep 2025 23:23:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vivaldi-159.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vivaldi-159.html
</guid><description>
Vivaldi is a browser designed for users who have power and offer the option to customize high. You can choose the location of the tabs and the address bar, put the hotkeys for the common tasks and many other features. Also, Vivaldi also provides a number of improvements such as Tab Stacks to group multiple open tabs into a tab, leads to interface less cluttered. Can notes and added a screenshot of a web page while browsing, storing an attachment, and add the URL to easily sort and locate...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft PowerToys for Windows 10/11 0.94.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Sep 2025 23:23:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-powertoys-for-windows-6014.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-powertoys-for-windows-6014.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft PowerToys is a user-proficiency set to adjust and streamline their Windows experience for higher productivity. Inspired by Windows 95's PowerToys project, this reboot provides users with proficiency in ways to exploit the more efficient Windows 10 and customisable processes it provides for each work process.
Utility of Microsoft PowerToys
	FancyZones is a window manager that allows you to easily create complex windows layout and quickly locate windows in those layout.
	Image...
</description></item><item><title>Download LastPass Password Manager 5.1.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Sep 2025 23:18:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lastpass-269.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lastpass-269.html
</guid><description>
LastPass is a free software to help manage passwords allows you to store all the login information of your site in a warehouse password cross-platform compatibility only. Instead of remember the user name and personal password, you only need to remember the main password to open the lock the password of his safe.
LastPass
LastPass can automatically fill in the login box for all the account website is your hosting. Whenever you log into a website has stored your vault, the program will...
</description></item><item><title>Download Pazu StreamGet All-In-One Video Downloader 2.8.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Sep 2025 23:17:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pazu-streamget-all-in-one-video-downloader-12037.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pazu-streamget-all-in-one-video-downloader-12037.html
</guid><description>
StreamGet All-In-One Video Downloader is the ultimate downloading solution for you. It supports downloading any movies and shows from the most popular streaming sites including Netflix, Prime Video, Disney Plus, Max, Hulu, and Apple TV Plus. The downloader is continuously updated to support more platforms in the future.
Download movies and shows from various streaming platforms to MP4/MKV on your Windows device and enjoy them anywhere you want.
Features of Pazu StreamGet All-In-One...
</description></item><item><title>Download XL-Connector 3.6.11.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Sep 2025 23:17:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xl-connector-12415.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xl-connector-12415.html
</guid><description>
XL-Connector is a popular plugin that securely integrates Excel and Salesforce to export, import, refresh and transform data seamlessly with ultra-fast api connection. It provides Salesforce administrators with a comprehensive toolbox that easily performs data and metadata management activities in a familiar Excel environment.
Features
Export from Salesforce to Excel
	Get data from existing Salesforce reports or build your own SOQL queries directly into Excel.
Import data into...
</description></item><item><title>Download Private Windows Script (PrivWindoze) 5.7.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Sep 2025 23:17:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-private-windows-script-12878.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-private-windows-script-12878.html
</guid><description>
Are you concerned about your personal information sent to others? Or do you feel that your Windows settings have many programs that you never use? Private Windows Script (or Privwindoze) provides a comprehensive anti -remote monitoring set designed to enhance your privacy when using Windows operating system.
The main features
	End the positive process. All unnecessary processes are turned off while the scanning program. A small white list is maintained.
	Clean up the positive runonce....
</description></item><item><title>Download Zoom Player Max 22.0 Beta 1</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Sep 2025 23:16:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zoom-player-max-104.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zoom-player-max-104.html
</guid><description>
Zoom Player MAX help you to see the film on DVD, Blu-ray, Flash movies and HD format with high quality and the ability to display subtitles in English very well. The advantage of software is that takes up very little system resources to play the movie with quick speed, change the wallpaper options while viewing movies.
Zoom Player MAX is the movies, browse high-quality photos on the computer with the advantages such as compact size, quick start, built-in codec. The application supports...
</description></item><item><title>Download Viber for PC 26.2.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Sep 2025 23:14:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-viber-2406.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-viber-2406.html
</guid><description>
Viber is a software of instant messaging, based on VoIP protocols, multi-platform due to the Viber Media development for smart phones used to send sms and make calls over the internet. Along with text messaging, users can exchange images, video and audio.
Viber - software news message, chat online
This is a program that is quite popular is mainly designed for mobile phones, but now we are talking about the version for Windows, so immediately. It will allow you to send messages to other...
</description></item><item><title>Download Flyby11 1.20.400</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Sep 2025 23:14:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-flyby11-12467.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-flyby11-12467.html
</guid><description>
Flyby11 is a simple patcher that removes annoying restrictions that prevent you from installing Windows 11 (24H2) on unsupported hardware. Do you have an old PC? No TPM, Secure Boot or your processor is not supported? Flyby11 allows you to install Windows 11 24H2. There are no complicated steps. Just run the tool and you'll be running Windows 11 on your outdated machine in no time.
Technical overview
Flyby11 takes advantage of a feature of the Windows 11 setup process that uses the...
</description></item></channel></rss>