<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 13:50:08 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 13:50:08 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Media Player Classic Black Edition 1.8.9</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Dec 2025 15:35:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-media-player-classic-black-edition-3351.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-media-player-classic-black-edition-3351.html
</guid><description>
Media Player Classic Black Edition is abbreviated as MPC-BE is a free program that can interface black support users to watch movies, listen to music on the computer with the new interface. Media Player Classic - BE is based on the project "Media Player Classic" original (Gabest) and the project "Media Player Classic Home Cinema" (Casimir666), contains additional features and bug fixes.
Both programs are quite similar, because they are based on Media Player Classic original. In fact, MPC...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare Repairit 6.6.1.7</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Dec 2025 15:31:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-recoverit-video-repair-3889.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-recoverit-video-repair-3889.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare Recoverit Video Repair is a reliable application that helps you fix the broken video, Wondershare Recoverit Video Repair supports file formats MP4, MOV, M4V, M2TS, MKV, MTS, 3GP, AVI and FLV is corrupt and broken. Great service we provide. It fixes the video that there is corruption in the process of shooting, when done, file transfer, while editing, convert.
Wondershare Recoverit Video Repair - video repair broken
Features of Wondershare Recoverit Video Repair
	Repair...
</description></item><item><title>Download Zortam Mp3 Media Studio Pro 33.65</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Dec 2025 15:31:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zortam-mp3-media-studio-pro-135.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zortam-mp3-media-studio-pro-135.html
</guid><description>
Zortam Mp3 Media Studio Pro brings you rich processing tools music includes extract and convert music from CD to Mp3 format, edit, music cards, music download....You can also create discs CD high-quality music, with Zortam Mp3 Media Studio search music files duplicated to remove them from the system, rename music files, switch back and forth between formats.
Zortam Mp3 Media Studio Pro is rated as perfect software in the processing of the MP3 files on the computer. First of all, you can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Free YouTube Download 4.4.48.1225 Premium</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Dec 2025 15:30:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-download-1177.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-download-1177.html
</guid><description>
Free YouTube Download Premium is the most popular application to download videos from YouTube. The program was released in 2006 and regularly updated since then. Use the program to download and convert YouTube videos to view offline anytime.
Free YouTube Download - added Support to download youtube
Download more videos! Save whole playlists and YouTube channels, videos from a playlist individually (history, video be favorite, favourites, Watch later), videos from many different...
</description></item><item><title>Download FastStone Photo Resizer 4.5 Corporate</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Dec 2025 15:30:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-faststone-photo-resizer-364.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-faststone-photo-resizer-364.html
</guid><description>
FastStone Photo Resizer is an image converter batch, such as rename, resize, crop, rotate, change color depth. FastStone Photo Resizer supports drag and drop will help you to quickly complete his work. FastStone Photo Resizer output files in the most popular formats, including TIFF, GIF, JPEG and BMP. Besides the skills, batch conversion, the application also can rename bulk images.
This program demonstrated speedy performance in our testing and we appreciate that its main window can be...
</description></item><item><title>Download Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium 4.4.48.1225</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Dec 2025 15:29:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-to-mp3-converter-premium-844.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-to-mp3-converter-premium-844.html
</guid><description>
Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium version is a software used to convert YouTube to MP3, extract audio from playlists YouTube, show listings, charts, video responses, channels, favorites of the user. With Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium, you can download and convert playlists, channels, stream original tv series and get them into iTunes at the same time.
Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium - convert YouTube to MP3
Features Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium from the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Draftable Desktop 25.12.100</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Dec 2025 15:29:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-draftable-desktop-3749.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-draftable-desktop-3749.html
</guid><description>
Draftable Desktop is comparison tool documents the fastest. Compare over 300 pages in a few seconds. Draftable Desktop 2.0 is now available - faster and stronger than ever! See all the changes in your documents, locally and online. Take your work to the next level. Compare secret and private do not use the internet and your documents never leave your computer. Specifically, Draftable Desktop compatible with .xls, .xlsx, .xlsxm. With Office 2013, 2016 or 365, you can compare text in...
</description></item><item><title>Download DAZ Studio Professional 4.24.0.4</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Dec 2025 15:28:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-daz-studio-professional-4946.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-daz-studio-professional-4946.html
</guid><description>
DAZ Studio Professional is a professional application to create 3D models and customize them with many different accessories. This app allows you to create scenes by using the model are included in the package. With this app, you can download drum patterns as well as customize it by changing the location, direction as well as the size of each component. DAZ Studio Professional provides the tools to help you can create the presets for any element by arranging the location as well as save it...
</description></item><item><title>Download Aidfile Recovery Software Professional 3.7.9.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Dec 2025 15:28:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aidfile-recovery-software-professional-4316.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aidfile-recovery-software-professional-4316.html
</guid><description>
Aidfile Recovery Software Professional is a software small but powerful will assist you to recover files lost, deleted or damaged. It is ideal to restore data such as videos, files, office, images, folders and many other things. Professional tool this will help you to perform full scan and in-depth hard drive and partition, USB drive, memory card or removable media , to fully restore your data. This software can restore the data file from the file system partition FAT32, NTFS and ExFAT,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Coolmuster iPhone Data Recovery 6.0.48</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Dec 2025 15:27:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-iphone-data-recovery-6599.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-iphone-data-recovery-6599.html
</guid><description>
Coolmuster iPhone Data Recovery is a useful tool designed to help users retrieve all lost data in the iPhone, iPad, or iPod quickly and efficiently. This professional software provides users with a safe way to find lost or deleted data on the Windows system. It can be used in any situation, both online and offline.
Features of Coolmuster iPhone Data Recovery
	Quickly restore the missing or deleted files from the iOS device and the iTunes backup.
	The processing of your iPhone data in...
</description></item><item><title>Download Helium Music Manager Premium 17.4.551</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Dec 2025 15:27:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-helium-music-manager-premium-164.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-helium-music-manager-premium-164.html
</guid><description>
Helium Music Manager is a music manager that can rip, tag, play, browse, search, rename, burn and synchronize your music with the mobile. You can control your music collection with Helium Music Manager. Stop using time looking for the file on your computer or looking through CDS, vinyl records and tapes - instead, simply enjoy and explore your music! Helium Music Manager can replace the ripper, the player, tag editor and related software to audio your other.
Helium Music Manager...
</description></item><item><title>Download Publicspace Photo Date Changer 1.20</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Dec 2025 15:26:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-publicspace-photo-date-changer-5151.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-publicspace-photo-date-changer-5151.html
</guid><description>
Publicspace Photo Date Changer is an easy to use utility allows you to troubleshoot with the date of shooting JPEG (called EXIF timestamp). Publicspace Photo Date Changer ensure arranged in order of time accuracy in the application of the Tuesday (app management, photo slideshow, photo website online, etc., and once captured, there is no easy way to change the date is embed this. forget to change the time zone when traveling or simply have the camera clock is set...
</description></item><item><title>Download Coolmuster iPhone WhatsApp Recovery 2.0.4</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Dec 2025 15:26:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-iphone-whatsapp-recovery-12378.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-iphone-whatsapp-recovery-12378.html
</guid><description>
Coolmuster iPhone WhatsApp Recovery provides effective recovery of WhatsApp messages and attachments from iPhone and iPad devices, ensuring you never lose important chats. View and access WhatsApp chat history and attachments conveniently on your PC, giving you complete control over your WhatsApp data.
Recover WhatsApp data in accessible formats for seamless management and use. Coolmuster iPhone WhatsApp Recovery ensures high retrieval speed and wide compatibility with many devices for...
</description></item><item><title>Download VovSoft Bulk QR Code Generator 2.4</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Dec 2025 15:25:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-bulk-qr-code-generator-7909.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-bulk-qr-code-generator-7909.html
</guid><description>
QR Code are commonly used to contain data for locators, identifiers, or trackers that point to a web page. QR Code stores data efficiently by supporting different encoding modes such as numeric, alphanumeric, byte, binary. Generating thousands of QR Code with different data individually can be time consuming. But with VovSoft Bulk QR Code Generator, you can generate QR Code containing different plain texts at the same time by generating QR Code in bulk.
Although there are various online...
</description></item><item><title>Download Coolmuster iCloud Backup Recovery 2.0.4</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Dec 2025 15:25:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-icloud-backup-recovery-10586.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-icloud-backup-recovery-10586.html
</guid><description>
Want to select files from your iCloud backup? Now, with the help of this iCloud Backup Restore tool, you can do it directly. With this iCloud backup restore program, you can save iCloud backup files to your computer in readable formats. So you can view and access them easily.
Coolmuster iCloud Backup Recovery can log in directly to iCloud there and preview your backup contacts. So, you have regained your contacts from your iCloud backup. By the way, this tool also supports other files....
</description></item><item><title>Download DesktopDigitalClock 6.19</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Dec 2025 15:24:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopdigitalclock-4114.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopdigitalclock-4114.html
</guid><description>
DesktopDigitalClock is a program that desktop clock digital simply and beautifully with the theme and different custom for all MS-OS was inspired from the lock screen! Be made according to numerous requests of users, with the idea of the clock lock screen appearance in Windows 10 / 8.1 after login, display the time and date when the log in the left corner, to the analog clock to appear on desktop Windows.
DesktopDigitalClock - the clock on the computer
The basic function: high...
</description></item><item><title>Download Chris-PC RAM Booster 7.25.1229</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Dec 2025 15:24:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chris-pc-ram-booster-1181.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chris-pc-ram-booster-1181.html
</guid><description>
ChrisPC RAM Booster is software speed up your system by managing and acceleration of the RAM in the operating system. RAM Booster will monitor the RAM usage (memory random access) and upon reaching the threshold memory certain low, it will trigger the process of freeing up memory for the new program open while moving at the same time the old programs from the RAM memory into virtual memory on disk.
Chris-PC RAM Booster - speed up processing RAM
Certainly this is a slower process...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sante DICOM Viewer Pro 14.3.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Dec 2025 15:23:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sante-dicom-viewer-pro-11761.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sante-dicom-viewer-pro-11761.html
</guid><description>
Sante DICOM Viewer Pro is a professional DICOM viewer, anonymizer, converter, PACS client, mini PACS server, patient CD/DVD burner (with viewer) and more. This is a unique program with unique capabilities, designed and developed by us in-house from the ground up, with the most advanced programming tools and is the result of extensive research and development on DICOM image over the past two decades. Sante DICOM Viewer Pro has been developed since 1999 and is one of the most popular...
</description></item><item><title>Download Coolmuster iPhone SMS + Contacts Recovery 5.0.6</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Dec 2025 15:23:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-iphone-sms-contacts-recovery-8524.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-iphone-sms-contacts-recovery-8524.html
</guid><description>
Coolmuster iPhone SMS + Contacts Recovery is professional software that helps to recover all contacts and SMS from iPhone. It recovers not only phone numbers and text messages, but also contact names, addresses, companies, emails, SMS attachments, and more. The 100% read-only and safe recovery process provided by the iPhone data recovery program allows you to back up your recovered iPhone text messages and contacts on your computer without any quality loss.
Features of Coolmuster iPhone...
</description></item><item><title>Download Coolmuster iPhone Backup Extractor 4.0.4</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Dec 2025 15:23:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-iphone-backup-extractor-8007.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-iphone-backup-extractor-8007.html
</guid><description>
The iTunes backup file is not a regular file but a SQlitedb file. It cannot be read. So even if you find the backup file, you won't be able to get the contents out of the file let alone restore your iPhone. Coolmuster iPhone Backup Extractor is an iPhone Extractor program, dedicated to help you extract iPhone backup from iTunes on Windows easily. And it also allows iPhone users to recover specific files with a simple click.
Features of Coolmuster iPhone Backup Extractor
	Extract...
</description></item><item><title>Download Stellarium 25.4</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Dec 2025 15:22:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stellarium-2534.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stellarium-2534.html
</guid><description>
Stellarium is a software planetarium shows 3D simulation realistic about the night sky on your computer screen, you. It includes a default category with more than 600,000 stars, images of nebulae, galaxies fact, as well as the planets and satellites of them (additional categories available to download). You can click on each object to view the name, distance and other details and can also zoom to see more closely.
Stellarium - astronomical App
The program can show the sky based on the...
</description></item><item><title>Download FrostWire 7.0.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Dec 2025 15:21:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-frostwire-158.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-frostwire-158.html
</guid><description>
FrostWire is the tool to share files peer allows you to share your files with other users and also search files are is others share. This is the software protocol used to share peer-to-peer should be the opening gate for Frost Wire on the firewall machine and the firewall of the Modem is quite important, it will help you increase the number of people connected to machines, as much source download then the download speed will be as fast.
FrostWire - Share, download files peer to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sante DICOM Editor 10.3.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Dec 2025 15:21:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sante-dicom-editor-11760.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sante-dicom-editor-11760.html
</guid><description>
Sante DICOM Editor is a professional DICOM editor, viewer, anonymizer, converter, dicomizer, PACS client, mini PACS server, patient CD/DVD burner (with viewer) and more that too.
Sante DICOM Editor is the industry's leading post-processing application for editing, converting and processing DICOM files, it is used by most major corporations and medical device manufacturers and is DICOM drafting is chosen by the largest universities and colleges. hospitals around the world. Among other...
</description></item><item><title>Download MPV-EASY Player 0.41.0.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Dec 2025 00:19:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mpv-easy-player-3110.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mpv-easy-player-3110.html
</guid><description>
MPV-EASY Player is movies player based on mpv. It comes with easy to use interface, you can quickly adjust many parameters, the default settings are carefully adjusted will be able to stimulate all the performance of the mpv, so use mpv player simple than before a lot.
Basically, MPV-EASY Player is the assembly and combination of MPV, configuring mpv files, the command lua (including all scripts to be shared by other people on github), and the command js with the to read and fully...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinShift Forge 0.5.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Dec 2025 00:18:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winshift-forge-14401.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winshift-forge-14401.html
</guid><description>
What is WinShift Forge?
WinShift Forge is a lightweight utility built to enhance the performance of Windows 11. WinShift Forge allows you to easily remove them, free up space, and speed up your system. WinShift Forge lets you instantly refresh your computer screen by customizing the most important icons. No more fumbling through complex system settings—easily take direct control of the core Windows visuals and make your PC truly your own.
Key Features:
Personalize Your PC
	Replace...
</description></item></channel></rss>