<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 17:34:55 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 17:34:55 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Topaz Photo Pro 1.0.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 17:44:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-photo-ai-8105.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-photo-ai-8105.html
</guid><description>
What is Topaz Photo AI?
Topaz Photo AI is a professional software that automatically adjusts for your image quality needs. Simply import images into Topaz Photo AI and it will use specially trained AI models to first detect unique details, clarity, and resolution issues before applying the intelligently adjusts to maximize your image quality.
For users experienced with Topaz Labs image quality applications, it combines the functionality of DeNoise AI, Sharpen AI and Gigapixel AI into...
</description></item><item><title>Download CyberLink ColorDirector Ultra 2026 v14.0.5921.11</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 17:43:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-colordirector-ultra-283.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-colordirector-ultra-283.html
</guid><description>
CyberLink ColorDirector Ultra is a necessary tool to create impressive, stories, and evoking responses from your video viewers. ColorDirector provides all the video creators of all skill levels the means to dramatically improve their projects through the use of tools to control color and light.
Features of CyberLink ColorDirector Ultra
HDR Video : Apply HDR to your videos to add more dynamic range than in your scenes, bring out the detail and highlight the best parts of your...
</description></item><item><title>Download FastStone Capture 11.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 17:43:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-faststone-capture-2044.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-faststone-capture-2044.html
</guid><description>
FastStone Capture is a screen capture tool and screen video recording, powerful, lightweight, yet full-featured. FastStone Capture that allows you to easily capture and annotate anything on the screen including windows, objects, menus, full screen, rectangular area / freedom / fixed as well as scrolling the window / web page. It also allows you to record all the activity on the screen, including changes on the screen, speech from microphone, mouse movement and click on the video file is...
</description></item><item><title>Download Free YouTube Download 4.4.46.1127 Premium</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 17:42:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-download-1177.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-download-1177.html
</guid><description>
Free YouTube Download Premium is the most popular application to download videos from YouTube. The program was released in 2006 and regularly updated since then. Use the program to download and convert YouTube videos to view offline anytime.
Free YouTube Download - added Support to download youtube
Download more videos! Save whole playlists and YouTube channels, videos from a playlist individually (history, video be favorite, favourites, Watch later), videos from many different...
</description></item><item><title>Download SysNucleus WebHarvy 7.9.0.245</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 17:41:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sysnucleus-webharvy-881.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sysnucleus-webharvy-881.html
</guid><description>
SysNucleus WebHarvy is software to extract data website such as Text, image, URL &amp;amp; email from the website and save the content... WebHarvy is a tool which scans website intuitive. Absolutely no need to write any scripts or code to scrape data. You will use the browser built-in of WebHarvy to navigate the website.
WebHarvy automatically identifies patterns of data occurring in web pages. So if you need a list of items (name, address, email, price etc) from a website, you do not need to...
</description></item><item><title>Download XYplorer 28.00.1100</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 17:41:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-533.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-533.html
</guid><description>
XYplorer - File Manager for Windows is software that supports users to manage files on the Window quickly and to arrange the folder tidy. XYplorer features tabbed browsing, search, files, powerful, preview, flexible, highly customizable interface, dual frame options and a variety of unique ways to automate effective tasks often repeat. It's fast, lightweight, and portable.
Features XYplorer
	XYplorer is a file manager mobile. It does not require any settings, store all configuration...
</description></item><item><title>Download CyberLink PowerDirector Ultimate 2026 v24.0.1128.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 17:40:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-powerdirector-ultimate-425.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-powerdirector-ultimate-425.html
</guid><description>
CyberLink PowerDirector Ultimate is software editor, edit video and make movies on the computer from a variety of templates are made available, complete with effects, transitions, animations, and music. CyberLink PowerDirector 17 is a combination of video editing software with advanced video editing features powerful. Cblowing need to add your clips into the time line and click on 'Production'!
The tool design video in CyberLink PowerDirector have the ability to customize helps you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium 4.4.46.1127</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 17:40:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-to-mp3-converter-premium-844.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-to-mp3-converter-premium-844.html
</guid><description>
Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium version is a software used to convert YouTube to MP3, extract audio from playlists YouTube, show listings, charts, video responses, channels, favorites of the user. With Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium, you can download and convert playlists, channels, stream original tv series and get them into iTunes at the same time.
Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium - convert YouTube to MP3
Features Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium from the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Maplesoft Maple 2025.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 17:39:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-maplesoft-maple-1365.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-maplesoft-maple-1365.html
</guid><description>
Maplesoft Maple is a package of computer engineering top Maple has been performed for all the mathematical functions and includes the basic operations and algorithms handling complex data. Maplesoft Maple be download easy on taiwebs.com. In addition, the package includes more than 400 math functions and chart types. According to the manufacturer, package Maple is the leading company on scalability and performance (thanks to the support of multi-core processors). Package Maple has a unique...
</description></item><item><title>Download MobaXterm Professional 25.4 / Personal / Educational</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 17:39:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mobaxterm-professional-2026.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mobaxterm-professional-2026.html
</guid><description>
MobaXterm Professional is an SSH Client application server administration remotely via SSH for the client quite well and are more convenient. MobaXterm Professional offers a multitude of functions suitable for programmers, webmasters, IT administrators and pretty much the user need to handle the job from far more simple way. MobaXterm provides all the tools network key remote (SSH, X11, RDP, VNC, FTP, MOSH, ...) and Unix commands (bash, ls, cat, sed, grep, awk, rsync, ...) , in a file exe...
</description></item><item><title>Download ManicTime Pro 2025.3.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 17:38:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-manictime-18.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-manictime-18.html
</guid><description>
ManicTime is a software automatically collect information about how to use your computer. It records the time of operation of the machine, see the change data in the machine, how much data you share, received on or moved away, what software you use, use at any time
ManicTime allows you to keep up the work of the staff, send progress reports accurately and manage your time better than ever. This type of software can help your business more efficient when it comes to the internal problems...
</description></item><item><title>Download MusConv 4.10.435 Lifetime</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 17:37:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html
</guid><description>
MusConv transfers playlists, albums, followed artists and liked songs across a variety of services – Spotify, Apple Music, Amazon Music, YouTube, YouTube Music, iTunes, Deezer, Tidal, SoundCloud, Pandora and more 125 music services!
Features of MusConv Ultimate
	Transfer playlists, albums, followed artists and liked tracks between over 125 music servicesManage playlists (Delete, Merge, Split, Copy...)
	More than 125 music services supported
	Access DAILY updated music charts on...
</description></item><item><title>Download ExamDiff Pro Master Edition 16.0.1.15</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 17:37:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-examdiff-pro-master-312.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-examdiff-pro-master-312.html
</guid><description>
ExamDiff Pro Master is a tool to compare files and folders intuitive and easy to use, intuitive and easy to use for Windows. ExamDiff Pro Master has unique features distinguishes ExamDiff Pro with the program compare other. ExamDiff Pro Master to help perform reviews of code and share other reports with your colleagues and compare local website with FTP server by plug-ins more integrated.
ExamDiff Pro Master can create a snapshot folder for comparison and storage in the future, compare...
</description></item><item><title>Download Realtek Ethernet Controller All-In-One Drivers 11.27.1128.2025</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 17:36:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-realtek-ethernet-controller-all-in-one-drivers-6485.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-realtek-ethernet-controller-all-in-one-drivers-6485.html
</guid><description>
Realtek Ethernet All-In-One Controller Driver is the software driver for the Realtek Ethernet cards. It is a program used to communicate from the Windows PC OS to the device. This software is required in most cases for the hardware device to function properly. In most cases, drivers come with Windows or can be found by going to Windows Update in Control Panel and checking for updates as well as downloaded from the Realtek support website.
</description></item><item><title>Download Ahnenblatt 4.38.0.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 17:36:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ahnenblatt-3844.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ahnenblatt-3844.html
</guid><description>
Ahnenblatt is a genealogy software full-featured, easy to use suitable for beginners and even pedigree has the experience to organize genealogy research by you. Use plausibility checks to find out the inaccuracies in your family and create the chart impressive with just a few mouse clicks.
Ahnenblatt - Create family tree,
Recently, there has been strong increase of the general interest of the public for genealogical tree. Users who desire to track their heritage have many tools at...
</description></item><item><title>Download SoftwareNetz Budget Book 7.26</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 17:36:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-softwarenetz-budget-book-3857.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-softwarenetz-budget-book-3857.html
</guid><description>
SoftwareNetz Budget Book support you can view stats and reports about how you have spend your money. All your family can use Window budget without problems. You can specify a maximum of 30 people. You can determine the cost for people is done. With the help of a budget plan, you can control your costs. At any time you can also see the amount of money you have left from your monthly budget yourself.
SoftwareNetz Budget Book - notepads spend
The features of SoftwareNetz Budget...
</description></item><item><title>Download Axialis IconWorkshop Professional 6.9.7.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 17:30:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-axialis-iconworkshop-professional-9739.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-axialis-iconworkshop-professional-9739.html
</guid><description>
Axialis IconWorkshop Professional is a professional icon creation tool that runs under Windows and allows you to easily create high-quality icons for all available platforms and devices. It is a powerful tool for professional icon designers and developers. It offers a user-friendly interface and a wide range of features to efficiently create, edit and manage icons.
Features of Axialis IconWorkshop Professional
	Windows Icons: ICO file format for all versions up to 768x768 for Windows...
</description></item><item><title>Download SoftwareNetz Cash Book 10.11</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 17:29:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-softwarenetz-cash-book-6045.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-softwarenetz-cash-book-6045.html
</guid><description>
SoftwareNetz Cash Book is a simple accounting program that allows you to score your cash and bank breaks easily, quickly and without any knowledge of the accounting. Due to the user-friendly design, all 'non-computer experts' can use the NPC immediately.
Just add the invoice that has paid, receipts, etc. Many years later, you can still show the receipts and print it if necessary. Besides, you can print a monthly log that includes the documents or save it into a single PDF...
</description></item><item><title>Download PortableApps.com Platform 30.1.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 17:29:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-portableappscom-platform-1935.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-portableappscom-platform-1935.html
</guid><description>
PortableApps.com Platform is the open source application can be installed directly onto your USB thumb drive. It offers a wide range of mobile apps, including the mobile version of Firefox, Skype and many other applications. None of them comes, but you can download them directly from the application directory integrated.
PortableApps.com Platform - The launch the app
Other features include
	Integrated backup
	Theme modern interface
	Search options
	Support personal files, favorites...
</description></item><item><title>Download Anthemion Jutoh 3.28</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 17:28:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anthemion-jutoh-801.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anthemion-jutoh-801.html
</guid><description>
Anthemion Jutoh is a software to create electronic books in popular formats and design your own cover with editor, cover integrated. Create your project in seconds from existing files using The guide to new projects; or create your book from scratch using the text editor as integrated.
Anthemion Jutoh - Create ebooks
The features of Anthemion Jutoh
	Quick to generate Epub, Mobipocket or other format of your.
	Fast to edit content and switch between variations of your ebooks.
	Jutoh...
</description></item><item><title>Download CrawlRhino SEO Monitor 1.0.5</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 17:26:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-crawlrhino-seo-monitor-14292.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-crawlrhino-seo-monitor-14292.html
</guid><description>
CrawlRhino SEO Monitor is a professional desktop monitoring solution designed for digital agencies, SEO consultants, and businesses that depend on stable website performance.
It continuously tracks your site's uptime, downtime, and important SEO tag changes — including titles, meta descriptions, H1 headings, robots directives, and canonicals — so you can immediately identify any issues that could impact rankings or user experience.
Core Features of CrawlRhino SEO...
</description></item><item><title>Download AccdbMerge 1.36.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 17:26:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-accdbmerge-12716.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-accdbmerge-12716.html
</guid><description>
AccdbMerge is a reliable program that allows you to quickly combine information and structure from multiple Microsoft Access database files, in two projects. The application can perform advanced data segregation, to avoid duplicate entries. Furthermore, the program provides support for differential comparison of batch data.
AccdbMerge Features
	The software can open password-protected files and compare them in two parallel projects. You can save settings, in case you often work with...
</description></item><item><title>Download SoftwareNetz MyMoney 3.57</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 17:21:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-softwarenetz-mymoney-6057.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-softwarenetz-mymoney-6057.html
</guid><description>
SoftwareNetz MyMoney will support you managing and storing your finances is easy and simple. The program provides you with assessments and statistics regarding your bank transactions with only one click. SoftwareNetz MyMoney supports Paypal account. Transactions from your Paypal account can be taken directly from the Paypal server. With HBCI-Banking, you can retrieve your transactions in most German banks, directly through the internet. For all other financial accounts, you can enter a...
</description></item><item><title>Download Flyby11 2.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 16:46:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-flyby11-12467.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-flyby11-12467.html
</guid><description>
Flyby11 is a simple patcher that removes annoying restrictions that prevent you from installing Windows 11 (24H2) on unsupported hardware. Do you have an old PC? No TPM, Secure Boot or your processor is not supported? Flyby11 allows you to install Windows 11 24H2. There are no complicated steps. Just run the tool and you'll be running Windows 11 on your outdated machine in no time.
Technical overview
Flyby11 takes advantage of a feature of the Windows 11 setup process that uses the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Flyoobe 2.2.812</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 16:46:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oobelux-13956.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oobelux-13956.html
</guid><description>
Flyoobe was born out of the frustration many users felt with the Windows 11 setup experience. Whether it was the mandatory online account, the endless "Next, next, next..." screens, or the incomplete configuration options when you finally reached the desktop, the current setup lacked focus on what users really wanted.
Why choose Flyoobe?
	Simplifies the Windows 11 setup process right out of the box.
	Allows easy local account creation without need to hunt for hidden options.
	Includes...
</description></item></channel></rss>