<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 17:37:12 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 17:37:12 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download PDF editor &amp;amp; PDF converter pro 9.8.0 build 114</title><pubDate> Tue, 26 Aug 2025 20:09:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pdf-editor-pdf-converter-pro-9852.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pdf-editor-pdf-converter-pro-9852.html
</guid><description>
PDF Converter &amp;amp; PDF Editor is a very comprehensive tool to perform various operations on pdf files
	Convert Word files to PDF: Now you can convert doc files to pdf files.
	Convert images to PDF files: Convert your jpg to PDF. Click image from camera or select an image from gallery and convert it.
	Website to PDF: Convert html website to PDF and save all articles/news reports to read later.
	Merge pdf: Combine pdf documents into a single document.
	Split documents: Is the file too...
</description></item><item><title>Download 1.1.1.1 + WARP: Safer Internet 6.38.5</title><pubDate> Tue, 26 Aug 2025 20:09:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-1111-warp-safer-internet-11078.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-1111-warp-safer-internet-11078.html
</guid><description>
1.1.1.1 w/ WARP makes your Internet more private and secure. No one can track what you do on the Internet. We created 1.1.1.1 so you can connect securely to the Internet anytime, anywhere.
Features of 1.1.1.1 + WARP
A better way to connect
	1.1.1.1 with WARP replaces the connection between your phone and the Internet with a modern, optimized protocol.
Higher privacy
	1.1.1.1 with WARP prevents anyone from spying on you by further encrypting traffic leaving your phone. We believe...
</description></item><item><title>Download Talking Translator - Languages 3.4.4</title><pubDate> Tue, 26 Aug 2025 20:08:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-talking-translator-9776.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-talking-translator-9776.html
</guid><description>
With the instant translation feature, the Talking Translator application will help you communicate in any multilingual environment such as when traveling, going on business trips, meeting buyers or just simple conversations. You can translate into more than 100 languages ​​with just this one app: Talking Translator! You don't know how to read sentences? Nothing! Talking Translator provides handwritten text translation.
Supports more than 100 languages ​​including English,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Elevate - Brain Training Games 5.203.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 26 Aug 2025 20:07:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-elevate-brain-training-games-8564.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-elevate-brain-training-games-8564.html
</guid><description>
Elevate is a brain training program designed to improve speech, processing speed, memory skills, mental math, and more. Each person is provided with their own personalized learning program, which is adjusted over time to maximize results.
The more you practice with Elevate, the more you'll improve key cognitive skills proven to increase productivity, earning potential, and confidence. More than 90% said their vocabulary, memory, math skills and overall acuity improved when they...
</description></item><item><title>Download Aloha Private Browser - VPN 7.6.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 26 Aug 2025 20:07:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-aloha-private-browser-vpn-13058.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-aloha-private-browser-vpn-13058.html
</guid><description>
Aloha Private Browser - VPN is a fast, safe web browser and focuses on privacy available on Android, iOS and PC platforms. It integrates a free, unlimited VPN service, user data encryption with 256-bit military encryption, allowing users to browse private and safe web from anywhere while ignoring geographical restrictions. The browser does not record user activities, enhance privacy and security.
The main features of Aloha Browser include:
	Free and unlimited VPN: Providing fast VPN...
</description></item><item><title>Download AppChecker - App &amp;amp; System info 4.1.1 build 4001003</title><pubDate> Tue, 26 Aug 2025 20:07:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-appchecker-app-system-info-12091.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-appchecker-app-system-info-12091.html
</guid><description>
AppChecker - App &amp;amp; System Information is a mobile application that provides detailed information about the applications installed on your device as well as system information. It provides detailed information about the version numbers, permissions, package names and signatures of installed applications, allowing you to have a comprehensive overview of your application collection.
Some key features of AppChecker include:
	App Information: AppChecker displays detailed information...
</description></item><item><title>Download Total Launcher 3.3.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 26 Aug 2025 20:06:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-total-launcher-8673.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-total-launcher-8673.html
</guid><description>
Total Launcher is a custom launcher for Android devices. The launcher is the interface that controls the home screen, app drawer, and overall look and feel of your Android device. Total Launcher offers a high level of customization and allows users to personalize their device to suit their personal needs and preferences.
Total Launcher Features
	Customizable home screen: Users can arrange icons, widgets, and shortcuts on the home screen to their liking.
	Themes and icon packs: Total...
</description></item><item><title>Download Radio Alarm Clock+ 25.08.4</title><pubDate> Tue, 26 Aug 2025 20:06:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-radio-alarm-clock-10755.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-radio-alarm-clock-10755.html
</guid><description>
This is an online radio alarm / clock radio app. It evolved from 'Radio Alarm Clock (100% free and no ads!)'. This is a heavily revamped version with a more modern design, many improvements and new features. This app is still under development and improvement. There may be bugs and errors that may prevent the clock radio from waking you up as intended! Please consider using a 'normal' alarm clock in addition to this app.
Features of Radio Alarm Clock+
	Brand new, more modern design
	A...
</description></item><item><title>Download Avast Cleanup – Phone Cleaner 25.17.0 build 800011239</title><pubDate> Tue, 26 Aug 2025 20:06:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-avast-cleanup-phone-cleaner-8885.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-avast-cleanup-phone-cleaner-8885.html
</guid><description>
Avast Cleanup - Phone Cleaner is a mobile app for Android devices designed to help users optimize their phone's performance and free up storage space. This application provides many tools and features to clean and speed up your phone.
One of the main features of Avast Cleanup is the Junk Cleaner, which scans your phone for unnecessary files such as temporary files, app cache, and other junk data. The app will then provide a list of files that can be safely deleted to free up space on...
</description></item><item><title>Download PeakFinder 4.8.54</title><pubDate> Tue, 26 Aug 2025 20:06:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-peakfinder-10050.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-peakfinder-10050.html
</guid><description>
Explore more mountains than any other climber! PeakFinder AR makes it possible… and shows the names of all the mountains and peaks with a 360° panoramic display. This functionality is completely offline - and worldwide! PeakFinder knows more than 650,000 mountain peaks - from Mount Everest to that little hill on the corner.
PeakFinder Features
	Works offline and worldwide
	Includes more than 650,000 peak names
	Install the camera image using a panoramic drawing *
	Display real-time...
</description></item><item><title>Download Scientific calculator plus 991 7.4.1.484</title><pubDate> Tue, 26 Aug 2025 20:05:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-scientific-calculator-plus-991-8869.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-scientific-calculator-plus-991-8869.html
</guid><description>
Scientific Calculator 300 Plus, 991 is the Calculator for Students and Engineering Student. Calculator 991 Plus Proved Powerfuls in a Real Calculator 991 300. It makes Advanced Calculator 991 Become the most useful calculator for University and School.
Basic Calculator 300 Plus and 115 Plus: Supports from Basic Mathematics to Advanced Math Functions: Percentage, Powers, Roots, TruneMetric, Logarithms Calculator. Fraction Calculation 991 Supports Convert Fraction to Decimal, Mixed...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ask AI - Chat with AI Chatbot 3.2.18</title><pubDate> Tue, 26 Aug 2025 20:05:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ask-ai-chat-with-ai-chatbot-13188.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ask-ai-chat-with-ai-chatbot-13188.html
</guid><description>
Experience conversations with AI that understands you, adapts to your mood, and personalizes interactions, making each interaction unique.
ASK ANYTHING, ANYTIME:
Ignite your curiosity and engage in engaging conversations with historical figures, business experts, or even your favorite celebrities. Powered by the latest ChatGPT and GPT-4o technology, Ask AI is ready to provide recommendations, inspiration, and information on any topic.
CREATE AND DISCOVER IMAGES:
Be your own artist:...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wifi Password: Wifi Hotspot 1.2.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 26 Aug 2025 20:03:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wifi-hotspot-speed-test-11513.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wifi-hotspot-speed-test-11513.html
</guid><description>
Wifi Hotspot - Wifi Hotspot helps you share internet with other mobile devices and create your own free hotspot. This is a simple and free Wifi Hotspot app for Android that you can use to share Internet with other devices. Instantly turn your phone into a wi fi hotspot with this Wifi Hotspot - Wifi Hotspot application without root. Simple to use and easy to install, this hotspot proxy app will turn your phone into a powerful wifi for mobile monitor transmitter!
Amazing Wifi Hotspot -...
</description></item><item><title>Download QR &amp;amp; Barcode Reader (Pro) 3.2.4-P</title><pubDate> Tue, 26 Aug 2025 20:03:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-qr-barcode-reader-pro-11205.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-qr-barcode-reader-pro-11205.html
</guid><description>
QR &amp;amp; Barcode Reader is a modern QR code scanner and barcode scanner with all the features you need. Scan any QR code or barcode to get more information including results from popular online services: Amazon, eBay and Google!
Main features:
	Scan all popular barcode formats: QR, Data Matrix, Aztec, UPC, EAN, Code 39 and many more.
	Open URLs, connect to WiFi hotspots, add calendar events, read VCards, find product and price information, and more
	Protect yourself from malicious...
</description></item><item><title>Download Lux Light Meter Photometer PRO 5.10.4.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 26 Aug 2025 20:02:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-lux-light-meter-photometer-pro-13663.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-lux-light-meter-photometer-pro-13663.html
</guid><description>
Free app to measure the amount of light (in lux), to the ambient light sensor. Ambient light sensors measure light in lux, a measurement of illuminance that depends on the amount of incident light and the area over which it is spread.
Functions:
	No ads
	Free
	Highly accurate light measurement
	Export all measurements (lx, fx, W/m2) to CSV files and work with data like a pro!
	Lux and Foot Candle Units
	Measure and record minimum, average and maximum possible illuminance
	Full sensor...
</description></item><item><title>Download Temp Mail - Temporary Email 4.04</title><pubDate> Tue, 26 Aug 2025 20:02:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-temp-mail-temporary-email-11697.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-temp-mail-temporary-email-11697.html
</guid><description>
Temp Mail is a service that provides email addresses for users who need a temporary email account. Temporary email addresses can be used to register for online services, verification emails, or in online forums without revealing your personal or permanent email address. With the Temp-Mail app, you can instantly create a disposable temporary email address and receive emails instantly, including photos or any other attachments. Forget revealing your real email to everyone. That will bring...
</description></item><item><title>Download BeautyPlus - AI Photo Video Edit 7.16.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 26 Aug 2025 20:01:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-beautyplus-ai-photo-video-edit-13168.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-beautyplus-ai-photo-video-edit-13168.html
</guid><description>
With the BeautyPlus AI photo and video editor, you can instantly take sweet selfies and edit beautiful photos: remove pimples and blemishes, smooth skin, experiment with hair color changer, whiten teeth, slim face and body, try trendy makeup looks. Transform your photos with Anime filters, add stickers, blur photos, and even erase and change backgrounds for an artistic touch.
Create amazing photo art with AI tools
	Clean up photos by easily removing unwanted people or objects with AI...
</description></item><item><title>Download Bubble Screen Translate 4.3.8</title><pubDate> Tue, 26 Aug 2025 20:01:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-bubble-screen-translate-11757.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-bubble-screen-translate-11757.html
</guid><description>
Bubble Screen Translate recognizes any text on your screen and translates it instantly into your language. Browser, SNS, games, photos, documents, etc. everything can be translated. It is flexible and easy to use. And translate your screen very fast, just wait 3 seconds and all the text on your screen will be translated. Free and secure translation. We provide the latest machine learning models with the most improved accuracy.
Main features:
	Full screen translation
	Partial...
</description></item><item><title>Download Physics Formulas 5.1.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 26 Aug 2025 20:00:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-physics-formulas-11509.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-physics-formulas-11509.html
</guid><description>
From the success of the Math Formula application, Physics Formula was developed and launched to help users quickly refer to any Physics formula for their study and work. This application displays the most popular as well as advanced formulas in seven categories: Mechanics, Electricity, Thermal Physics, Periodic Motion, Optics, Atomic Physics, Constants.
This application has full functions to help users use the application conveniently
	- Tool: users can enter data and the application...
</description></item><item><title>Download AI Photo Editor - Polish 1.67.225</title><pubDate> Tue, 26 Aug 2025 20:00:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-photo-editor-polish-8895.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-photo-editor-polish-8895.html
</guid><description>
Photo Editor Pro offers everything you want for photo editing on this artistic photography trip. 500+ stylish effects, face tones, collages, photo blurs, filters, grids, background changes and beauty plus tools to help you create cool photo collages or create memes ! With Photo Editor Pro, you can directly post your artwork to Instagram, WhatsApp, Facebook, etc. Be creative and edit photos like a pro!
Features of Photo Editor Poland
	Delete: Remove anything you don't want, like...
</description></item><item><title>Download AOA: Always on Display 7.2.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 26 Aug 2025 20:00:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-aoa-always-on-display-8461.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-aoa-always-on-display-8461.html
</guid><description>
AOA: Always On Display (AOD) is a feature found on some Android devices that keeps the screen on and displays important information, such as time, date, and notifications, even when the device is locked. This feature is intended to make it easier for users to view important information without having to unlock their device. This feature can be enabled and disabled in the device's settings, and the information displayed on the AOD can also be customized.
AOA features: Always on...
</description></item><item><title>Download Showly: Track TV Shows &amp;amp; Movie 3.52.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 26 Aug 2025 19:59:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-showly-track-tv-shows-movie-13172.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-showly-track-tv-shows-movie-13172.html
</guid><description>
Showly is a modern, open-source TV Show &amp;amp; Movie tracking app that works with the Trakt.tv service. Browse and search for the most popular, trending and anticipated TV Shows and Movies. See detailed information about each show, episode and read reviews from Trakt users. Tailor your feed to your personal preferences.
Features of Showly
	Track the progress of the shows and movies you're watching. See upcoming premieres and never miss an upcoming episode
	Manage the shows and movies...
</description></item><item><title>Download SpeedChecker Speed Test 2.8.4</title><pubDate> Tue, 26 Aug 2025 19:59:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-speedchecker-speed-test-8162.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-speedchecker-speed-test-8162.html
</guid><description>
SpeedChecker Speed ​​Test is a mobile application that allows users to test the speed of their internet connection. To use the app, users simply download and install the app on their Android device, open the app, and then follow the on-screen instructions to run a speed test. The application will measure the download and upload speed of the user's internet connection and display the results in a clear and easy-to-read format.
It can also provide additional information such as...
</description></item><item><title>Download VPN - Super Unlimited Proxy 2.15.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 26 Aug 2025 19:59:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-vpn-super-unlimited-proxy-13687.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-vpn-super-unlimited-proxy-13687.html
</guid><description>
VPN Super Unlimited ProxyVPN Free Proxy, super fast VPN to proxy websites, watch videos and movies, protect WiFi security and protect privacy. Turbo charge your video streaming experience.
Why choose VPN Super Unlimited Proxy?
	Large number of servers, high speed bandwidth
	Choose apps to use VPN (requires Android 5.0+)
	No time limit, no data limit, no bandwidth limit
	No registration or login required
	No Logs are kept from any user
	Simple, one tap connect to VPN
	Protect your...
</description></item><item><title>Download Stopwatch Timer 3.2.8</title><pubDate> Tue, 26 Aug 2025 19:58:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-stopwatch-timer-10044.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-stopwatch-timer-10044.html
</guid><description>
Stopwatch and Timer is a simple, easy and accurate application for Android that will help you measure the time of any situation, such as sports, cooking, games, education, etc.
You can access the LAP list with the top drop-down menu or just swipe your finger to the left. In this lap list, you can choose to see the time or the total time. LAP lists can be saved to SD card, shared to social media, or emailed.
Features of Stopwatch Timer
	Stopwatch and Timer (countdown) modes.
	Digital...
</description></item></channel></rss>