<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 15:51:59 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 15:51:59 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Glary Disk Cleaner 6.0.1.40</title><pubDate> Mon, 19 Jan 2026 17:14:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-disk-cleaner-1341.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-disk-cleaner-1341.html
</guid><description>
Glary Disk Cleaner is the software helps to erase the file system temporarily, cleanup your browser cache, or release the folder. Glary Disk Cleaner show scan results in detail, help you pick exactly each file to delete. The list file is much more wide open, with temporary files, user-generated, or the file system, cache, bug report, log files, data in recycle bin, the shortcut expires.
Glary Disk Cleaner - garbage system
Glary Disk Cleaner is designed to be simple as possible in use....
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow QR Code Maker 4.0.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 19 Jan 2026 17:14:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qr-code-maker-9760.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qr-code-maker-9760.html
</guid><description>
QR Code Maker is a simple app to generate QR Code for text, link, email, Whatsapp, SMS, Call and Wifi. With QR Codes, you have complete flexibility, because only a short URL points to the encrypted content. So you can modify the links or stored files without having to generate and reprint the Codes. This will save resources and allow you to respond to any campaign changes as quickly as possible.
Features of QR Code Maker
	Generate QR Code for Text, Link, Email, Whatsapp, SMS, Call and...
</description></item><item><title>Download SecretDNS 3.8.4</title><pubDate> Mon, 19 Jan 2026 16:10:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secretdns-12481.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secretdns-12481.html
</guid><description>
SecretDNS provides a quick means to deploy DNS over HTPS, meaning it allows DNS (short for Domain Name Server) resolution to be performed remotely using the HTTPS protocol to encrypts data between the client and the DNS resolver. Its purpose, obviously, is related to data security and user privacy, to prevent unauthorized interception and manipulation of DNS data.
Default DNS settings in SecretDNS use CloudFlare to ensure security. You can change DNS configuration in the dedicated tab...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube Downloader 3.9.18 (1801)</title><pubDate> Mon, 19 Jan 2026 16:09:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube Downloader  is a dedicated software that helps users  downloading youtube videos  Favorites on PC for offline viewing. With MediaHuman YouTube  Downloader  you can download videos from youtube website to your computer with  fast speed , with special software development technology that automatically receives videos from Websites, in addition to the ability to download videos from software websites, can convert downloaded video formats to various formats for the purpose...
</description></item><item><title>Download FX Math Tools Manifest 26.01.14</title><pubDate> Mon, 19 Jan 2026 16:09:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fx-draw-tools-multidocs-8814.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fx-draw-tools-multidocs-8814.html
</guid><description>
MultiDocs is a new way to create self-modifying Word documents. MultiDocs' amazing new document reproduction features allow you to create reproducible tests and quizzes in minutes. Get new numbers, new diagrams and even brand new solutions! MultiDocs combines the power of Word with two leading products: FX Draw and FX Equation in a new and exciting way.
Features of FX Draw Tools MultiDocs
	Create multiple documents: The software allows users to create multiple math and evaluation...
</description></item><item><title>Download Batch Image Converter 2.2.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 19 Jan 2026 16:00:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-batch-image-converter-7430.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-batch-image-converter-7430.html
</guid><description>
Batch Image Converter is software that helps you batch convert image files. It can work with many image types (*.bmp, *.gif, *.jpg, *.png, *.tiff, *.tif, *.psd, *.pcx, *.pbm, *.pgm , *. ppm, *.tga, *.tpic, etc.).
Features of Batch Image Converter
	Easy, intuitive, one-click configuration.
	Save/load session for easy use again.
	Support command line execution.
	Execute automatically at specific time.
</description></item><item><title>Download ReShade 6.7.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 19 Jan 2026 15:59:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-450-3227.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-450-3227.html
</guid><description>
ReShade is an open Source tool help improve the look of the old games on modern video cards as well as allow additional display technology / new video over on the old game doesn't support the technology that.
ReShade, technically, is a tool processing general for the games and video software. Imagine you see your favorite game yourself with the obscure-around, effects market the true depth or color correction. Function ReShade by showing in an automatic way and general access to...
</description></item><item><title>Download XMedia Recode 3.6.2.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 19 Jan 2026 15:59:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xmedia-recode-919.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xmedia-recode-919.html
</guid><description>
XMedia Recode is software to change the quality for video files on windows operating system, it has the ability to change quality, video format. XMedia Recode supports the format conversion such as 3GP, 3GPP, 3GPP2, AAC, AC3, AIFF, AMR, ASF, AU, AVI, DIVX, DTS, DVR-MS, FLV, H. 261, H. 263, H. 264, M4A, M1V, M2V, M4V, MKV.
Parameters advanced
The user can step into the more advanced and modify bitrate, frame interval the frame rate, modes, speed control and many other settings regarding...
</description></item><item><title>Download VovSoft Collect URL 4.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 19 Jan 2026 15:58:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-collect-url-7395.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-collect-url-7395.html
</guid><description>
VovSoft Collect URL is an internet scanner like a search engine bot. Starting from the URL the user entered, it lists all the links on the URL. Then it recursively scans all the links in the list. Users can limit URL Crawl to only one domain name. The file extension ignore list can be edited. Connection and response timeout values ​​are editable. Additionally, the user can change the user agent value for HTTP and HTTPS connections.
Features of VovSoft Collect URL
	Scan the...
</description></item><item><title>Download FX Science Tools Manifest 26.01.14</title><pubDate> Mon, 19 Jan 2026 15:50:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fx-science-tools-3744.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fx-science-tools-3744.html
</guid><description>
FX Science Tools provided to teachers of chemistry and physics the effective means to create equations and chemical structures. Just type and create. FX Chem FX Chem makes writing chemical equations become simple. You just type and FX Chem know enough about chemistry to put all the components of the equation at the right point. FX Chem can even create the chemical equations for nuclear - a very difficult thing in the Word. FX ChemSturation FX ChemSturation made the organic structure, what...
</description></item><item><title>Download Directory Opus Pro 13.20.5 Beta</title><pubDate> Mon, 19 Jan 2026 15:50:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-opus-pro-779.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-opus-pro-779.html
</guid><description>
Directory Opus Pro is a software replacement for Explorer with traditional strength and function more than any manager other files. Directory Opus Pro full support for high DPI screen (for example 4K and 5K) with the rename dialog is redesigned, with new features. Besides being a recording macro only allows you to perform mass renaming complex that don't need regular expressions. In addition, Directory Opus Pro also enhances the ability to script.Better handling of renaming recursive and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Gammadyne DJ Jukebox 35.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 19 Jan 2026 15:43:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gammadyne-dj-jukebox-9556.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gammadyne-dj-jukebox-9556.html
</guid><description>
Gammadyne DJ Jukebox is a software application developed by Gammadyne Corporation. It is designed to provide a comprehensive solution for managing and playing music playlists, especially in a DJ or jukebox-like environment. DJ Jukebox allows you to create and organize playlists from your music library. It supports various audio file formats, including MP3, WAV and OGG. The software includes features such as automatic playlist generation, smart randomization, interlacing between songs,...
</description></item><item><title>Download HTML Compiler 2026.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 19 Jan 2026 15:36:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-html-compiler-2548.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-html-compiler-2548.html
</guid><description>
HTML Compiler is a program for Microsoft Windows (tm) allows you to put an entire HTML application (including HTML, CSS, JavaScript, images, etc.) into a Windows application independent can be executed like any other application window the application. HTML Compiler allows you to customize file real exam results by changing the icon of them and set some other options. For example, you can allow or not allow the ability to print the HTML pages, allow or disallow the text selection and many,...
</description></item><item><title>Download SmartGit 25.1.109</title><pubDate> Mon, 19 Jan 2026 15:35:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-smartgit-13978.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-smartgit-13978.html
</guid><description>
SmartGit is a cross-platform, graphical Git application designed for professional users to simplify and enhance Git version control workflows. SmartGit supports major Git hosting services like GitHub, Bitbucket, GitLab, and Azure DevOps with built-in features to handle pull requests, comments, and code reviews directly in the app.
Why choose SmartGit as your Git Client?
	One for all.
	SmartGit helps new Git users as well as helps experienced developers work more efficiently.
	SmartGit...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinScript 1.4.5</title><pubDate> Mon, 19 Jan 2026 15:35:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winscript-12800.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winscript-12800.html
</guid><description>
WinScript is an open source tool built to help you build custom scripts for Windows 10 and 11. It includes scripts for debugging, privacy, performance, and more, along with the ability to install all your favorite apps with just one click.
Features
	Debloat: Remove Windows bloatware, CoPilot, Edge, OneDrive, and other pre-installed features preset.
	Privacy: Disable Windows and 3rd party data collection, tracking, app access, and telemetry.
	Performance: Set background services to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Network Monitor &amp;amp; Antivirus 1.0.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 19 Jan 2026 13:06:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-network-monitor-antivirus-14511.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-network-monitor-antivirus-14511.html
</guid><description>
Take complete control of your computer security. Monitor network activity on a live global map, scan files with over 70 antivirus tools, and block threats instantly—all for a single payment. Network Monitor &amp;amp; Antivirus combines real-time connection monitoring with advanced file scanning to give you complete control over what goes in and out of your computer. See exactly which applications are online and where your data is going.
Key Features
	Proactive Network Monitoring: See...
</description></item><item><title>Download ResizeScaleAI 1.0.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 19 Jan 2026 12:55:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-resizescaleai-14510.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-resizescaleai-14510.html
</guid><description>
ResizeScaleAI enhances the sharpness and clarity of your old, blurry, or low-resolution photos. Using advanced Artificial Intelligence, the app precisely upgrades your images—preserving texture, fine detail, and natural image quality.
With intelligent face restoration, the app realistically reconstructs faces, restoring lost features while maintaining recognition and proportions. Unlike cloud-based tools, ResizeScaleAI runs entirely on your computer—no internet and no uploads...
</description></item><item><title>Download CrossNova 1.0.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 19 Jan 2026 12:47:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-crossnova-14509.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-crossnova-14509.html
</guid><description>
CrossNova is a modern crosshair utility for Windows 10/11 that displays a crosshair overlay that is always visible on top and customizable. Use the available settings, browse your library, or create your own crosshair with the built-in Create tool.
Key Features:
	Always-on overlay: Transparent crosshair always shows on all windows. Show/hide at any time, center, or reposition as needed. Perfect for aiming practice, unaimed practice, or streaming.
	Available settings: Classic dot,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Addinsoft Zenplot 1.1.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 19 Jan 2026 12:41:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-addinsoft-zenplot-14508.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-addinsoft-zenplot-14508.html
</guid><description>
Addinsoft Zenplot (ZENPLOT) is data visualization software developed by Addinsoft, focusing on creating advanced, highly customizable charts and graphs. It is designed to allow users to build visualizations by stacking multiple graphic “layers” within a single image.
What Zenplot does
	Creates various chart types such as scatter plots, line plots, bar plots, frequency plots, area plots, and 2D heatmaps/planes.
	Allows you to stack multiple graphic layers within a visualization...
</description></item><item><title>Download Free Music and Video Downloader 3.12</title><pubDate> Sun, 18 Jan 2026 23:25:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-music-and-video-downloader-123.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-music-and-video-downloader-123.html
</guid><description>
Free Music &amp;amp; Video Downloader (formerly the Free Music Downloader) allows you to download his favorite music at the form of MP3 files from many different online sources, including Last.FM, Grooveshark, Sogou, VKontakte, SoundCloud, and many other things.Just enter name of artist or song you are looking for and click the Search button to see a list of results and download the songs you want.You can customize the services that applications will use to search, put the download folder...
</description></item><item><title>Download Explzh 10.01</title><pubDate> Sun, 18 Jan 2026 23:24:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-explzh-2278.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-explzh-2278.html
</guid><description>
Explzh is software that originated from Japan. This program works with most formats, can extract the file directly to FTP server, split large files into multiple smaller size. I would like to note that the storage supports encryption of files compressed using AES algorithm, has a system of tabs in the main window, you can search for the information you need in the repository and work with files, batch mode is done.
Explzh - Compress and decompress file
The file is support work with the...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinTools.net Professional / Premium / Classic 26.1.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 18 Jan 2026 23:20:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wintoolsnet-304.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wintoolsnet-304.html
</guid><description>
WinTools.net is an optimal tool working performance of the operating system and delete the unnecessary program from the hard drive and control the start-up process of Windows.
WinTools.net integrates many useful tools, to support increased processing speed and ability, stable operation for the computer include: Clean Uninstaller, Scan Files, Scan Registry, Start Up, Tweak UI, Net Tweaker, The Privacy. Scan Files are often used to scan the hard drive periodically, search for junk files or...
</description></item><item><title>Download RAM Saver Professional 26.1.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 18 Jan 2026 23:19:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ram-saver-pro-565.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ram-saver-pro-565.html
</guid><description>
RAM Saver Pro is a professional software optimize RAM is for system stable operation with high performance. RAM Saver Pro aims to provide all the tools necessary to increase the amount of free memory, at any time, also monitor and check the RAM.
When using RAM Saver Pro, you will be allowed to access its main menu by right-clicking on the tray icon. Also, if you want to display the main panel of the program you just double-click the icon. In addition, from the main interface of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Premium 22.2.1142</title><pubDate> Sun, 18 Jan 2026 23:19:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-diskimage-server-4547.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-diskimage-server-4547.html
</guid><description>
O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Server is software that is specially designed for use in enterprise environments, the software allows users to backup all the files you want and keep them safe from any incident or disaster computer. O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Server comes with a variety of easy to use utility that allows users to backup entire partitions of the specific files from their PC, as well as recover the version previous data of them, all from a simple interface.
O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Server - data...
</description></item><item><title>Download ExtraMAME 26.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 18 Jan 2026 23:18:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-extramame-2608.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-extramame-2608.html
</guid><description>
ExtraMAME is a simple tool that allows simulation of the arcade game from the most popular platform but is long forgotten, thanks to which the game industry has reached the current level. After launch, you will get 11 games pre-installed, among which are: Super Mario Bros, Pac-Man Plus, Space Invaders II and other games.
The simulation of multiple machine arcade is authored by Nicola Salmoria and team MAME. MAME lets you play thousands of arcade game old school on your computer. ExtraMAME...
</description></item></channel></rss>