<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 20:02:27 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 20:02:27 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Vivaldi Browser 7.7.3851.56</title><pubDate> Fri, 28 Nov 2025 20:45:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vivaldi-159.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vivaldi-159.html
</guid><description>
Vivaldi is a browser designed for users who have power and offer the option to customize high. You can choose the location of the tabs and the address bar, put the hotkeys for the common tasks and many other features. Also, Vivaldi also provides a number of improvements such as Tab Stacks to group multiple open tabs into a tab, leads to interface less cluttered. Can notes and added a screenshot of a web page while browsing, storing an attachment, and add the URL to easily sort and locate...
</description></item><item><title>Download Vivaldi for macOS 7.7.3851.56</title><pubDate> Fri, 28 Nov 2025 20:45:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/mac/download-vivaldi-for-macos-3443.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/mac/download-vivaldi-for-macos-3443.html
</guid><description>
The Vivaldi for MacOS browser does not track users and offers more features than any other modern browser. Managed by Jon von Tetzchner (co-founder of Opera browser), Vivaldi for MacOS is driven by the real needs of today's users and ensures that they have the best tools to browse and get work done.
Vivaldi for MacOS - Modern web browser
Users can adjust Vivaldi to suit their browsing needs them without limiting customization options. Vivaldi takes the browser to the next level with a...
</description></item><item><title>Download NxFilter 4.7.4.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 28 Nov 2025 20:44:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nxfilter-50.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nxfilter-50.html
</guid><description>
NxFilter is a server filter DNS have the ability to filter Internet traffic based on domain names and content types. In addition, it can use check package DNS to protect your network from malware and botnet activity.
NxFilter is installed on a single computer, where it acts as a proxy server, DNS. To route Internet traffic through NxFilter, you will need to change the DNS settings on all the machines that you want to protect to use the IP address of the individual NxFilter (instead of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download CareUEyes Pro 2.4.11</title><pubDate> Fri, 28 Nov 2025 16:35:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-careueyes-783.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-careueyes-783.html
</guid><description>
CareUEyes is software that protects the eye by adjusting the light as normal, intelligent auto. CareUEyes can automatically filter blue light and make your screen come up naturally, comfortable to your eyes not feel tired.
CareUEyes providing notice of rest to help you not work too long at a time It is very important to rest often and not just your eyes benefit from them. This app can make sure you don't forget to rest at all times, by displaying the notification on the screen in a...
</description></item><item><title>Download AVS Video Converter 14.1.4.3</title><pubDate> Fri, 28 Nov 2025 16:35:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs-video-converter-427.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs-video-converter-427.html
</guid><description>
AVS Video Converter is a software to convert video format, burn VCD, SVCD, DVD, editor video raise.  AVS Video Converter can convert the formats AVI, MPEG, WMV, DVD to the formats AVI, MPEG, WMV, RM, burn DVD, SVCD or VCD, package conversion, editing, effects and filters, video overlay, extract audio from video and save in a file, separate audio, extract a frame (frame) and save as images, split into segments and connect video, rotate video, more in the form of text, banners, logos,...
</description></item><item><title>Download GiliSoft Audio Recorder Pro 13.9</title><pubDate> Fri, 28 Nov 2025 16:34:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-audio-recorder-pro-855.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-audio-recorder-pro-855.html
</guid><description>
GiliSoft Audio Recorder Pro is software perfect recorder to record audio and microphone of your computer to AAC, AC3, AIFF, AMR, AU, FLAC, M4A, M4B, M4R, MKA, MP2, MP3, OGG, RA, VOC , WAV Files or WMA files on Windows 7/8. Recording the sound that goes through your sound card is not at all a difficult task, but GiliSoft Audio Recorder Pro promises to make everything a lot easier, even for those who do not have computer knowledge advanced.
GiliSoft Audio Recorder Pro - audio recording...
</description></item><item><title>Download MultiPack Visual C++ Installer 4.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 28 Nov 2025 16:34:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-multipack-visual-c-installer-7104.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-multipack-visual-c-installer-7104.html
</guid><description>
MultiPack Visual C++ Installer is designed to install all of the Microsoft Visual C++ end-user runtimes simply.The author came up with this pack after seeing all of the confusing packs available and decided to bundle them all into one easy to use installer. If you just want to fix a problem with an app or game not running due to the missing Visual C+, then this pack is the simplest way to fix the problem.
MultiPack Visual C++ Installer does not have installer or uninstallers, and...
</description></item><item><title>Download AVS Audio Editor 11.1.4.3</title><pubDate> Fri, 28 Nov 2025 16:33:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs-audio-editor-1194.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs-audio-editor-1194.html
</guid><description>
AVS Audio Editor is editor audio professional allows you to edit, record and encode music. The program has more than 20 effects and filters built in, including delay, flanger, chorus, reverb, filters to remove irritating sounds such as "vuvuzelas", new sound effects, strange, unique.
AVS Audio Editor - audio editing
Features of AVS Audio Editor
Save to all major formats
	Edit and save audio files into MP3, FLAC, WAV, M4A, WMA, AAC, MP2, AMR, OGG and other files with the help of AVS...
</description></item><item><title>Download 4K Video Downloader Plus 25.4.3</title><pubDate> Fri, 28 Nov 2025 16:32:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-video-downloader-617.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-video-downloader-617.html
</guid><description>
4K Video Downloader Plus is software support downloads video, audio and subtitles from YouTube with high quality up to 4K. Download process video is very simple: just copy the video link from your browser and click Paste Url. Done! If you want that video on your iPad, iPhone or other device, we have protected you.
The feature on 4K Video Downloader Plus
	Download entire playlists and channels from YouTube and save them in MP4, MKV, M4A, MP3, FLV, 3G, create a file .m3u for...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cockos REAPER 7.55</title><pubDate> Fri, 28 Nov 2025 16:31:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cockos-reaper-889.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cockos-reaper-889.html
</guid><description>
Cockos REAPER is a powerful software for for windows, chp lets you record, arrange, edit, and display the audio waveform multi-track. Cockos REAPER offers an extensive feature set includes many effects and a sample project. REAPER supports ASIO, Kernel Streaming, WaveOut, and DirectSound for playback and recording. It reads the files in WAV, OGG and MP3 files and records WAV files. You can arrange any number of items in any number of tracks and use plug-in sound processing (DirectX and...
</description></item><item><title>Download SIW Technicians 2025 v15.11.1119a</title><pubDate> Fri, 28 Nov 2025 16:30:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-siw-technicians-3584.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-siw-technicians-3584.html
</guid><description>
SIW Technicians is an information tool complex system, for Microsoft Windows, check your PC and collect detailed data about the properties and system settings and displays it in a way very easy to understand. SIW Technicians can create a report file (JSON, HTML, TXT, CSV or XML) and you can use that file in batch mode (for Inventory computer inventory of hardware and software, asset inventory, security audit, license Management software, configuration Management server).
SIW Technicians...
</description></item><item><title>Download DesktopOK 12.24</title><pubDate> Fri, 28 Nov 2025 16:30:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopok-1635.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopok-1635.html
</guid><description>
DesktopOK is software save and restore the positions of icons. DesktopOK also offers a solution small but effective for the user to change the screen resolution often. DesktopOK is not installed and can be executed easily from the desktop, and can be carried on a small USB or memory device to another. Start of the program. The first time you use the program, the program will show you screen license. Free program and license info is only displayed the first time (on each PC).
DesktopOK -...
</description></item><item><title>Download OneCommander Pro 3.104.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 28 Nov 2025 16:29:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-one-commander-4232.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-one-commander-4232.html
</guid><description>
One Commander is a file manager for Microsoft Windows with function improved user interface and navigation experience, system file and manipulating the files. Utilities use the tree view to sort the folder, subfolders, and files your, make sure that the current location of you always clear. It supports multiple tabs, allowing you to easily switch between them and access the folder you need.
One Commander - a filemanager for Windows
Depending on the format of the files, some files can...
</description></item><item><title>Download 4K YouTube to MP3 25.4.3</title><pubDate> Fri, 28 Nov 2025 16:29:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-youtube-to-mp3-622.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-youtube-to-mp3-622.html
</guid><description>
4K YouTube to MP3 is a software to convert video youtube to mp3 quickly and easily by the manipulation drag-and-drop simple. With 4K YouTube to MP3 you just drag and drop the link to the favorite songs of you and get the MP3 files to your computer, as easy as that. Transfer songs directly to iPod, iPhone and iPad everywhere you go. No install annoying and complex to solve, just a clean interface, user friendly and functional.
When using 4K YouTube to MP3, users will get the playlists,...
</description></item><item><title>Download DeskSoft EarthView 7.13.16</title><pubDate> Fri, 28 Nov 2025 16:28:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desksoft-earthview-184.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desksoft-earthview-184.html
</guid><description>
With software DeskSoft EarthView you can easily create wallpapers to your computer or select screen saver of your favorite. the program can change day and night, the clouds will also change according to weather conditions current on one or another part of the earth, you can see the lights of the city.
Features of DeskSoft EarthView can be interesting, because of DeskSoft EarthView support for day and night, you can view atmospheric phenomena, light city can see, the cloud is displayed,...
</description></item><item><title>Download AVS4YOU Software AIO Installation Package 6.1.4.3</title><pubDate> Fri, 28 Nov 2025 16:28:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs4you-software-aio-installation-package-1200.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs4you-software-aio-installation-package-1200.html
</guid><description>
AVS4YOU Software AIO Installation Package is the package includes programs to work with video, audio, graphics, documents, and system cleaning. You can install as a complete package, or separate. Which program are presented: AVS Video Editor, AVS Video Converter, AVS Video ReMaker, AVS Media Player, AVS Audio Editor, AVS Audio Converter, AVS Disc Converter, AVS Image Converter, AVS Document Converter, AVS Registry Cleaner.
AVS4YOU Software AIO Installation Package - Full set of tools,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Syncovery Premium 11.11.1.131</title><pubDate> Fri, 28 Nov 2025 16:27:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncovery-pro-enterprise-232.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncovery-pro-enterprise-232.html
</guid><description>
Syncovery Pro Enterprise is a great application used to back up data and to synchronize personal computers, servers, laptops, notepads and storage online. The software comes with support for FTP and secure FTP servers, SSH, WebDAV, Amazon S3, http, update the part file, ZIP compression, data encryption, and schedule automatic backups.
Syncovery Pro Enterprise have the ability to freely select files and folders across the whole folder hierarchy in tree view and supports email...
</description></item><item><title>Download OutlookAttachView 3.55</title><pubDate> Fri, 28 Nov 2025 16:26:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-outlookattachview-1884.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-outlookattachview-1884.html
</guid><description>
OutlookAttachView scans the folder, your Outlook and give you a list of all attached files that it finds. Then you can sort the list by size, sender, subject or any other criterion of any other, and the attachment to the folder you selected or delete it from your inbox. The program can also create a report on the file list can be save as xml / html / text / csv.
OutlookAttachView - View and extract files to Outlook
Standalone software, works with all versions of Outlook, no...
</description></item><item><title>Download AVS Video Editor 11.1.4.3</title><pubDate> Fri, 28 Nov 2025 16:26:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs-video-editor-426.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs-video-editor-426.html
</guid><description>
AVS Video Editor is software professional video editing for windows with full features useful, easy-to-use.  When using AVS Video Editor you can record a video, to impose various effects, create and burn DVD, export movies to various video formats, convert video to iPod, PSP, mobile phones and the other portable device.
Features AVS Video Editor
Format support
	AVS Video Editor supports all major video formats. Edit and save the video file in the codec AVI, VOB, MP4, DVD, WMV, 3GP,...
</description></item><item><title>Download EarthTime 6.30.16</title><pubDate> Fri, 28 Nov 2025 16:26:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-earthtime-185.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-earthtime-185.html
</guid><description>
EarthTime is software that displays the time and date local time of any place in the world. This application has database integration good for 3000 city, users can manually add, download at EarthTime if you want to. EarthTime allows you to install for the time zone and current local time.EarthTime displays the Earth according to the view night and day, you can view the map in full screen mode.
EarthTime
The feature on EarthTime
	EarthTime allows users to interact with visualization...
</description></item><item><title>Download AVS Video ReMaker 8.1.4.3</title><pubDate> Fri, 28 Nov 2025 16:25:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs-video-remaker-1196.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs-video-remaker-1196.html
</guid><description>
AVS Video ReMaker is software that support quick editing of video files without reducing the video quality. Detection algorithm scenes used in AVS Video ReMaker will save time when processing video images and split it into the set. So, no need to preview every frame of the video file to find the transitions manually. With the help of AVS Video ReMaker, you can delete the unwanted parts and TV commercials from video files or file format DVD, recorded by various cameras, various video...
</description></item><item><title>Download AVS Audio Converter 11.1.4.3</title><pubDate> Fri, 28 Nov 2025 16:25:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs-audio-converter-1195.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs-audio-converter-1195.html
</guid><description>
AVS Audio Converter is a program that convert audio files from this format to other formats support many different formats. Support converting WAV, OGG Vorbis, MP3, MP2, Microsoft ADPCM, WMA, VOX, AAC, M4A, AMR and other audio formats. Before transition, the program determines the frequency, number of channels and other parameters of audio files. In addition, the AVS Audio Converter allows you to make settings for the format MP3 and OGG formats when converting audio files and change the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Coder Technologies Coder 2.27.7</title><pubDate> Fri, 28 Nov 2025 16:24:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coder-oss-enterprise-8726.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coder-oss-enterprise-8726.html
</guid><description>
Coder OSS Enterprise is a development platform that provides a complete cloud-based solution for software development, testing and deployment. It is designed to simplify the software development process by providing developers with a collaborative and streamlined environment.
Coder offloads development from local workstations to your on-premises infrastructure and public cloud. Boost developer productivity with powerful server resources and instant integration. Keep the code and data...
</description></item><item><title>Download WACUP (Winamp Community Update Project) 1.99.43.23234 Preview</title><pubDate> Fri, 28 Nov 2025 16:23:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wacup-winamp-community-update-project-3880.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wacup-winamp-community-update-project-3880.html
</guid><description>
WACUP (Winamp Community Update Project). Get new features and bug fixes for release Winamp 5.666 have patch of you from those who are interested keep Winamp in existence and operate through the new plugin and replace. Build preview latest available is # 5118 (28 January 2, 2020) and build current beta is # 5118 (28 January 2, 2020)
WACUP (Winamp Community Update Project) - bug Fixes Winamp
WACUP (can be pronounced as wakeup or WAC-up or however you like it in your native tongue) is...
</description></item><item><title>Download NoScript 13.5 Chrome + Firefox</title><pubDate> Fri, 28 Nov 2025 16:23:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-noscript-116.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-noscript-116.html
</guid><description>
NoScript is an add-ons extension Firefox , Google Chrome allows you to interactively block Java, JavaScript, Flash a one-click button.
You can choose to temporary block or allow scripts on the current web page and also allows the reliable site by you is excluded from any action to block any.
Whenever you visit a website, all content scripts potential invasive are blocked by default and you can select it on the basis of each script from the status bar of browsers like Google Chrome,...
</description></item></channel></rss>