<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 09:45:09 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 09:45:09 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download 3DP Chip 25.7</title><pubDate> Fri, 01 Aug 2025 00:04:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-3dp-chip-2282.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-3dp-chip-2282.html
</guid><description>
3DP Chip is software commonly used in the update of the version latest driver for your computer. The advantage of this software is completely free, compact and easy to use. 3DP Chip will help the hardware always works in the best state, with the 3DP Chip, you can know the driver has been outdated, then let the software automatically searches for the latest version and installed for your system.
3DP Chip - Download and update driver
With the 3DP Chip you can learn everything about the...
</description></item><item><title>Download ProxyCap 5.42</title><pubDate> Fri, 01 Aug 2025 00:03:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-proxycap-1569.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-proxycap-1569.html
</guid><description>
ProxyCap enables you to redirect the network connection of the computer through the proxy server. You can tell ProxyCap to know which applications will connect to the Internet through a proxy and under what circumstances. This is done through the interface user friendly without the need to reconfigure any application clients Internet how your. ProxyCap has native support for the SSH protocol, allowing you to specify a SSH server as the proxy server.
ProxyCap - redirect a network...
</description></item><item><title>Download Inno Setup Unpacker 2.0.4</title><pubDate> Thu, 31 Jul 2025 23:58:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-inno-setup-unpacker-12546.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-inno-setup-unpacker-12546.html
</guid><description>
Inno Setup is a popular and reliable application that creates program installers by helping you create scripts. Extracting the installation files from their container, resulting from compiling code with Inno Setup, can only be done through self-extracting files. In other words, you need to create a self-extracting executable to shell the installation documents.
Inno Setup Unpacker can help you avoid such actions, which is especially useful because some system security protocols block...
</description></item><item><title>Download Psiphon 186.202500731</title><pubDate> Thu, 31 Jul 2025 23:57:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-psiphon-7347.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-psiphon-7347.html
</guid><description>
Psiphon is a firewall bypass tool by Psiphon Inc. Uses VPN, SSH and HTTP Proxy technology to give you uncensored access to Internet content. Your Psiphon app automatically learns about new hotspots to maximize your chances of bypassing censorship.
The way the software works is that Psiphon constantly changes the proxy, so the user's IP address is also constantly changing, the server will not detect the user's real address, so you can feel free. roof. access to websites and software...
</description></item><item><title>Download Opera One 120.0.5543.128</title><pubDate> Thu, 31 Jul 2025 23:53:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-972.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-972.html
</guid><description>
Opera is a fast, safe, configurable and compliant intranet web browser, which includes both the reader and the application. The Opera browser supports web browsing, listening to music, watching high speed movies, you can open many tabs on the Opera without affecting your browsing speed. Opera now supports almost all devices and operating systems such as windows, IOS, Android, linux, MacOS ...
Opera is a beautiful interface and many interesting features, operating on both PCs and mobile,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare Recoverit 13.5.24.4</title><pubDate> Thu, 31 Jul 2025 23:52:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-recoverits-374.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-recoverits-374.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare Recoverit is a data recovery software that is easily lost at a rapid rate and is used by many people. You will do what happens if one day your data is suddenly lost due to the virus or deleted it, .. Wondershare Recoverit will provide you with an environment to protect important data.
Wondershare Recoverit has all the scanning processes that are divided into multiple types, from the typical recovery of the deleted files that are deleted to the recovery of missing files due...
</description></item><item><title>Download CyberLink PhotoDirector Ultra 2025 v16.6.1925.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 31 Jul 2025 23:52:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-photodirector-ultra-129.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-photodirector-ultra-129.html
</guid><description>
Cyberlink PhotoDirector Ultra is known to be photo editing tools and videos with the effect is extremely rich, help you to change the style for the individual images or the videos of his favorite. This software integrated the 3D engine helps to speed up Video processing, which allows accessing the repository effect online and extract the Videos into the movies 3D Bru-ray, 3D AVCHD.
Cyberlink PhotoDirector Ultra to offer users a more professional tool to handle their images, remove...
</description></item><item><title>Download Remote Desktop Manager Enterprise 2025.2.23</title><pubDate> Thu, 31 Jul 2025 23:51:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-remote-desktop-manager-enterprise-242.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-remote-desktop-manager-enterprise-242.html
</guid><description>
Remote Desktop Manager Enterprise software is the complete management of remote connections and virtual machines from a single location, at the same time access support data online and cloud storage. Remote Desktop Manager supports multiple types of connections, not only connections for the protocol connect remote computer Remote Desktop Protocol (RDP).
Remote Desktop Manager easily add, edit, delete, share, organize and find your remote connection of you quickly. Compatible with...
</description></item><item><title>Download Auslogics BoostSpeed 14.0.1.3</title><pubDate> Thu, 31 Jul 2025 23:51:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-auslogics-boostspeed-140.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-auslogics-boostspeed-140.html
</guid><description>
Auslogics BoostSpeed is software support speed up an Internet connection for the computer with Auslogics BoostSpeed restrictions on your Internet speed will be corrective and limited to the lowest level to bring high efficiency in work as well as in their learning. Auslogics BoostSpeed improves the speed surfing the web for the computer through the way in data compression and image to gảm capacity when participating online, with the mechanism and how it works so users also software feel...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe InDesign 2025 v20.5.0.048 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Thu, 31 Jul 2025 23:50:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-001en-adobe-indesign-334.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-001en-adobe-indesign-334.html
</guid><description>
Adobe InDesign is the industry-leading page design and layout software for print and digital media. Create beautiful graphic designs with typography from the world's leading foundries and images from Adobe Stock. Quickly share content and feedback as PDFs. Easily manage production with Adobe Experience Manager. InDesign has everything you need to create and publish books, digital magazines, eBooks, posters, interactive PDFs, and more.
Adobe InDesign was developed by Adobe Systems, first...
</description></item><item><title>Download Macrium Reflect Workstation / Server / Server Plus 8.1.8628</title><pubDate> Thu, 31 Jul 2025 23:49:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-macrium-reflect-1444.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-macrium-reflect-1444.html
</guid><description>
Macrium Reflect is software backup and recovery files, image files, with big improvements in speed, simplicity and strength. The software we provide taiwebs.com 've included 3 version is Macrium Reflect Workstation / Server / Server Plus. Whole our focus is to help organizations protect critical data and business systems, without fuss and budget breaking.
Macrium Reflect - backup and restore files
The function of Macrium Reflect
	Backup tool new: image gradually increases and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe InCopy 2025 v20.5.0.048 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Thu, 31 Jul 2025 23:49:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-incopy-3894.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-incopy-3894.html
</guid><description>
Adobe InCopy 2023 is a solution to write and edit professional, tightly integrated with the software Adobe InDesign. Adobe InCopy allows a process to work in parallel between design staff and editorial copy, accurate copy to layout and efficiently meet editorial deadline. Adobe software this is designed to expand according to the needs of the content publishers, small, medium and large. You will be able to deliver content that will support both print and digital, thereby simplifying the...
</description></item><item><title>Download 4DDiG Disk Copy 1.0.6.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 31 Jul 2025 23:48:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4ddig-disk-copy-12660.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4ddig-disk-copy-12660.html
</guid><description>
4DDiG Disk Copy is user-friendly disk cloning software that allows you to completely and safely clone one hard drive or partition to another. With this disk cloning feature, you can clone HDD to SSD for device upgrade, clone SSD or HDD for data backup, clone disk for data transfer. Here's how to clone a drive.
Main features
	Efficient disk cloning to upgrade your hard drive or computer
	Easily transfer data to another hard drive
	Create secure local backups of specific partitions or...
</description></item><item><title>Download MSI Center 2.0.57.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 31 Jul 2025 23:48:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-msi-center-12314.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-msi-center-12314.html
</guid><description>
The AI ​​era of computing: MSI laptops are equipped with MSI's exclusive AI technology capable of providing completely new smart features. The AI ​​revolution has arrived on MSI laptops. MSI AI Engine automatically recognizes various user situations, triggering appropriate adjustments in performance, sound effects, display modes and keyboard backlighting. Users do not need to make manual adjustments to achieve optimal situations.
MSI Center combines all of MSI's exclusive...
</description></item><item><title>Download Memtest86 Pro 11.4 Build 1000 + ISO</title><pubDate> Thu, 31 Jul 2025 23:47:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-memtest86-pro-725.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-memtest86-pro-725.html
</guid><description>
Memtest86 Pro is software check free RAM memory in your computer to detect the latent fault inside the memory. Anyone know RAM is very important part of the computer. If RAM is error that does not fix soon will greatly affect your computer. Therefore, the Memtest86 Pro is the software necessary for the system of your computer.
Memtest86 Pro - Check memory RAM
Features of Memtest86 Pro
	13 algorithm to check RAM different
	Support RAM DDR4 (and DDR2 &amp;amp; DDR3)
	XMP - configuration...
</description></item><item><title>Download Jailer 16.7.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 31 Jul 2025 23:46:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jailer-3196.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jailer-3196.html
</guid><description>
Jailer is a tool to reset the database, schema and browse data. It the sets of continuous, intact reference from the database relations. It removes outdated data without violating integrity. Theory is that force majeure DBMS (using JDBC), platform-independent and tạobộ data DbUnit , XML has hierarchical structure and SQL-DML is arranged in the link structure.
Jailer - Installed back to the database
Database Jailer is growing both in scale and complexity to meet the growing needs of...
</description></item><item><title>Download SweetScape 010 Editor 16.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 31 Jul 2025 23:42:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sweetscape-010-editor-1492.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sweetscape-010-editor-1492.html
</guid><description>
SweetScape 010 Editor is a text editor and hex editor professional is designed to quickly and easily edit any file or drive on your computer. Combine the easy to use interface with a complete set of editing tools, 010 Editor is a valuable tool for anyone working with text files or binary files. One of the most powerful features of 010 Editor is the ability to analyze virtually any file binary how to change binary form.
Instead of browsing through a bunch of bytes hex as the hex editor...
</description></item><item><title>Download TerraExplorer Pro 8.1.0 Build 41223</title><pubDate> Thu, 31 Jul 2025 23:41:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-terraexplorer-pro-5231.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-terraexplorer-pro-5231.html
</guid><description>
TerraExplorer Pro is a program to create and view 3D GIS on the desktop advanced provides powerful tools and 3D environments, high resolution to view, query, analysis and presentation of data geographic space. With strong ability and extension of TerraExplorer, realistic 3D images can be created by coating the terrain with the layers unlimited data, 3D models, virtual objects, and more.
In addition to the measurement tools and fundamental analysis to measure the distance, slope and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ultimaker Cura 5.10.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 31 Jul 2025 23:41:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ultimaker-cura-7179.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ultimaker-cura-7179.html
</guid><description>
Trusted by millions of users, Ultimaker Cura is the world's most popular 3D printing software. Prepare prints with a few clicks, integrate with CAD software for an easier workflow, or dive into custom settings for in-depth control.
Features of Ultimaker Cura
	Ultimaker Cura is a powerful, open source slicing tool, built through years of expert in-house development and user input.
	Intent records to print specific applications at the click of a button
	Recommended profiles are tested...
</description></item><item><title>Download Opera GX (Gaming Browser) 120.0.5543.127</title><pubDate> Thu, 31 Jul 2025 23:40:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-gx-3170.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-gx-3170.html
</guid><description>
Opera GX is a special version of the Opera browser is built to complement gamers avid. Browser this game comes with the unique features to help users make maximum use of both the game and their browser. Opera GX is built specifically to support the game. This browser includes the unique features to help users have the best experience when gaming and surfing the web.
Opera GX - special browser for gamers
GX Control allows you to set a limit on the level of use RAM, CPU and network where...
</description></item><item><title>Download Autokroma Bundle 2025.7</title><pubDate> Thu, 31 Jul 2025 23:40:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-autokroma-bundle-11157.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-autokroma-bundle-11157.html
</guid><description>
Autokroma provides software plugins for the Adobe CC Video application to help simplify and accelerate your daily workflow, with missing codecs and features for both import and export. AfterCodecs is a Fast Exporter for After Effects/Premiere Pro/Media Encoding and BRAW Studio A full-featured Blackmagic RAW Importer for After Effects/Premiere Pro/Media Encoding. PlumePack collects your PrPro projects and trims the media to make it lighter: Cut, Store, Organize and more!. Influx is an...
</description></item><item><title>Download KISSsoft 2025 SP1 25.0.0.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 31 Jul 2025 23:40:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kisssoft-8095.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kisssoft-8095.html
</guid><description>
KISSsoft is a modular calculation program for the design, optimization and verification of machine parts according to international standards. Custom-tailored software packages for a wide range of applications ensure tailor-made solutions and integrate with all popular CAD software to complete the product.
It includes internationally recognized computing standards as well as various optimization and design options, based on the experience of customers and development engineers. KISSsoft...
</description></item><item><title>Download Start Everywhere 1.4.2.43</title><pubDate> Thu, 31 Jul 2025 23:39:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-start-everywhere-4897.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-start-everywhere-4897.html
</guid><description>
Start Everywherel is software Start Menu provides a number of unique solutions to allow you to launch the application is installed on the computer and access the documents. The appearance, operation, and management of Start Everywhere can be flexibly customized.
Features of Start Everywhere
	It provides effective access to applications, documents, and computer settings are installed.
	It put the long list in alphabetical order and also allows you to sort them by date.
	System menu of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Pale Moon 33.8.1.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 31 Jul 2025 23:39:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pale-moon-1883.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pale-moon-1883.html
</guid><description>
Pale Moon is a copy of Firefox has been optimized for the Windows operating System with the processor performance, high current. It looks identical to Firefox browser standard, and supports the extensions, themes and identities of Firefox. All extensions, bookmarks and settings of your existing be entered during the installation process, so except for the logo, you won't notice any difference on function.
Pale Moon - secure web browser
However, what you may notice is the difference in...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sequentum Enterprise (Content Grabber) 2.82.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 31 Jul 2025 23:33:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-content-grabber-premium-2813.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-content-grabber-premium-2813.html
</guid><description>
Content Grabber is a very good software to extract information from the Internet site. The usual information you see on the website is associated with website structure and can not be saved to format your favorite. With this program you can extract different information, such as tables, images, videos and other types of data from almost every site and store them in structured format in the report XML, CSV and Excel. One of the important features of this program is the ability to automate...
</description></item></channel></rss>