<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 09:03:01 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 09:03:01 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download JRiver Media Center 34.0.71</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Sep 2025 23:53:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jriver-media-center-110.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jriver-media-center-110.html
</guid><description>
JRiver Media Center can help you strictly manage all your files media and enjoy them in a completely new way. Launching the application for the first time, users will be immediately impressed with the intuitive and eye-catching interface with many interesting features to explore. Most people who have used JRiver Media Center evaluate that the software interface design is youthful and modern.
The software for arranging cover art of music files is also extremely neat, especially Insert...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare Recoverit 14.0.0.28</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Sep 2025 23:52:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-recoverits-374.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-recoverits-374.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare Recoverit is a data recovery software that is easily lost at a rapid rate and is used by many people. You will do what happens if one day your data is suddenly lost due to the virus or deleted it, .. Wondershare Recoverit will provide you with an environment to protect important data.
Wondershare Recoverit has all the scanning processes that are divided into multiple types, from the typical recovery of the deleted files that are deleted to the recovery of missing files due...
</description></item><item><title>Download VLC Media Player 3.0.22 RC1</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Sep 2025 23:51:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vlc-media-player-63.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vlc-media-player-63.html
</guid><description>
VLC Media Player is a multimedia player supporting many audio formats and video (MPEG-1, MPEG-2, MPEG-4, DivX, mp3, ogg, etc.) without the need for additional codecs , as well as DVDS, VCDS, and various streaming protocols different online.It also comes with a server, streaming allows you to stream media in unicast or multicast from your network.
VLC Media Player 
VLC Media Player provides a simple interface, with simple buttons control the playback standard and make the most of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download 3D Youtube Downloader 1.23</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Sep 2025 23:51:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-3d-youtube-downloader-1631.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-3d-youtube-downloader-1631.html
</guid><description>
3D Youtube Downloader is application support users to download the videos from Youtube website with great quality. The advantage of this software is the ability to download the videos in 3D, make the download process is fully automated and the download speed is extremely fast. In addition to Youtube, this tool also allows to download videos from many other sites, so users can own any favorite videos yet. 3D Youtube Downloader is a downloads simple but powerful from Youtube, Vimeo,...
</description></item><item><title>Download PIDKey Lite 1.64.4 b49</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Sep 2025 23:50:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pidkey-lite-2693.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pidkey-lite-2693.html
</guid><description>
PIDKey Lite is a program intended to show the renovation and preservation in the database of the product information to check "validity" of the key Microsoft from the famous program we or is Ratiborus and VAMT. Program PIDKey LiteIt is the successor of the PIDKey. and I got out of it the idea the best program (allows you To add new keyboard with two methods additional mode key).
The program has a number of configuration integration, but you can also create custom profiles by themselves....
</description></item><item><title>Download EmEditor Pro 25.3.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Sep 2025 23:50:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-emeditor-pro-69.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-emeditor-pro-69.html
</guid><description>
EmEditor Pro - the professional version of editor text powerful for programmers, web developers and ordinary users with illumination of syntax and Unicode support. The features of the editor such as search and replace in files using regular expressions, automatic code detect, bookmark link and address email, block selection mode, configure the button bar, menu, font and elements color. With each language you can set separate configuration.
EmEditor Pro - text Editor professional
The...
</description></item><item><title>Download Serato DJ Pro 3.3.5</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Sep 2025 23:49:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-serato-dj-pro-169.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-serato-dj-pro-169.html
</guid><description>
Serato DJ Pro is software mix DJ music, professional support, sound effects, and combined to create music, Great DJ. Serato DJ Pro supports the sound effects such as Delay, Reverb, Flanger, Echo, PingPong Delay, Phaser, Distortion, High and Low Pass Filter, as well as combinations of them. Supports MIDI in full, be made in the program, providing the ability to adapt to the controller and program for every need. It allows you to use at the same time from two to four floors. Program Serato...
</description></item><item><title>Download Opera One 122.0.5643.71</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Sep 2025 23:49:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-972.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-972.html
</guid><description>
Opera is a fast, safe, configurable and compliant intranet web browser, which includes both the reader and the application. The Opera browser supports web browsing, listening to music, watching high speed movies, you can open many tabs on the Opera without affecting your browsing speed. Opera now supports almost all devices and operating systems such as windows, IOS, Android, linux, MacOS ...
Opera is a beautiful interface and many interesting features, operating on both PCs and mobile,...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDF Architect Pro + OCR 9.1.75.23074</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Sep 2025 23:48:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-architect-pro-ocr-6381.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-architect-pro-ocr-6381.html
</guid><description>
PDF Architect  is professional software that provides PDF creation and editing features according to your needs. Our PDF editor keeps you up to date with forward-looking features. Take complete control of your PDF files with our PDF editor. Modify text, images, and pages, and convert PDF to Word and Excel and more.
It has many advanced options and features for customizing, securing, and collaborating PDF files. All necessary features are included in this for better user experience. This...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wipe Pro 2025.11</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Sep 2025 23:47:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wipe-pro-710.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wipe-pro-710.html
</guid><description>
Wipe Pro is software that helps clean up litter, increase in hard drive space besides also protect your privacy on the Internet, it removes records about personal activity on the computer. You will be able to delete browser history and the cache, the file index.dat, registry, files, cookies, internet history, auto complete, temporary internet files and many other items. This program also delete all activities other individuals that you made when using the PC and regardless of which...
</description></item><item><title>Download PhotoPad Image Editor Pro 14.44 Beta</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Sep 2025 23:47:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photopad-image-editor-572.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photopad-image-editor-572.html
</guid><description>
PhotoPad Image Editor is a software to help edit photos and supports lots of features like edit, cut, rotate, resize and flip digital photos. With PhotoPad Image Editor, you can freely perform the basic editing for their images and also can add some neat effect. It has the option to create a photo collage and mosaic images from your photos, and you can also add text and captions. If you prefer, you can complete your masterpiece by adding the frame or contour is simple.
The main features...
</description></item><item><title>Download dslrBooth Photo Booth Software Pro 7.48.0923.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Sep 2025 23:46:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dslrbooth-photo-booth-software-666.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dslrbooth-photo-booth-software-666.html
</guid><description>
Photo Booth Software is a software to create, list and combine the images back together in the same theme as travel, haloween. Created by the professional photographer for the operator photo booth at all skill levels, photo booth software dslrBooth built from scratch with the sole purpose of running the photo booth. The software uses the latest technology to provide you and your guests, high quality prints and the ability to share photos and GIF on the means of social media including...
</description></item><item><title>Download Classroom Spy Professional 5.4.10</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Sep 2025 23:46:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-classroom-spy-professional-916.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-classroom-spy-professional-916.html
</guid><description>
Classroom Spy Professional is a software classroom management effective. Manage and track activities of all the computers of students remotely. Plus, you can share your screen with the activity record of the student, the computer controls for performance, limit the use of the Internet, the application blocks and more.
Classroom Spy Professional - software classroom management
The main features of Classroom Spy Professional
	Display live images of the remote computer.
	You can control...
</description></item><item><title>Download Rufus 4.10 + Portable</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Sep 2025 23:45:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rufus-2442.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rufus-2442.html
</guid><description>
Rufus support create a USB install Windows operating system like installing from a Windows installation disc often. Rufus offers to users the features from simple to lift the cap fit the needs as well as the ability of many objects. Rufus also has useful functions such as automatic identification, USB, display information about the connected USB.
A new version of a small program has been released that allows you to create and format the USB flash drive that can boot, it also can operate...
</description></item><item><title>Download Macrium Site Manager 8.1.8602</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Sep 2025 23:44:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-macrium-site-manager-4193.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-macrium-site-manager-4193.html
</guid><description>
Macrium Site Manager is a wonderful new addition for line backup solution based on images Reflect. Now, the deployment of large number of agents to backup end point Macrium Reflect and manage them from a central location will be much easier. IT administrators will be able to use the Dashboard can be customized to quickly see backup status, along with identifying and solving problems easily. Macrium Site Manager do?
Macrium Site Manager - site Manager
Use the procedure in 4 steps is...
</description></item><item><title>Download Inno Setup Compiler 6.5.4</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Sep 2025 23:39:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-inno-setup-compiler-2655.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-inno-setup-compiler-2655.html
</guid><description>
Inno Setup Compiler is a system installed based on free software created by Delphi by Jordan Russell. The first version was released in 1997. QuickStart of Inno Setup include main Inno Setup and also includes an option to install the script editor Inno Script Studio. The script editor is not official and is not mandatory for general use, but help Inno Setup easier to use.
Inno Setup Compiler - software create file setup.exe
The features of Inno Setup Compiler
	Support for every...
</description></item><item><title>Download ViceVersa Pro 6 Build 6015</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Sep 2025 23:38:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-viceversa-pro-6545.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-viceversa-pro-6545.html
</guid><description>
ViceVersa Pro is a professional Windows software designed to co-file files, File Copy, File Copy, and File Comparison. ViceVersa allows you to synchronize files, copy folders, perform backup and perform more file and folder comparison than ever: create, quickly and save time.
ViceVersa operates between computers, e.g. laptops, desktop computers, workstations, servers, through LAN, WAN, VPN, USB, and with any type of storage medium including an external hard disk, a Zip disk, USB flash...
</description></item><item><title>Download MusConv 4.10.421 Lifetime</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Sep 2025 23:38:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html
</guid><description>
MusConv transfers playlists, albums, followed artists and liked songs across a variety of services – Spotify, Apple Music, Amazon Music, YouTube, YouTube Music, iTunes, Deezer, Tidal, SoundCloud, Pandora and more 125 music services!
Features of MusConv Ultimate
	Transfer playlists, albums, followed artists and liked tracks between over 125 music servicesManage playlists (Delete, Merge, Split, Copy...)
	More than 125 music services supported
	Access DAILY updated music charts on...
</description></item><item><title>Download Source Insight 4.00.0146</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Sep 2025 23:37:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-source-insight-2185.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-source-insight-2185.html
</guid><description>
Source Insight is an editor, programming-oriented strong project, browse the code and the analysis help you understand the code in when you work and plan. Source insight has built-in analysis for C / C ++, C #, Java, Objective-C, and much more. Source Insight is a powerful program created to give you a browser, as well as tools to view and edit the source code for the application is written in the programming language different. Everyone knows that the analysis and processing of the source...
</description></item><item><title>Download Explzh 9.86</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Sep 2025 23:37:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-explzh-2278.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-explzh-2278.html
</guid><description>
Explzh is software that originated from Japan. This program works with most formats, can extract the file directly to FTP server, split large files into multiple smaller size. I would like to note that the storage supports encryption of files compressed using AES algorithm, has a system of tabs in the main window, you can search for the information you need in the repository and work with files, batch mode is done.
Explzh - Compress and decompress file
The file is support work with the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Net Monitor for Employees Professional 6.4.10</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Sep 2025 23:36:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-network-lookout-net-monitor-for-employees-professional-2098.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-network-lookout-net-monitor-for-employees-professional-2098.html
</guid><description>
Network LookOut Net Monitor for Employees Professional is a software platform to help manage user activity, gives the ability to inspect and control computer activities, as well as record activity on the screen as AVI file. Net Monitor for Employees Professional allows access from remote computers. This feature proved particularly useful when you want to see the activity of each user on the computer, or assist them perform the work on the computer with the mouse manipulation or the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mass Image Compressor 4.1.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Sep 2025 23:36:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mass-image-compressor-12571.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mass-image-compressor-12571.html
</guid><description>
Mass Image Compressor is easy to use - a point-and-shoot mass image compression and conversion tool for Web page optimization, photographers, HTML game creators, and regular Windows users.
MassImageCompressor reduces image size significantly (&amp;gt;90%) according to user-selected size and quality parameters. Reduce large numbers of images in a folder (and optional subfolders) with just one click. Batch compressing images for websites, emails or mobile storage has never been easier! Most...
</description></item><item><title>Download HE - Hardware Read and Write Utility 1.25.09.24</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Sep 2025 23:34:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-he-hardware-read-and-write-utility-4287.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-he-hardware-read-and-write-utility-4287.html
</guid><description>
HE - Hardware Read and Write Utility is a powerful utility intended for hardware engineer, engineer, BIOS developer, driver, engineer, QA engineers, performance test engineers, diagnostic, etc., this utility access almost all the computer hardware, including PCI (PCI Express), index / Data, PCI, memory, index memory / Data space I / O, Index I / O / Data, Super I / O, DIMM SPD, CPU The registers MSR, screen, SMART, physical area of the hard drive identification data, ATA, dump tables ACPI...
</description></item><item><title>Download TickTick Premium 6.3.7</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Sep 2025 23:33:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ticktick-premium-7770.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ticktick-premium-7770.html
</guid><description>
TickTick Premium is a task management application that helps users stay organized, it is very suitable for educators and students with many incentives. TickTick turns your Windows PC device into a flexible, easy-to-use and highly efficient office platform. Join millions of people to capture ideas, organize their lives, and do something creative every day.
Whether there are work related tasks or personal goals, TickTick is here to help you manage all your to-dos. With five different...
</description></item><item><title>Download InnoExtractor Ultra 2026 v11.1.0.153</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Sep 2025 23:33:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-innoextractor-plus-4009.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-innoextractor-plus-4009.html
</guid><description>
InnoExtractor Plus is a handy lightweight but strong will allow you to use technology InnoUnp to easily extract the installer Inno Setup. Using this tool, you will be able to explore the content and the internal structure of installers and extract them to a folder on the local drive or on the storage device mobile without running the file setup. InnoExtractor Plus comes with graphical interface simple and user friendly, allowing you to easily open the installed just by drag and drop...
</description></item></channel></rss>