<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 20:47:14 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 20:47:14 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Dont Sleep 9.99</title><pubDate> Thu, 12 Feb 2026 19:49:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dont-sleep-89.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dont-sleep-89.html
</guid><description>
Don't Sleep allows you can set the date and custom time that you want to reactivate the feature manager usual sources or you can set a countdown fast to pause the power management in X hours.
Can temporarily disable the protection of your screen or off your computer at a certain time.
The main features of the Dont Sleep:
- Optimal power supply for computer
- Installation time power source according to
- Prevent computer reboot
Content update Dont Sleep 5.66:
The official website...
</description></item><item><title>Download Fender Studio Pro (PreSonus Studio One Pro) 8 v8.0.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 12 Feb 2026 19:46:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-presonus-studio-one-pro-780.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-presonus-studio-one-pro-780.html
</guid><description>
PreSonus Studio One Pro is software production music professional perfect combination between the studio model with the production process according to the beat and loop today so you can bring music ideas to actual sounds. Screen interface, simple, effective contains the number of tracks is not limited to , the editing tools are intuitive and the tools advanced virtual. Spend precious time to create music instead of wondering what to click next. Studio One does not dictate how you work or...
</description></item><item><title>Download Room Arranger 10.3.6.748</title><pubDate> Thu, 12 Feb 2026 19:46:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-room-arranger-3779.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-room-arranger-3779.html
</guid><description>
Room Arranger is a 3D application lets you easily plan for the room, office or his apartment just a few mouse clicks. The application comes with a simple interface will significantly simplify your work. You can draw many kinds of objects and items to create furniture of your own. This app also includes a library of object rich.
Software Room Arranger enables you to view your project in 3D form. You can also upload the 3D scene interact on your blog or your website. The application uses...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Downloader 10.2.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 12 Feb 2026 19:46:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html
</guid><description>
YTD Youtube Downloader is an application that reliable and intuitive, allowing you to quickly download YouTube videos and save them to your computer. You can also convert the media files to the format desired video or extract audio streams and save separately. YTD Youtube Downloader lets you save your favorite clips of yourself from Youtube, Facebook, Vimeo and Dailymotion to your desktop. The software supports URLS from many web site hosting, multimedia and allows you to download desired...
</description></item><item><title>Download Active@ Disk Editor 26.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 12 Feb 2026 16:49:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-active-disk-editor-4606.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-active-disk-editor-4606.html
</guid><description>
Active Disk Editor is the editing tool, disk usage viewer, disk low-level, simple, displays information in the binary mode and text at the same time. You can use this view to analyze the content of the structural components data storage, such as: hard Drives, floppy Drives, partitions, other objects.
The app allows you to quickly navigate to almost all areas, although the whole code is displayed. This can be done through the drop-down menu where you can select the boot sector of NTFS /...
</description></item><item><title>Download Photo Reducer 6.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 12 Feb 2026 16:47:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photo-reducer-10218.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photo-reducer-10218.html
</guid><description>
Photo Reducer is free software that supports image size reduction in various formats by choosing from countless presets or defining values yourself, then sending via email or save locally. In terms of optimization, the app comes with a lot of preset configurations. These are found in a drop-down menu, with options for ideal print size, digital frames, screens for HD TVs and 4K TVs, ideal sizes for the web, as well as customization options. The second choice allows you to adjust quality...
</description></item><item><title>Download Office Tool Plus 11.0.27.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 12 Feb 2026 16:45:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-tool-plus-3664.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-tool-plus-3664.html
</guid><description>
Office Tool Plus based on the Office deployment tool from Microsoft. You can customize configuration files installation and install Office of to install Office without Internet. Configure install Office, as well as customize the product C2R have installed, such as add and remove components, language packs, etc.
Office Tool Plus - Download and install Office
The characteristics of Office Tool Plus
	1. Configure install Office, as well as customize the product C2R have installed, such...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft Office 2024 Professional Plus LTSC v2408 Build 17932.20670 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Thu, 12 Feb 2026 16:40:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-office-2024-professional-plus-64-bit-10679.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-office-2024-professional-plus-64-bit-10679.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft has officially announced the final version of the Office 2024 release for Windows and Mac users. After releasing a preview version in the first half of this year, the product has been finalized and is now available to users. Office 2024 includes updated versions of apps from the Word 2024, Excel 2024, PowerPoint 2024, Outlook 2024, Access 2024, and Publisher 2024 suites.
Office 2024 includes virtually every change that has been added to the suite of programs in Office 365 over...
</description></item><item><title>Download 4K Video Downloader Plus 26.0.3</title><pubDate> Thu, 12 Feb 2026 16:39:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-video-downloader-617.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-video-downloader-617.html
</guid><description>
4K Video Downloader Plus is software support downloads video, audio and subtitles from YouTube with high quality up to 4K. Download process video is very simple: just copy the video link from your browser and click Paste Url. Done! If you want that video on your iPad, iPhone or other device, we have protected you.
The feature on 4K Video Downloader Plus
	Download entire playlists and channels from YouTube and save them in MP4, MKV, M4A, MP3, FLV, 3G, create a file .m3u for...
</description></item><item><title>Download Windows 11 Pro 25H2 v26200.7840 NoTPM Multilingual Preactivated</title><pubDate> Thu, 12 Feb 2026 16:39:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-11-pro-6618.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-11-pro-6618.html
</guid><description>
Windows 11 is officially leaked to a developer version. Previously, when Windows 10 was released, Microsoft once stated that Windows 10 would be the last version of Windows for users. Clearly, with the arrival of Windows 11, Microsoft needed a major reason to reverse its previous claims and still remove Windows 10 by introducing some new operating systems.
About the interface of Windows 11 is quite similar to Windows 10X (a version of Windows 10 has stopped growing). The logo image of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Bluetooth Version Finder 1.7</title><pubDate> Thu, 12 Feb 2026 16:32:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bluetooth-version-finder-7692.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bluetooth-version-finder-7692.html
</guid><description>
Bluetooth Version Finder is a lightweight and free solution that can help you identify the specific Bluetooth version that corresponds to the device you just connected to your PC.
Some features in the Windows operating system are only available if you are running a specific Bluetooth version or later. For example, Nearby Sharing (file sharing between two Windows 10 computers) requires Bluetooth 4.0 or later. Bluetooth 4.0 adds the Bluetooth Smart / Bluetooth Low Energy standard in...
</description></item><item><title>Download reaConverter Pro 8.0.195</title><pubDate> Thu, 12 Feb 2026 16:31:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html
</guid><description>
reaConverter Pro is software image processing feature with batch conversion and image editing periodically becomes simple. eaConverter also provide command line utilities allow you to process images automatically, thus helping you shorten the time for other work.
reaConverter Pro integrated powerful tool of Uber with many great features. It provides advanced solutions to process and adjust images. Management of the conversion process the base image with the latest version of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Office 2021 Professional Plus (64-bit) LTSC v2108 Build 14334.20522 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Thu, 12 Feb 2026 16:31:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-office-professional-plus-2021-64-bit-7187.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-office-professional-plus-2021-64-bit-7187.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft 365 is a subscription that comes with premium apps like Word, Excel, PowerPoint, OneNote, Outlook, Publisher, and Access (Publisher and Access are available on PC only). Applications can be installed on a variety of devices, including PCs, Macs, iPads, iPhones, tablets, and Android phones. Microsoft 365 also comes with services like 1 TB OneDrive storage, 60 Skype minutes per month, and Microsoft support by phone and chat. When you're on a subscription, you'll receive the...
</description></item><item><title>Download 4K YouTube to MP3 26.0.3</title><pubDate> Thu, 12 Feb 2026 16:30:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-youtube-to-mp3-622.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-youtube-to-mp3-622.html
</guid><description>
4K YouTube to MP3 is a software to convert video youtube to mp3 quickly and easily by the manipulation drag-and-drop simple. With 4K YouTube to MP3 you just drag and drop the link to the favorite songs of you and get the MP3 files to your computer, as easy as that. Transfer songs directly to iPod, iPhone and iPad everywhere you go. No install annoying and complex to solve, just a clean interface, user friendly and functional.
When using 4K YouTube to MP3, users will get the playlists,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Picture Window Pro 8.0.549</title><pubDate> Thu, 12 Feb 2026 16:29:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-picture-window-pro-7452.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-picture-window-pro-7452.html
</guid><description>
Picture Window Pro is a powerful image editing tool designed for serious photographers with strict creative and quality standards. Its comprehensive set of photo editing and editing tools let you control and shape every aspect of your images.
Picture Window Pro 8 is a complete rewrite of Picture Window Pro 7. It features non-destructive image editing through a novel interface based on an image tree. It also fully supports large, high-resolution displays and can be used in dual monitor...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tails 7.4.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 12 Feb 2026 16:28:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tails-3241.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tails-3241.html
</guid><description>
Tails is a live operating system that you can boot on almost any computer from a USB memory stick or DVD. Tails does this by using the distribution classic Gnome of Linux. The top navigation bar allows you quick access to "Applications" and "Places" so you can easily access what you need quickly and easily and not lost.
Tails - independent operating System for security
Menu "apps" provide shortcuts for bundled software, including graphics, audio and video, office, system tools, and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Fast Video Cutter Joiner 7.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 12 Feb 2026 16:28:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fast-video-cutter-joiner-7542.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fast-video-cutter-joiner-7542.html
</guid><description>
Fast Video Cutter Joiner is a fast video cutter and joiner with an easy to use interface. It allows users to trim parts of a video quickly while maintaining the quality of the original video. It supports various formats like AVI, MPEG, MP4, WMV, 3GP, FLV...
This tool helps you to cut video files into small parts, to keep only the parts you need and remove unwanted parts like trailers and advertisements in a movie. The clips you cut can then be used for other video productions or for a...
</description></item><item><title>Download Windows 11 Enterprise 25H2 v26200.7840 NoTPM Multilingual Preactivated</title><pubDate> Thu, 12 Feb 2026 16:27:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-11-pro-enterprise-untouched-6672.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-11-pro-enterprise-untouched-6672.html
</guid><description>
Windows 11 is the latest version of the Windows operating system released, with new interfaces and other new features such as the new Microsoft Store, the new source of personalized data supported by AI and the best browser performance in the segment from Microsoft Edge, the chat from Microsoft Teams is integrated in the taskbar and more!
Attention when installing Windows 11 Pro Enterprise: The settings environment and Windows installation is to upgrade from the Windows 10 20H2 ISO,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Geekbench Pro 6.6.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 12 Feb 2026 16:26:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-geekbench-pro-606.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-geekbench-pro-606.html
</guid><description>
Geekbench Pro 4 gauge power your system and let you know whether your computer is ready to roar up. Mobile device or computer to your desk how strong? Each workload CPU model a task or application in the real world, to ensure meaningful results. The trial is very complex, avoid the incidents with simple patterns, memory access, simple and push the limits of your system.
Features Geekbench Pro
Calculate the benchmark
	Measuring the calculation performance of your GPU with benchmark...
</description></item><item><title>Download KMPlayer (KMP) 2026.1.26.43 x64 / 4.2.3.32 x86</title><pubDate> Thu, 12 Feb 2026 16:25:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kmplayer-kmp-902.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kmplayer-kmp-902.html
</guid><description>
KMPlayer (KMP) is software watch movies listen to music multi-function for video enthusiasts. KMPlayer development is many types of the format different. KMPlayer has improved on sound quality, images when listening to music and watching movies, the playback speed of video is faster, more codec player is added to the software video decoder is optimized.
KMPlayer also supports a variety of audio formats and video and offers a the interface can be customized with the preview coverflow and...
</description></item><item><title>Download MSI Dragon Center 2.0.155.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 12 Feb 2026 16:24:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-msi-dragon-center-7095.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-msi-dragon-center-7095.html
</guid><description>
MSI Dragon Center is an official control panel for MSI computers that enables you to get the most out of your MSI experience by enhancing per-key RGB lighting, tones, and tones. bar, get information about the cooling system, or change the display. With MSI Dragon Center, you can closely monitor CPU, GPU and RAM performance to optimize your PC's performance while gaming.
Features of MSI Dragon Center:
	Optimize gaming performance with just 1 click.
	Free up memory, prioritize system...
</description></item><item><title>Download iFoneTool EasyDown 2.4.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 12 Feb 2026 16:24:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ifonetool-easydown-14405.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ifonetool-easydown-14405.html
</guid><description>
iFoneTool EasyDown is a download software for Windows that allows you to save videos and music from platforms like YouTube, TikTok, Spotify, and many others, with features such as batch downloading and support for high-quality formats. It's compatible with major platforms including YouTube, NicoNico, Apple Music, Spotify, TikTok, and Twitter. It supports batch downloading of playlists, channels, individual songs, albums, podcasts, and more. High quality, lossless downloads, fast saving of...
</description></item><item><title>Download CoolUtils Total Doc Converter 5.1.0.373/145</title><pubDate> Thu, 12 Feb 2026 16:23:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-total-doc-converter-84.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-total-doc-converter-84.html
</guid><description>
CoolUtils Total Doc Converter Program that will allow you to document conversion DOC to others, the list can be viewed on the official website or you can watch carefully the screenshot, I think the question would no longer can download CoolUtils Total Doc Converter below. There is batch processing,in general, everything is convenient, I hope you like it.
Total Doc Converter is conversion tools text comprehensive and multi-featured, very necessary when storing or printing the text. It also...
</description></item><item><title>Download ExtraDisks Home 26.2.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 12 Feb 2026 16:23:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-extradisks-home-7758.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-extradisks-home-7758.html
</guid><description>
ExtraDisks is a set of tools for creating virtual disks on your computer physical drives that do not change and are not divided into additional partitions. The program contains tools for creating encrypted disks, file-based virtual disks and directory-based virtual disks. The current version includes the following tools: Encrypted Disks, Virtual Disks, Folder Disks, Startup Manager, System Tweaker.
Features of ExtraDisks
ExtraDisks: Encrypted Disk
This tool is used to create encrypted...
</description></item><item><title>Download Altium Designer Agile 26.3.0 Build 18</title><pubDate> Thu, 12 Feb 2026 16:22:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-altium-designer-agile-14320.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-altium-designer-agile-14320.html
</guid><description>
Explore how Altium Agile helps organizations grow by seamlessly connecting users and engineering systems with integrations with Jira, PLM (Enterprise), and access to SiliconExpert and Z2Data components and supply chain data. Altium Agile is Altium's platform-based approach to agile hardware development, providing integrated tools and workflows for managing the electronics product lifecycle with collaboration, governance, and traceability.
	Supply chain intelligence improves decision...
</description></item></channel></rss>