<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 17:31:29 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 17:31:29 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download AnExplorer Pro File Transfer 5.8.8</title><pubDate> Sun, 05 Oct 2025 19:27:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-file-manager-pro-tv-usb-otg-8358.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-file-manager-pro-tv-usb-otg-8358.html
</guid><description>
AnExplorer File Explorer is a unique file manager for TV and Watch file management tool. It is simple, small, fast and efficient File Explorer. Only file managers support RTL and display the size of folders on storage. It is designed for all devices including Phones, Phablets, Tablets, Watches and TVs. It is completely designed using Material Design.
Pro TV USBOTG File Manager Features
	Full-featured It provides all file management features including cut, copy, delete, rename,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Duolingo: language lessons 6.50.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 05 Oct 2025 19:25:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-duolingo-language-lessons-8265.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-duolingo-language-lessons-8265.html
</guid><description>
Duolingo is a popular language learning app that offers interactive lessons to help users learn new languages. This application offers many languages for you to choose from, including Spanish, French, German, Italian, Portuguese, Chinese, Japanese and many more.
This app offers an gamified learning experience with interactive lessons, exercises, and quizzes designed to help users learn new words, phrases, and grammar rules. This app is designed to be easy to use and suitable for people...
</description></item><item><title>Download Easy Excel Spreadsheet Editor 1.69</title><pubDate> Sun, 05 Oct 2025 19:25:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-excel-spreadsheet-sheets-app-8326.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-excel-spreadsheet-sheets-app-8326.html
</guid><description>
Are you a frequent user of excel spreadsheets? Do you find it difficult to use to create different types of table entries, such as scanning barcodes from a mobile application. Then Excelled is the best solution to use excel spreadsheets for mobile devices.
Excel spreadsheet features: Sheets App
Create spreadsheet
	You can create an excel spreadsheet with column names and corresponding input methods of your choice.
Simplified interface for input.
	You can add/update entries to the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Bluelight Filter for Eye Care 6.5.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 05 Oct 2025 19:00:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-bluelight-filter-for-eye-care-8192.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-bluelight-filter-for-eye-care-8192.html
</guid><description>
Blue light from smartphones or tablets causes eye strain and makes it difficult to sleep at night. This app adjusts your screen color to reduce blue light and relax your eyes, helping you sleep better.
Features of Blue Light Filter for Eye Care
	Free screen filter app to protect your eyes
	Screen filter with natural colors
	Easy operation
	Turn on or off quickly and easily
	Automatic start
	Eye care on your smartphone or tablet
	This app works on most smartphones like Samsung Galaxy,...
</description></item><item><title>Download 1Weather: Forecast &amp;amp; Radar 11.4.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 05 Oct 2025 19:00:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-1weather-forecast-radar-8846.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-1weather-forecast-radar-8846.html
</guid><description>
1Weather is the most popular weather application on Google Play. Whether you want to check temperatures, forecast precipitation, Doppler radar, or simply track the current phases of the sun and moon, 1Weather has you covered. Plus, it's got an outstanding design that makes getting your weather information easy and fun.
Track current conditions and forecasts for your location and up to 12 locations of your choice. Access charts, precipitation forecasts, maps, weather information and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Drivvo - car management 8.6.12</title><pubDate> Sun, 05 Oct 2025 19:00:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-drivvo-car-management-8614.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-drivvo-car-management-8614.html
</guid><description>
Drivvo is a car management app that helps users track and manage expenses related to their vehicles. It provides a platform to record and analyze fuel consumption, maintenance costs and other expenses, making it easier to budget and manage car-related expenses.
Save Money: Manage fuel consumption and economic costs, car maintenance costs and service costs of your car, motorcycle, bus or truck.
Control Finances: Track average KM/liter, monthly costs, average per day, fuel,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Shazam: Find Music &amp;amp; Concerts 16.12.0-250925</title><pubDate> Sun, 05 Oct 2025 18:56:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-shazam-music-discovery-10763.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-shazam-music-discovery-10763.html
</guid><description>
Shazam will identify any song in seconds. Discover, artists, lyrics, videos &amp;amp; playlists, all for free. Over 1 billion installs and counting. Use Pop-up Shazam to identify music in any app - Instagram, YouTube, TikTok... No connection? No problem! Shazam while offline.
Features of Shazam: Music Discovery
	Find the name of any song in seconds.
	Listen and add to Apple Music playlists.
	Follow along with time-synced lyrics.
	Watch music videos from Apple Music or YouTube.
	Enable...
</description></item><item><title>Download Smart AudioBook Player 11.5.3</title><pubDate> Sun, 05 Oct 2025 18:56:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-smart-audiobook-player-8181.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-smart-audiobook-player-8181.html
</guid><description>
Smart AudioBook Player is a type of application that allows users to listen to audiobooks on their mobile devices. This app is designed to improve the listening experience by providing features such as automatic bookmarking, adjustable playback speed, and sleep timer. The program is specially designed to play audio books. Let's say you have audiobooks and have copied them to your phone.
Smart AudioBook Player Features
	Supports Chromecast.
	Control playback speed.
	Categorize books...
</description></item><item><title>Download WPSApp Pro 1.7.01</title><pubDate> Sun, 05 Oct 2025 18:55:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wpsapp-pro-8802.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wpsapp-pro-8802.html
</guid><description>
WPSApp Pro is an ad-free version of WPSApp that tests your network security using the WPS protocol. This protocol allows you to connect to a WiFi network using an 8-digit pin number that is usually predefined in the router, the problem is that the pin codes of many routers from different companies are known or know how to calculate.
This application uses these pins to try connections and check if the network is vulnerable. It implements some known algorithms to generate pins and some...
</description></item><item><title>Download Anti Spy Detector - Spyware 6.7.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 05 Oct 2025 18:55:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-anti-spy-scanner-spyware-8753.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-anti-spy-scanner-spyware-8753.html
</guid><description>
Anti-spy scanner &amp;amp; Spyware is an Android app that scans your device for spyware and other harmful applications that can compromise your privacy and security. This is a useful tool for users who want to ensure their devices are not infected with spyware or other malware that could collect sensitive information or cause other harm.
Anti Spy has been developed to scan Android devices to detect potential spies effectively. Thanks to artificial intelligence (AI), real-time signature...
</description></item><item><title>Download Compass and GPS tools 29.0.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 05 Oct 2025 18:54:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-compass-and-gps-tools-8300.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-compass-and-gps-tools-8300.html
</guid><description>
Compass and GPS tool is a compass and GPS tool. There are many apps available on the Google Play Store or other app stores that provide compass and GPS functionality for Android devices.
Compass and GPS tool features
	GPS Essentials: This app provides many GPS-related tools such as compass, speedometer, and waypoint navigation.
	GPS Navigation &amp;amp; Maps: This app offers turn-by-turn voice navigation, offline maps, and real-time traffic updates.
	Compass: This app provides a simple...
</description></item><item><title>Download Magnet Search - Torrent Search 1.2.98</title><pubDate> Sun, 05 Oct 2025 18:54:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-magnet-search-pro-torrent-tool-10821.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-magnet-search-pro-torrent-tool-10821.html
</guid><description>
You can use this app to search for the resource you want, then copy the magnet link and download it. That's easy. You can also search for torrents, have a good time.
</description></item><item><title>Download The Guardian - Live World News 6.192.22024</title><pubDate> Sun, 05 Oct 2025 18:53:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-the-guardian-news-sport-8572.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-the-guardian-news-sport-8572.html
</guid><description>
Read the best news stories, hot news &amp;amp; comments along the way. The Guardian app gives you access to the latest politics, business and sports news through award-winning journalism.
World news, live updates &amp;amp; opinion - take your news feed with you wherever you go. Explore US stories, headlines, content and media on a variety of topics; from business to music, politics, sports, culture &amp;amp; more.
5 reasons to download The Guardian App
	Breaking news alerts, sent straight to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Genius Scan Enterprise 7.32.1 build 6153</title><pubDate> Sun, 05 Oct 2025 18:48:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-genius-scan-enterprise-8561.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-genius-scan-enterprise-8561.html
</guid><description>
Genius Scan Enterprise: Quickly scan your paper documents on the go and export them as multi-page PDF files. Place any document in front of your device's camera: our scanner app automatically recognizes the paper on the background, crops it and cleans the result. You get sharp, easy-to-read scans. Batch scanning allows you to scan dozens of pages in just a few seconds. Powerful tools help you organize, share or archive your documents.
Features of Genius Scan Enterprise for...
</description></item><item><title>Download BikeComputer Pro 9.2.3</title><pubDate> Sun, 05 Oct 2025 18:48:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-bikecomputer-pro-8146.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-bikecomputer-pro-8146.html
</guid><description>
BikeComputer Pro is a mobile application that allows users to track their cycling and other outdoor activities using GPS. The app is available to download from the Google Play Store and Apple App Store. It is designed for cycling enthusiasts and offers many features to help users track and improve their performance. Some features of the application include:
	Track distance, speed and route with GPS
	Altitude tracking
	Audible signals for distance and speed
	Personalized training...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tools Pro - All In One Tools 7.5</title><pubDate> Sun, 05 Oct 2025 18:47:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-tools-pro-8128.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-tools-pro-8128.html
</guid><description>
Tools Pro is an application with many functions such as generating QR codes, recording daily life, calculating normal weight and more.
Tools Pro Features
	Generate QR codes and color them with your favorite colors.
	Record the time of all events that occur.
	Easily calculate your age difference.
	Calculate profits from applicable discounts.
	Calculate debts payable over a period of time certain.
	Convert text to audio and save as mp3.
	Determine if your weight is normal, underweight,...
</description></item><item><title>Download 9GAG: Funny GIF, Meme &amp;amp; Video 8.15.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 05 Oct 2025 18:45:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-9gag-funny-gif-meme-video-11500.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-9gag-funny-gif-meme-video-11500.html
</guid><description>
9GAG has the best funny, cute, weird, wacky, cosplay photos, GIFs, videos, memes, photos on the web. We are your greatest and happiest source. With millions of visitors every day, 9GAG is an application that helps you play LOL, kill time and make new friends around the world.
9GAG features
	The 9GAG app loads quickly and allows for easy scrolling. Don't waste time picking me up or just having a good laugh.
	Carry unlimited fun in your pocket. Enjoy 9GAG anytime, anywhere and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Flowx: Weather Map Forecast 4.126</title><pubDate> Sun, 05 Oct 2025 18:45:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-flowx-weather-map-forecast-8535.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-flowx-weather-map-forecast-8535.html
</guid><description>
Visualize forecasts anywhere in the world with unique Flowx weather maps and charts. Move your finger across the screen to control the forecast animation over time. Choose data according to your needs from over 30 data types and several forecast models, including GFS, GDPS, NAM, HRRR, ICON, ICON-EU, APERGE, AROME, HIRLAM, COSMO, RDPS &amp;amp; HRDPS. Use Flowx for weather planning, for aviation, fishing, boating, surfing, cycling, hiking, photography, storm tracking, or anyone interested in...
</description></item><item><title>Download AccuWeather: Weather Radar 21.1.2-8-rc</title><pubDate> Sun, 05 Oct 2025 18:45:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-accuweather-weather-radar-8893.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-accuweather-weather-radar-8893.html
</guid><description>
Weather warnings from AccuWeather are exceptionally accurate. Whether it's windy, sunny or rainy, you can stay one step ahead with AccuWeather weather radar. Be prepared for daily forecasts or sudden changes in weather with live alerts and accurate weather forecasts. Daily weather snapshots provide storm warnings, weather updates and RealFeel Temperature®, helping to predict today's weather.
With AccuWeather's superior accuracy™ for local forecasts, you'll never miss a memorable...
</description></item><item><title>Download ArsClip 5.43</title><pubDate> Sun, 05 Oct 2025 16:11:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-arsclip-3552.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-arsclip-3552.html
</guid><description>
ArsClip help you monitor and keep track of all the items in the clipboard. The paste is completed using a pop-up window. This window can be toggled using keyboard shortcuts, hold down the button, right-click, a window to be activated and other methods. ArsClip used to be a basic software, but thanks to feedback received from users, it has become a program is highly customizable and has the ability to customize high. This program is specialized in automation of the task of copy and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Picture Window Pro 8.0.532</title><pubDate> Sun, 05 Oct 2025 16:10:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-picture-window-pro-7452.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-picture-window-pro-7452.html
</guid><description>
Picture Window Pro is a powerful image editing tool designed for serious photographers with strict creative and quality standards. Its comprehensive set of photo editing and editing tools let you control and shape every aspect of your images.
Picture Window Pro 8 is a complete rewrite of Picture Window Pro 7. It features non-destructive image editing through a novel interface based on an image tree. It also fully supports large, high-resolution displays and can be used in dual monitor...
</description></item><item><title>Download Flyby11 1.25.485</title><pubDate> Sun, 05 Oct 2025 16:09:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-flyby11-12467.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-flyby11-12467.html
</guid><description>
Flyby11 is a simple patcher that removes annoying restrictions that prevent you from installing Windows 11 (24H2) on unsupported hardware. Do you have an old PC? No TPM, Secure Boot or your processor is not supported? Flyby11 allows you to install Windows 11 24H2. There are no complicated steps. Just run the tool and you'll be running Windows 11 on your outdated machine in no time.
Technical overview
Flyby11 takes advantage of a feature of the Windows 11 setup process that uses the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Flyoobe 1.25.485</title><pubDate> Sun, 05 Oct 2025 16:09:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oobelux-13956.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oobelux-13956.html
</guid><description>
Flyoobe was born out of the frustration many users felt with the Windows 11 setup experience. Whether it was the mandatory online account, the endless "Next, next, next..." screens, or the incomplete configuration options when you finally reached the desktop, the current setup lacked focus on what users really wanted.
Why choose Flyoobe?
	Simplifies the Windows 11 setup process right out of the box.
	Allows easy local account creation without need to hunt for hidden options.
	Includes...
</description></item><item><title>Download Private Windows Script (PrivWindoze) 5.7.6</title><pubDate> Sun, 05 Oct 2025 16:09:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-private-windows-script-12878.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-private-windows-script-12878.html
</guid><description>
Are you concerned about your personal information sent to others? Or do you feel that your Windows settings have many programs that you never use? Private Windows Script (or Privwindoze) provides a comprehensive anti -remote monitoring set designed to enhance your privacy when using Windows operating system.
The main features
	End the positive process. All unnecessary processes are turned off while the scanning program. A small white list is maintained.
	Clean up the positive runonce....
</description></item><item><title>Download Ad Detector &amp;amp; Ad Blocker 1.0.4</title><pubDate> Sun, 05 Oct 2025 15:59:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ad-detector-ad-blocker-14209.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ad-detector-ad-blocker-14209.html
</guid><description>
Are you fed up with mysterious pop-up ads ruining your experience? With Ad Detector &amp;amp; Ad Blocker, you can identify which apps are showing annoying ads and manage them for more efficient, focused use.
Key Features
Popup Ad Detector: This feature helps monitor your device to find out the origin of ads outside the app. When annoying ads appear, Ad Detector will tell you which app is responsible, giving you more control.
Smart Ad Blocker: Limit pop-up and video ads with Ad Blocker....
</description></item></channel></rss>