<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 15:45:27 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 15:45:27 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Duplicate Photo Cleaner 7.23.0.57</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 18:18:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-duplicate-photo-cleaner-3892.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-duplicate-photo-cleaner-3892.html
</guid><description>
Duplicate Photo Cleaner is a powerful application and effective to help you easily find and delete the duplicate image from the hard disk. Using this tool, you will be able to easily manage and arrange the collection of your photos. Duplicate Photo Cleaner is a utility secure and free. The program has a simple interface and intuitive, allowing you to retrieve and delete the duplicate and similar images with just a few mouse clicks. The application can compare even the photo has been...
</description></item><item><title>Download Any Video Downloader Pro 10.0.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 18:18:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-video-downloader-pro-3731.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-video-downloader-pro-3731.html
</guid><description>
Any Video Downloader Pro is software support you can download video HD 720p, 1080p, 2K, 4K and 8K from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion, Vimeo, Metacafe and thousands of video sharing sites, other. It is a tool to speed up multi-threading can speed up your download faster up to 5 times. This helpful program support download at the same time. Any Video Downloader Pro lets you download multiple videos at the same time. Moreover, it allows you to pause and resume downloads if you need more...
</description></item><item><title>Download Office Timeline Plus 13.06.00.00 Expert / Pro / Pro+ Edition</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 18:17:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-timeline-2106.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-timeline-2106.html
</guid><description>
Office Timeline is an add-on very useful and powerful software for Microsoft PowerPoint. With add-ons, you can create PowerPoint documents look more beautiful. With add-ons, you can add the time Line on the project by yourself. Application time for the composition and different segments of the document, your PowerPoint will not only increase the beauty for your work, but also for customers and your manager. The people who created this product is also believe that add-ons this is the only...
</description></item><item><title>Download Kotato All Video Downloader Pro 10.0.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 18:17:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kotato-all-video-downloader-pro-5228.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kotato-all-video-downloader-pro-5228.html
</guid><description>
Kotato All Video Downloader Pro is a Windows application professional to download and convert your favorite videos from the video sharing website. It speeds up your downloads up to 5 times! Kotato All Video Downloader Pro can download videos from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion and hundreds of video sharing sites, other. After downloading, you will be able to play them smoother on your PC or your mobile device, even when you don't have Internet access.
The main features of Kotato All...
</description></item><item><title>Download Robin YouTube Video Downloader Pro 7.0.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 18:16:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-video-downloader-pro-2828.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-video-downloader-pro-2828.html
</guid><description>
YouTube Video Downloader Pro is a Windows application professional to download and convert videos from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion and thousands of video sharing sites, other. It accelerates your download up to 5 times. YouTube Video Downloader Pro allows you to download multiple videos at the same time. It also allows you to pause, resume and cancel a download at any time.
YouTube Video Downloader Pro - Download online videos on social networks
Features of YouTube Video Downloader...
</description></item><item><title>Download BarTender Enterprise 11.8.0.247912</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 18:16:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bartender-enterprise-2462.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bartender-enterprise-2462.html
</guid><description>
BarTender Enterprise is software barcode labeling comprehensive. Create, automate and manage labels, barcodes, rfid tags and more. Barcode software to convert the letters, numbers, and even binary data into a pattern of lines, squares or dots that can be read at high speed by the bar code scanner and converted back to original information.
This is the best program in the world that allows you to print and create labels and barcodes as well as RFID card. The product can operate...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT-DL 12.0.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 18:15:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-dl-5876.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-dl-5876.html
</guid><description>
YT-DL is a small program to download videos from YouTube and other video sites. Our goal is to make the program as simple as its name.
The features of YT-DL
	Download the video from YouTube and other video sites
	Increase download speed up to 400%
	Download multiple videos at the same time
	Pause and continue to download at any time
	Preview video content while downloading
</description></item><item><title>Download Cascadeur 2025.3.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 18:15:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cascadeur-9720.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cascadeur-9720.html
</guid><description>
Cascadeur is a standalone software for 3D keyframe animation of human figures or other characters. Never before has it been so easy and fun to create an animation from scratch or re-edit. Thanks to AI-powered tools, you can perform key poses very quickly, see the physical results immediately, and adjust the secondary movement. All while retaining full control at any point.
Cascadeur uses advanced simulation techniques and algorithms to accurately simulate the movements and interactions...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Geek YTDL Pro 12.0.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 18:14:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-geek-ytdl-pro-9895.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-geek-ytdl-pro-9895.html
</guid><description>
YT Geek YTDL Pro is software that helps users easily download videos from YouTube and hundreds of other video sites. It is very easy to use, just paste the video URL and you can download the video while keeping the original quality. Not only videos on Youtube, users can download any video from social networking sites like Facebook, Vimeo, Myspace video,...
Features of YT Geek YTDL Pro
	Download videos from YouTube and other video sites.
	Increase download speed up to 400%.
	Download...
</description></item><item><title>Download WaveMetrics Igor Pro 10.00.29815</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 18:14:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wavemetrics-igor-pro-9545.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wavemetrics-igor-pro-9545.html
</guid><description>
WaveMetrics Igor Pro is a powerful scientific and engineering graph and data analysis software. It is commonly used in various fields such as physics, chemistry, engineering and biology to analyze and display experimental data. Igor Pro provides a comprehensive environment for data manipulation, mathematical analysis and presentation.
Igor Pro combines powerful tools with an easy-to-use point-and-click interface for casual users and a programming environment for professional users. Igor...
</description></item><item><title>Download CyberLink PhotoDirector Ultra 2026 v17.0.1202.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 17:35:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-photodirector-ultra-129.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-photodirector-ultra-129.html
</guid><description>
Cyberlink PhotoDirector Ultra is known to be photo editing tools and videos with the effect is extremely rich, help you to change the style for the individual images or the videos of his favorite. This software integrated the 3D engine helps to speed up Video processing, which allows accessing the repository effect online and extract the Videos into the movies 3D Bru-ray, 3D AVCHD.
Cyberlink PhotoDirector Ultra to offer users a more professional tool to handle their images, remove...
</description></item><item><title>Download StartAllBack 3.9.19.5344</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 17:35:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-startallback-6857.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-startallback-6857.html
</guid><description>
With the official release of Windows 11, chances are that most of you want to try it out. As the name suggests, StartAllBack is a small, lightweight tool that can help you enjoy the power of the new operating system while keeping the look and feel, especially because main work area, desktop of Windows 7, Windows 10 as taskbars and start menu styles.
StartAllBack is specially designed for Windows 11 and will not work on any older operating systems. If you want to get the start menu back...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Premiere Pro 2025 v25.6.3 Pre-activated</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 17:34:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-premiere-pro-0021-1361.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-premiere-pro-0021-1361.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Premiere Pro is the leading video editing software for film, TV, and the web. Creative tools, integration with other Adobe apps and services, and the power of Adobe Sensei help you turn footage into finished movies and videos in a seamless workflow. It offers high-quality video editing at 4K x 4K resolution and beyond, with 32-bit color, in both RGB and YUV color spaces. Edit audio samples, support for VST audio plug-ins (plug-ins), and 5.1 surround sound tracks. The Premiere Pro...
</description></item><item><title>Download MyLanViewer Enterprise 6.7.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 17:33:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mylanviewer-enterprise-1274.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mylanviewer-enterprise-1274.html
</guid><description>
MyLanViewer is a program for scanning IP address, Netbios and LAN / Network powerful for Windows tool whois and traceroute, remote shutdown and process management Wake On LAN (WOL), scan and monitor wireless networks. This app will help you find all IP addresses, MAC addresses and shared folders of computers on the network wired or wireless (Wi-Fi).
MyLanViewer Enterprise - Scan IP address LAN/Network
The program scans network and displays the computer network in your window, friends...
</description></item><item><title>Download TickTick Premium 6.4.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 17:33:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ticktick-premium-7770.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ticktick-premium-7770.html
</guid><description>
TickTick Premium is a task management application that helps users stay organized, it is very suitable for educators and students with many incentives. TickTick turns your Windows PC device into a flexible, easy-to-use and highly efficient office platform. Join millions of people to capture ideas, organize their lives, and do something creative every day.
Whether there are work related tasks or personal goals, TickTick is here to help you manage all your to-dos. With five different...
</description></item><item><title>Download Social Media Downloader 8.0.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 17:32:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-socialmediaapps-facebook-video-downloader-3742.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-socialmediaapps-facebook-video-downloader-3742.html
</guid><description>
SocialVideo Downloader (formerly SocialMediaApps Facebook Video Downloader) is a Windows application to download and convert your favorite videos from Facebook and hundreds of other video sharing sites. It increases your loading speed by up to 500%, or even more! The application has a simple and intuitive user interface, its main functions and features are quite obvious to anyone. , regardless of prior experience with similar purpose tools.
&amp;nbsp;
SocialVideo Downloader
The main...
</description></item><item><title>Download ExamDiff Pro Master Edition 16.0.1.16</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 17:32:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-examdiff-pro-master-312.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-examdiff-pro-master-312.html
</guid><description>
ExamDiff Pro Master is a tool to compare files and folders intuitive and easy to use, intuitive and easy to use for Windows. ExamDiff Pro Master has unique features distinguishes ExamDiff Pro with the program compare other. ExamDiff Pro Master to help perform reviews of code and share other reports with your colleagues and compare local website with FTP server by plug-ins more integrated.
ExamDiff Pro Master can create a snapshot folder for comparison and storage in the future, compare...
</description></item><item><title>Download VovSoft Batch Audio Converter 1.7</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 17:31:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-batch-audio-converter-12638.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-batch-audio-converter-12638.html
</guid><description>
Vovsoft Batch Audio Converter is the right solution to convert audio files quickly and efficiently. This powerful Windows software allows you to handle batch audio conversions with ease. Just drag and drop your files, select the desired output format and let the software do the rest.
Main features
	Whether you're managing a music library, preparing audio files for a project, or ensuring compatibility across platforms, this program delivers high-quality results with minimal effort...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Saver Pro 10.10.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 17:31:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-saver-6830.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-saver-6830.html
</guid><description>
YT Saver is a software that supports downloading Video, Audio, Playlist from 10,000+ websites, Convert Video to MP4, MOV, AAC, WAV and more. YT Saver is a powerful downloader that allows you to save video and audio for free. The output format of the high-speed converter is high-quality MP4, MP3. Fully compatible with iPhone, iPad, iTunes, iMovie, Android Phone and more.
Supported Input Formats:
	Video: MP4, M4V, 3GP, MPEG, DAT, AVI, ASF, WMV, VOB, MKV, FLV, 3GS, 3G2, F4V, WEBM, TS,...
</description></item><item><title>Download PPTube 10.10.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 17:30:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pptube-12556.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pptube-12556.html
</guid><description>
PPTube Video Downloader allows you to download HD videos easily, from 720p, 1080p, 2K, 4K and 8K. You can save multiple videos at the same time. Just copy multiple video URLs from various websites and paste them into PPTube Downloader, then you can download multiple videos in seconds.
In addition, you can download HD videos from Instagram, TikTok, Facebook, Apple Music, Vimeo, adult websites, etc. and convert them to MP4, MP3, MOV, AAC and more than 20 other output formats. PPTube...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tomabo MP4 Downloader Pro 6.0.5</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 17:30:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tomabo-mp4-downloader-pro-3602.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tomabo-mp4-downloader-pro-3602.html
</guid><description>
Tomabo MP4 Downloader Pro is the app designed exclusively for Windows users to help them download videos from the Internet. In addition, it also increase download speeds by up to 500%, or even more. Tomabo MP4 Downloader Pro, interface design, simple, well-organized, beautifully. Here, users can view a list of videos has download with gravatar, URL, quality, duration and size of them. Software allows download video series at the same time, at the same time, support create a list of clips...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Video Downloader 12.0.8</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 17:29:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-video-downloader-9636.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-video-downloader-9636.html
</guid><description>
YT Video Downloader is software used to easily and quickly download any video or audio content from any website in HD quality using video downloader online. Save videos from almost any website supported by a video downloader on your local hard drive. Media search is a convenient way to do this.
Features of YT Video Downloader
	Download videos from hundreds of video sites.
	Really increase your download speed by up to 500% or even more!
	Download 8K, 5K, 4K Ultra HD, 2K Quad HD, 1080p...
</description></item><item><title>Download NWinfo 1.5.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 16:40:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nwinfo-12590.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nwinfo-12590.html
</guid><description>
NWinfo is a Win32 program that allows you to obtain system and hardware information. It displays essential information about CPU, memory, disk, network, and even system operating details. Because it's portable, you can carry NWinfo on a USB stick and use it on any Windows machine, making it a useful tool for both tech enthusiasts and troubleshooters.
Features of NWinfo
	Get detailed information about SMBIOS, CPUID, S.M.A.R.T., PCI, EDID, etc.
	Supports export in JSON, YAML and LUA...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tixati 3.41.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 16:39:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tixati-2355.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tixati-2355.html
</guid><description>
A Bittorrent free, good have been updated, are designed for operating systems Microsoft Windows and Linux (for the OS Monday, you can download a version from the official website of the developer). The difference between a client and a large number of others is that users are provided a wide opportunity to control the torrent of them, they also write on your program that it consumes less memory than uTorrent and Halite famous.
Tixati - App download torrent
Tixati is also ready to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Vivaldi for macOS 7.7.3851.58</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 16:39:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/mac/download-vivaldi-for-macos-3443.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/mac/download-vivaldi-for-macos-3443.html
</guid><description>
The Vivaldi for MacOS browser does not track users and offers more features than any other modern browser. Managed by Jon von Tetzchner (co-founder of Opera browser), Vivaldi for MacOS is driven by the real needs of today's users and ensures that they have the best tools to browse and get work done.
Vivaldi for MacOS - Modern web browser
Users can adjust Vivaldi to suit their browsing needs them without limiting customization options. Vivaldi takes the browser to the next level with a...
</description></item></channel></rss>