<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 05:34:40 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 05:34:40 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Mozilla Firefox 145.0.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 01:59:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-firefox-quantum-501.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-firefox-quantum-501.html
</guid><description>
Firefox Quantum is a web browser independently provide the tabbed browsing combined with numerous handy features like pop-up blocker, Bookmarks, direct (integrated RSS), password manager, and more. Functionality can be extended with dozens of plugins available for free (extensions).
Firefox Quantum are interface completely new, beautiful, neat, minimalistic and delicate, eats less RAM to 30% compared with the old version and solve the condition consuming capacity
Firefox can import all...
</description></item><item><title>Download Blender 4.5.5</title><pubDate> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 01:58:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blender-3017.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blender-3017.html
</guid><description>
Blender has a tool that new and very powerful, whose name is Ciking provides the ability to display extremely impressive and extremely realistic.
Features of Blender
	- Feature button support complete
	- The ball exactly on the physical side, SSS and translucency
	- Support languages open for coding the ball unique
Blender - The software-rendered optical
Tool output integration provides:
	- The GPU and CPU
	- Preview options view real-time
	- Support light HDR
	- The license...
</description></item><item><title>Download Glary Utilities Pro 6.34.0.38</title><pubDate> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 01:54:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-utilities-pro-76.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-utilities-pro-76.html
</guid><description>
Glary Utilities Pro is a collection of tools and system utilities to fix, speed up, maintain and protect your computer. Glary Utilities Pro allows you to clean junk files, system downloads, as well as the subscriptions are not valid and Internet traces (that support the plug-in more for the 45+ program outside). You can also manage and delete add-ons of the browser, analyze the use of disk and find the file duplicate.
Glary Utilities Pro - optimized system
Key features Glary Utilities...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare PDFelement Pro 12.1.0.3814</title><pubDate> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 01:54:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-pdfelement-pro-105.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-pdfelement-pro-105.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare PDFelement Pro support users to convert PDF to office documents for easier use, modify in every situation. Is one of the software conversion material is rated best today, integrated with many features. We recommend that you should use experience software many useful features this.
Wondershare PDFelement Pro - conversion Fie PDF more features, multi-language
Wondershare PDFelement Pro what?
Convert PDF into Word, Excel, PowerPoint...
• Convert PDF and protected PDF into...
</description></item><item><title>Download Office Installer Plus 1.33</title><pubDate> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 01:53:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-installer-plus-11616.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-installer-plus-11616.html
</guid><description>
Office Installer Plus is the next version of Ratiborus that helps you download, install, update, uninstall, activate office 2024, 2021, 2019, 2016 and it has added an Office activator to the program. submit. Office Installer+ is considered a useful application that helps users install and manage office applications from Microsoft Office easily and quickly. This application is designed to help users save time and effort when installing popular office applications such as Word, Excel,...
</description></item><item><title>Download EaseUS Fixo Technician 4.1.0 Build 20251114</title><pubDate> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 01:53:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-fixo-9814.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-fixo-9814.html
</guid><description>
Video is corrupted or inaccessible after power failure and sudden blackout, whole system crash, update failure, wrong file handling or some other reason? EaseUS Fixo allows you to repair many different video file formats including MOV, MP4, M2TS, MKV, MTS, 3GP, etc. easier no matter how broken it is.
It can intelligently and intelligently repair damaged and damaged photos from computers or other external storage devices such as USB flash drives, memory cards, SD cards, digital cameras...
</description></item><item><title>Download SimpleMind Desktop Pro 2.8.0 Build 6584</title><pubDate> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 01:52:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-simplemind-desktop-pro-1520.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-simplemind-desktop-pro-1520.html
</guid><description>
SimpleMind Desktop Pro is a software tool great for the brainstorm session. You sit with friends and discuss different ideas. Anyone who tells you, you for some reason refuse his idea and put out a different idea. Discuss the challenge. Note the important points. But where? It works on paper, but it has many limitations, for example: you can't attach photos, you can't save the file, sound ideas, you can't easily make the necessary corrections.
SimpleMind Desktop Pro - Draw diagram...
</description></item><item><title>Download Office Installer by Ratiborus 1.33</title><pubDate> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 01:52:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-installer-11545.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-installer-11545.html
</guid><description>
Office Installer is a software program by Ratiborus used to install Microsoft Office on computers or devices. Office is a productivity suite that includes programs like Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Outlook, and more. The installer ensures that all required Microsoft Office files and components are installed, properly configured, and ready for use on the user's computer.
Office Installer allows users to choose which Office applications they want to install, select the installation location,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Irix HDR Pro 2.3.53</title><pubDate> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 01:50:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-irix-hdr-pro-10653.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-irix-hdr-pro-10653.html
</guid><description>
Irix HDR Pro is an AI-powered photo editing application for Windows, it is available on Microsoft Store. This program has tons of professional HDR photo editing features including Sky Replacement, Face Sculpting &amp;amp; body, over 200 presets &amp;amp; AI powered tool' and is a Photo Editor in the category of photo &amp;amp; Graphics. It delivers true-to-life HDR photo editing, providing one-click edits for a full-scale professional editing toolkit.
Features of Irix HDR Pro
	Sky Replacement...
</description></item><item><title>Download Autodesk 3ds Max 2026.3 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 01:50:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-autodesk-3ds-max-0001-1273.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-autodesk-3ds-max-0001-1273.html
</guid><description>
Autodesk 3ds Max 2024 provides a tool powerful, integrated three-dimensional modeling, animation, rendering, and synthesis to work with speed and efficiency. Autodesk 3ds Max provides innovative methods to build and texture models, accumulated data, forming character and creating high quality images. Application for three-dimensional environments, animated, rendered, and combined Autodesk 3ds Max is designed for professionals graphics and computer animation, who developed computer games,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ashampoo Background Remover 2.0.3</title><pubDate> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 01:49:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-background-remover-10243.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-background-remover-10243.html
</guid><description>
Are you tired of having to manually crop people and remove backgrounds during hours-long point-and-click sessions? Download Ashampoo Background Remover and it will help you with the job. It is a program that automatically detects objects and people down to the most delicate details, such as hair, and removes or replaces image backgrounds in just a few clicks.
Ashampoo Background Remover has a user-friendly interface so anyone can use it and achieve great results in no time, whether a...
</description></item><item><title>Download Irix HDR Classic Pro 2.3.53</title><pubDate> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 01:44:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-irix-hdr-classic-pro-10652.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-irix-hdr-classic-pro-10652.html
</guid><description>
Irix HDR Classic Pro is an AI-powered photo editor that delivers true-to-life HDR photo editing, providing one-click edits to the editing toolkit professional at full scale with a highly cognitive user interface (UI).
Main features:
	Sky replacement (SkyXpress): replaces the sky and imports weather. Import custom skies and merge, blend, and integrate with your images for a natural look with AI Edge Detect.
	Presets &amp;amp; Filters: 200+ social media optimized presets with just one tap...
</description></item><item><title>Download reaConverter Pro 8.0.157</title><pubDate> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 01:44:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html
</guid><description>
reaConverter Pro is software image processing feature with batch conversion and image editing periodically becomes simple. eaConverter also provide command line utilities allow you to process images automatically, thus helping you shorten the time for other work.
reaConverter Pro integrated powerful tool of Uber with many great features. It provides advanced solutions to process and adjust images. Management of the conversion process the base image with the latest version of...
</description></item><item><title>Download GiliSoft Audio Recorder Pro 13.8</title><pubDate> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 01:43:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-audio-recorder-pro-855.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-audio-recorder-pro-855.html
</guid><description>
GiliSoft Audio Recorder Pro is software perfect recorder to record audio and microphone of your computer to AAC, AC3, AIFF, AMR, AU, FLAC, M4A, M4B, M4R, MKA, MP2, MP3, OGG, RA, VOC , WAV Files or WMA files on Windows 7/8. Recording the sound that goes through your sound card is not at all a difficult task, but GiliSoft Audio Recorder Pro promises to make everything a lot easier, even for those who do not have computer knowledge advanced.
GiliSoft Audio Recorder Pro - audio recording...
</description></item><item><title>Download Pazu StreamGet All-In-One Video Downloader 2.8.8</title><pubDate> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 01:35:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pazu-streamget-all-in-one-video-downloader-12037.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pazu-streamget-all-in-one-video-downloader-12037.html
</guid><description>
StreamGet All-In-One Video Downloader is the ultimate downloading solution for you. It supports downloading any movies and shows from the most popular streaming sites including Netflix, Prime Video, Disney Plus, Max, Hulu, and Apple TV Plus. The downloader is continuously updated to support more platforms in the future.
Download movies and shows from various streaming platforms to MP4/MKV on your Windows device and enjoy them anywhere you want.
Features of Pazu StreamGet All-In-One...
</description></item><item><title>Download RadioMaximus Pro 2.33.12</title><pubDate> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 01:34:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-radiomaximus-pro-747.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-radiomaximus-pro-747.html
</guid><description>
RadioMaximus Pro is a software support listen to the radio and record thousands of radio stations available on the Internet. When using the RadioMaximus Pro you will experience the ability to hear radio the most wonderful. The quality of radio is very good, there are many channels to choose from and the software continuously updates the news, latest music in the world to take to the listening station.
RadioMaximus Pro - Listen to the radio
Features RadioMaximus Pro
	Listen to and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Glarysoft Malware Hunter Pro 1.208.0.839</title><pubDate> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 01:27:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glarysoft-malware-hunter-pro-235.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glarysoft-malware-hunter-pro-235.html
</guid><description>
Glarysoft Malware Hunter capabilities, comprehensive protection against threats, data protection and privacy, ensure the computer is no longer virus. It allows you against many types of viruses, trojans with the ability to super fast scanning to detect and remove the malware quickly. Glarysoft Malware Hunter has a simple design of the interface, but the pace of new work is the most important problem of this software.
Features Glarysoft Malware Hunter Pro
	Automatically search, detect,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Glary Malware Hunter PRO 1.208.0.839</title><pubDate> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 01:27:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-malware-hunter-pro-77.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-malware-hunter-pro-77.html
</guid><description>
Glary Malware Hunter PRO - detection of file malware on your computer and delete dangerous content, allowing you to run on-demand scan of the area, important system or specific files. As suggested by its name, Malware Hunter is designed to find and remove the files and components potential danger on your computer, keep it out of the virus and the type of threat other.
Glary Malware Hunter PRO - perfect protection of your equipment
Features Glary Malware Hunter PRO
- Scan ultrasound...
</description></item><item><title>Download Filmworkz Phoenix 2025.3.000</title><pubDate> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 01:27:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-digital-vision-phoenix-6617.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-digital-vision-phoenix-6617.html
</guid><description>
The Phoenix Ministry of products provides world-class restoration tools for the most demanding jobs. With the DVO technology that has won many of our awards, Phoenix is designed to produce great results quickly with fewer handicrave interventions. With a familiar time-based interface, artists and storage houses can easily review and edit things according to the context if required. Each product has been designed around a set of features for specific work and budget.
Features of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Robin YouTube Video Downloader Pro 6.18.5</title><pubDate> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 01:26:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-video-downloader-pro-2828.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-video-downloader-pro-2828.html
</guid><description>
YouTube Video Downloader Pro is a Windows application professional to download and convert videos from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion and thousands of video sharing sites, other. It accelerates your download up to 5 times. YouTube Video Downloader Pro allows you to download multiple videos at the same time. It also allows you to pause, resume and cancel a download at any time.
YouTube Video Downloader Pro - Download online videos on social networks
Features of YouTube Video Downloader...
</description></item><item><title>Download Net Monitor for Employees Professional 6.4.12</title><pubDate> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 01:26:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-network-lookout-net-monitor-for-employees-professional-2098.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-network-lookout-net-monitor-for-employees-professional-2098.html
</guid><description>
Network LookOut Net Monitor for Employees Professional is a software platform to help manage user activity, gives the ability to inspect and control computer activities, as well as record activity on the screen as AVI file. Net Monitor for Employees Professional allows access from remote computers. This feature proved particularly useful when you want to see the activity of each user on the computer, or assist them perform the work on the computer with the mouse manipulation or the...
</description></item><item><title>Download MusConv 4.10.432 Lifetime</title><pubDate> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 01:25:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html
</guid><description>
MusConv transfers playlists, albums, followed artists and liked songs across a variety of services – Spotify, Apple Music, Amazon Music, YouTube, YouTube Music, iTunes, Deezer, Tidal, SoundCloud, Pandora and more 125 music services!
Features of MusConv Ultimate
	Transfer playlists, albums, followed artists and liked tracks between over 125 music servicesManage playlists (Delete, Merge, Split, Copy...)
	More than 125 music services supported
	Access DAILY updated music charts on...
</description></item><item><title>Download Monkeys Audio 11.86</title><pubDate> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 01:25:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-monkeys-audio-949.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-monkeys-audio-949.html
</guid><description>
Monkey\'s Audio is software that compresses digital music without loss of quality. Supports high quality WAV files and CD ripping. Monkeys Audio will compress .wav tracks into .ape files to reduce their size without loss of sound quality, decompress .ape, convert files, check file integrity and manage tags.
Unlike traditional methods like MP3 and OGG, which permanently remove quality to save space, Monkey\'s Audio only creates perfect copies with the same sound quality as the originals....
</description></item><item><title>Download Filou NC Gorilla 2025.11.18</title><pubDate> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 01:24:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-filou-nc-gorilla-10211.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-filou-nc-gorilla-10211.html
</guid><description>
Experts estimate that 80-90% of all CNC parts are 2.5D parts. So there is no need to create complex 3D models, but 2.5D CNC codes can be quickly and easily obtained with the CAM module from easy-to-create 2D geometries. With Filou NC Gorilla, you create all your work in one software, from simple and fast 2D design to transfer to CNC machine/control to mill your workpiece.
Features of Filou NC Gorilla
	No complex 3D models
	Many CAM functions
	Create NC code easily
	Editor with 3D...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tomabo MP4 Downloader Pro 5.9.6</title><pubDate> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 01:23:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tomabo-mp4-downloader-pro-3602.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tomabo-mp4-downloader-pro-3602.html
</guid><description>
Tomabo MP4 Downloader Pro is the app designed exclusively for Windows users to help them download videos from the Internet. In addition, it also increase download speeds by up to 500%, or even more. Tomabo MP4 Downloader Pro, interface design, simple, well-organized, beautifully. Here, users can view a list of videos has download with gravatar, URL, quality, duration and size of them. Software allows download video series at the same time, at the same time, support create a list of clips...
</description></item></channel></rss>