<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 23:42:28 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 23:42:28 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download CherryPlayer 3.4.3</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 01:47:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cherryplayer-1499.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cherryplayer-1499.html
</guid><description>
CherryPlayer is a great utility that brings the user a viewing experience Youtube videos Twitch.tv new, high quality and totally free. Download CherryPlayer for your computer, in addition to features watch the video the user can play files on other entertainment.
CherryPlayer - Youtube, Twitch.tv
CherryPlayer for Yoututbe, the playlist is classified according to each category such as sports, entertainment, movies,... allows users to easily search and choose their own favorite video....
</description></item><item><title>Download Windows Memory Cleaner 3.0.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 01:46:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-memory-cleaner-9959.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-memory-cleaner-9959.html
</guid><description>
Sometimes programs don't release the memory they used, making the computer slow, but you don't want to restart the system to get the used memory back. This is where you use Windows Memory Cleaner to clean up memory so you can continue working without having to restart Windows.
How to clean RAM of Windows Memory Cleaner
	Clean Combined Page List Removes blocks from the combined page list. Valid only when site merge is enabled.
	Clean Modified Page List Clears memory from the Modified...
</description></item><item><title>Download Network Notepad 6.1.5</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 01:45:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-network-notepad-1665.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-network-notepad-1665.html
</guid><description>
Network Notepad is a software tool built to help you design network diagrams and save them to analyze and safe guard. Network Notepad is a major rewrite using Microsoft .NET, so it provides compatibility and stability better with the Windows operating system. Network Notepad offers management features can determine a user's, such as telnet and FTP, HTTP and Ping. The objects can be chosen from the provided library and drag into diagram, where they can be linked together with the link type...
</description></item><item><title>Download RapidRAW 1.3.3</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 01:45:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rapidraw-13957.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rapidraw-13957.html
</guid><description>
RapidRAW is a modern, high-performance, open-source RAW photo editor, designed to deliver a fast and clean editing experience with a lightweight footprint (under 30MB). Built with performance and usability in mind, the software is aimed at photographers who want a simple, efficient, and fun workflow without compromising performance.
Key Features
	GPU-accelerated processing: Uses a custom WGSL shader to process all image adjustments on the GPU, allowing for smooth, responsive editing...
</description></item><item><title>Download SkinFiner 5.7.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 03 Aug 2025 16:03:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-skinfiner-6346.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-skinfiner-6346.html
</guid><description>
SkinFiner  is photo editing software designed to free you from tedious manual work in skin retouching. It helps to smooth and strengthen the skin easily and quickly.
Features of SkinFiner
	Smartly smooths skin and removes blemishes while preserving skin texture to give portraits a natural and professional look
	Skin tone adjustment helps you to improve skin tone, change skin color, refine skin light with shadows and highlights, adjust skin brightness and contrast, make skin look...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Fresco 5.7.0.1447 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Sun, 03 Aug 2025 16:03:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-fresco-03en-3453.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-fresco-03en-3453.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Fresco collection collection brush vector and raster largest in the world, plus Live Brush new, revolutionary, to bring the experience to paint and draw completely natural. For the painter, illustrator, artist, cartoon, sketch drawing and any who would like to discover - or rediscover - the joy of painting and drawing.
Adobe Fresco - painting App new of Adobe
Adobe Fresco also allows the artist drawing with pencil drawing vector and raster, combining the features of the app Adobe...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinRAR Portable 7.13</title><pubDate> Sun, 03 Aug 2025 16:02:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winrar-portable-4106.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winrar-portable-4106.html
</guid><description>
WinRAR Portable is the mobile version help you easy to use WinRAR on many different devices without the need to install. WinRAR can backup your data and reduce size of email attachments, decompress RAR, ZIP and other files downloaded from Internet and create new archive in the file format RAR and ZIP. The store put you up in front of the crowd when it comes to compression. By constantly creating documents smaller archives, WinRAR is often faster than the opponent. WinRAR is archive manager...
</description></item><item><title>Download MyLanViewer Enterprise 6.5.4</title><pubDate> Sun, 03 Aug 2025 16:01:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mylanviewer-enterprise-1274.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mylanviewer-enterprise-1274.html
</guid><description>
MyLanViewer is a program for scanning IP address, Netbios and LAN / Network powerful for Windows tool whois and traceroute, remote shutdown and process management Wake On LAN (WOL), scan and monitor wireless networks. This app will help you find all IP addresses, MAC addresses and shared folders of computers on the network wired or wireless (Wi-Fi).
MyLanViewer Enterprise - Scan IP address LAN/Network
The program scans network and displays the computer network in your window, friends...
</description></item><item><title>Download nTopology 5.27.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 03 Aug 2025 16:00:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ntopology-7887.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ntopology-7887.html
</guid><description>
nTopology is software that enables engineers and designers to create any geometry no matter how complex and meet the requirements of high performance products . Our software is used from research through production to create breakthrough products and processes for the aerospace, automotive, medical and consumer industries. Our customers depend on the general design capabilities of the nTopology to get the most out of new hardware, optimize components where performance is important,...
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 7.0.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 03 Aug 2025 15:59:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-11-7760.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-11-7760.html
</guid><description>
TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 is a program that allows users to discover hidden settings in Windows 11. This application is specially designed for Windows 11, groups many registry settings and distribute them from the easy and secure user interface. With TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 you can move the Windows taskbar to the top and resize the taskbar by editing the registry value. With any application that modifies the registry, we recommend that you have a backup copy...
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 7.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 03 Aug 2025 15:59:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-10-7759.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-10-7759.html
</guid><description>
TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 is a utility that allows users to discover hidden settings in Windows 10. This application is specially designed for Windows 10, groups many registry settings and provide them from an easy and secure user interface. With TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 you can move the Windows taskbar to the top and resize the taskbar by editing the registry value. With any application that modifies the registry, we recommend that you have a backup copy to...
</description></item><item><title>Download GLview (OpenGL Extensions Viewer) 7.3.12</title><pubDate> Sun, 03 Aug 2025 15:53:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opengl-extension-viewer-3468.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opengl-extension-viewer-3468.html
</guid><description>
OpenGL Extensions Viewer is a reliable software that displays useful information about the accelerated OpenGL current 3D API and 3D Vulkan new. This program displays the vendor name, the version implemented, the name renderer and extension of the accelerated OpenGL 3D current.
OpenGL Extensions Viewer - Display detailed information graphics
This software utility analyzes the hardware and software of your PC and give you detailed information about the renderers such as DirectX version ,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Alternate Memo 3.460</title><pubDate> Sun, 03 Aug 2025 15:52:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-alternate-memo-5102.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-alternate-memo-5102.html
</guid><description>
Alternate Memo is a simple program to manage the text component of the table temporarily. While running in the background, the program is collection of matching content when changing the clipboard. You can choose the number of items the clipboard will be kept. The items collected can also be saved to a file and open it again for further use. Images can also be managed with the program - but they must be glued by hand.
Program is free software. It requires .NET-framework 2.0 or above...
</description></item><item><title>Download Alternate Math Solver 2.040</title><pubDate> Sun, 03 Aug 2025 15:52:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-alternate-math-solver-125.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-alternate-math-solver-125.html
</guid><description>
Alternate Math Solver is a computer allows you to solve the equation contains the variable X towards this variable. The equations can also include the additional variables.You can enter or paste the equation or use the calculator button is provided and the function common for input. While solving equations, the program will also provide the intermediate steps leading to the solution.
Alternate Math Solver - Solve equations
Alternate Math Solver what?
Solving math equations with the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Alternate Password DB 3.640</title><pubDate> Sun, 03 Aug 2025 15:52:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-alternate-password-db-2723.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-alternate-password-db-2723.html
</guid><description>
Alternate Password DB is a program to securely store the password and your PIN code. With just one password, you have access to the encrypted data (BLOWFISH 256 bit). The password file can be converted into an executable file, can be transferred on a USB memory stick or other removable drive without the need to install this program.
Alternate Password DB - password storage safe
You can also configure the program locks itself after a period of time (main password will be required...
</description></item><item><title>Download Alternate TextBrowser 4.350</title><pubDate> Sun, 03 Aug 2025 15:51:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-alternate-textbrowser-2743.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-alternate-textbrowser-2743.html
</guid><description>
Alternate TextBrowser is a text editor, markup syntax, reliable and useful, useful for users that need to browse through a number of documents TXT and HTML in few minutes. Alternate TextBrowser will syntax highlighting for some programming languages / file types are available and can be configured for the file extensions different. The program includes the memorandum replaced and the Computer replaced as the additional tool. It is free software and requires Net-Framework 2.0 or higher...
</description></item><item><title>Download Neevia Document Converter Pro 7.6.0.272</title><pubDate> Sun, 03 Aug 2025 15:49:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-neevia-document-converter-pro-2047.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-neevia-document-converter-pro-2047.html
</guid><description>
Neevia Document Converter Pro is a software product that dynamically converts Microsoft Office 2003/2007/2010/2013/2016/2019/365, Worderinf, HTML, AutoCAD DWG / DWF, EML, MSG, PostScript and many other document types to PDF, PDF / A, PostScript, JPEG, TIFF, PNG, PCX, BMP. It works in both batch mode via the scan folder or email and in direct mode through a COM component (ActiveX). Document Converter can be configured to recognize text - this is known as OCR - for the converting image and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Xreveal 2.8.3</title><pubDate> Sun, 03 Aug 2025 15:39:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xreveal-7252.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xreveal-7252.html
</guid><description>
Xreveal is an application similar to AnyDVD. This is an interactive research and purpose project. Xreveal does NOT contain any decryption key, it is based solely on the official public AACS specification. You need the decryption key or key database to make it work.
Features of Xreveal
	Remove Blu-ray AACS 1.0 protection
	Remove Blu-ray AACS 2.0 (UHD) protection
	Remove BD+ protection
	Remove BDAV Protection
	Remove DVD CSS protection
	Remove CPRM Protection
	Remove CPPM...
</description></item><item><title>Download Patch My PC 5.3.0.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 03 Aug 2025 15:34:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-patch-my-pc-3748.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-patch-my-pc-3748.html
</guid><description>
Patch My PC is a comprehensive application and reliable will provide the simple solution for managing patch party Tuesday. The category Enterprise SCUP will provide an incentive simple and unique about the updates and the application updates of the Tuesday easy and updated. The update application can be easily installed on your computer in a few minutes, through the function software updates are integrated into The configuration manager center system MS. No additional agent or server...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wing IDE Pro 11.0.3</title><pubDate> Sun, 03 Aug 2025 15:33:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wing-ide-pro-2080.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wing-ide-pro-2080.html
</guid><description>
Wing IDE Pro is a integrated development environment to create applications using the Python language. Wing IDE Pro provides a code editor professional, in which you can use the keyboard shortcuts vi and emacs, auto-complete code re-structure, follow up calls, reminders, contextual. A code debugger graphics to debug locally and remotely, an interface to version control system, a test unit, a search tool flexibility available.
Wing IDE Pro - programming language Python
Features of Wing...
</description></item><item><title>Download TikTok Bot Pro 3.6.4</title><pubDate> Sun, 03 Aug 2025 15:33:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tiktok-bot-pro-11635.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tiktok-bot-pro-11635.html
</guid><description>
TikTok Bot Pro is software designed to automate activities and interactions on TikTok to attract real followers on TikTok. It automates your “likes” and “comments,” finds new followers categorized by similar accounts, and attracts followers who are actually interested in your content.
Here is a list of features you will find in this software:
	GET FOLLOWERS: Export your TikTok followers from those who follow other profiles and/or users based on specific tags.
	AUTO-FOLLOW:...
</description></item><item><title>Download Argente Registry Cleaner 4.0.2.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 03 Aug 2025 15:31:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-argente-registry-cleaner-13814.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-argente-registry-cleaner-13814.html
</guid><description>
Argente Registry Cleaner is a free Windows utility designed to scan, clean and repair invalid or obsolete entries in the Windows Registry, helping to improve system stability and performance. This utility quickly analyzes the entire Registry for errors such as invalid entries left by uninstalled programs, missing keys, broken references, and other junk that can cause system crashes.
Key Features:
	Fast and Thorough Scan: Provides multiple scan modes including Safe (fastest), Normal...
</description></item><item><title>Download SQLite Expert Professional 5.5.38.649</title><pubDate> Sun, 03 Aug 2025 15:30:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sqlite-expert-professional-109.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sqlite-expert-professional-109.html
</guid><description>
SQLite Expert Professional  is a powerful program that allows you to manage and  organize  SQLite databases, visually display you tables and working classes. The user interface is convenient, but due to the lack of Russian support and a lot of customization, not everyone can figure it out, although if you work with the database I think you can understand where and click. In the main window, you can see all your databases, and if you want you can execute the   SQL   using the  SQL ...
</description></item><item><title>Download Rowbyte Plugins Bundle 2025.8</title><pubDate> Sun, 03 Aug 2025 12:58:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rowbyte-plugins-bundle-13994.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rowbyte-plugins-bundle-13994.html
</guid><description>
Rowbyte Plugins Bundle is a collection of Rowbyte's featured plugins designed primarily for motion graphics and visual effects for Adobe After Effects and Premiere Pro users.
Plugins Included:
Aura
	Aura is a sophisticated 3D geometric wave effect plugin for Adobe After Effects.
Buena Depth Cue
	Buena Depth Cue is a collection of powerful plugins that allow AE artists to create depth of field in their projects with creative workflows and simulate Z-depth in a unique way.
Fast...
</description></item><item><title>Download 3D Space TopoLT 17.2.0.11</title><pubDate> Sun, 03 Aug 2025 12:51:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-3d-space-topolt-13993.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-3d-space-topolt-13993.html
</guid><description>
3D Space TopoLT is a dedicated software tool designed to create and manage topographic and cadastral maps in digital format in CAD environments such as AutoCAD, BricsCAD, ZWCAD and GstarCAD. The software provides comprehensive 2D and 3D functions, useful for professionals designing topographic or cadastral projects.
Features of 3D Space TopoLT
	Draw points directly from coordinate files and total stations, with the ability to transfer data bidirectionally between drawings and...
</description></item></channel></rss>