<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 11:35:11 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 11:35:11 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download SpaceSniffer 2.0.5.18</title><pubDate> Wed, 15 Oct 2025 13:08:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-spacesniffer-14130.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-spacesniffer-14130.html
</guid><description>
SpaceSniffer is a free and portable tool that allows you to understand how folders and files are structured on your drive. Using the intuitive Treemap layout, you can instantly see where large folders and files are located on your device. The Treemap concept was invented by Professor Ben Shneiderman, who kindly gave permission to use his concept in this tool.
Start the scan and see the overall situation. The larger the elements in the view, the larger the folders and files on your...
</description></item><item><title>Download Hasleo Backup Suite 5.4.2.5</title><pubDate> Wed, 15 Oct 2025 13:07:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hasleo-backup-suite-6588.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hasleo-backup-suite-6588.html
</guid><description>
Hasleo Backup Suite is a free backup and free Windows recovery, integration of backup features, recovery, and replication, it is designed for Windows operating system users and can be used on both Windows PC and Windows Server. The backup and recovery feature of Hasleo Backup Suite can help you backup and restore your Windows, disk and partition operating system to protect your Windows operating system and your personal data. The replication feature of Hasleo Backup Suite can help you...
</description></item><item><title>Download AI Video Upscaler Pro 1.2.6</title><pubDate> Wed, 15 Oct 2025 13:05:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ai-video-upscaler-pro-14184.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ai-video-upscaler-pro-14184.html
</guid><description>
Break new life into your old or low-resolution videos with AI Video Upscaler Pro. This powerful and private desktop application uses advanced artificial intelligence to enhance and upscale your video files, bringing incredible new levels of detail and clarity. Designed with privacy at its core, AI Video Upscaler Pro works 100% offline after a one-time setup. Your video files will never be uploaded to the cloud or shared with anyone, ensuring your content stays under your control on your...
</description></item><item><title>Download Quick Clipboard Editor 3.1.1.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 15 Oct 2025 13:04:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quick-clipboard-editor-9421.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quick-clipboard-editor-9421.html
</guid><description>
Quick Clipboard Editor is free software that provides direct access to the text stored in your clipboard, allowing you to quickly modify it to meet your needs. meet your needs before pasting the text into the app you want. It allows you to quickly retrieve previous clips from your clipboard history, find and replace specific words or phrases, insert new content into each line, trim unwanted pieces of text, keep or remove lines or characters based on different criteria, arrange text using...
</description></item><item><title>Download O&amp;amp;O ShutUp10++ 2.0.1009</title><pubDate> Wed, 15 Oct 2025 13:04:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-shutup10-1535.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-shutup10-1535.html
</guid><description>
O&amp;amp;O ShutUp10 is software that puts you in full control of today's latest Windows 10 and Windows 11 features, it's up to you to decide what information to pass on Windows 10 or Windows 11. Using a simple user interface, this program disables the parts of Windows 10 and Windows 11 that don't want to receive and send your data. The program is completely free and requires no installation, and once downloaded, you can run it immediately. The program does not install adware and spam software...
</description></item><item><title>Download iTubeGo YouTube Downloader 10.9.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 15 Oct 2025 13:03:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-itubego-youtube-downloader-3681.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-itubego-youtube-downloader-3681.html
</guid><description>
iTubeGo YouTube Downloader  is the best way to download live video from 1000+ streaming sites. iTubeGo YouTube Downloader is a powerful download tool that allows you to save video and audio for free. The output format of high speed converter is high quality MP4, MP3. Fully compatible with iPhone, iPad, iTunes, iMovie, Android Phone and more.
iTubeGo YouTube Downloader - Solution for downloading high quality Youtube video 
Features of iTubeGo YouTube Downloader
	Download videos from...
</description></item><item><title>Download CudaText 1.229.0.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 15 Oct 2025 13:02:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cudatext-2914.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cudatext-2914.html
</guid><description>
CudaText is a text editor and code multi-platform advanced is written in Lazarus, have the ability to support a variety of programming languages and coding. The program comes with highlighted syntax for C ++, JavaScript, CSS, Python, C, Java, HTML, PHP, XML and many more. The program supports more than 160 lexers from SynWrite.
CudaText includes a set of features and powerful functions, such as tree structure code, Multi select, Plugins for the Python language, user interface, tabbed...
</description></item><item><title>Download PanFone WhatsApp Transfer 2.4.8</title><pubDate> Wed, 15 Oct 2025 13:00:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-panfone-whatsapp-transfer-5580.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-panfone-whatsapp-transfer-5580.html
</guid><description>
PanFone WhatsApp Transfer is the best solution to backup, restore and transfer WhatsApp iOS / Android messages as well as export WhatsApp messages to HTML and CSV files. This PanFone WhatsApp Transfer easily and securely transferred iOS to Android WhatsApp can be a useful tool to help you backup and restore WhatsApp data. It will not overwrite or delete previous backups. You can restore WhatsApp backups to your phone any time you want.
Seamlessly transfer all WhatsApp chat history,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Photo Supreme 2025.3.3.8117</title><pubDate> Wed, 15 Oct 2025 13:00:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photo-supreme-430.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photo-supreme-430.html
</guid><description>
Photo Supreme is a software product management professional pictures of idimager. With Photo Supreme you can arrange, manage back stock photo archive of yourself and share them with you here and relatives easily via Email or Facebook. Photo Supreme provides users method to sort images effective, logical, as well as edit and share your photos with friends and relatives in the family. Especially the Photo Supreme allows to work with multiple image formats and support mounting support,...
</description></item><item><title>Download BatteryCare 0.9.40.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 15 Oct 2025 12:59:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-batterycare-5799.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-batterycare-5799.html
</guid><description>
BatteryCare is a software created to optimize the use and battery performance of the modern laptop computer, monitor the exhaust cycle of the battery and help increase the ability to autonomy and improve the life of the battery.
The features of BatteryCare
	The advanced algorithm records the exact time a total discharge cycle is done.
	It calculators the rest of the statistics in the laptop that does not support the battery's remaining time information and only lists the percentage of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Grub2Win 3.0.0.6</title><pubDate> Wed, 15 Oct 2025 12:58:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-grub2win-3177.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-grub2win-3177.html
</guid><description>
Grub2Win is a open source program to dual boot Windows and Linux safely. Grub2Win boot code the GNU Grub version 2.04. Everything is in a folder of 20 MB on Windows drive C: On the EFI system, a few small modules to be installed into the EFI partition of your.
Grub2Win - Boot system, Windows
Using GUI Windows and simple instructions you can install Grub2Win quickly and safely. Notice the boot time and help can be displayed in multiple languages. After installing interface, it's easy to...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Saver Pro 10.9.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 15 Oct 2025 12:58:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-saver-6830.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-saver-6830.html
</guid><description>
YT Saver is a software that supports downloading Video, Audio, Playlist from 10,000+ websites, Convert Video to MP4, MOV, AAC, WAV and more. YT Saver is a powerful downloader that allows you to save video and audio for free. The output format of the high-speed converter is high-quality MP4, MP3. Fully compatible with iPhone, iPad, iTunes, iMovie, Android Phone and more.
Supported Input Formats:
	Video: MP4, M4V, 3GP, MPEG, DAT, AVI, ASF, WMV, VOB, MKV, FLV, 3GS, 3G2, F4V, WEBM, TS,...
</description></item><item><title>Download CoolUtils Total Audio Converter 6.1.0.286</title><pubDate> Wed, 15 Oct 2025 12:57:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-total-audio-converter-807.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-total-audio-converter-807.html
</guid><description>
CoolUtils Total Audio Converter is the convert audio files of various extensions, various as MP3, WAV, RMVB, MIDI, AMR, FLAC and M4A. Total Audio Converter is a program interface is quite easy and convenient combined control panel in which you can select the installation size and source.
Total Audio Converter supports batch conversion. This is a very good tool for those who love music. The program supports ID3 tags and CUE, convert the audio clips that don't create WAV files intermediate...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cerberus FTP Server Enterprise 2025.3</title><pubDate> Wed, 15 Oct 2025 12:56:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cerberus-ftp-server-enterprise-317.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cerberus-ftp-server-enterprise-317.html
</guid><description>
Cerberus FTP Server Enterprise is software that provides encrypted SSL / TLS industrial safety and server performance FTP most powerful. The special point is Cerberus FTP Server Enterprise uses very little CPU and memory, Cerberus has friendly interface, users can easily hidden or accessed from the system tray.
Server can listen to connections on multiple interfaces (PC users), integrated with the user database Windows NT or Active Directory, run as NT service, resume transfer not...
</description></item><item><title>Download Vovsoft Auto Change Screensavers 2.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 15 Oct 2025 12:56:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-auto-change-screensavers-2784.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-auto-change-screensavers-2784.html
</guid><description>
Vovsoft Auto Change Screensavers is a tool to the desktop mini will change the screen saver of you. App Auto Change Screensavers allows you to automatically change the screen saver of his. Have you installed more screensavers interesting? Sometimes people spend a lot of time trying to choose which one to make default. Manager this screensaver solves that problem.
Now you can have all your savers run on your screen and this does not need to adjust the Windows settings every time you want...
</description></item><item><title>Download O&amp;amp;O Defrag Pro 30.0.1063</title><pubDate> Wed, 15 Oct 2025 12:55:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-o-o-defrag-pro-149.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-o-o-defrag-pro-149.html
</guid><description>
O&amp;amp;O Defrag Pro is the professional software has the ability to defragment the hard disk and can work with the file system different from FAT / 32 to NTFS / 5, and support for the different arrays Volume / Stripe Sets. You can also set the schedule which O &amp;amp; O Defrag will be booted and perform a number of manipulation certain. Regular defragmentation of the disk partition optimized performance of your computer. The user interface is very easy to use. It has a ribbon bar displays all...
</description></item><item><title>Download Psiphon 186.20251014</title><pubDate> Wed, 15 Oct 2025 12:55:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-psiphon-7347.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-psiphon-7347.html
</guid><description>
Psiphon is a firewall bypass tool by Psiphon Inc. Uses VPN, SSH and HTTP Proxy technology to give you uncensored access to Internet content. Your Psiphon app automatically learns about new hotspots to maximize your chances of bypassing censorship.
The way the software works is that Psiphon constantly changes the proxy, so the user's IP address is also constantly changing, the server will not detect the user's real address, so you can feel free. roof. access to websites and software...
</description></item><item><title>Download O&amp;amp;O Defrag Server 30.0.1063</title><pubDate> Wed, 15 Oct 2025 12:54:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-defrag-server-2521.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-defrag-server-2521.html
</guid><description>
O&amp;amp;O Defrag Server professional software has the ability to defragment the hard disk and can work with the file system different from FAT / 32 to NTFS / 5, and support for the different arrays Volume / Stripe Sets. You can also set the schedule which O &amp;amp; O Defrag will be booted and perform a number of manipulation certain. Regular defragmentation of the disk partition optimized performance of your computer. The user interface is very easy to use. It has a ribbon bar displays all the...
</description></item><item><title>Download iDownerGo 10.9.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 15 Oct 2025 12:54:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idownergo-12439.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idownergo-12439.html
</guid><description>
iDownerGo is the best tool that allows users to download videos, music and playlists from more than 10,000 streaming sites. It can easily convert videos to MP4, MOV, MKV, 3GP, AAC, WAV, FLAC and other formats on PC and Mac. With this amazing program, users can enjoy their favorite media content without restrictions.
iDownerGo Features
	Download any video up to 8K resolution
	Download 1080p videos online from over 10,000 popular streaming sites easily.
	Save any video in various...
</description></item><item><title>Download Supremo 4.11.6.2928</title><pubDate> Wed, 15 Oct 2025 12:54:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-supremo-2334.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-supremo-2334.html
</guid><description>
Supremo is a powerful solution, simple and full for control the desktop remotely. It allows you to control a remote PC or host a meeting in seconds. Interface Supremo with USilio control Panel , computer management.
Supremo - control your computer remotely
Features of Supremo
	Supremo include a file single executable very light and does not require installation. It's fast and author to the test.
	Supremo encrypting data stream with AES-256 algorithm and interface with USilio control...
</description></item><item><title>Download MailWasher Pro 7.15.45</title><pubDate> Wed, 15 Oct 2025 12:53:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-firetrust-mailwasher-pro-825.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-firetrust-mailwasher-pro-825.html
</guid><description>
MailWasher Pro software is ready to filter all of your email accounts and blocked, remove the spam from the list of email. MailWasher allows you to preview all your email before to your computer or your mobile device, you allows you to read all your email securely, and instantly delete any unwanted emails or suspicious. Email good rest of you is download at PC or mobile devices, to help you not get any virus, spam or any email.
Firetrust MailWasher Pro - Blocker remove spam
The...
</description></item><item><title>Download ChrisPC Free VPN Connection 4.25.1014</title><pubDate> Wed, 15 Oct 2025 12:52:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-free-vpn-connection-2887.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-free-vpn-connection-2887.html
</guid><description>
ChrisPC Free VPN Connection software allows you to create VPN connection (virtual private network) to the server for free from the United States, Germany, Canada, France, Germany, Russia, Singapore, the Netherlands. This will help you to unblock your favorite sites to watch free TV and on-demand television when living abroad, travelling, on business or vacation. In addition, here is the solution to overcome the limited area for the popular websites: Google, YouTube, Facebook, Instagram,...
</description></item><item><title>Download CoolUtils PDF Combine Pro 8.1.0.65</title><pubDate> Wed, 15 Oct 2025 12:51:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-pdf-combine-pro-580.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-pdf-combine-pro-580.html
</guid><description>
CoolUtils PDF Combine Pro  is software that helps you combine  PDF, DOC, TXT, DOCX, HTML, XLS, images  h (TIFF, JPEG, PNG) and  email  as a  PDF  file. With PDF Combine Pro it is easier than ever to combine documents into one PDF file. Now you don't have to use some programs and converters to get a PDF. Everything for PDF Combine Pro to do for you.
Office, fax, email files - get combined PDF in seconds for personal use, commercial needs, electronic discovery, or manufacturing.  PDF...
</description></item><item><title>Download PPTube 10.9.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 15 Oct 2025 12:51:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pptube-12556.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pptube-12556.html
</guid><description>
PPTube Video Downloader allows you to download HD videos easily, from 720p, 1080p, 2K, 4K and 8K. You can save multiple videos at the same time. Just copy multiple video URLs from various websites and paste them into PPTube Downloader, then you can download multiple videos in seconds.
In addition, you can download HD videos from Instagram, TikTok, Facebook, Apple Music, Vimeo, adult websites, etc. and convert them to MP4, MP3, MOV, AAC and more than 20 other output formats. PPTube...
</description></item><item><title>Download AVG Clear 25.10.10528</title><pubDate> Wed, 15 Oct 2025 12:50:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avg-clear-4945.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avg-clear-4945.html
</guid><description>
AVG Clear is free program help completely erase everything from installing AVG current your including the registry entries, file, settings, files, users, etc. AVG Clear is provided by AVG and is the last measure to use if you encounter a problem when deleting AVG current whether it is error repair, reinstall, or delete altogether.
Please note that all user settings AVG will be removed after the uninstall process is complete. The items should be deleted to include content from Virus...
</description></item></channel></rss>