<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:54:39 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:54:39 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download TidyWindow 3.8.8</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 01:50:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tidywindow-14454.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tidywindow-14454.html
</guid><description>
TidyWindow is a Windows desktop assistant that automates developer PC setup, cleanup, diagnostics, software package installation, registry tweaking, and driver updates—powered by a WPF interface and robust PowerShell 7 automation capabilities in the background.
Key Features
	Essentials Repair Center (docs/essentials.md): Queues selected automation tasks Filter for network, Defender, printing, and Windows Update issues. Each task supports preview run, sequential execution, restore...
</description></item><item><title>Download anyPDF 1.5.2.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 01:49:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anypdf-11943.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anypdf-11943.html
</guid><description>
AnyPDF is an integrated PDF viewer and manager as it facilitates viewing and editing of PDF files in a user-friendly manner where users can merge multiple documents, protect and compress important data, etc. This program aims to be a more or less general tool for PDF workflow. That said, it doesn't necessarily specialize in anything specific as it has a number of uses related to working with PDF files.
Features of anyPDF
	User-friendly user interface
	Convert from JPG to...
</description></item><item><title>Download BlueStacks 5.22.150.1014</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 01:48:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bluestacks-133.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bluestacks-133.html
</guid><description>
BlueStacks allows you to run many Android applications in a full-screen environment on your PC. BlueStacks is the best Android emulator application today, used by many people thanks to its perfect gaming support ability. BlueStacks allows you to play most of today's Android games with multitasking features, can run multiple games in parallel on multiple screens, giving gamers an interesting experience.
In addition to emulator software, game cheat software, such as Cheat Engine, is also of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Premiere Pro 2025 v25.6.4 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 01:44:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-premiere-pro-0022-1361.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-premiere-pro-0022-1361.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Premiere Pro is the leading video editing software for film, TV, and the web. Creative tools, integration with other Adobe apps and services, and the power of Adobe Sensei help you turn footage into finished movies and videos in a seamless workflow. It offers high-quality video editing at 4K x 4K resolution and beyond, with 32-bit color, in both RGB and YUV color spaces. Edit audio samples, support for VST audio plug-ins (plug-ins), and 5.1 surround sound tracks. The Premiere Pro...
</description></item><item><title>Download AITextTune 1.6.3.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 01:44:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aitexttune-12973.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aitexttune-12973.html
</guid><description>
AITextTune is an AI-powered tool designed to enhance and refine text content. It offers features such as improving clarity and coherence, generating summaries, and translating text into multiple languages. Users can easily adjust their writing style from formal to creative. This tool is very flexible and can be used on many different software and platforms.
AITextTune Features
	WRITE PERFECTLY: Improve the clarity and coherence of your writing! Create summaries and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Media Encoder 2025 v25.6.4 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 01:43:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-0010-adobe-media-encoder-1360.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-0010-adobe-media-encoder-1360.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Media Encoder 2024 is a professional audio and video converter that allows you to encode audio and video files into various distribution formats for applications different uses and audiences. Such video and audio formats are characterized by a high degree of compression. By downloading this program on taiwebs.com, you can export videos in formats supported by various devices, from DVD players and websites to mobile phones, portable media players and High Definition and High...
</description></item><item><title>Download SweetScape 010 Editor 16.0.3</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 01:42:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sweetscape-010-editor-1492.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sweetscape-010-editor-1492.html
</guid><description>
SweetScape 010 Editor is a text editor and hex editor professional is designed to quickly and easily edit any file or drive on your computer. Combine the easy to use interface with a complete set of editing tools, 010 Editor is a valuable tool for anyone working with text files or binary files. One of the most powerful features of 010 Editor is the ability to analyze virtually any file binary how to change binary form.
Instead of browsing through a bunch of bytes hex as the hex editor...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cash Register Pro 4.1.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 01:42:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cash-register-pro-3853.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cash-register-pro-3853.html
</guid><description>
Cash Register Pro a software cash register full of features and creative for a Windows computer, it will help you to better handle all the activities of the computer money. The application comes with the user interface logical and user friendly allows you to work quickly and do not commit the common error. The program can be used on a number of computers and offers a wide range of authorization secure and reliable. Cash Register Pro will help you track products and goods remain...
</description></item><item><title>Download Perfectly Clear WorkBench 5.0.0.3037</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 00:10:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfectly-clear-workbench-6892.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfectly-clear-workbench-6892.html
</guid><description>
Perfectly Clear Workbench is an application that uses image editing libraries Perfectly Clear by Athentech and is provided to demonstrate the capabilities of the Perfectly Clear processing libraries, which recognize faces and allow quick export of processing settings for use.
One of the key features in Workbench is the ability to "export to API" when saving a Preset. This allows you to make image edits in Workbench and adjust the settings to suit your editing style and needs. You can...
</description></item><item><title>Download XnViewMP 1.9.10</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 00:09:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xnview-mp-1074.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xnview-mp-1074.html
</guid><description>
XnViewMP "XnView MP" is the enhanced version of XnView Classic. This is the view and convert images multi-platform powerful, compatible with more than 500 image formats, different today. XnView MP easily export images to about 70 file format is different. Similar to XnConvert, XnView MP also features integrated switch at the same time batch file to help you process photos faster. XnView is another version of the photo viewer but with the ability to support formats more limited.
XnView...
</description></item><item><title>Download ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro 15.26.0115</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 00:09:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-videotube-downloader-pro-1276.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-videotube-downloader-pro-1276.html
</guid><description>
ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro is the professional version support download videos and playlists from YouTube, videos from Dailymotion, BBC iPlayer, ITV Player, ABC,  FOX,CBS.com Vimeo, Prosieben, Metacafe, Blip.tv CBC.ca many more video sites. After the video is downloaded, you can convert them to the formats compatible with iPad, iPhone, iPod, MPEG-4, H. 264, MP3, AC3.
ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro - Download videos on Youtube
This is one of the software download the most...
</description></item><item><title>Download Iperius Backup Full 8.7.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 00:08:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iperius-backup-621.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iperius-backup-621.html
</guid><description>
Iperius Backup software supports backup and restore of data can be stored on a cloud service, and AES 256-bit. This is the perfect software to get the advantages of the many services that cloud storage is provided by the famous supplier like Google or Microsoft. With a single application, you will can easily save your files externally on Google Drive, Dropbox or Microsoft SkyDrive.
Iperius Backup uses the technology images Windows drive most advanced, allows to copy entire operating...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Acrobat Pro DC 2025.001.21078 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 00:07:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-001en-adobe-acrobat-pro-458.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-001en-adobe-acrobat-pro-458.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Acrobat Pro DC is a comprehensive software that helps you create and edit the PDF&amp;nbsp;document, or create form, sign, protect PDF, connect, split PDF, export PDF to various formats. The Acrobat Pro DC is the latest version of Adobe with improvements in the interface with the polished ribbon bar and the ability to create and handle pdf files as well as its male versions.
The highlight of the Acrobat Pro DC is probably the ability to connect, store documents on the cloud, you can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wise Registry Cleaner Pro 11.3.1.733</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 00:06:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wise-registry-cleaner-pro-468.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wise-registry-cleaner-pro-468.html
</guid><description>
Wise Registry Cleaner Pro software is dọp registry cleaner, defragment the hard drive to help optimize system and speed up computer. The advantage is, before cleanup registry software will allow users to create a backup safety. Therefore the cleanup, speed up pc back up safe and does not encounter the bug, what I wanted.
Wise Registry Cleaner is used as a tool to manage the program and lets you search for and delete obsolete files, folders, register, temporary hot key combination and...
</description></item><item><title>Download LDPlayer 9.1.98.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 00:06:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ldplayer-2331.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ldplayer-2331.html
</guid><description>
LDPlayer is an Android emulator that allows users to play games and run applications on Windows computers. LDPlayer supports heavy gaming, running chat applications, editing photos, videos, and many other Android applications. LDPlayer is compatible with Android 5.1 and above, supporting multitasking for an experience that is not inferior to that of using on Mobile.
Installation is a simple and quick process that does not require any special attention from you, there are more. settings,...
</description></item><item><title>Download RyTuneX 1.6.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 00:05:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rytunex-11852.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rytunex-11852.html
</guid><description>
RyTuneX is an advanced optimizer built on the WinUI 3 framework, designed to enhance the performance of Windows devices. Designed for Windows 10 and 11, RyTuneX empowers users to easily remove stubborn pre-installed apps and optimize system resources.
RyTuneX Features
	Selectively remove apps: Easily uninstall unwanted pre-installed apps.
	Background services management: Streamline your system by disabling unnecessary services.
	Privacy enhancements: Strengthen your privacy by...
</description></item><item><title>Download Navicat Premium 17.3.8 Enterprise</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 00:05:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-navicat-premium-87.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-navicat-premium-87.html
</guid><description>
Navicat Premium is a developer tool database allows you to connect simultaneously with the MySQL database, MariaDB, SQL Server, Oracle, PostgreSQL and SQLite from a single application. Navicat Premium is compatible with the database cloud such as Amazon RDS, Amazon Aurora, Amazon Redshift, SQL Azure, Oracle Cloud and Google Cloud. You can quickly and easily build, manage and maintain database of your.
Features, characteristics, Navicat Premium:
Move data seamlessly
Data transfer, data...
</description></item><item><title>Download Secure Delete Professional 2026 v216</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 00:04:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secure-delete-professional-4991.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secure-delete-professional-4991.html
</guid><description>
Secure Delete Professional is very simple tool but very effective to delete files and folders in a secure way. After using this tool, the files and folders selected will not be available for recovery. We have attached a number of security options so you can choose the security level that you need (this reflects the processing speed).
You can use this application in 3 ways. First, you can drag and drop the file or folder that you want to delete securely to the main window of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download KMPlayer (KMP) 2025.12.22.13 x64 / 4.2.3.31 x86</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 00:03:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kmplayer-kmp-902.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kmplayer-kmp-902.html
</guid><description>
KMPlayer (KMP) is software watch movies listen to music multi-function for video enthusiasts. KMPlayer development is many types of the format different. KMPlayer has improved on sound quality, images when listening to music and watching movies, the playback speed of video is faster, more codec player is added to the software video decoder is optimized.
KMPlayer also supports a variety of audio formats and video and offers a the interface can be customized with the preview coverflow and...
</description></item><item><title>Download CalendarTask (formerly DesktopCal) 3.26.263.8409</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 00:03:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopcal-1831.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopcal-1831.html
</guid><description>
CalendarTask (formerly DesktopCal) is a simple desktop calendar that blends into your desktop without blocking access to your desktop icons. You can double-click on a date to quickly add notes and also jump to specific dates in the past or future.
CalendarTask - Computer calendar
CalendarTask can use your current wallpaper or loop through images from your folder and update your desktop every few minutes. The program helps you make appointments, make plans... Not only that, the Screen...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDF Annotator 10.0.0.1005</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 00:02:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-annotator-178.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-annotator-178.html
</guid><description>
PDF Annotator software user open any PDF file and add annotations, using the mouse or pen Tablet PC, directly on the Page of the PDF file. PDF Annotator allows users to perform editing operations on PDF files such as: add notes, edit signature, highlight, insert images or text... From the this useful tool, you can completely modify PDF files as you like in order to meet the different work.
PDF Annotator
With the PDF Annotator the document has annotations can then be saved directly back...
</description></item><item><title>Download Altium Designer Agile 26.2.0 Build 28</title><pubDate> Thu, 15 Jan 2026 23:56:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-altium-designer-agile-14320.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-altium-designer-agile-14320.html
</guid><description>
Explore how Altium Agile helps organizations grow by seamlessly connecting users and engineering systems with integrations with Jira, PLM (Enterprise), and access to SiliconExpert and Z2Data components and supply chain data. Altium Agile is Altium's platform-based approach to agile hardware development, providing integrated tools and workflows for managing the electronics product lifecycle with collaboration, governance, and traceability.
	Supply chain intelligence improves decision...
</description></item><item><title>Download Opera GX (Gaming Browser) 126.0.5750.36</title><pubDate> Thu, 15 Jan 2026 23:56:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-gx-3170.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-gx-3170.html
</guid><description>
Opera GX is a special version of the Opera browser is built to complement gamers avid. Browser this game comes with the unique features to help users make maximum use of both the game and their browser. Opera GX is built specifically to support the game. This browser includes the unique features to help users have the best experience when gaming and surfing the web.
Opera GX - special browser for gamers
GX Control allows you to set a limit on the level of use RAM, CPU and network where...
</description></item><item><title>Download Opera One 126.0.5750.37</title><pubDate> Thu, 15 Jan 2026 23:55:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-972.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-972.html
</guid><description>
Opera is a fast, safe, configurable and compliant intranet web browser, which includes both the reader and the application. The Opera browser supports web browsing, listening to music, watching high speed movies, you can open many tabs on the Opera without affecting your browsing speed. Opera now supports almost all devices and operating systems such as windows, IOS, Android, linux, MacOS ...
Opera is a beautiful interface and many interesting features, operating on both PCs and mobile,...
</description></item><item><title>Download FontViewOK 9.21</title><pubDate> Thu, 15 Jan 2026 23:55:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fontviewok-1337.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fontviewok-1337.html
</guid><description>
FontViewOK is a simple tool that helps show your location and can install any fonts in list of it. To view (display) the font is not installed on Windows, you can also thanks to the help of Font View OK. Launch FontViewOK on the program screen, click the select folder Button From. Then just select the category to which the display font.
FontViewOK - Support install fonts
Many users install available font on Windows operating system of them and want tocompare the font visually on...
</description></item></channel></rss>