<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:54:06 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:54:06 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Microsoft .NET Desktop Runtime 10.0.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:47:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-net-desktop-runtime-5748.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-net-desktop-runtime-5748.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft .NET Desktop Runtime allows you to run existing Windows desktop applications. This release includes the .NET Runtime, which requires no separate installation. The Microsoft .NET Desktop Runtime redistributable package installs the .NET Desktop Runtime and related files needed to run many applications that use this programming language.
This is Microsoft's comprehensive and consistent programming model for building applications with stunningly intuitive user experiences,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cloudflare WARP 2025.10.186.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:46:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cloudflare-warp-12256.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cloudflare-warp-12256.html
</guid><description>
Cloudflare WARP is a free application developed by Cloudflare that provides a secure and private connection to the internet. The app acts as a Virtual Private Network (VPN) service, encrypting users' internet traffic and routing it through Flare's global network. Cloudflare Zero Trust replaces legacy security perimeters with Cloudflare's global network, making the Internet faster and more secure for teams around the world. Consult our reference architecture to learn how to evolve your...
</description></item><item><title>Download TidyWindow 3.8.6</title><pubDate> Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:46:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tidywindow-14454.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tidywindow-14454.html
</guid><description>
TidyWindow is a Windows desktop assistant that automates developer PC setup, cleanup, diagnostics, software package installation, registry tweaking, and driver updates—powered by a WPF interface and robust PowerShell 7 automation capabilities in the background.
Key Features
	Essentials Repair Center (docs/essentials.md): Queues selected automation tasks Filter for network, Defender, printing, and Windows Update issues. Each task supports preview run, sequential execution, restore...
</description></item><item><title>Download EditPlus 6.1 Build 835</title><pubDate> Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:44:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-editplus-338.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-editplus-338.html
</guid><description>
EditPlus is editor text, editor, HTML and editor program for Windows. EditPlus works as a text editor as well as editor, PHP editor, HTML, editor, Java viewer and Hex. It supports syntax highlighting for many languages, such as HTML, CSS, Java, PHP, C / C ++, Perl, and Python, and can act as a web browser to preview the HTML page. EditPlus also provides some other useful features, such as auto completion, code folding, spell checking, search and replace, keyboard shortcuts, custom and HTML...
</description></item><item><title>Download FFmpeg Batch AV Converter 3.2.7 + Portable</title><pubDate> Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:43:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ffmpeg-batch-av-converter-10540.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ffmpeg-batch-av-converter-10540.html
</guid><description>
FFmpeg Batch AV Converter is an ffmepg gui, a user interface for Windows ffmpeg users and for Linux via Wine, allowing to use the full potential of the ffmpeg command line only with a few mouse clicks in a convenient GUI. Among other things, you can drag and drop, view progress information, change encoding priority, pause and resume, and set auto shutdown. It's good for seasoned ffmpeg users as well as beginners.
It offers unlimited batch encoding of one or more files for almost any...
</description></item><item><title>Download Directory List and Print Pro 4.39</title><pubDate> Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:43:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-list-and-print-pro-481.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-list-and-print-pro-481.html
</guid><description>
Directory List and Print Pro is software that provides function lists and support printing content, quick, simple. In addition, the file list can be formatted, filtered, saved to several file formats and also further processed (delete / copy / move files). By copying to the clipboard the list can be exported into other programs or opened directly in Word and Excel.
The features Directory List and Print basic
	Choose the folders listed in a tree structure.
	Select the folder by...
</description></item><item><title>Download Monkeys Audio 12.00</title><pubDate> Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:42:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-monkeys-audio-949.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-monkeys-audio-949.html
</guid><description>
Monkey\'s Audio is software that compresses digital music without loss of quality. Supports high quality WAV files and CD ripping. Monkeys Audio will compress .wav tracks into .ape files to reduce their size without loss of sound quality, decompress .ape, convert files, check file integrity and manage tags.
Unlike traditional methods like MP3 and OGG, which permanently remove quality to save space, Monkey\'s Audio only creates perfect copies with the same sound quality as the originals....
</description></item><item><title>Download IObit Software Updater Pro 8.3.0.12</title><pubDate> Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:42:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iobit-software-updater-pro-2234.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iobit-software-updater-pro-2234.html
</guid><description>
IObit Software Updater Pro software is useful for those who don't download apps for Windows 10 from the store company, virtually all software was installed will not be updated automatically. The web browser will naturally inform you about a new version, software security of you will also be automatically updated, just like Windows, but almost all other apps will quietly operate in the normal mode and you will never know that the update was available, if you can't run itself.
IObit...
</description></item><item><title>Download Nconvert 7.230</title><pubDate> Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:41:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nconvert-2363.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nconvert-2363.html
</guid><description>
Nconvert is a command line program powerful that allows you to easily convert images from this format to other formats, also you can rotate the image in the right corner, change the size and apply natural all kinds of filters and watermarks.
Nconvert - convert image format
Nconvert can import about 400 graphic formats, export about 40 formats, can work with TIFF, GIF, ICO, you can easily change image size, adjust brightness and contrast, change the number of colors in images and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mullvad Browser 15.0.4</title><pubDate> Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:41:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mullvad-browser-12254.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mullvad-browser-12254.html
</guid><description>
Mullvad Browser is a privacy-focused web browser developed through a partnership between Mullvad VPN and Tor Project. This browser is designed to minimize tracking and fingerprinting. You can say that this is the Tor browser to use without the Tor Network. Instead, you can use this browser with a reliable VPN. The idea is to provide one more alternative – besides the Tor Network – to browse the internet with more privacy. To get as many people as possible together against today's big...
</description></item><item><title>Download DU Meter 9.20</title><pubDate> Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:40:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-du-meter-91.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-du-meter-91.html
</guid><description>
DU Meter provides users the ability to check the internet connection at any time. The software allows users to check download and upload speeds practice at different times. DU Meter also provides features press the clock to measure the exact download time of the communication line and report back. DU Meter really useful and necessary for parents to control their children use the internet or the manager supervision of his employees during office hours
DU Meter - Check the internet...
</description></item><item><title>Download reaConverter Pro 8.0.180</title><pubDate> Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:40:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html
</guid><description>
reaConverter Pro is software image processing feature with batch conversion and image editing periodically becomes simple. eaConverter also provide command line utilities allow you to process images automatically, thus helping you shorten the time for other work.
reaConverter Pro integrated powerful tool of Uber with many great features. It provides advanced solutions to process and adjust images. Management of the conversion process the base image with the latest version of...
</description></item><item><title>Download MusConv 4.10.447 Lifetime</title><pubDate> Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:39:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html
</guid><description>
MusConv transfers playlists, albums, followed artists and liked songs across a variety of services – Spotify, Apple Music, Amazon Music, YouTube, YouTube Music, iTunes, Deezer, Tidal, SoundCloud, Pandora and more 125 music services!
Features of MusConv Ultimate
	Transfer playlists, albums, followed artists and liked tracks between over 125 music servicesManage playlists (Delete, Merge, Split, Copy...)
	More than 125 music services supported
	Access DAILY updated music charts on...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mozilla Thunderbird 147.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:39:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thunderbird-1788.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thunderbird-1788.html
</guid><description>
Thunderbird is an email program full featured with controls spam integration, mail filter, address book, news groups and more. It provides a clean interface and easy to use (customizable). Thunderbird also provides the security features such as S / MIME, digital signing, message encryption, support for certificates and security devices.
Before using this feature, you should review the settings IMAP, SMTP, and SSL/TLS his. Now, what all you need to do is provide your name, email address,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Rhinoceros 8.27.25357.11371</title><pubDate> Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:38:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rhinoceros-179.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rhinoceros-179.html
</guid><description>
Rhinoceros is design software 3D easy to learn, easy to use and has range of application in various industries. Rhinoceros (or Rhino, Rhino3D) is a graphics software CAD and 3D developed by Robert McNeel &amp;amp; Associates, a private company established in the year 1980. Rhinoceros is developed according to the algorithm NURBS mathematical model, algorithm, focus on the correct presentation of curves and surfaces mathematics in computer graphics (in contrast to the application polygon...
</description></item><item><title>Download PassFab 4EasyPartition 3.9.2.19</title><pubDate> Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:38:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-passfab-4easypartition-7983.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-passfab-4easypartition-7983.html
</guid><description>
After using your PC for many years, there are bound to be many files you want to transfer to your new PC. PassFab 4EasyPartition can perform a one-click migration saving you hours of reinstalling operating systems and applications. It has an intuitive interface and step-by-step wizard that makes migrating the system in just a few steps. PassFab 4EasyPartition will effectively solve the problem of low disk space, speed up your computer and make it run faster.
Features of PassFab...
</description></item><item><title>Download Daum PotPlayer 1.7.22769</title><pubDate> Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:37:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-daum-potplayer-1015.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-daum-potplayer-1015.html
</guid><description>
Daum PotPlayer is a multimedia player has almost all the functions and interface similar, but improved markedly with KMP. Software Daum PotPlayer Stable have the special feature is the high quality playback, support for all video formats and audio modern and the presence of video codecs DXVA integration. Has a modern design, easy to install, have the ability to assign and change the hot keys, record sound to play, display subtitles, connect the plug-in DSP that allows visual display when...
</description></item><item><title>Download O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Premium 22.2.1142</title><pubDate> Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:37:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-diskimage-server-4547.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-diskimage-server-4547.html
</guid><description>
O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Server is software that is specially designed for use in enterprise environments, the software allows users to backup all the files you want and keep them safe from any incident or disaster computer. O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Server comes with a variety of easy to use utility that allows users to backup entire partitions of the specific files from their PC, as well as recover the version previous data of them, all from a simple interface.
O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Server - data...
</description></item><item><title>Download VideoByte BD-DVD Ripper 2.2.32</title><pubDate> Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:36:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-videobyte-bd-dvd-ripper-14311.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-videobyte-bd-dvd-ripper-14311.html
</guid><description>
VideoByte BD-DVD Ripper is a versatile program to convert Blu-ray and DVD discs (including ISO and VIDEO_TS folders) to digital video and audio files on Windows and macOS. The software is designed to handle both homemade discs and most copyright-protected commercial discs, so users can backup and watch movies on computers, phones, TVs, and media servers instead of having to use physical discs every time.
Features of VideoByte BD-DVD Ripper
	Supports Blu-ray and DVD discs, folders, and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Lightmap HDR Light Studio 9.3.0.2025.1221</title><pubDate> Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:36:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lightmap-hdr-light-studio-xenon-5459.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lightmap-hdr-light-studio-xenon-5459.html
</guid><description>
HDR Light Studio software gives 3D artists a new way to illuminate 3D images. Adorn your photos with lights. Lighting process is now easy, fast, accurate, creative and fun. HDR Light Studio builds the lighting used by your existing 3D rendering software and renderers. By adding HDR Light Studio, 3D artists become more productive and image quality improves.
When combining photography and CG images, combining light between the image content and CG elements is the key to a successful and...
</description></item><item><title>Download UltFone Windows Data Recovery 10.6.14.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:35:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ultfone-windows-data-recovery-14195.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ultfone-windows-data-recovery-14195.html
</guid><description>
UltFone Windows Data Recovery is a comprehensive data recovery software designed for Windows system to recover lost or deleted files from various storage devices such as hard drive, USB drive, SD card, etc. The software supports recovering many file types, including photos, videos, documents, music and archive files. The software offers two scanning modes—quick scan for recently deleted files and deep scan for comprehensive recovery, and also allows users to preview recoverable files...
</description></item><item><title>Download ChrisPC Free VPN Connection 4.26.0113</title><pubDate> Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:35:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-free-vpn-connection-2887.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-free-vpn-connection-2887.html
</guid><description>
ChrisPC Free VPN Connection software allows you to create VPN connection (virtual private network) to the server for free from the United States, Germany, Canada, France, Germany, Russia, Singapore, the Netherlands. This will help you to unblock your favorite sites to watch free TV and on-demand television when living abroad, travelling, on business or vacation. In addition, here is the solution to overcome the limited area for the popular websites: Google, YouTube, Facebook, Instagram,...
</description></item><item><title>Download SkyDemon 4.2.3.107</title><pubDate> Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:34:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-skydemon-6442.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-skydemon-6442.html
</guid><description>
SkyDemon is designed to make the flight planning less tedious and more interesting, by bringing the best aviation summary information directly to your reach in real time when you explore the charts. Planning a journey, summaring yourself about potential hazards, prepare for flight and analysis of your path. Direct summary data includes NOTAM, airport documentation and maps, TAF, METAR and wind forecast at altitude.
Features of SkyDemon
	Planning a route with SkyDemon simply by...
</description></item><item><title>Download The Dude 7.21</title><pubDate> Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:34:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-the-dude-3238.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-the-dude-3238.html
</guid><description>
The Dude is a new application by MikroTik which can dramatically improve the way you manage your network environment. It will automatically scan all devices in the subnet is specified, draw and layout a map of your networks, monitor services of your devices and alert you in case some service has problems.is a new application by MikroTik which can dramatically improve the way you manage your network environment. It will automatically scan all devices in the subnet is specified, draw and...
</description></item><item><title>Download FireAlpaca 2.14.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:34:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-firealpaca-2882.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-firealpaca-2882.html
</guid><description>
FireAlpaca is software painting Digital free available in 10 languages and is compatible with both Mac and Windows. The tools and simple controls allow you to draw a easy illustration. Convenient tool will be adding this one to the other! Download FireAlpaca right now! FireAlpaca is the utility to create and edit image files, add image overlays, as well as providing many other advanced features, bring an effective tool to help you draw a picture or edit a photo from the most basic...
</description></item></channel></rss>