<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 09:33:33 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 09:33:33 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Java SE Runtime Environment (JRE) 8.0 Update 481</title><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jan 2026 00:16:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-java-runtime-environment-4338.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-java-runtime-environment-4338.html
</guid><description>
Java Runtime Environment allows you to play online games, chat with people around the world, calculate mortgage interest and view images in 3D, just to name a few. Java technology allows you to work and play in a computing environment secure. Upgrade to the latest Java version improves the security of your system, as older versions do not include the update latest security.
Java Runtime Environment - Support Java on the computer
Java Runtime Environment is used in all major industries...
</description></item><item><title>Download CalendarTask (formerly DesktopCal) 3.26.264.8434</title><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jan 2026 00:11:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopcal-1831.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopcal-1831.html
</guid><description>
CalendarTask (formerly DesktopCal) is a simple desktop calendar that blends into your desktop without blocking access to your desktop icons. You can double-click on a date to quickly add notes and also jump to specific dates in the past or future.
CalendarTask - Computer calendar
CalendarTask can use your current wallpaper or loop through images from your folder and update your desktop every few minutes. The program helps you make appointments, make plans... Not only that, the Screen...
</description></item><item><title>Download Office Installer Plus 1.34</title><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jan 2026 00:10:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-installer-plus-11616.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-installer-plus-11616.html
</guid><description>
Office Installer Plus is the next version of Ratiborus that helps you download, install, update, uninstall, activate office 2024, 2021, 2019, 2016 and it has added an Office activator to the program. submit. Office Installer+ is considered a useful application that helps users install and manage office applications from Microsoft Office easily and quickly. This application is designed to help users save time and effort when installing popular office applications such as Word, Excel,...
</description></item><item><title>Download BandiView Pro (Honeyview) 7.24</title><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jan 2026 00:10:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-honeyview-4871.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-honeyview-4871.html
</guid><description>
HoneyView is an image viewer, comic book archive support with formats such as zip, cbz, rar....and support the photo format display, such as JPG, GIF, TIFF, PNG,... can see the photos automatically change after a period of time, adjust the time from 1 to 90 seconds and the options like repeat or random. In addition, support photo editing basics like rotate, add effects, zoom and pan or zoom display frame.
Features of HoneyView
	Operating system supported: Windows XP / Vista / 7/8 /...
</description></item><item><title>Download GoodSync Enterprise 12.9.24.4</title><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jan 2026 00:09:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-goodsync-enterprise-163.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-goodsync-enterprise-163.html
</guid><description>
GoodSync Enterprise is a software that saves files and files easily and is reliable. It automatically analyts, synchronize and backup your email, family photos, contacts, MP3, financial documentation and other important files-between desktop computers, laptops, servers, external drives and Windows Mobile devices as well as remotely via FTP , SFTP, WebDAV and more. The GoodSync synchronized software combines bulletproof reliability with an extremely easy interface to compare, synchronize...
</description></item><item><title>Download Serato DJ Pro 4.0.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jan 2026 00:09:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-serato-dj-pro-169.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-serato-dj-pro-169.html
</guid><description>
Serato DJ Pro is software mix DJ music, professional support, sound effects, and combined to create music, Great DJ. Serato DJ Pro supports the sound effects such as Delay, Reverb, Flanger, Echo, PingPong Delay, Phaser, Distortion, High and Low Pass Filter, as well as combinations of them. Supports MIDI in full, be made in the program, providing the ability to adapt to the controller and program for every need. It allows you to use at the same time from two to four floors. Program Serato...
</description></item><item><title>Download Office Installer by Ratiborus 1.34</title><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jan 2026 00:08:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-installer-11545.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-installer-11545.html
</guid><description>
Office Installer is a software program by Ratiborus used to install Microsoft Office on computers or devices. Office is a productivity suite that includes programs like Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Outlook, and more. The installer ensures that all required Microsoft Office files and components are installed, properly configured, and ready for use on the user's computer.
Office Installer allows users to choose which Office applications they want to install, select the installation location,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Canva Affinity 3.0.3.4027</title><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jan 2026 00:08:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-canva-affinity-14271.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-canva-affinity-14271.html
</guid><description>
With Canva, you can design, create, print, and work on anything. And now, Canva has integrated Affinity's suite of products to release Canva Affinity is the new unified professional design app, combining photo editing, vector design, and layout tools into a single app. Affinity includes powerful photo editing, illustration, graphic design, and page layout tools—offering a high-performance, subscription-free alternative to traditional design software.
Affinity's suite of creative tools...
</description></item><item><title>Download UltFone Windows Data Recovery 10.7.0.16</title><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jan 2026 00:07:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ultfone-windows-data-recovery-14195.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ultfone-windows-data-recovery-14195.html
</guid><description>
UltFone Windows Data Recovery is a comprehensive data recovery software designed for Windows system to recover lost or deleted files from various storage devices such as hard drive, USB drive, SD card, etc. The software supports recovering many file types, including photos, videos, documents, music and archive files. The software offers two scanning modes—quick scan for recently deleted files and deep scan for comprehensive recovery, and also allows users to preview recoverable files...
</description></item><item><title>Download Reg Organizer 9.90</title><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jan 2026 00:06:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reg-organizer-1595.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reg-organizer-1595.html
</guid><description>
Reg Organizer is a software to scan and clean your registry windows register errors and help optimize performance computer system. Reg Organizer is a software subscription, professional, and professional, and any way that the Windows registry are necessary and therefore, the overall performance of Windows improves, there is this software.
Reg Organizer - registry Cleaning and pc optimization
The main features of Reg Organizer
	Cleaning the registry of the lock is not valid and not...
</description></item><item><title>Download WordWeb Pro 10.55</title><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jan 2026 00:06:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wordweb-pro-4045.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wordweb-pro-4045.html
</guid><description>
WordWeb Pro this is the most basic tool of WordWeb Software, Other than WordWeb Pro Ultimate Reference Bundle, WordWeb Pro includes only lookup the most basic use support references from other reliable sources such as Wikipedia,... WordWeb Pro help you lookup dictionaries to find the synonyms are widely used, great for helping you to write clear English easy to understand. In addition to using dictionary comprehensive English dictionary and thesaurus supplied, if you online, you can also...
</description></item><item><title>Download Vov Sticky Notes 10.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jan 2026 00:05:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vov-sticky-notes-2818.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vov-sticky-notes-2818.html
</guid><description>
Vov Sticky Notes is a simple tool that allows you to create notes on the screen just like you use stickers to remind the public, the event which I will participate. You can choose the style of stick notes with different colors, change the size and font. This helps you to always keep in mind is the intended key of his.
Vov Sticky Notes to help you create the piece of paper to remember on the computer screen for you to remember the work in days, in weeks, of the intended key will do, the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tenorshare 4DDiG 10.7.0.16</title><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jan 2026 00:05:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tenorshare-4ddigs-pro-5629.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tenorshare-4ddigs-pro-5629.html
</guid><description>
Tenorshare 4DDiG is software to recover data from laptop / PC, external drive or USB flash disk. Recover Windows partitions, such as raw partitions, formatted partitions, damaged partitions, etc. Recover lost or deleted photos, videos, audio, videos, documents, etc.
With 4DDiG, you can recover many different types of data from this powerful Windows Data Recovery Tool feature. No matter what you have lost, 4DDiG is capable of recovering deleted files Windows 10 / 8.1 / 8/7 /...
</description></item><item><title>Download Fast Video Cutter Joiner 6.9.7</title><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jan 2026 00:04:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fast-video-cutter-joiner-7542.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fast-video-cutter-joiner-7542.html
</guid><description>
Fast Video Cutter Joiner is a fast video cutter and joiner with an easy to use interface. It allows users to trim parts of a video quickly while maintaining the quality of the original video. It supports various formats like AVI, MPEG, MP4, WMV, 3GP, FLV...
This tool helps you to cut video files into small parts, to keep only the parts you need and remove unwanted parts like trailers and advertisements in a movie. The clips you cut can then be used for other video productions or for a...
</description></item><item><title>Download PhotoMarks 4.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jan 2026 00:03:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photomarks-10598.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photomarks-10598.html
</guid><description>
PhotoMarks is a full-featured solution for creating visual watermarks in batch mode for your desktop or mobile devices. With PhotoMarks, you can fully customize the look of your text and logo watermarks as well as perform additional edits such as Resize, Rename, Auto-rotate or add Graphic Frames to your photos. you in the same session. It works by editing photos in batch mode and takes advantage of a multi-core processor to speed up the process. You can also save your settings as a...
</description></item><item><title>Download SpaceSniffer 2.1.0.21</title><pubDate> Tue, 20 Jan 2026 23:13:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-spacesniffer-14130.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-spacesniffer-14130.html
</guid><description>
SpaceSniffer is a free and portable tool that allows you to understand how folders and files are structured on your drive. Using the intuitive Treemap layout, you can instantly see where large folders and files are located on your device. The Treemap concept was invented by Professor Ben Shneiderman, who kindly gave permission to use his concept in this tool.
Start the scan and see the overall situation. The larger the elements in the view, the larger the folders and files on your...
</description></item><item><title>Download PCSX2 2.6.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 20 Jan 2026 22:51:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pcsx2-4470.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pcsx2-4470.html
</guid><description>
PCSX2 is a software application copy your Playstation 2, allowing you to play the game on your computer. As a gaming machine, virtual PCSX2 can overcome the hardware limitations to bring you these important advantages such as the ability to use the memory card is not limited to save games, screen resolution, custom, game cheats, save game is loading at any time during your game - play, the ability to tom to use any controller compatible Windows operating system and HD recordings of your...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Acrobat Pro DC 2025.001.21108 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Tue, 20 Jan 2026 22:48:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-001en-adobe-acrobat-pro-458.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-001en-adobe-acrobat-pro-458.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Acrobat Pro DC is a comprehensive software that helps you create and edit the PDF&amp;nbsp;document, or create form, sign, protect PDF, connect, split PDF, export PDF to various formats. The Acrobat Pro DC is the latest version of Adobe with improvements in the interface with the polished ribbon bar and the ability to create and handle pdf files as well as its male versions.
The highlight of the Acrobat Pro DC is probably the ability to connect, store documents on the cloud, you can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Flip PDF Plus Corporate 7.11.9</title><pubDate> Tue, 20 Jan 2026 22:41:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-flip-pdf-corporate-edition-3438.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-flip-pdf-corporate-edition-3438.html
</guid><description>
Flip PDF Corporate Edition is Windows software that helps to convert PDF to publications page flip digital with many powerful features. Version Corporate Edition contains all the great features in Flip PDF Professional and Flip Shopping Catalog. Version Flip PDF Corporate Edition is an edited version PDF most powerful for small and medium enterprises.
Software Flip PDF Corporate Edition provides all features of Flip PDF Professional and Flip Shopping Catalog, including the conversion mode...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Acrobat Reader DC 2025.001.21111</title><pubDate> Tue, 20 Jan 2026 22:40:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-acrobat-reader-3707.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-acrobat-reader-3707.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Acrobat Reader DC is a system of application software and Web services developed by Adobe Systems to view, create, manipulate, print and manage PDF files. With Adobe Acrobat Reader DC, you can create, export, edit, and track PDF files from anywhere - and maintain connection with the recent set of files on all your devices.
Adobe Acrobat Reader current DC is connected with Adobe Document Cloud - help working on the computers and mobile devices becomes easier than ever before. This is...
</description></item><item><title>Download Gilisoft Image Editor 8.6.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 20 Jan 2026 22:40:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-image-editor-12457.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-image-editor-12457.html
</guid><description>
Gilisoft Image Editor offers a variety of features to help you enhance and transform your images. With Gilisoft Image Editor, you can easily crop, resize and rotate images to get the perfect composition. The software also allows you to adjust the color, brightness, contrast, and saturation to bring out the best in your photos.
One of the standout features of Gilisoft Image Editor is the ability to add filters and effects. You can choose from a variety of presets or customize your own...
</description></item><item><title>Download Pale Moon 34.0.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 20 Jan 2026 22:39:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pale-moon-1883.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pale-moon-1883.html
</guid><description>
Pale Moon is a copy of Firefox has been optimized for the Windows operating System with the processor performance, high current. It looks identical to Firefox browser standard, and supports the extensions, themes and identities of Firefox. All extensions, bookmarks and settings of your existing be entered during the installation process, so except for the logo, you won't notice any difference on function.
Pale Moon - secure web browser
However, what you may notice is the difference in...
</description></item><item><title>Download iTop Voicy 1.1.0.1618</title><pubDate> Tue, 20 Jan 2026 22:39:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-itop-voicy-14482.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-itop-voicy-14482.html
</guid><description>
Transform your voice into anyone you want in real time. iTop Voicy uses the most advanced AI tuning technology to change your age, gender, and voice style while maintaining a natural sound. Whether you want to set a cute girl's voice or a robot voice, this free voice changer software for PC will produce high-quality voices instantly, without lag or delay.
Features of iTop Voicy
	Real-time, lag-free voice changer software
	Voice changer software for audio/video files
	Audio voice...
</description></item><item><title>Download Directory Opus Pro 13.20.6 Beta</title><pubDate> Tue, 20 Jan 2026 22:38:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-opus-pro-779.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-opus-pro-779.html
</guid><description>
Directory Opus Pro is a software replacement for Explorer with traditional strength and function more than any manager other files. Directory Opus Pro full support for high DPI screen (for example 4K and 5K) with the rename dialog is redesigned, with new features. Besides being a recording macro only allows you to perform mass renaming complex that don't need regular expressions. In addition, Directory Opus Pro also enhances the ability to script.Better handling of renaming recursive and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft PowerToys for Windows 10/11 0.97.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 20 Jan 2026 22:38:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-powertoys-for-windows-6014.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-powertoys-for-windows-6014.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft PowerToys is a user-proficiency set to adjust and streamline their Windows experience for higher productivity. Inspired by Windows 95's PowerToys project, this reboot provides users with proficiency in ways to exploit the more efficient Windows 10 and customisable processes it provides for each work process.
Utility of Microsoft PowerToys
	FancyZones is a window manager that allows you to easily create complex windows layout and quickly locate windows in those layout.
	Image...
</description></item></channel></rss>