<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 15:59:38 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 15:59:38 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Slimjet 49.0.2.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 30 Jan 2026 18:59:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-slimjet-3298.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-slimjet-3298.html
</guid><description>
Slimjet is a web browser that the page loading speed quite fast. Launch the browser, faster page loading, faster user interface response is provided by the tool Blink in the industry. Slimjet is loaded with powerful features and flexible options, Slimjet do more for every user without relying on external plugins. Automatic protection against phishing and malicious software, the control options privacy advanced architecture multi-process strong.
Slimjet - web-browser automatically...
</description></item><item><title>Download Lansweeper 12.6.2.3</title><pubDate> Fri, 30 Jan 2026 18:58:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lansweeper-2011.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lansweeper-2011.html
</guid><description>
Lansweeper is an application to manage IT assets and the scanning device is connected to the network. This software can scan and identify all network devices have workstation IP and Windows, Linux and Mac and indexing for them. Deep Scan Engine this software uses a set of protocols to detect and receive data from any device connected to the network. All data received can be stored in database SQL Compact or SQL Server.
Lansweeper - Scan system Internet
Software Lansweeper design open...
</description></item><item><title>Download Filezo 6.0.14</title><pubDate> Fri, 30 Jan 2026 18:58:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-filezo-14317.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-filezo-14317.html
</guid><description>
Filezo instantly finds any file, folder or application on your Windows PC at lightning speed. Just type a few keys and launch! That's it! Filezo's smart search feature ensures meaningful and clean results. It makes your computing life more enjoyable by eliminating boring clicks. Saves a lot of time and effort!
	Quickly access any document, folder or program on Windows in less than 5 seconds! Whether it's on your local hard drive, cloud drive or network drive.
	Tag files and folders to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tomabo MP4 Downloader Pro 6.1.8</title><pubDate> Fri, 30 Jan 2026 18:57:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tomabo-mp4-downloader-pro-3602.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tomabo-mp4-downloader-pro-3602.html
</guid><description>
Tomabo MP4 Downloader Pro is the app designed exclusively for Windows users to help them download videos from the Internet. In addition, it also increase download speeds by up to 500%, or even more. Tomabo MP4 Downloader Pro, interface design, simple, well-organized, beautifully. Here, users can view a list of videos has download with gravatar, URL, quality, duration and size of them. Software allows download video series at the same time, at the same time, support create a list of clips...
</description></item><item><title>Download eDocPrinter PDF Pro 10.66 Build 10668</title><pubDate> Fri, 30 Jan 2026 18:57:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-edocprinter-pdf-pro-3915.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-edocprinter-pdf-pro-3915.html
</guid><description>
eDocPrinter PDF Pro is an application to create PDF files from applications in Windows 2000, Windows XP and above. eDocPrinter PDF Pro works as a printer under windows environment, hence users can print from any application window using the device printing GDI. Extremely easy to work with this tool, because it installs on your system as a virtual printer and lets you convert documents to PDF in an easy way. eDocPrinter PDF Pro comes with advanced functions that can meet the requirements of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Kotato All Video Downloader Pro 10.1.7</title><pubDate> Fri, 30 Jan 2026 18:56:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kotato-all-video-downloader-pro-5228.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kotato-all-video-downloader-pro-5228.html
</guid><description>
Kotato All Video Downloader Pro is a Windows application professional to download and convert your favorite videos from the video sharing website. It speeds up your downloads up to 5 times! Kotato All Video Downloader Pro can download videos from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion and hundreds of video sharing sites, other. After downloading, you will be able to play them smoother on your PC or your mobile device, even when you don't have Internet access.
The main features of Kotato All...
</description></item><item><title>Download Soulstices StoryFlow Editor 1.2.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 30 Jan 2026 15:52:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-soulstices-storyflow-editor-14547.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-soulstices-storyflow-editor-14547.html
</guid><description>
StoryFlow Editor is an intuitive node-based story design tool used to create branching dialogue systems, interactive stories, and complex game storylines. Built with the familiar Blueprint-style visual scripting interface for Unreal Engine developers—no programming required. Connect dialogue nodes. Create branching choices. Add conditional logic. See your entire story structure at a glance. Check any path instantly without leaving the editor.
Features of Soulstices StoryFlow...
</description></item><item><title>Download LosslessCut 3.68.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 30 Jan 2026 05:16:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-losslesscut-1789.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-losslesscut-1789.html
</guid><description>
LosslessCut is the video editor to trim and cut video without loss of quality. Just download the video file and use seal cutter start / stop to only the part you want to cut. Click the crop icon and the highlighted part will be exported to the file new video without any decoding or encoding whatsoever. LosslessCut using ffmpeg (included) to carry all the heavy stuff.
LosslessCut - Cut and edit videos
LosslessCut based on Chromium and uses the video player HTML5, so not all formats are...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tor Browser 15.0.5</title><pubDate> Fri, 30 Jan 2026 05:16:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tor-browser-1833.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tor-browser-1833.html
</guid><description>
Tor Browser also has full name is Tor Browser Bundle is a web browser give you ability to access the internet safety and security your personal information as well as sensitive documents absolutely. By Tor Browser Bundle will automatically change the IP address on the machine to hide the identity when surfing the web. Tor Browser is free web browser full-featured basic and advanced allows you to leverage the Tor network anonymously without need to make any configuration changes or install...
</description></item><item><title>Download TidyWindow 4.3.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 30 Jan 2026 05:15:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tidywindow-14454.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tidywindow-14454.html
</guid><description>
TidyWindow is a Windows desktop assistant that automates developer PC setup, cleanup, diagnostics, software package installation, registry tweaking, and driver updates—powered by a WPF interface and robust PowerShell 7 automation capabilities in the background.
Key Features
	Essentials Repair Center (docs/essentials.md): Queues selected automation tasks Filter for network, Defender, printing, and Windows Update issues. Each task supports preview run, sequential execution, restore...
</description></item><item><title>Download OCCT 15.0.14.99</title><pubDate> Fri, 30 Jan 2026 05:15:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-occt-perestroika-1680.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-occt-perestroika-1680.html
</guid><description>
OCCT is a free application designed to benchmark and overclock system components. Test tool OverClock includes 4 different tests to assess the stability of your computer. CPU and CPU: Linpack to test the processor, GPU: 3D to check stability of the graphics processor and power supply combination of CPU: Linpack and GPU: 3D to download power of you up to the maximum.
OCCT - Measuring system components
The features of OCCT
	Support is enabled for a maximum of 16 cores.
	All the tests...
</description></item><item><title>Download RegRun Reanimator 17.96.2026.127</title><pubDate> Fri, 30 Jan 2026 05:14:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-regrun-reanimator-1205.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-regrun-reanimator-1205.html
</guid><description>
RegRun Reanimator is a software supports to Remove Trojan / adware / spyware and rootkits, as well as the types of other malicious software. RegRun Reanimator is not just a set of standard tools, but also have a reporting feature in-depth. This can create a detailed report about the current state of your PC, including applications, drivers, codecs, browser settings, extensions, Explorer, network settings, link file the details, Windows services, startup programs, scheduled tasks, running...
</description></item><item><title>Download iTop Voicy 1.1.1.1622</title><pubDate> Fri, 30 Jan 2026 05:14:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-itop-voicy-14482.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-itop-voicy-14482.html
</guid><description>
Transform your voice into anyone you want in real time. iTop Voicy uses the most advanced AI tuning technology to change your age, gender, and voice style while maintaining a natural sound. Whether you want to set a cute girl's voice or a robot voice, this free voice changer software for PC will produce high-quality voices instantly, without lag or delay.
Features of iTop Voicy
	Real-time, lag-free voice changer software
	Voice changer software for audio/video files
	Audio voice...
</description></item><item><title>Download CyberLink AudioDirector Ultra 2026 v16.1.6122.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jan 2026 21:25:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-audiodirector-ultra-288.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-audiodirector-ultra-288.html
</guid><description>
Sound is half the movie experience and improving the audio in the project video will greatly enhance the final result. AudioDirector contains advanced tools help edit and edit the audio quickly and simply. With the audio feature and seamless integration with PowerDirector.
We provide CyberLink AudioDirector Ultra editor software, mix, and adjust the soundtrack, effects, audio for video, and all the passages spoken in the video. CyberLink AudioDirector Ultra is the upgrade version of...
</description></item><item><title>Download RocketCake Professional 7.0.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jan 2026 21:24:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rocketcake-professional-2632.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rocketcake-professional-2632.html
</guid><description>
RocketCake Professional is a WYSIWYG HTML editor that allows you to create a website based on the responsive template without coding. Simply choose your template and customize it or create a new design from scratch.In addition to text content you can add images, galleries, slideshows, YouTube videos, Flash, buttons, audio / video HTML5, table and many page elements enhance the other.
RocketCake Professional - design application Website
Allows you to create a website as quickly as...
</description></item><item><title>Download Freemake Video Converter Gold 5.0.0.32</title><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jan 2026 21:24:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-freemake-video-converter-gold-167.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-freemake-video-converter-gold-167.html
</guid><description>
Freemake Video Converter Gold is a software to help convert tail high quality videos with many different formats on many devices. Freemake Video Converter - convert video to AVI, MP4, WMV, MKV, 3GP, DVD, MP3, iPad, iPhone, PSP, Android phone. Video to MP3 just with one click! Rip and burn DVD. Convert YouTube to MP4, AVI, etc. with Freemake! Results guaranteed. Freemake Video Converter has fast conversion speed, guarantee the output quality,support create HTML5 videos have the embed code...
</description></item><item><title>Download RocketCake 7.0.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jan 2026 21:23:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rocketcake-1697.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rocketcake-1697.html
</guid><description>
RocketCake is WYSIWYG HTML editor allows you to create a website based on the responsive template without coding. Simply choose your template and customize it or create a new design from scratch.In addition to text content you can add images, galleries, slideshows, YouTube videos, Flash, buttons, audio / video HTML5, table and many page elements enhance the other.
RocketCake - WYSIWYG HTML editor
RocketCake does not require any knowledge of HTML or CSS, you only need to drag the page...
</description></item><item><title>Download 4K YouTube to MP3 26.0.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jan 2026 21:22:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-youtube-to-mp3-622.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-youtube-to-mp3-622.html
</guid><description>
4K YouTube to MP3 is a software to convert video youtube to mp3 quickly and easily by the manipulation drag-and-drop simple. With 4K YouTube to MP3 you just drag and drop the link to the favorite songs of you and get the MP3 files to your computer, as easy as that. Transfer songs directly to iPod, iPhone and iPad everywhere you go. No install annoying and complex to solve, just a clean interface, user friendly and functional.
When using 4K YouTube to MP3, users will get the playlists,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Intuitibits WiFi Explorer Pro 1.1.12.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jan 2026 21:21:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intuitibits-wifi-explorer-pro-14331.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intuitibits-wifi-explorer-pro-14331.html
</guid><description>
Use WiFi Explorer Pro to help design and validate wireless networks, identify channel conflicts and overlapping channels, low signal quality, and other issues that may affect the connectivity or performance of your home, office, or business wireless network.
Includes visual visibility of the Wi-Fi environment, support for Wi-Fi 4 through 7 across 2.4, 5, and 6 GHz bands, custom columns from over 850 data fields, advanced filtering features, and compatibility with remote sensors. It allows...
</description></item><item><title>Download TickTick Premium 8.0.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jan 2026 21:21:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ticktick-premium-7770.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ticktick-premium-7770.html
</guid><description>
TickTick Premium is a task management application that helps users stay organized, it is very suitable for educators and students with many incentives. TickTick turns your Windows PC device into a flexible, easy-to-use and highly efficient office platform. Join millions of people to capture ideas, organize their lives, and do something creative every day.
Whether there are work related tasks or personal goals, TickTick is here to help you manage all your to-dos. With five different...
</description></item><item><title>Download WonderFox DVD Video Converter 31.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jan 2026 21:21:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wonderfox-dvd-video-converter-189.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wonderfox-dvd-video-converter-189.html
</guid><description>
WonderFox DVD Video Converter is a software to convert Video DVD to the Video format the other with fast speed. Convenient program to convert the popular video formats and movie DVD, download WonderFox DVD Video Converter below. You can create videos that will be optimized for viewing on mobile devices. There is a simple video editor, it will allow you to add effects, crop photos, and etc.
WonderFox DVD Video Converter
WonderFox DVD Video Converter support rip DVD and videos to various...
</description></item><item><title>Download MobiKin Eraser for iOS 2.1.21</title><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jan 2026 21:20:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mobikin-eraser-for-ios-5373.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mobikin-eraser-for-ios-5373.html
</guid><description>
MobiKin Eraser for iOS is one of the top deletion programs that gives you the functionality to delete all deleted files, private data, system settings and other files on your iOS device without have a chance to recover. When you decide to give up your old iDevice, you need to delete all the data on it. Otherwise, your personal data such as bank accounts and passwords, contact information, chat records or other information will be at high risk of disclosure. Luckily, you have MobiKin Eraser...
</description></item><item><title>Download WonderFox DVD Ripper Pro 24.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jan 2026 21:20:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wonderfox-dvd-ripper-pro-2066.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wonderfox-dvd-ripper-pro-2066.html
</guid><description>
WonderFox DVD Ripper is a tool to extract DVD fast number 1 really, only takes about 20 minutes to extract DVD 150 minutes to MP4, AVI, MKV, MOV, WMV with 0-quality loss and takes less time to MPG (only 5 ~ 10 minutes). Moreover, it complements the presets are optimized for all mobile devices pop as DVD to iPhone 5S, iPad Air, iPad mini 3, DVD to Samsung Galaxy S5, Sony, Nokia, BlackBerry, HTC, Xbox, Android devices, etc. WonderFox DVD Ripper Pro provides the best solution to convert DVD...
</description></item><item><title>Download Axialis IconVectors Pro 1.20</title><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jan 2026 21:19:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-axialis-iconvectors-pro-14187.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-axialis-iconvectors-pro-14187.html
</guid><description>
Axialis IconVectors is a lightweight and fast SVG icon editor built specifically for developers, providing precise control and quick editing of vector icons. It easily integrates into existing development workflows with real-time code preview (SVG, ReactTS, VueTS, XAML, C++), compatible with Visual Studio, VS Code and Adobe Illustrator. Its developer-focused features remove unnecessary complexity, making vector icon creation efficient and simple.
Features of Axialis IconVectors...
</description></item><item><title>Download Eagle Mode 0.96.4</title><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jan 2026 21:19:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-eagle-mode-11944.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-eagle-mode-11944.html
</guid><description>
Eagle Mode is a powerful and innovative file management application for Windows that provides users with a unique and rich way to navigate and organize files and folders. One of Eagle Mode's key features is its 3D interface, which allows users to navigate their files and folders in an impressively intuitive and interactive way. The app displays all your files and folders in three-dimensional space, with each file represented as a clickable icon. Users can easily zoom in and out of the 3D...
</description></item></channel></rss>