<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 19:58:24 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 19:58:24 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download MultiAlarm 1.4.1 + Portable</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Dec 2025 17:00:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-multialarm-12745.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-multialarm-12745.html
</guid><description>
MultiAlarm is a multi-timer and alarm setup tool with system tray, desktop widget, and RGB light notification on the keyboard. Each alarm can be configured for up to 24 hours, making them ideal for a variety of tasks that require constant reminders. Users can conveniently stop, restart, and reconfigure these alarms at any time, providing flexibility based on changing schedules or needs. Additionally, timed alarms are permanently stored in the system memory until you decide to delete...
</description></item><item><title>Download Executor 2.2.0.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Dec 2025 16:59:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-executor-271.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-executor-271.html
</guid><description>
Executor for windows is a software alternative premium customization features for the Windows "Run" and "Search Programs". When you press WIN + Z and provides the search results instant, as-you-type for any keywords you enter. By default, Executor will index all the Desktop and Start Menu and you can easily expand the search range by adding the folder location additional.
Executor for windows
The program comes with a list of commands built in which you can use to quickly access many...
</description></item><item><title>Download Screenpresso Pro 2.1.41</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Dec 2025 16:56:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-screenpresso-pro-1362.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-screenpresso-pro-1362.html
</guid><description>
Screenpresso Pro is a program easy to take great photos on your screen! Screenpresso blocked Print Screen key and screen capture the best in a few seconds. Allows you to capture windows and screen area, roll the part of the screen, edit the images obtained, add effects, resize a group of images, send screenshots by email and post them to Web resources.
Screenpresso Pro - Shooting the computer screen
Features of Screenpresso Pro
	Take the window and screen area. Take a partial screen...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare PDFelement Pro 12.1.3.3909</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Dec 2025 16:55:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-pdfelement-pro-105.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-pdfelement-pro-105.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare PDFelement Pro support users to convert PDF to office documents for easier use, modify in every situation. Is one of the software conversion material is rated best today, integrated with many features. We recommend that you should use experience software many useful features this.
Wondershare PDFelement Pro - conversion Fie PDF more features, multi-language
Wondershare PDFelement Pro what?
Convert PDF into Word, Excel, PowerPoint...
• Convert PDF and protected PDF into...
</description></item><item><title>Download JRiver Media Center 35.0.31</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Dec 2025 16:55:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jriver-media-center-110.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jriver-media-center-110.html
</guid><description>
JRiver Media Center can help you strictly manage all your files media and enjoy them in a completely new way. Launching the application for the first time, users will be immediately impressed with the intuitive and eye-catching interface with many interesting features to explore. Most people who have used JRiver Media Center evaluate that the software interface design is youthful and modern.
The software for arranging cover art of music files is also extremely neat, especially Insert...
</description></item><item><title>Download Astute Graphics Plug-ins Elite Bundle 4.4.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Dec 2025 16:54:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-astute-graphics-plug-ins-elite-bundle-5523.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-astute-graphics-plug-ins-elite-bundle-5523.html
</guid><description>
Astute Graphics Plug-ins Elite Bundle is a set of graphics editing tools for Adobe Illustrator. It includes many unique tools like Phantasm, VectorScribe, WidthScribe and many others. Get the complete set of plug-ins and transform your workflow in Illustrator. Add speed, ease, and precision with all our plug-ins and become the Astute Graphics Plug-in Elite Package!
Astute Graphics Plug-ins Elite Bundle Features:
	Correct alignment + selection
	Sketching visual vector
	Instantly...
</description></item><item><title>Download VectorStyler 1.3.004</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Dec 2025 16:54:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vectorstyler-7917.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vectorstyler-7917.html
</guid><description>
VectorStyler provides a complete set of drawing, design and illustration tools needed for modern design. Create illustrations, logos, icons, drawings, typography, vector art for screen, print and web. With many new features, VectorStyler redefines and extends the tools available to illustrators and designers, improving the creation of complex illustrations and designs.
Shape effects can be used to adjust the shape of objects, create different distortions, or add detail to shapes. Shape...
</description></item><item><title>Download ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro 15.25.1219</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Dec 2025 16:54:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-videotube-downloader-pro-1276.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-videotube-downloader-pro-1276.html
</guid><description>
ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro is the professional version support download videos and playlists from YouTube, videos from Dailymotion, BBC iPlayer, ITV Player, ABC,  FOX,CBS.com Vimeo, Prosieben, Metacafe, Blip.tv CBC.ca many more video sites. After the video is downloaded, you can convert them to the formats compatible with iPad, iPhone, iPod, MPEG-4, H. 264, MP3, AC3.
ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro - Download videos on Youtube
This is one of the software download the most...
</description></item><item><title>Download AB Download Manager 1.8.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Dec 2025 16:53:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ab-download-manager-12399.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ab-download-manager-12399.html
</guid><description>
With this application, you can easily download files from anywhere. Enjoy fast, free downloads with seamless browser extension support. It is built to be a desktop application that allows you to manage and organize your downloads better than before.
AB Download Manager features
	Simple and modern UI: Simple UI and dark mode by default
	Faster download speeds: Download files using multiple connections to increase your download speed by up to 500%
	Download Queue: Create and manage your...
</description></item><item><title>Download HitmanPro.Alert 3.21.1 Build 2033</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Dec 2025 16:53:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hitmanpro-alert-112.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hitmanpro-alert-112.html
</guid><description>
HitmanPro is a lightweight application that can monitor your browser activity and detect the hidden threats may include security systems. Tool HitmanPro is built specifically to add an additional layer of security for system of you, to protect you whenever you shop on the Internet , or perform banking activities online. It offers computer protection in real time against the exploitation of software, download at in drive, encryption software, online fraud and identity...
</description></item><item><title>Download Geekbench AI Corporate 1.6.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Dec 2025 16:52:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-geekbench-ai-corporate-12385.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-geekbench-ai-corporate-12385.html
</guid><description>
Geekbench AI is a cross-platform AI benchmark that uses real-world machine learning tasks to evaluate the performance of AI workloads. Geekbench AI measures your CPU, GPU, and NPU to determine whether your device is ready for today's and tomorrow's advanced machine learning applications.
Evaluating real-world AI performance:
Real-world AI performance
	Geekbench AI runs ten AI workloads, each with three different types of data, giving you a multidimensional picture of on-device AI...
</description></item><item><title>Download AntiPlagiarism.NET 4.153</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Dec 2025 16:52:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-antiplagiarismnet-2457.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-antiplagiarismnet-2457.html
</guid><description>
AntiPlagiarism NET is software to check the originality of some given text, most people find a section of text on the Internet, often the search engines quickly put out the answer to this question. Sometimes the results can be wrong, because not all results are accurate, a hundred percent. Fortunately, there are other solutions to the problem, for example, AntiPlagiarism.NET it can help you determine the originality of some given text. Application to operate correctly, you need to install...
</description></item><item><title>Download Metatogger 7.7.0.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Dec 2025 16:51:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-metatogger-62.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-metatogger-62.html
</guid><description>
Metatogger enables you to tag, rename and arrange the files Ogg Vorbis, FLAC, Speex and MP3 your. It allows you to rename files based on the existing cards of them and also follow the links folder of them (useful if the folder path of your contains artist name, and album are related).
Interface work modern
The interface of the utility is clean and intuitive. Import the audio track into the workspace is done by using the browser files, folder view, or the method of "drag and drop"; you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Internet Download Manager Portable 6.42 Build 58</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Dec 2025 16:51:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-internet-download-manager-portable-11965.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-internet-download-manager-portable-11965.html
</guid><description>
Internet Download Manager (IDM) is a popular software tool that helps users download files from the internet at faster speeds. It is designed to increase download speeds up to five times, resume and schedule downloads, and support multiple download queues. IDM also has many features that make it easy to use and customize to fit your needs.
IDM has a simple and friendly interface that makes it easy to use. The software integrates seamlessly with popular web browsers such as Google Chrome,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Disk Sorter Ultimate 17.6.18 + Server + Pro</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Dec 2025 16:50:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-disk-sorter-ultimate-1464.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-disk-sorter-ultimate-1464.html
</guid><description>
Disk Sorter Ultimate is the utility classification file lightweight and simple helps people detect files on most types of drives, as well as manage them according to many different criteria to create more capacity on the disc. This app allows you to search through the 500,000 files, have storage capacity of 2TB. To start sorting, all what you have to do is select a directory, drive or server and click the button "Classification". You should know that you can search for the type specific...
</description></item><item><title>Download Stardock Start11 2.6 Beta</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Dec 2025 16:50:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stardock-start11-7029.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stardock-start11-7029.html
</guid><description>
Start11 is an application capable of customizing the Start Menu and Taskbar on Windows 11 and Windows 10. This is an application that allows users to customize Windows 11 to suit their preferences. his personal. Start11 will help you bring the new Start Menu of Windows 11 to Windows 10. And vice versa, Start11 also helps you to bring the Start Menu of Windows 10 to Windows 11.
Start11 also helps users bring some functions of Windows 10 to Windows 11 through customizing the Taskbar such...
</description></item><item><title>Download Secret Video Downloader 1.0.8</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Dec 2025 16:49:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secret-video-downloader-13775.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secret-video-downloader-13775.html
</guid><description>
Secret Video Downloader is a free application designed to facilitate easy video downloading from various websites. It leverages the yt-dlp command line program to efficiently grab video content, allowing users to save videos in the highest quality available without complicated installation or configuration. The tool has a minimalist interface focused on simplicity: the user pastes the video URL into the built-in browser, clicks the Download button, and the video is added to the download...
</description></item><item><title>Download TikTok Bot Pro 3.7</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Dec 2025 16:49:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tiktok-bot-pro-11635.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tiktok-bot-pro-11635.html
</guid><description>
TikTok Bot Pro is software designed to automate activities and interactions on TikTok to attract real followers on TikTok. It automates your “likes” and “comments,” finds new followers categorized by similar accounts, and attracts followers who are actually interested in your content.
Here is a list of features you will find in this software:
	GET FOLLOWERS: Export your TikTok followers from those who follow other profiles and/or users based on specific tags.
	AUTO-FOLLOW:...
</description></item><item><title>Download K-Lite Codec Pack Update 19.3.7</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Dec 2025 16:49:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-update-5145.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-update-5145.html
</guid><description>
K-Lite Codec Pack Update is the update of the set of codecs and related tools. Codec stands for Compressor-decompressor. Codec is necessary to encode and decode (play) audio and video. K-Lite Codec Pack Update is designed as a user-friendly solution with users to play all movie files your. With Codec Pack K-Lite, you can play 99% of all the movies found on your computer. A number of packages codec is not friendly with computers, as they tend to slow down Windows, break down multimedia...
</description></item><item><title>Download QontrolPanel (QuickSoundSwitcher) 1.11.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Dec 2025 16:48:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quicksoundswitcher-14033.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quicksoundswitcher-14033.html
</guid><description>
QuickSoundSwitcher is a lightweight, open-source Windows utility designed to quickly and easily manage audio input and output devices. It allows users to switch between multiple audio devices (e.g. speakers, headphones, microphones) and control the volume directly from the system tray without navigating to complex Windows settings.
The program also provides an application volume mixer, allowing for volume adjustment and muting for individual programs. This tool is especially useful for...
</description></item><item><title>Download TrayStatus Pro 5.1.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Dec 2025 16:48:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-traystatus-pro-1597.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-traystatus-pro-1597.html
</guid><description>
TrayStatus Pro is professional software to help display the status of the keys Caps Lock, Num Lock, Scroll Lock, Kana, Alt, Ctrl, Shift in the system tray. In addition, the software TrayStatus this Pro also displays CPU, memory or operation of the hard drive or use performance counters to track things like the queue length, disk, network activity, requires IIS and more.
TrayStatus Pro - Show keyboard status and parameters of the computer
The features and functions TrayStatus...
</description></item><item><title>Download InstaBot Pro 7.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Dec 2025 16:47:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-instabot-pro-8820.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-instabot-pro-8820.html
</guid><description>
InstaBot Pro is a piece of software designed to automate your “likes”, finding new followers profiled by similar accounts and Get your followers really interested in your content. Everyone knows now that the success of an instagram account also depends on the interactions and activity level of that particular account in the community.
Features of InstaBot Pro
	GET FOLLOWERS: Export followers of other profiles and/or users based on specific Hashtags.
	AUTO FOLLOW: Automatically...
</description></item><item><title>Download OutlookAddressBookView 2.46</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Dec 2025 16:47:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-outlookaddressbookview-2381.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-outlookaddressbookview-2381.html
</guid><description>
OutlookAddressBookView is a simple utility that displays the details of all recipients stored in the address book of Microsoft Outlook. For each entry of the recipient, the following information will be displayed: email Address, display Name, address Type (MS-Exchange or SMTP), street Address, phone Number, creation Time, modified Time (works Only with address books of Exchange server) and more... You can easily select one or more recipients from the list and export them into a file...
</description></item><item><title>Download SQL Backup Master 8.0.1020 All Editions</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Dec 2025 16:46:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sql-backup-master-6687.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sql-backup-master-6687.html
</guid><description>
SQL Backup Master backup your SQL Server database into any popular cloud hosting service such as Dropbox, OneDrive, Amazon S3, Microsoft Azure, Box and Google Drive. It can also backup the database to the FTP server-or a directory on your local machine, network server or storage device.
The backup of your SQL Server database to the cloud will not be complex or expensive. SQL Backup Master is born by providing an easy way to download copies of your database to one or more of the most...
</description></item><item><title>Download Thimeo Stereo Tool 10.73</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Dec 2025 16:46:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stereo-tool-4066.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stereo-tool-4066.html
</guid><description>
Stereo Tool is an audio processor based on software, provide sound quality superior and comes with many unique features. It is used by over 1500 FM stations, from the station of the small local to the station 50 - 100 kW and nationwide network with dozens of generators, thousands of stations online and many radio DAB +, HD, AM and TV. Stereo Tool can make recordings sound equal and consistent in volume and sound color, highlight details and increase the stereo effect is there. It can...
</description></item></channel></rss>