<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 15:45:04 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 15:45:04 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Visual C++ Redistributable Runtimes AIO Repack 0.103.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 24 Nov 2025 17:05:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-visual-c-redistributable-runtimes-aio-repack-7825.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-visual-c-redistributable-runtimes-aio-repack-7825.html
</guid><description>
Visual C++ Redistributable Runtimes AIO Repack is a setup package that includes all the latest Microsoft Visual C++ Redistribution Runtimes without the initial setup payload.
	Built on VBCRedis_AIO_x86_x64.exe
	This process is handled by a command set of windows command, which runs hidden in the background by default.
	Before installation, the script will check and remove the existing Visual C + + runtime settings, including the original EXE or MSI setup or the older MSI package...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft Visual C++ 2015-2022 Redistributable 14.50.35719</title><pubDate> Mon, 24 Nov 2025 16:50:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-visual-c-4856.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-visual-c-4856.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft Visual C++ Redistributable Package contains the component run-time libraries of Visual C ++ required to run the application on a PC without installed Visual C ++. Microsoft Visual C++ or also known as MSVC development environment integrated (IDE) for the programming language C, C++, at the same time integrated tools for developing and debugging C++ source code. Microsoft Visual C++ supports the function of automatic completion of the coding and the debugging function...
</description></item><item><title>Download StartAllBack 3.9.18.5338</title><pubDate> Mon, 24 Nov 2025 16:49:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-startallback-6857.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-startallback-6857.html
</guid><description>
With the official release of Windows 11, chances are that most of you want to try it out. As the name suggests, StartAllBack is a small, lightweight tool that can help you enjoy the power of the new operating system while keeping the look and feel, especially because main work area, desktop of Windows 7, Windows 10 as taskbars and start menu styles.
StartAllBack is specially designed for Windows 11 and will not work on any older operating systems. If you want to get the start menu back...
</description></item><item><title>Download Internet Download Manager (IDM) 6.42 Build 55</title><pubDate> Mon, 24 Nov 2025 16:48:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-inetnet-download-manager-161.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-inetnet-download-manager-161.html
</guid><description>
Internet Download Manager is the download acceleration software, the best download support now, it can help you speed up the download up to five times, continue and schedule downloads. The latest version of IDM adds the compatibility of Windows 10 and Windows 11, it has supported all current popular browsers such as Internet Explorer, Mozilla Firefox, Opera, Google Chrome, ..
Download IDM with the latest version on taiwebs.com making it easy to download and manage your downloaded files...
</description></item><item><title>Download IDM Retail 6.42 Build 55</title><pubDate> Mon, 24 Nov 2025 16:48:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-internet-download-manager-retail-3609.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-internet-download-manager-retail-3609.html
</guid><description>
IDM - Internet Download Manager Retail is a reliable utility and high efficiency will help you to increase your download speed and manage download at better. The program allows you to easily schedule, pause and resume downloads with a single click. Moreover, the application provides error resilience robust and can restart the download at the interrupted or broken. You can restore the download is interrupted due to network problems, lost connections, unexpected power outages, computer...
</description></item><item><title>Download DiskDigger Pro 2.0.13.4127</title><pubDate> Mon, 24 Nov 2025 16:47:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-diskdigger-pro-435.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-diskdigger-pro-435.html
</guid><description>
DiskDigger Pro is software restore data files, videos, pictures, sounds, media files, from a USB Flash drive, memory card.  DiskDigger can recover all the deleted files from your means, can help even when files or folders lost due to virus attack. It gives users the ability to restore various types of data including: pictures, video, audio, text.
DiskDigger Pro support in multiple files with different formats: JPG, PNG, GIF, BMP, TIFF, ICO, ANI, DOC, DOCX, XLS, PPT, PDF, VSD, PPTX,...
</description></item><item><title>Download KpRm 2.21</title><pubDate> Mon, 24 Nov 2025 16:47:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kprm-2672.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kprm-2672.html
</guid><description>
KpRm is a small utility that can be useful when you want to do deep cleaning system, other applications create a folder in the folder that the average user usually does not look into. Program KpRm will allow you to scan Windows and delete the folder Quarantine - the rest after you have removed the virus and all spyware, the whole folder with all content inside will be deleted completely, also you will get rid of the software as ZHPDiag, ZHPCleaner, CryptoSearch and others created to search...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ultracopier 3.0.1.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 24 Nov 2025 16:46:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-supercopier-2121.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-supercopier-2121.html
</guid><description>
SuperCopier is a replacement for advanced copy command Windows standard. Supercopier support pause and resume the copy operation is ongoing, install copy speed can adjust, automatically rename the old file, and more.
You can view a detailed list of queue copy and optionally move files up or down in the list, add additional files and also can delete or ignore the category when needed. This can be especially useful when you copy large number of files.
Supercopier - copy...
</description></item><item><title>Download Memtest86+ 8.00 Stable</title><pubDate> Mon, 24 Nov 2025 16:45:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-memtest86-7893.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-memtest86-7893.html
</guid><description>
Memtest86+ offers you some of the best tools for RAM testing purposes. It can detect almost any irregularity in the RAM stick, thus notifying you of problems you may have with your system memory. Faulty RAM can manifest as a series of errors often accompanied by a BSOD (Blue Screen of Death) that may not point directly to the actual problem.
Memtest86+ can and does provide accurate results on RAM and ensures that your system memory is in top shape.
Features of Memtest86+
	Free...
</description></item><item><title>Download EditPlus 6.1 Build 780</title><pubDate> Mon, 24 Nov 2025 16:44:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-editplus-338.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-editplus-338.html
</guid><description>
EditPlus is editor text, editor, HTML and editor program for Windows. EditPlus works as a text editor as well as editor, PHP editor, HTML, editor, Java viewer and Hex. It supports syntax highlighting for many languages, such as HTML, CSS, Java, PHP, C / C ++, Perl, and Python, and can act as a web browser to preview the HTML page. EditPlus also provides some other useful features, such as auto completion, code folding, spell checking, search and replace, keyboard shortcuts, custom and HTML...
</description></item><item><title>Download Stellar Repair for Excel 7.0.0.4</title><pubDate> Mon, 24 Nov 2025 16:42:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stellar-repair-for-excel-5490.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stellar-repair-for-excel-5490.html
</guid><description>
Stellar Repair for Excel is an important application for securing Excel workbook data from permanent corruption and loss. This tool can protect you and your business from major losses due to sudden corruption of Excel data such as financial reports, BI data, and other analytics. It rebuilds the corrupted Excel file data at the granular level to restore all datasets and provide a visual representation of its original, intact state.
Software provides a simple way to deal with damaged or...
</description></item><item><title>Download Beauty Box Video for After Effects &amp;amp; Premiere Pro 6.0.3</title><pubDate> Mon, 24 Nov 2025 16:42:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-beauty-box-video-for-after-effects-premiere-pro-12591.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-beauty-box-video-for-after-effects-premiere-pro-12591.html
</guid><description>
Digital Anarchy's Beauty Box Video is a powerful skin retouching plugin designed for use in Adobe After Effects and Premiere Pro. This plugin streamlines the process of enhancing skin tones and removing imperfections, allowing editors to achieve professional results with minimal effort.
Beauty Box Video will assist in this digital skin and makeup editing by automatically identifying skin tones and creating masks that limit the smoothing effect on skin areas. Simply apply a video filter,...
</description></item><item><title>Download iDefender 5.2.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 24 Nov 2025 16:41:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idefender-13959.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idefender-13959.html
</guid><description>
iDefender is an advanced security solution designed for the home, providing both a High-Performance Intrusion Prevention System (HIPS) and Real-Time Endpoint Detection and Response (EDR). This integrated system protects against potential threats, ensuring the safety and integrity of your devices by proactively monitoring and responding to suspicious activity.
Why iDefender?
Ransomware Prevention
	Detects and blocks ransomware in real time to protect important files from malicious...
</description></item><item><title>Download RadioBOSS Ultimate 7.1.6.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 24 Nov 2025 16:40:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-radioboss-advanced-599.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-radioboss-advanced-599.html
</guid><description>
The application programming radio professional, tradition designed for the traditional radio can and is expected to pay thousands of dollars for software is extremely complex and complicated. But if that's not you? If you need a simple, affordable, reliable solution to automating demand your broadcast, RadioBOSS is the solution you've been looking for.
Whether it's building and scheduling programming cross for radio ground or your Internet, create sound atmosphere suitable in restaurant...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tenorshare 4DDiG 10.6.6.6</title><pubDate> Mon, 24 Nov 2025 16:39:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tenorshare-4ddigs-pro-5629.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tenorshare-4ddigs-pro-5629.html
</guid><description>
Tenorshare 4DDiG is software to recover data from laptop / PC, external drive or USB flash disk. Recover Windows partitions, such as raw partitions, formatted partitions, damaged partitions, etc. Recover lost or deleted photos, videos, audio, videos, documents, etc.
With 4DDiG, you can recover many different types of data from this powerful Windows Data Recovery Tool feature. No matter what you have lost, 4DDiG is capable of recovering deleted files Windows 10 / 8.1 / 8/7 /...
</description></item><item><title>Download MemoryCleaner 1.9.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 24 Nov 2025 16:39:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-memorycleaner-12469.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-memorycleaner-12469.html
</guid><description>
MemoryCleaner is a tool to free up memory on your computer. This is a free app with a simple user interface that makes it easy for users of all skill levels to use. MemoryCleaner uses many functions built into Windows to free up memory without affecting your system. You can also access Memory Cleaner's functions right from the system tray without having to open the program. The cleaning processes are silent and the only time you see a warning is to briefly display the amount of RAM...
</description></item><item><title>Download Kodi 21.3</title><pubDate> Mon, 24 Nov 2025 16:38:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kodi-2948.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kodi-2948.html
</guid><description>
Kodi is a media player and entertainment center, open source and free can be used on OSX, Linux, iOS, Windows and Android, user interface graphics for use with TV and remote commands. It allows users to play and view most music, videos, podcasts and other media files digital other.
Kodi - The powerful multimedia
Features of Kodi
Music
Kodi can play all your music formats including flac, mp3, wav or wma. It has table hints, features card reader and smart playlists to control the music...
</description></item><item><title>Download IsoBuster Pro 5.7 Build 5.7.0.00</title><pubDate> Mon, 24 Nov 2025 16:38:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-isobuster-pro-146.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-isobuster-pro-146.html
</guid><description>
IsoBuster is a recovery tool, data CD and DVD is used, very professional and easy to use. It supports all disc formats CD and DVD, and all the system files CD and regular DVD... rescue lost files from CD or DVD is damaged or broken, save important documents, precious pictures, video from the family, the backup system your unique.
IsoBuster Pro
Salient features IsoBuster Pro
Download at from FileNugget Fast and secure download speed high Download and stream more than 10,000 movies,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Digital Anarchy Samurai Sharpen Video OFX 1.3.1 for DaVinci Resolve and Nuke</title><pubDate> Mon, 24 Nov 2025 16:37:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-digital-anarchy-samurai-ofx-11151.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-digital-anarchy-samurai-ofx-11151.html
</guid><description>
Easily enhance your footage with Samurai Sharpen for video. Video footage is often a bit soft, and enhancing it to sharpen certain details can make a difference. Samurai Sharpen lets you do this quickly with tools designed to make it easy for you to isolate specific areas of your footage and sharpen only those areas. It's advanced sharpening technology makes video footage precise and simple.
Built-in masking tools let you protect shadows and highlights from sharpening. This is important...
</description></item><item><title>Download UltFone Windows Data Recovery 10.6.6.6</title><pubDate> Mon, 24 Nov 2025 16:37:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ultfone-windows-data-recovery-14195.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ultfone-windows-data-recovery-14195.html
</guid><description>
UltFone Windows Data Recovery is a comprehensive data recovery software designed for Windows system to recover lost or deleted files from various storage devices such as hard drive, USB drive, SD card, etc. The software supports recovering many file types, including photos, videos, documents, music and archive files. The software offers two scanning modes—quick scan for recently deleted files and deep scan for comprehensive recovery, and also allows users to preview recoverable files...
</description></item><item><title>Download Alternate File Move 2.610</title><pubDate> Mon, 24 Nov 2025 16:36:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-alternate-file-move-5104.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-alternate-file-move-5104.html
</guid><description>
Alternate File Move is a simple program to sync (or mirroring) the content of two folders. To achieve this, the number of file operations required is reduced to a minimum. The program provides a number of options / settings to perform the processing like this:
	- Compare files by size
	- Compare files by date (different, older, newer)
	- Compare files by content
	- Added missing files into the destination folder
	- Delete files not in source directory
	- Include the empty folder to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Digital Anarchy Flicker Free OFX 3.0.4 for DaVinci Resolve and Nuke</title><pubDate> Mon, 24 Nov 2025 16:36:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-digital-anarchy-flicker-free-ofx-11150.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-digital-anarchy-flicker-free-ofx-11150.html
</guid><description>
Digital Anarchy Flicker Free OFX is a plugin designed for video editing and compositing software that supports the OFX (OpenFX) standard. It was developed by Digital Anarchy, a software company known for creating various plugins and tools for video editors and visual effects artists.
Flicker Free OFX is specifically designed to solve the problem of flickering or inconsistent lighting in video footage. Flicker can occur in video for a variety of reasons, including changes in lighting...
</description></item><item><title>Download JoyToKey 7.3.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 24 Nov 2025 16:35:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-joytokey-1983.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-joytokey-1983.html
</guid><description>
JoyToKey (or Joy2Key) enables game controller PC simulation input keyboard and mouse for Windows applications and web games can be controlled by the joystick of your favorite! Whenever the buttons and sticks are pressed on the controller, JoyToKey will convert them into keyboard strokes and / or mouse movement to the destination application will act as able to use the keyboard and mouse real. JoyToKey lets create some configuration file, which supports up to 16 joysticks, compatible with...
</description></item><item><title>Download Beauty Box Photo for Photoshop 6.0.3</title><pubDate> Mon, 24 Nov 2025 16:35:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-beauty-box-for-photoshop-12578.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-beauty-box-for-photoshop-12578.html
</guid><description>
Beauty Box for Photoshop is a powerful skin retouching plugin designed for Adobe Photoshop, aimed at simplifying the process of enhancing your portraits and images. It allows you to quickly and easily erase skin blemishes and wrinkles, even out skin tone and reduce shine – achieving consistent professional results. This plugin uses advanced skin smoothing techniques that enhance the work of photographers of all levels in Adobe Photoshop. Plus, over 30 new presets let you apply a...
</description></item><item><title>Download Simple Sticky Notes 6.8.5</title><pubDate> Mon, 24 Nov 2025 16:34:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-simple-sticky-notes-2180.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-simple-sticky-notes-2180.html
</guid><description>
Simple Sticky Notes is software that creates sticky notes on screen Desktop computer help you easily remember the schedule of his. Simple Sticky Notes allow users to fashion digital sticky / post it notes and almost "sticky" notes on a desktop operation Windows. It is completely ideal for the kind of users who need to write everything down with pen and paper to avoid the discomfort of forget everything. This program of articles simple digital notes, it certainly will prove to be of great...
</description></item></channel></rss>