<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 21:37:11 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 21:37:11 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download MemoryCleaner 1.9.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Dec 2025 00:12:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-memorycleaner-12469.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-memorycleaner-12469.html
</guid><description>
MemoryCleaner is a tool to free up memory on your computer. This is a free app with a simple user interface that makes it easy for users of all skill levels to use. MemoryCleaner uses many functions built into Windows to free up memory without affecting your system. You can also access Memory Cleaner's functions right from the system tray without having to open the program. The cleaning processes are silent and the only time you see a warning is to briefly display the amount of RAM...
</description></item><item><title>Download Driver Easy Professional 7.1.1 Build 3510</title><pubDate> Mon, 22 Dec 2025 23:20:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-driver-easy-pro-431.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-driver-easy-pro-431.html
</guid><description>
DriverEasy Pro is a compact software that allows users to scan the computer system to find, download missing drivers for the computer or update outdated drivers on the system. DriverEasy Pro is considered the leading software in software used to install Drivers for computers.
The process of using DriverEasy Pro software is very simple. Users just need to download the software and install &amp;gt;&amp;gt; select "Scan Now" to scan Drivers on the system &amp;gt;&amp;gt; "Update All" Update. When using...
</description></item><item><title>Download Photo Calendar Creator Pro 20.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 22 Dec 2025 23:18:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photo-calendar-creator-pro-6296.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photo-calendar-creator-pro-6296.html
</guid><description>
Photo Calendar Creator Pro  is a feature-rich application for designing and printing original photo calendars. A wide range of pre-made templates, a rich image gallery, and plenty of editing tools are available to you to create hundreds of unique calendar designs. This calendar maker allows you to create calendars for any year and month, past or future.
The step-by-step wizard guides you through the main steps of creating a custom calendar, from choosing a template, starting year and...
</description></item><item><title>Download 3DP Chip 25.12</title><pubDate> Mon, 22 Dec 2025 23:18:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-3dp-chip-2282.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-3dp-chip-2282.html
</guid><description>
3DP Chip is software commonly used in the update of the version latest driver for your computer. The advantage of this software is completely free, compact and easy to use. 3DP Chip will help the hardware always works in the best state, with the 3DP Chip, you can know the driver has been outdated, then let the software automatically searches for the latest version and installed for your system.
3DP Chip - Download and update driver
With the 3DP Chip you can learn everything about the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Duplicate Photo Cleaner 7.24.0.58</title><pubDate> Mon, 22 Dec 2025 23:17:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-duplicate-photo-cleaner-3892.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-duplicate-photo-cleaner-3892.html
</guid><description>
Duplicate Photo Cleaner is a powerful application and effective to help you easily find and delete the duplicate image from the hard disk. Using this tool, you will be able to easily manage and arrange the collection of your photos. Duplicate Photo Cleaner is a utility secure and free. The program has a simple interface and intuitive, allowing you to retrieve and delete the duplicate and similar images with just a few mouse clicks. The application can compare even the photo has been...
</description></item><item><title>Download KMPlayer (KMP) 2025.12.22.13 x64 / 4.2.3.30 x86</title><pubDate> Mon, 22 Dec 2025 23:17:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kmplayer-kmp-902.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kmplayer-kmp-902.html
</guid><description>
KMPlayer (KMP) is software watch movies listen to music multi-function for video enthusiasts. KMPlayer development is many types of the format different. KMPlayer has improved on sound quality, images when listening to music and watching movies, the playback speed of video is faster, more codec player is added to the software video decoder is optimized.
KMPlayer also supports a variety of audio formats and video and offers a the interface can be customized with the preview coverflow and...
</description></item><item><title>Download OCCT 15.0.12.99</title><pubDate> Mon, 22 Dec 2025 23:16:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-occt-perestroika-1680.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-occt-perestroika-1680.html
</guid><description>
OCCT is a free application designed to benchmark and overclock system components. Test tool OverClock includes 4 different tests to assess the stability of your computer. CPU and CPU: Linpack to test the processor, GPU: 3D to check stability of the graphics processor and power supply combination of CPU: Linpack and GPU: 3D to download power of you up to the maximum.
OCCT - Measuring system components
The features of OCCT
	Support is enabled for a maximum of 16 cores.
	All the tests...
</description></item><item><title>Download SEO Checker 10.5</title><pubDate> Mon, 22 Dec 2025 23:16:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-seo-checker-2514.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-seo-checker-2514.html
</guid><description>
SEO Checker (A product of genuine VOVSoft) is a tool to analyze all type of web site or personal web page. The software works in many different ways, it can help you discover the content that you have specifically chosen to analyze from suitable site. As the authors write, the program, as this program allows you to plan for your SEO strategy by providing information about the function of it, you will get a set of keyword analysis and tracking the reverse link.
SEO Checker - Support SEO...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cash Register Pro 4.0.8</title><pubDate> Mon, 22 Dec 2025 23:15:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cash-register-pro-3853.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cash-register-pro-3853.html
</guid><description>
Cash Register Pro a software cash register full of features and creative for a Windows computer, it will help you to better handle all the activities of the computer money. The application comes with the user interface logical and user friendly allows you to work quickly and do not commit the common error. The program can be used on a number of computers and offers a wide range of authorization secure and reliable. Cash Register Pro will help you track products and goods remain...
</description></item><item><title>Download HopToDesk 1.45.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 22 Dec 2025 23:15:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hoptodesk-11056.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hoptodesk-11056.html
</guid><description>
HopToDesk is a remote desktop application that allows users to access their remote computer or server from anywhere using a mobile device or browser their website. It provides a secure and convenient way to control and manage computers remotely, making it easier for individuals and teams to work remotely or access their files and applications on the go.
With HopToDesk, users can establish a secure connection to a remote computer or server and perform tasks as if they were sitting in...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tablacus Explorer 25.12.20</title><pubDate> Mon, 22 Dec 2025 23:14:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tablacus-explorer-3674.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tablacus-explorer-3674.html
</guid><description>
Tablacus Explorer is a file manager open-source is designed to help you arrange the contents of your folders. Tablacus Explorer has a user interface very simple and you will be familiar with working with this program immediately. Folders and files can be sorted or grouped by name, type, size and date when they were last modified. App can automatically remember to set your tab if you close it and allows you to copy or move items to different positions and save the settings to format an XML...
</description></item><item><title>Download Irix HDR Pro 2.3.56</title><pubDate> Mon, 22 Dec 2025 17:16:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-irix-hdr-pro-10653.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-irix-hdr-pro-10653.html
</guid><description>
Irix HDR Pro is an AI-powered photo editing application for Windows, it is available on Microsoft Store. This program has tons of professional HDR photo editing features including Sky Replacement, Face Sculpting &amp;amp; body, over 200 presets &amp;amp; AI powered tool' and is a Photo Editor in the category of photo &amp;amp; Graphics. It delivers true-to-life HDR photo editing, providing one-click edits for a full-scale professional editing toolkit.
Features of Irix HDR Pro
	Sky Replacement...
</description></item><item><title>Download Activation Program 1.16.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 22 Dec 2025 17:16:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-activation-program-12767.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-activation-program-12767.html
</guid><description>
Activation Program is a Windows and Office activator from Ratiborus for Windows 7 to 11. The program is created based on the MASSGRAVE code.
What advantages does this method have over other activation methods?
It offers the most advantages for activating older versions of Windows, such as Windows 7 to 8.1, as it can permanently activate any version of the versions This without modifying the Windows system boot process or executable files. This is the only public activator that provides...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tenorshare 4DDiG File Repair 4.3.4.6</title><pubDate> Mon, 22 Dec 2025 17:12:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tenorshare-4ddig-file-repair-5630.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tenorshare-4ddig-file-repair-5630.html
</guid><description>
Tenorshare 4DDiG File Repair is AI-powered software to repair damaged or damaged videos, photos, files and audios, improve their quality and add color to black media white. 4DDiG photo editing solves all photo problems like blurry photos, overexposed photos, etc. Powered by AI, it can dramatically improve image resolution and colorize black and white photos in seconds, not hours.
Features of Tenorshare 4DDiG File Repair
	Easily repair any blurry, overexposed and damaged videos, photos...
</description></item><item><title>Download Irix HDR Classic Pro 2.3.56</title><pubDate> Mon, 22 Dec 2025 17:11:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-irix-hdr-classic-pro-10652.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-irix-hdr-classic-pro-10652.html
</guid><description>
Irix HDR Classic Pro is an AI-powered photo editor that delivers true-to-life HDR photo editing, providing one-click edits to the editing toolkit professional at full scale with a highly cognitive user interface (UI).
Main features:
	Sky replacement (SkyXpress): replaces the sky and imports weather. Import custom skies and merge, blend, and integrate with your images for a natural look with AI Edge Detect.
	Presets &amp;amp; Filters: 200+ social media optimized presets with just one tap...
</description></item><item><title>Download Fan Control v252</title><pubDate> Mon, 22 Dec 2025 17:11:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fancontrol-5749.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fancontrol-5749.html
</guid><description>
FanControl is a highly customizable fan control software for Windows. Stay in control of every aspect of your PC's GPU and CPU fan with the help of this highly customizable fan control app.
Features of FanControl
	Save, edit and load multiple configurations
	Multiple temperature sources (CPU, GPU, motherboard, hard drive, ".sensor" files)
	Custom fan curve
	Fine tune fan control response with steps,% start,% stop, response time and delay
	Mix different curves and sensors...
</description></item><item><title>Download Private Windows Script (PrivWindoze) 5.8.7</title><pubDate> Mon, 22 Dec 2025 17:11:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-private-windows-script-12878.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-private-windows-script-12878.html
</guid><description>
Are you concerned about your personal information sent to others? Or do you feel that your Windows settings have many programs that you never use? Private Windows Script (or Privwindoze) provides a comprehensive anti -remote monitoring set designed to enhance your privacy when using Windows operating system.
The main features
	End the positive process. All unnecessary processes are turned off while the scanning program. A small white list is maintained.
	Clean up the positive runonce....
</description></item><item><title>Download VovSoft Auto Mouse Clicker 3.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 22 Dec 2025 17:05:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-auto-mouse-clicker-7805.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-auto-mouse-clicker-7805.html
</guid><description>
VovSoft Auto Mouse Clicker is free, simple and straightforward desktop clicker software that frees users from repetitive clicking work. This program can simulate left, right and middle mouse clicks on any window. The software maps the screen based on the coordinates to ensure that it clicks exactly where the user wants it. The program identifies clicks using user-set X and Y coordinates.
It is fully compatible with all popular programs and games that require a lot of mouse clicks such...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cppcheck 2.19.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 22 Dec 2025 17:05:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cppcheck-3379.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cppcheck-3379.html
</guid><description>
Cppcheck is a tool for static code analysis for the C programming language and C ++. It is a versatile tool can check the code is not standard. Creator and lead developer is Daniel Marjamäki. Cppcheck is free software under The GNU general public License. Cppcheck is an analysis tool static code C / C ++. It provides code analysis only for error detection and focus on detecting behaviors not defined and the coding structure dangerous. The goal is only to detect the actual error in the...
</description></item><item><title>Download VovSoft Duplicate File Finder 2.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 22 Dec 2025 16:58:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-duplicate-file-finder-6639.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-duplicate-file-finder-6639.html
</guid><description>
VovSoft Duplicate File Finder is a tool to find duplicate files on your computer. It can scan file name, file size or file content (using SHA-1 algorithm).
You may have hundreds of photos, videos, music files, or documents that you've lost track of. You're running out of disk space on your PC, but organizing your files can seem overwhelming because there are so many of them.
This utility will help you locate and remove useless file duplicates to free up disk space and better organize...
</description></item><item><title>Download GnuCash 5.14</title><pubDate> Mon, 22 Dec 2025 16:57:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gnucash-1312.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gnucash-1312.html
</guid><description>
GnuCash is an accounting application, powerful financial is designed to help you to perform all tasks related to finance. The application can be used to track all activities of your finances from bank accounts, shares and income and other costs.
GnuCash supports databases including PostgreSQL, SQLite3 and MySQL (XML backend). Note, memory is the default XML file is compressed and use the SQL database replace is optional. Note, memory is the default XML file is compressed and use the SQL...
</description></item><item><title>Download Gammadyne Scratchboard 38.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 22 Dec 2025 16:53:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gammagyne-scratchboard-7306.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gammagyne-scratchboard-7306.html
</guid><description>
The average savvy Internet user amasses countless usernames, passwords, links, contacts, account numbers, software keys, and who knows what else. Scratchboard is a store of this kind of information, the data is arranged in a "tree" structure, like a hard drive. Text can be entered into each branch of the tree and copied to the clipboard with a simple double click.
Features of Scratchboard
	Works with all versions of Windows 10, 8, 2012, 7, 2008, Vista, XP, 2003 and 2000.
	Tree data...
</description></item><item><title>Download ProfExam Suite 8.2.2.334</title><pubDate> Mon, 22 Dec 2025 16:52:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-profexam-suite-12008.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-profexam-suite-12008.html
</guid><description>
ProfExam Suite is a comprehensive software solution designed to create, manage and administer exams and tests. It is widely used in educational institutions, certification bodies and corporate training departments.
The software suite includes two main components: ProfExam Creator and ProfExam Simulator
	ProfExam Creator: This tool allows users to create and design tests with a variety of question types, including multiple choice, true/false fill-in-the-blanks, matching, and more. It...
</description></item><item><title>Download Double Commander 1.1.31</title><pubDate> Mon, 22 Dec 2025 16:52:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-double-commander-7801.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-double-commander-7801.html
</guid><description>
Double Commander is an open source file manager with two panels side by side. The idea is based on Total Commander but with new and different features. Double Commander has multi-rename tool, tabbed interface, custom columns, internal text editor, built-in file viewer, archive support (ZIP, RAR), extensive search functionality, configurable button bar, file activity logging, plug-in support and more.
Features of Double Commander
	Internal text editor (F4) with syntax...
</description></item><item><title>Download Darktable 5.4.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 22 Dec 2025 16:51:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-darktable-3959.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-darktable-3959.html
</guid><description>
Darktable is an application process work, photography, open source and developer rough. A lighttable virtual and Darktable for the photographer. It manages the negative of your digital in the database, lets you view them through a lamp can zoom and allows you to develop raw images and enhance them. Original image of you never be modified! Features color management professional to ensure fidelity in all the way in and handle GPU acceleration means you can speed up the process of his work by...
</description></item></channel></rss>