<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 11:59:19 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 11:59:19 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download OBS Studio 31.1.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 29 Jul 2025 11:27:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-open-broadcaster-software-2451.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-open-broadcaster-software-2451.html
</guid><description>
Open Broadcaster Software is abbreviated as OBS is a program to detect the type of multimedia content to the internet. It is worth noting that a simple interface and the presence of a good tool. You can adjust the quality of the audio and video before starting the broadcast, you can specify the URL, choose the resolution of the screen, etc. With strong desire, videos which you found can be saved to your hard drive.
Open Broadcaster Software - LiveStream on PC
The basic features of Open...
</description></item><item><title>Download Waterfox 6.5.11 / 2022.11</title><pubDate> Tue, 29 Jul 2025 11:26:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-waterfox-114.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-waterfox-114.html
</guid><description>
Waterfox is a 64-bit version of the foundation Firefox was built and the compiler Intel is optimized for speed and performance on Windows systems.Waterfox does not add any additional features or bling, in fact, it will automatically import all the gadgets and install is have of you, so you will feel like at home when you run it the first time.All the add-on your Firefox will work with Waterfox, however, only support the plug-in more 64-bit, is includes Adobe Flash, Oracle Java and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Folder Guard Professional 25.7.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 29 Jul 2025 11:25:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-folder-guard-professional-1314.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-folder-guard-professional-1314.html
</guid><description>
Folder Guard Professional (The most professional) software includes password computer folder to help you control access to files, folders and the Windows resource. Folder Guard to lock files and folders, your personal password to stop other users from peeking into your records.  You can even completely hide the private folder of his from almost all the apps and the folders that will be hidden until you enter the valid password. You can also protect files sensitive system from modification...
</description></item><item><title>Download Abelssoft Win11PrivacyFix 2026 v5.02</title><pubDate> Tue, 29 Jul 2025 11:24:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-abelssoft-win11privacyfix-7088.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-abelssoft-win11privacyfix-7088.html
</guid><description>
Win11PrivacyFix is a utility that allows you to disable services on the Windows operating system and prevent the collection of user's personal data in Windows 11. The program will help solves all the problems of Windows 11 violating user privacy when using PC.
Win11PrivacyFix is easy to use, but if you don't understand what you're turning off, you risk breaking apps or features that require some of these settings. Luckily, you may want to create a restore point before you begin, just in...
</description></item><item><title>Download VSO ConvertXtoDVD 7.5.0.135</title><pubDate> Tue, 29 Jul 2025 11:24:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vso-convertxtodvd-182.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vso-convertxtodvd-182.html
</guid><description>
VSO ConvertXtoDVD is specialized software used to convert video and burn to DVD with many formats including AVI, MKV, MOV, DivX, WMV, MTS, MPEG... and you can watch it on any player whatsoever, in general is convenient. ConvertXtoDVD supports work with a large number of video formats among them MPEG, AVI, DV, MOV and so on, you can see on the official website, also support working with video online.
VSO ConvertXtoDVD
In addition, the use of VSO ConvertXtoDVD to edit the audio files as...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sandboxie 5.71.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 29 Jul 2025 11:23:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sandboxie-818.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sandboxie-818.html
</guid><description>
Sandboxie software to browse the Web securely while still keeping all the functionality your browser for content works against harmful agents such as sanbox up your computer. You may not know, when you browse the Web, the change will occur with the system of your computer. When you use Sandboxie, the software will protect the web browser of their own.
Sandboxie - web protection, safe browsing
The main features of Sandboxie
Stay safe on the Internet with Sandboxie
	Run the program in...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sandboxie Plus 1.16.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 29 Jul 2025 11:23:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sandboxie-plus-4962.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sandboxie-plus-4962.html
</guid><description>
Sandboxie Plus is an application version of the open source project on Github, equipped with software to protect your information while browsing the web or running valuable software. doubt. Web browsing, downloading or running software can affect system security. To prevent this from happening, a high user experience and strong layers of protection are needed to prevent malware from spreading to the system. For example, by opening an unknown application, malware in flash memory can...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinScript 1.3.7</title><pubDate> Tue, 29 Jul 2025 11:22:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winscript-12800.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winscript-12800.html
</guid><description>
WinScript is an open source tool built to help you build custom scripts for Windows 10 and 11. It includes scripts for debugging, privacy, performance, and more, along with the ability to install all your favorite apps with just one click.
Features
	Debloat: Remove Windows bloatware, CoPilot, Edge, OneDrive, and other pre-installed features preset.
	Privacy: Disable Windows and 3rd party data collection, tracking, app access, and telemetry.
	Performance: Set background services to...
</description></item><item><title>Download PilotEdit Pro 20.1.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 29 Jul 2025 11:21:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pilotedit-979.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pilotedit-979.html
</guid><description>
PilotEdit is software edit the textfile to help you execute scripts, extract strings and edit large files. PilotEdit is the editing file will help you search and replace multi-line text, edit files, FTP or even download and upload files and folders FTP. With edit file PilotEdit becomes easier.
PilotEdit - edit text files
PilotEdit is a hex-editor and advanced text support opening files larger than 4GB. It provides syntax to customize and highlight keywords, advanced search and replace...
</description></item><item><title>Download Windows Activator by Goddy 5.4</title><pubDate> Tue, 29 Jul 2025 11:21:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-activator-by-goddy-8844.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-activator-by-goddy-8844.html
</guid><description>
Windows Activator by Goddy is a very simple and fast activator to activate Windows 11, 10, 8.1, 8 and 7.
It has a very simple interface like a command line interface provided by the Windows operating system. Windows versions are clearly ordered and divided into tables corresponding to each version of Windows in common use today.
Note: Since this is a Windows activator, your anti-virus software may prevent the application from working correctly. And always run the software with "Run as...
</description></item><item><title>Download XYplorer 27.10.0200</title><pubDate> Tue, 29 Jul 2025 11:20:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-533.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-533.html
</guid><description>
XYplorer - File Manager for Windows is software that supports users to manage files on the Window quickly and to arrange the folder tidy. XYplorer features tabbed browsing, search, files, powerful, preview, flexible, highly customizable interface, dual frame options and a variety of unique ways to automate effective tasks often repeat. It's fast, lightweight, and portable.
Features XYplorer
	XYplorer is a file manager mobile. It does not require any settings, store all configuration...
</description></item><item><title>Download Macrium Reflect Workstation / Server / Server Plus 8.1.8620</title><pubDate> Tue, 29 Jul 2025 11:20:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-macrium-reflect-1444.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-macrium-reflect-1444.html
</guid><description>
Macrium Reflect is software backup and recovery files, image files, with big improvements in speed, simplicity and strength. The software we provide taiwebs.com 've included 3 version is Macrium Reflect Workstation / Server / Server Plus. Whole our focus is to help organizations protect critical data and business systems, without fuss and budget breaking.
Macrium Reflect - backup and restore files
The function of Macrium Reflect
	Backup tool new: image gradually increases and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Abelssoft Win10 PrivacyFix 2026 v7.02.63960</title><pubDate> Tue, 29 Jul 2025 11:13:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-abelssoft-win10-privacyfix-2193.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-abelssoft-win10-privacyfix-2193.html
</guid><description>
Win10 PrivacyFix blocked servers transfer data of Microsoft and disable the appropriate service. Abelssoft Win10 PrivacyFix is an interesting program to disable the tracking function in Windows 10, now I will explain why. We immediately attracts attention to the developer, Abelssoft - as far as I remember, all their programs are paid, you definitely need to see the official website.
Abelssoft Win10 PrivacyFix - Disable Microsoft services
After the start, judging by the screenshot, we...
</description></item><item><title>Download GiMeSpace RAM Folder Pro 2.2.6.49</title><pubDate> Tue, 29 Jul 2025 11:08:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gimespace-ram-folder-pro-12250.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gimespace-ram-folder-pro-12250.html
</guid><description>
GiMeSpace RAM Folder Pro allows assigning folders to store files only in RAM memory instead of on your disk as well as providing secure write caching for file writes. So it combines the best of both RAM and disk caching programs but with minimal overhead making it even faster than those programs.
The Pro version has a special option to enable smart write caching on a folder. This means that the files in those folders will be written to disk once the program is done with them. This is...
</description></item><item><title>Download Abelssoft EasyBackup 2026 v16.0.63247</title><pubDate> Tue, 29 Jul 2025 11:07:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-abelssoft-easybackup-173.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-abelssoft-easybackup-173.html
</guid><description>
Abelssoft Backup is a great software that allows you to backup your important data to a safe location in case of corruption or damaged due to random or some form of data loss other surprises. Backup interface is modern, minimalist. It has a simple instructions guide you through the process of your backup in a few simple steps.
Abelssoft Backup
You can add multiple tasks into the manager and you can perform any task any of them by a single click. Utilities software mode support...
</description></item><item><title>Download Klevgrand STARK 1.2.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 29 Jul 2025 11:02:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-klevgrand-stark-13807.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-klevgrand-stark-13807.html
</guid><description>
STARK is a complete amplifier simulator consisting of four modules: Amplifier, Cabinet, Room and Pedal Board. The modules process the sound separately, making it possible to combine different amplifiers with different cabinets and rooms.
What makes STARK different from other amplifier simulators is that the cabinet, amplifier and ambient modules are built on Klevgrand's own algorithms, which do not involve any convolution or FFT analysis. This method creates a more natural response to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ultra Adware Killer 10.9.7</title><pubDate> Tue, 29 Jul 2025 11:02:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ultra-adware-killer-2137.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ultra-adware-killer-2137.html
</guid><description>
Ultra Adware Killer is a software dedicated to block and remove adware annoying, sluggish in performance of your operating system. Ultra Adware Killer interface is quite good-looking when the functions are arranged in tabs for easy control and use. App has the ability to scan the system and detect Adware on the browsers Internet Explorer, Chrome, FireFox. All the processes, the file contains Adware or doubt are software, ads are displayed for you to conduct screening and removal.
Ultra...
</description></item><item><title>Download Futuremark SystemInfo 5.85.1374</title><pubDate> Tue, 29 Jul 2025 11:01:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-futuremark-systeminfo-2568.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-futuremark-systeminfo-2568.html
</guid><description>
Futuremark SystemInfo is a small program created to conduct diagnostic analysis complete all kinds of processes, as well as equipment used on a personal computer of you. According to the author, you can use this tool as a component reference in the application be supported, it will determine the version of your operating system and other information about the hardware.
Note that Windows XP, 3DMark06, and PCMark05 are no longer be Futuremark support. Function SystemInfo on Windows XP is...
</description></item><item><title>Download SysTools OST Splitter 7.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 29 Jul 2025 11:01:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-systools-ost-splitter-5772.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-systools-ost-splitter-5772.html
</guid><description>
SysTools OST Splitter is an application that can easily split large Outlook OST files into smaller sized PST files. Outlook desktop installation is required in order to use this tool to split large OST files.
Features of SysTools OST Splitter
	Split oversized OST file into several sections by Date, Size, Year, Folder, Email ID,
	Category option to repair corrupted Outlook OST files before splitting
	Allow user to split OST file without any file size limitation into UNICODE PST...
</description></item><item><title>Download Steelray Project Analyzer 7.20.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 29 Jul 2025 11:00:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-steelray-project-analyzer-607.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-steelray-project-analyzer-607.html
</guid><description>
Steelray Project Analyzer is software reviews schedules and resources for multiple projects and create reports to improve quality and performance. Steelray Project Analyzer is software that eases the creation, maintenance and provide schedule quality. With The analysis, you can evaluate the progress of your project in terms of quality and performance in minutes and produce results easy to understand. The schedule can be analyzed against the best practices of project management best...
</description></item><item><title>Download Abelssoft HackCheck 2026 v8.0.63941</title><pubDate> Tue, 29 Jul 2025 11:00:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-abelssoft-hackcheck-686.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-abelssoft-hackcheck-686.html
</guid><description>
Abelssoft HackCheck is software to monitor the online account of you to detect the hacker attacks and alert you when attacks occur! If the data of the your account online, you have the risk of being stolen by criminals, the program will emit alarm sound. Scan and monitor all the user accounts constantly against the attacks of hacker. Who is notified can act with purpose! Hacks guides, news and basic information.
Features of Abelssoft HackCheck
	Protecting background for your account:...
</description></item><item><title>Download S.O.S Security Suite 2.9.7</title><pubDate> Tue, 29 Jul 2025 10:54:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sos-security-suite-6227.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sos-security-suite-6227.html
</guid><description>
S.O.S Security Suite is a free, user-friendly app that helps you remove malware, ad software, and spy software, and also prevent infection. There is also a hardware error detection and security error detection and system optimization module. All these features combine to bring you what stands for the application: A more secure and optimal system.
S.O.S Security Suite is a successor to UVK and is designed to help you remove malware, ad software, and spy software, and help you not get...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tape Label Studio Enterprise 2025.7.0.8330</title><pubDate> Tue, 29 Jul 2025 10:53:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tape-label-studio-enterprise-8907.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tape-label-studio-enterprise-8907.html
</guid><description>
Tape Label Studio Enterprise is a useful and effective software solution that aims to provide business owners with a simple way to create your own barcodes. It is a powerful tool for organizations that need to manage the number of labels and barcodes. By simplifying the label creation process and providing many advanced features, it can help organizations save time and improve their overall label management process.
Features of Tape Label Studio Enterprise
	Customizable Label...
</description></item><item><title>Download Vladovsoft Fitorg 16.1.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 29 Jul 2025 10:53:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vladovsoft-fitorg-5029.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vladovsoft-fitorg-5029.html
</guid><description>
Vladovsoft Fitorg is a software management room, easy to use, affordable. Vladovsoft Fitorg includes membership details, bookings, deliveries and sales, product, service, book, recipes, accounts, payments and track membership. Ideal for fitness clubs, gym, health club, entertainment center, and fitness.
The advantages of Vladovsoft Fitorg
	The software is optimized for fast operation even on the computer and old laptop
	Management software, club very easy to use
	User...
</description></item><item><title>Download Photo Grade Pro 1.2.6 Build 126</title><pubDate> Tue, 29 Jul 2025 08:17:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photo-grade-pro-13969.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photo-grade-pro-13969.html
</guid><description>
Photo Grade Pro is a color grading software designed to help content creators create stunning images quickly and easily without too much complexity. The software offers a user-friendly interface that allows color correction by simply pointing and clicking directly in the large viewer, making precise color adjustments easy even for beginners. The software supports both standalone use and plugins for Adobe Photoshop and Lightroom Classic, allowing integration into familiar...
</description></item></channel></rss>