<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 17:44:06 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 17:44:06 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Thorium Reader 3.3.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 10 Dec 2025 17:54:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thorium-reader-11878.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thorium-reader-11878.html
</guid><description>
Thorium Reader is open source ebook reading software designed to deliver a seamless and feature-rich reading experience. It supports various e-book formats, including EPUB, PDF, and CBZ, allowing users to read their favorite books, magazines, and comics from a single app.
Thorium Reader is a user-friendly, versatile ebook reader software designed to meet the needs of bookworms and digital readers. With a customizable interface, extensive format compatibility, accessibility features, and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare Recoverit 14.0.9.8</title><pubDate> Wed, 10 Dec 2025 17:52:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-recoverits-374.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-recoverits-374.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare Recoverit is a data recovery software that is easily lost at a rapid rate and is used by many people. You will do what happens if one day your data is suddenly lost due to the virus or deleted it, .. Wondershare Recoverit will provide you with an environment to protect important data.
Wondershare Recoverit has all the scanning processes that are divided into multiple types, from the typical recovery of the deleted files that are deleted to the recovery of missing files due...
</description></item><item><title>Download Topaz Gigapixel Pro 1.0.5</title><pubDate> Wed, 10 Dec 2025 17:52:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-ai-gigapixel-1318.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-ai-gigapixel-1318.html
</guid><description>
Topaz ONE Gigapixel is the first app and only use the power of artificial intelligence to enhance your photos, add natural details, for great results. Use technology to learn deep, AIGigapixel ™ can zoom in and fill in the details that the products change in size other are not included. The traditional method this created blurred image, a non-realistic and do not have the detail present in the image have high resolution.
Topaz A.I. Gigapixel - enhance image quality
The content of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare UniConverter 17.1.1.457</title><pubDate> Wed, 10 Dec 2025 17:51:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-uniconverter-4808.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-uniconverter-4808.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare UniConverter ( old name is Wondershare Video Converter Ultimate) which allows you to convert the video format. You can cut, splice, move, or add effects, subtitles a easy way. When using software you easily cut, splice, move, as well as add the effects, the subtitles to the video.... Or can switch the clods SD, HD video to any format popular for use with iPod (Classic, Nano and Touch), iPhone, Apple TV, Zune, PSP, Pocket PC...
Wondershare UniConverter helps convert formats...
</description></item><item><title>Download Topaz Video AI Pro 7.1.6 / 1.1.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 10 Dec 2025 17:50:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-video-enhance-ai-3733.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-video-enhance-ai-3733.html
</guid><description>
Topaz Video Enhance AI is a tool to increase video quality with this great technology ONE. Topaz Video Enhance WHO wide open your video to resolutions up to 8K with the details and consistency of motion. Until the present, there is no way to re-create a perfect high resolution video from the footage is low resolution. From the family film to SD low quality to DVD quality and more than that, Video Enhance WHO will convert your video into the footage is upgrade clear with resolutions up to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare Repairit 6.6.0.12</title><pubDate> Wed, 10 Dec 2025 17:49:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-recoverit-video-repair-3889.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-recoverit-video-repair-3889.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare Recoverit Video Repair is a reliable application that helps you fix the broken video, Wondershare Recoverit Video Repair supports file formats MP4, MOV, M4V, M2TS, MKV, MTS, 3GP, AVI and FLV is corrupt and broken. Great service we provide. It fixes the video that there is corruption in the process of shooting, when done, file transfer, while editing, convert.
Wondershare Recoverit Video Repair - video repair broken
Features of Wondershare Recoverit Video Repair
	Repair...
</description></item><item><title>Download PMAS - PowerShell Multi Activation System 10.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 10 Dec 2025 17:48:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-powershell-tsf-activation-13584.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-powershell-tsf-activation-13584.html
</guid><description>
This advanced PowerShell script is a flexible and modular solution designed for licensing Windows and Office products. It runs a custom .NET library called LibTSforge.dll directly from memory to license Office. It can work in GUI mode or silent mode.
Features
	License management for both Windows and Office products
	Generate product keys with the help of LibTSforge.dll
	User-friendly graphical options with Out-GridView
	Compatible with KMS, MAK, RETAIL, OEM, AVMA license types
	In...
</description></item><item><title>Download AIDA64 Extreme / Engineer 8.20.8100</title><pubDate> Wed, 10 Dec 2025 17:47:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aida64-1297.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aida64-1297.html
</guid><description>
AIDA64 is a powerful tool to identify and test virtually all components of personal computers running operating systems Windows.  AIDA64 give you detailed information on all hardware and software, in addition, with the integrated modules for testing and calibration can be checked more for each subsystem PC individually. Display detailed information about all hardware and software is installed on your system.
AIDA64 Extreme/Engineer
Features AIDA64
	Level information about motherboard...
</description></item><item><title>Download High-Logic FontCreator Professional 15.0.0.3038</title><pubDate> Wed, 10 Dec 2025 17:47:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-high-logic-fontcreator-professional-1533.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-high-logic-fontcreator-professional-1533.html
</guid><description>
High-Logic FontCreator Professional allows you to create and edit TrueType fonts and OpenType. It has the powerful drawing tools that typographers and graphic designers require, and an intuitive interface that allows beginners to become productive immediately.
When you create or open a font, FontCreator displays an overview of all available characters. You can only add the characters missing, or select an existing character, and modify its appearance. You can import (scanned) signature...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft .NET Desktop Runtime 10.0.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 10 Dec 2025 17:46:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-net-desktop-runtime-5748.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-net-desktop-runtime-5748.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft .NET Desktop Runtime allows you to run existing Windows desktop applications. This release includes the .NET Runtime, which requires no separate installation. The Microsoft .NET Desktop Runtime redistributable package installs the .NET Desktop Runtime and related files needed to run many applications that use this programming language.
This is Microsoft's comprehensive and consistent programming model for building applications with stunningly intuitive user experiences,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Dreamweaver 2021 v21.7.0.15757 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Wed, 10 Dec 2025 17:45:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-0010-adobe-dreamweaver-1701.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-0010-adobe-dreamweaver-1701.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Dreamweaver 2021 is software that provides you with faster, easier ways to design, write code and publish websites and web apps that look great on every screen size. Quickly create and publish websites almost everywhere with the web design software that supports HTML, CSS, JavaScript and more.
After using Adobe Dreamweaver CC, users will quickly create and publish web pages almost everywhere with the web design software that supports HTML, CSS, JavaScript and more. Create, encrypt...
</description></item><item><title>Download 4K Tokkit Pro 25.4.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 10 Dec 2025 17:44:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-tokkit-pro-6753.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-tokkit-pro-6753.html
</guid><description>
4K Tokkit Pro is an application created to bulk download TikTok content., save TikTok videos, captions, entire accounts, hashtags and single videos in high quality. . Watch TikToks offline, browse your TikTok feed without ads, repost clips to other social networks.
Features of 4K Tokkit Pro
	Download videos in bulk from your TikTok account. Save all videos from profile and get TikTok user's profile picture.
	Automatically get updates from your favorite TikTok creators and...
</description></item><item><title>Download AIDA64 Business / Network Audit 8.20.8100</title><pubDate> Wed, 10 Dec 2025 17:44:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aida64-business-5689.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aida64-business-5689.html
</guid><description>
AIDA64 Business can gather a very detailed arsenal of hardware and software from Windows clients connected to the corporate network. Since it supports command line switching, inventory creation can be fully automated, while reports collected from a PC can be saved in open formats ready for further processing. , as well as into SQL databases. Changes between network test snapshots taken at different times can be tracked in the built-in change manager. It can notify network administrators in...
</description></item><item><title>Download XtraTools Pro 25.12.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 10 Dec 2025 17:43:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xtratools-pro-7168.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xtratools-pro-7168.html
</guid><description>
XtraTools Pro is a universal tool for MS Windows system optimization that takes care of all aspects of your computer like optimizing the registry and removing unnecessary program to establish network connection and increase RAM speed. It is a compact tool with an intuitive interface that gives you complete control over the boot process, memory monitoring and a huge set of system settings that control your computer. The current version of the software provides the following tools: Folder...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ahnenblatt 4.39.0.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 10 Dec 2025 17:43:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ahnenblatt-3844.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ahnenblatt-3844.html
</guid><description>
Ahnenblatt is a genealogy software full-featured, easy to use suitable for beginners and even pedigree has the experience to organize genealogy research by you. Use plausibility checks to find out the inaccuracies in your family and create the chart impressive with just a few mouse clicks.
Ahnenblatt - Create family tree,
Recently, there has been strong increase of the general interest of the public for genealogical tree. Users who desire to track their heritage have many tools at...
</description></item><item><title>Download DoYourData Super Eraser 8.2 Business</title><pubDate> Wed, 10 Dec 2025 17:42:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-doyourdata-super-eraser-business-1210.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-doyourdata-super-eraser-business-1210.html
</guid><description>
DoYourData Super Eraser offers a simple solution and safe to delete the data from PC, hard drive, RAID arrays, servers, USB drive, memory card, digital camera, SD card, external hard drive. It will permanently cancel and delete the selected data, leaving no chance of recovery, which does not affect the lifespan of the device.
DoYourData Super Eraser Business - Delete data securely
Features of DoYourData Super Eraser Business
	Support delete data from many different devices, including...
</description></item><item><title>Download ArmorTools Professional / Home 25.12.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 10 Dec 2025 17:42:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-armortools-7726.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-armortools-7726.html
</guid><description>
ArmorTools is a set of tools that extend the capabilities of the MS Windows operating system in the field of security and protection of user confidential information. ArmorTools allows you to create secure virtual disks encrypted with AES128/AES256 algorithms, encrypting files and folder contents using any file as a password.
ArmorTools erases the user's work traces on the computer, deletes the history of accessing websites, deletes confidential information without the possibility of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Secure Eraser Pro 7.007</title><pubDate> Wed, 10 Dec 2025 17:41:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secure-eraser-1003.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secure-eraser-1003.html
</guid><description>
Secure Eraser is a software to delete data permanently on the folder of the hard drive to data can not be recovered by any software. Secure Eraser is software delete data completely best. The software has simple interface and very small capacity. In addition, the software Secure Eraser also helps to tidy and clean the system, prevent the fragmentation of the hard drive.
Secure Eraser - Tool To Delete Data Permanently
Secure Eraser supports 4 standard delete data (US DoD 5220,22-ME, US...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft Office Pro Plus - Online Installer 3.3.9</title><pubDate> Wed, 10 Dec 2025 17:41:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-office-professional-plus-online-installer-7661.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-office-professional-plus-online-installer-7661.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft Office 2021 Professional Plus x86-x64 - Online Installer is a small script that helps users to download and install Microsoft Office 2021 Professional Plus including all updates directly from Microsoft CDN Server.
The version of Office 2021 downloaded and installed on your computer will include the following programs: Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Outlook, OneNote, Publisher, Access, Visio, Project, ProofingTools, OneDrive Desktop.
Usage:
Unzip the downloaded ZIP Archive...
</description></item><item><title>Download 4KSoftware 4K Downloader 6.0.11</title><pubDate> Wed, 10 Dec 2025 17:40:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-downloader-3858.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-downloader-3858.html
</guid><description>
4K Downloader is a Windows application small but powerful to download and convert video in 4K and 8K Ultra HD from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion and thousands of other video-based websites. It speeds up your download by up to 5 times. Consider that most smart phones, TVS, computers, and tablets all support the high definition format, don't be surprised when many users want to enjoy quality content on their device. 4K Downloader is a lightweight software designed to help you grab videos...
</description></item><item><title>Download Leawo Music Recorder 3.0.0.7</title><pubDate> Wed, 10 Dec 2025 17:40:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-leawo-music-recorder-752.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-leawo-music-recorder-752.html
</guid><description>
Leawo Music Recorder is software that can record audio Mic and stream audio to another very useful for people who love music. Leawo Music Recorder is recorder computer, record music online and record music from Last.fm, iTunes Radio, YouTube audio, BBC music, Pandora and other programs. You can save the audio files recorded in multiple formats, such as MP3 or WAV. Leawo Music Recorder also provides The task scheduler to set the time and the start time recorded. Besides, the program can add...
</description></item><item><title>Download TubeMate Downloader 6.0.11</title><pubDate> Wed, 10 Dec 2025 17:39:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubemate-downloader-4250.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubemate-downloader-4250.html
</guid><description>
TubeMate Downloader is a smart application that lets you download any clip you want from the website hosting the main video and convert them in when download at or then. If you need a simple and effective tool to download videos, you can give it a try. With TubeMate Downloader, you can directly drag and drop video link from your browser into the drop-down box or application window to start downloading. You don't even need to copy and paste the video URL.
TubeMate Downloader - Support...
</description></item><item><title>Download pdfMachine Ultimate 20.52</title><pubDate> Wed, 10 Dec 2025 17:39:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdfmachine-ultimate-959.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdfmachine-ultimate-959.html
</guid><description>
pdfMachine Ultimate  is a PDF reader and editor. Additionally, pdfMachine converts a print stream from an application directly into PDF. Just open your document you want to convert, then click "print", choose "Broadgun pdfMachine printer" and the conversion is complete.
pdfMachine Ultimate - Read and edit PDF files 
Broadgun pdfMachine Ultimate  will make it easy to read  PDF  files for PDFs or other portable document formats that make extensive use of the original file formats...
</description></item><item><title>Download TikTok Bot Pro 3.6.7</title><pubDate> Wed, 10 Dec 2025 17:39:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tiktok-bot-pro-11635.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tiktok-bot-pro-11635.html
</guid><description>
TikTok Bot Pro is software designed to automate activities and interactions on TikTok to attract real followers on TikTok. It automates your “likes” and “comments,” finds new followers categorized by similar accounts, and attracts followers who are actually interested in your content.
Here is a list of features you will find in this software:
	GET FOLLOWERS: Export your TikTok followers from those who follow other profiles and/or users based on specific tags.
	AUTO-FOLLOW:...
</description></item><item><title>Download Notepad++ 8.8.9 + Portable</title><pubDate> Wed, 10 Dec 2025 17:04:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-notepad-1062.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-notepad-1062.html
</guid><description>
Notepad++ is software editor programming editor and edit source code support on Windows platform, working with many other programming languages like ASP, PHP, Java, C#, Python, Jsp... Notepad++ is a source code editor is many programmers choice with many functions than men of it is Notepad.
Notepad++ - tool editor programming
Notepad++ has many features, simple interface, and can combine with many programming languages different. Notepad++ supports you to automatically perform various...
</description></item></channel></rss>