<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 21:37:22 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 21:37:22 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download iDefender 5.3.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 10 Jan 2026 22:58:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idefender-13959.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idefender-13959.html
</guid><description>
iDefender is an advanced security solution designed for the home, providing both a High-Performance Intrusion Prevention System (HIPS) and Real-Time Endpoint Detection and Response (EDR). This integrated system protects against potential threats, ensuring the safety and integrity of your devices by proactively monitoring and responding to suspicious activity.
Why iDefender?
Ransomware Prevention
	Detects and blocks ransomware in real time to protect important files from malicious...
</description></item><item><title>Download PrivaZer 4.0.116</title><pubDate> Sat, 10 Jan 2026 22:57:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-privazer-66.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-privazer-66.html
</guid><description>
PrivaZer : the program performs the scan is very thorough not only includes the trace downloads like registration, Internet history, cookies, etc but also find the traces of potential in the field of free disk space of you. PrivaZer can permanently delete all traces by using the method of secure erase and also re-establish the sector disk free to 0 to remove all traces from the delete operation earlier. The process of scanning and cleaning the original can spend less time (20-30 minutes),...
</description></item><item><title>Download pdfFactory Pro 9.20</title><pubDate> Sat, 10 Jan 2026 18:29:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdffactory-pro-277.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdffactory-pro-277.html
</guid><description>
pdfFactory Pro is software to create PDF files according to standards in a simple and secure documents secure. pdfFactory Pro on taiwebs.com that support encryption (40 or 128bit) and control access to the PDF file.
pdfFactory Pro has all the features of pdfFactory and adds bookmarks, job order, title a letter and the email function automatically. Only pdfFactory allows printing to paper or PDF without printing twice. Acrobat is not needed for the printing. Increases the convenience of...
</description></item><item><title>Download reaConverter Pro 8.0.178</title><pubDate> Sat, 10 Jan 2026 18:29:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html
</guid><description>
reaConverter Pro is software image processing feature with batch conversion and image editing periodically becomes simple. eaConverter also provide command line utilities allow you to process images automatically, thus helping you shorten the time for other work.
reaConverter Pro integrated powerful tool of Uber with many great features. It provides advanced solutions to process and adjust images. Management of the conversion process the base image with the latest version of...
</description></item><item><title>Download WYSIWYG Web Builder 20.4.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 10 Jan 2026 18:29:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wysiwyg-web-builder-177.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wysiwyg-web-builder-177.html
</guid><description>
WYSIWYG Web Builder : The construction of the website from scratch using HTML code isn't a pleasant process, even when you know what you are doing. The website can be built using WYSIWYG Web Builder with using the element similar to the package published on the desktop: text and images placed in frames and tables on the page, so very little surprised when most of the efforts to make the web become a experience user-friendly than. the controls do you use to build your pages.
WYSIWYG Web...
</description></item><item><title>Download Corel Painter 2023 v23.0.0.255</title><pubDate> Sat, 10 Jan 2026 18:28:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-corel-painter-1847.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-corel-painter-1847.html
</guid><description>
Corel Painter is the photo editing software comprehensive help quickly change the quality, add effects to the images in a simple way, the tool also supports users to blur, creating a new picture... with the tools available pen color water color pencils... and other colors for users to design, build is a photo comments. Corel Painter will help the artist finishing the limitations are not there in the picture of her by the designer for this include the effects generated material oil...
</description></item><item><title>Download FinePrint 12.20</title><pubDate> Sat, 10 Jan 2026 18:27:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fineprint-276.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fineprint-276.html
</guid><description>
FinePrint is a software support you work in text saves paper and increases the lifespan of your printer. FinePrint is a software connected printer, you can print 4 or 8 pages file on the computer on a page of paper that still ensure the font is clear, easy to read.
With FinePrint works for you, the incidents of printing annoyances will disappear. Below are just some examples of incidents in which FinePrint can fix. Read more part of our Business for the benefit of the FinePrint in the...
</description></item><item><title>Download ManicTime Pro 2025.3.6.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 10 Jan 2026 18:27:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-manictime-18.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-manictime-18.html
</guid><description>
ManicTime is a software automatically collect information about how to use your computer. It records the time of operation of the machine, see the change data in the machine, how much data you share, received on or moved away, what software you use, use at any time
ManicTime allows you to keep up the work of the staff, send progress reports accurately and manage your time better than ever. This type of software can help your business more efficient when it comes to the internal problems...
</description></item><item><title>Download Secret Disk Pro 2026 v317</title><pubDate> Sat, 10 Jan 2026 18:26:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secret-disk-pro-933.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secret-disk-pro-933.html
</guid><description>
Secret Disk Pro 4 is a software to create a virtual disk can be hidden and password protected to keep your data private and safe. You can store any file and folder on the disk. Disc secret works like a hard disk typically, and is compatible with any any other program that you have installed. You can have more than one disk secret, and you can also choose disk letter.
Secret Disk Pro 4 - Create and secure drive
Secret Disk does not encrypt any files, it just limits access to your files...
</description></item><item><title>Download Bigasoft Video Downloader Pro 3.28.8.9497</title><pubDate> Sat, 10 Jan 2026 18:26:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bigasoft-video-downloader-pro-940.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bigasoft-video-downloader-pro-940.html
</guid><description>
Bigasoft Video Downloader Pro  is an online video downloader and converter from YouTube and other online movies to play on personal computers, mobile devices, mobile phones, players MP4 music, TV and easier. Video Downloader can save online video as HD, HQ and 3D movies, then convert to MP4, AVI, WMV, MOV, MKV, FLV, MPG, VOB, etc. for playback on a variety of great digital devices. iPad mini, iPad, iPod, iPhone, Google Nexus, Microsoft Surface, Kindle Fire, BlackBerry, Apple TV, Zune, PSP,...
</description></item><item><title>Download CoolUtils Total Image Converter 8.2.0.290</title><pubDate> Sat, 10 Jan 2026 18:25:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-total-image-converter-848.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-total-image-converter-848.html
</guid><description>
CoolUtils Total Image Converter is software to convert images to other formats, and can edit, cut, resize and rotate them. With Total Image Converter you easy convert TIFFs into JPEGS, make photos suitable for the web or recover old photos in the supported format.
&amp;nbsp;CoolUtils Total Image Converter - convert images to other formats
Features CoolUtils Total Image Converter
	Total Image Converter supports almost all image formats
	Support convert eagle picture series.
	Total Image...
</description></item><item><title>Download Memtest86 Pro 11.6 Build 1000 + ISO</title><pubDate> Sat, 10 Jan 2026 18:25:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-memtest86-pro-725.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-memtest86-pro-725.html
</guid><description>
Memtest86 Pro is software check free RAM memory in your computer to detect the latent fault inside the memory. Anyone know RAM is very important part of the computer. If RAM is error that does not fix soon will greatly affect your computer. Therefore, the Memtest86 Pro is the software necessary for the system of your computer.
Memtest86 Pro - Check memory RAM
Features of Memtest86 Pro
	13 algorithm to check RAM different
	Support RAM DDR4 (and DDR2 &amp;amp; DDR3)
	XMP - configuration...
</description></item><item><title>Download Chaos Intellect 10.7</title><pubDate> Sat, 10 Jan 2026 18:24:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chaos-intellect-4213.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chaos-intellect-4213.html
</guid><description>
Chaos Intellect is the email application and the contact management the next generation of our all in one great program! We will give you five good reasons to switch from app to email your ex and turn Intellect into the email program you choose! If you are looking for a contact manager without email integration, we also made. Chaos Intellect Email client and contact manager. The latest addition to our line, our products have big success since its release and is ready for Vista! Continue...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Video Downloader 12.1.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 10 Jan 2026 18:23:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-video-downloader-9636.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-video-downloader-9636.html
</guid><description>
YT Video Downloader is software used to easily and quickly download any video or audio content from any website in HD quality using video downloader online. Save videos from almost any website supported by a video downloader on your local hard drive. Media search is a convenient way to do this.
Features of YT Video Downloader
	Download videos from hundreds of video sites.
	Really increase your download speed by up to 500% or even more!
	Download 8K, 5K, 4K Ultra HD, 2K Quad HD, 1080p...
</description></item><item><title>Download Bigasoft Audio Converter 5.8.2.9497</title><pubDate> Sat, 10 Jan 2026 18:23:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bigasoft-audio-converter-6059.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bigasoft-audio-converter-6059.html
</guid><description>
Bigasoft Audio Converter is an easy sound conversion tool, which provides a quick way to convert favorites between most formats including MP3, WMA, M4A, AAC, AC3, WAV, OGG, AIFF, ALAC, CAF, etc. The digital conversion to sound can be used as MP3 converge, WMA converge, M4A converge, etc.
Moreover, the MP3 sound converge supports bulk transformation, so you can handle multiple transfers at the same time and place the starting point and time to listen to your great music videos....
</description></item><item><title>Download NTFS Permissions Reporter Enterprise 5.0.628.0 All Editions</title><pubDate> Sat, 10 Jan 2026 18:22:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ntfs-permissions-reporter-enterprise-6370.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ntfs-permissions-reporter-enterprise-6370.html
</guid><description>
System administrators are constantly required to check user rights for specific files and folders. This is often a time-consuming work, with multiple NTFS classes and repetitive adjustments over time creating a security maze. NTFS Permissions Reporter Enterprise allows you to confirm the security status of the entire file system quickly and efficiently. All have multiple export formats, command line support, integration scheduling, advanced filtration, and more.
Features of NTFS...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaMonkey Gold 2024.2.1.3201 Beta</title><pubDate> Sat, 10 Jan 2026 18:22:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediamonkey-gold-231.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediamonkey-gold-231.html
</guid><description>
MediaMonkey Gold is music manager and music player multimedia for the music collection and iPod users. MediaMonkey lists the audio file of you as CD, OGG, WMA, MPC, FLAC, APE, WAV and MP3 and includes the edit smart card and an automatic file and folder to arrange your music library.
MediaMonkey Gold also has CD ripper, CD / DVD Burner, and audio converter for saving music, and manual or editor list automatically to create mixed music.
Features MediaMonkey Gold
	Automatically find...
</description></item><item><title>Download XL-Connector 3.6.38.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 10 Jan 2026 18:22:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xl-connector-12415.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xl-connector-12415.html
</guid><description>
XL-Connector is a popular plugin that securely integrates Excel and Salesforce to export, import, refresh and transform data seamlessly with ultra-fast api connection. It provides Salesforce administrators with a comprehensive toolbox that easily performs data and metadata management activities in a familiar Excel environment.
Features
Export from Salesforce to Excel
	Get data from existing Salesforce reports or build your own SOQL queries directly into Excel.
Import data into...
</description></item><item><title>Download TubeMate Downloader 6.1.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 10 Jan 2026 18:21:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubemate-downloader-4250.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubemate-downloader-4250.html
</guid><description>
TubeMate Downloader is a smart application that lets you download any clip you want from the website hosting the main video and convert them in when download at or then. If you need a simple and effective tool to download videos, you can give it a try. With TubeMate Downloader, you can directly drag and drop video link from your browser into the drop-down box or application window to start downloading. You don't even need to copy and paste the video URL.
TubeMate Downloader - Support...
</description></item><item><title>Download Bigasoft WTV Converter 5.8.2.9497</title><pubDate> Sat, 10 Jan 2026 18:21:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bigasoft-wtv-converter-6058.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bigasoft-wtv-converter-6058.html
</guid><description>
Bigasoft WTV Converter is an ideal program that allows you to convert a live television program that has been written in WTV format from Windows Media Center to any other format for rebroadcast on multiple media or multimedia devices. This professional WTV Converter can also help convert video to WTV format that can be easily played on Windows PC or streaming to TV and certain multimedia devices, such as the Xbox 360.
Bigasoft WTV Converter is a good choice for switching between...
</description></item><item><title>Download Bitvise SSH Client 9.56</title><pubDate> Sat, 10 Jan 2026 17:52:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bitvise-ssh-client-2845.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bitvise-ssh-client-2845.html
</guid><description>
Bitvise SSH Client is a SSH terminal, tunneling and file transfer application SFTP for free with the command line interface and graphics. It supports all versions desktop and server of Windows! Bitvise SSH Client for free use! Bitvise SSH Client is an application multipurpose, fast and powerful in the transmission of the advanced file helps users control and manage the terminal remotely in a flexible manner. Bitvise SSH Client intensive support for establishing the secure connection...
</description></item><item><title>Download Visual Studio Code 1.108.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 10 Jan 2026 17:52:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-visual-studio-code-3182.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-visual-studio-code-3182.html
</guid><description>
Visual Studio Code is the encryption tool of Microsoft has met most of the needs of the developer. Environment this encoding was introduced to compete with other products such as Sublime and Nodepad ++ . Microsoft, in its new product, has not been released in many years, has provided many features in a simple environment. In addition to the familiar with a dozen programming languages, the syntax and get to know coding language as soon as be encrypted and allows for syntax highlighting, it...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Substance 3D Modeler 1.22.5.1223 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Sat, 10 Jan 2026 17:37:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-substance-3d-modeler-7876.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-substance-3d-modeler-7876.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Substance 3D Modeler is a 3D sculpting and modeling application that helps you create on both desktop and VR. Modelers aim to make working in 3D as intuitive as working with clay in real life. To help achieve this, with Adobe Substance 3D Modeler you don't have to worry about adjusting vertices or managing UVs, you can instead focus on the creative process.
With its intuitive design, Adobe Substance 3D Modeler frees you from the technical constraints of traditional 3D modeling....
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Substance 3D Sampler 5.1.3.8787 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Sat, 10 Jan 2026 17:37:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-substance-3d-sampler-6625.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-substance-3d-sampler-6625.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Substance 3D Sampler allows you to create and iterate on collections of materials by refining and blending existing materials or by extracting new materials from scans ( one or more images). A new set of powerful tools that combine different technologies and creation methods (AI-based and manual) will help you manage your entire document library and export them to other applications.
Features of Adobe Substance 3D Sampler
	AI-powered scan processing
	Use your content everywhere....
</description></item><item><title>Download O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro 22.1.235 / Server</title><pubDate> Sat, 10 Jan 2026 17:36:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-diskimage-pro-218.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-diskimage-pro-218.html
</guid><description>
O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro is software backup data comprehensive and effective is provided to protect the data of the computer system, it creates images for individual drives or the entire system that still does not affect your system.
O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro allows the user to backup the entire computer or drive, the and files whenever you want even while the computer is being used. Or can use O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro to create a copy chinh sac of computer disk drives, can be used instead of the...
</description></item></channel></rss>