<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 03:30:26 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 03:30:26 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download MSActBackUp 1.2.9</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Sep 2025 20:07:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-msactbackup-5215.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-msactbackup-5215.html
</guid><description>
MSActBackUp is a program to save and restore activation Windows versions: Vista, 7, Windows 8, 8.1, 10, Server 2008, 2008 R2, 2012, 2012 R2, 2016 and Office 2010/2016. Press the corresponding button, check the keys to determine the program and, if necessary, specify the correct key. When this button operation, the process flow activation is complete.
To restore activate: go to the tab "Restore activation", select the folder where you saved the activation and start activate the restore...
</description></item><item><title>Download iTop Easy Desktop 3.2.0.145</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Sep 2025 20:06:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-itop-easy-desktop-7879.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-itop-easy-desktop-7879.html
</guid><description>
iTop Easy Desktop is a lightweight and easy-to-use desktop manager that organizes desktop icons, files and folders according to your rules, helping you Freed from the tedious arrangement of icons on the screen. It provides various practical features including but not limited to grouping desktop items, awakening live search, and quickly accessing icons and files even across multiple desktop sites. desktop.
Untidy desktop If you're not one to diligently organize your Windows desktop icons...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Premiere Pro 2025 v25.5.0.013 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Sep 2025 20:03:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-premiere-pro-0021-1361.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-premiere-pro-0021-1361.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Premiere Pro is the leading video editing software for film, TV, and the web. Creative tools, integration with other Adobe apps and services, and the power of Adobe Sensei help you turn footage into finished movies and videos in a seamless workflow. It offers high-quality video editing at 4K x 4K resolution and beyond, with 32-bit color, in both RGB and YUV color spaces. Edit audio samples, support for VST audio plug-ins (plug-ins), and 5.1 surround sound tracks. The Premiere Pro...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Illustrator 2025 v29.8.1.2 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Sep 2025 20:02:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-illustrator-0016-749.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-illustrator-0016-749.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Illustrator is a powerful vector graphics editor developed by Adobe Inc., first released in 1987. It is primarily used by graphic designers, illustrators, and artists to create high-quality illustrations, logos, icons, and digital artwork. Unlike raster graphics editors like Adobe Photoshop, which manipulate images pixel by pixel, Illustrator uses mathematical formulas to create vector graphics. This allows designs to be scaled infinitely without losing quality, making it ideal for...
</description></item><item><title>Download Coolmuster Android Backup Manager 3.5.26</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Sep 2025 20:01:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-android-backup-manager-4744.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-android-backup-manager-4744.html
</guid><description>
Coolmuster Android Backup Manager is software assist you to data backup your Android phone before actually lost, such as contacts, SMS, photos, documents, etc. in Addition, if you need to restore backup Android phone to new Android phone, Coolmuster Android Backup Manager can help you realize all the requirements of backup and restore Android without any trouble.
Coolmuster Android Backup Manager allows you to backup Android phone to PC just by one-click and gives you full rights to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Media Encoder 2025 v25.5.0.013 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Sep 2025 20:01:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-0010-adobe-media-encoder-1360.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-0010-adobe-media-encoder-1360.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Media Encoder 2024 is a professional audio and video converter that allows you to encode audio and video files into various distribution formats for applications different uses and audiences. Such video and audio formats are characterized by a high degree of compression. By downloading this program on taiwebs.com, you can export videos in formats supported by various devices, from DVD players and websites to mobile phones, portable media players and High Definition and High...
</description></item><item><title>Download pdfMachine Ultimate 20.50</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Sep 2025 20:00:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdfmachine-ultimate-959.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdfmachine-ultimate-959.html
</guid><description>
pdfMachine Ultimate  is a PDF reader and editor. Additionally, pdfMachine converts a print stream from an application directly into PDF. Just open your document you want to convert, then click "print", choose "Broadgun pdfMachine printer" and the conversion is complete.
pdfMachine Ultimate - Read and edit PDF files 
Broadgun pdfMachine Ultimate  will make it easy to read  PDF  files for PDFs or other portable document formats that make extensive use of the original file formats...
</description></item><item><title>Download Pazu StreamGet All-In-One Video Downloader 2.8</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Sep 2025 19:59:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pazu-streamget-all-in-one-video-downloader-12037.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pazu-streamget-all-in-one-video-downloader-12037.html
</guid><description>
StreamGet All-In-One Video Downloader is the ultimate downloading solution for you. It supports downloading any movies and shows from the most popular streaming sites including Netflix, Prime Video, Disney Plus, Max, Hulu, and Apple TV Plus. The downloader is continuously updated to support more platforms in the future.
Download movies and shows from various streaming platforms to MP4/MKV on your Windows device and enjoy them anywhere you want.
Features of Pazu StreamGet All-In-One...
</description></item><item><title>Download MobiKin Backup Manager for Android 2.0.24</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Sep 2025 19:59:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mobikin-backup-manager-for-android-4861.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mobikin-backup-manager-for-android-4861.html
</guid><description>
MobiKin Backup Manager for Android is tool is top ranking for Android to backup and restore flexible, files Android to avoid data loss. Restore function of MobiKin Backup Manager for Android providing assistance timely for a number of users lost Android phone, accidentally deleted phone data or restore their device to its original factory settings. With backup Android to PC using this software, you can restore the backup from PC to any Android device just by a click of the mouse.
There...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft Activation Scripts 3.7</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Sep 2025 18:05:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-activation-scripts-5390.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-activation-scripts-5390.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft Activation Scripts is an open source Windows and Office activation tool that features online HWID, Ohook, KMS38 and KMS activation methods, along with advanced troubleshooting functionality.
Activation methods
			Trigger type
			Supported products
			Activation time
			HWID
			Windows 10-11
			Permanent
			Ohook
			Office
			Permanent
			KMS38
			Windows 10-11, Server
			Until 2038
			Online KMS
			Windows / Office
			180 days (with...
</description></item><item><title>Download Power-user for PowerPoint and Excel 1.7.53.156</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Sep 2025 18:03:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-power-user-for-powerpoint-and-excel-522.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-power-user-for-powerpoint-and-excel-522.html
</guid><description>
Power-user for PowerPoint and Excel is a utility providing you with a library of templates, icons, charts, maps and diagrams for spreadsheet and presentation. With Power-user for PowerPoint and Excel, you will attract the attention of your audience with stunning graphics will certainly impress.
Power-user comes with a collection of 2,000 icons to illustrate your slides. The icons are vector shapes so you can resize them without distortion and color back as you with. With Power-user, you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Master PDF Editor 5.9.94</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Sep 2025 18:03:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-master-pdf-editor-612.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-master-pdf-editor-612.html
</guid><description>
Master PDF Editor is a powerful software that helps users to view, create and modify PDF documents or combine multiple files into one, split a source document into several documents, and also review, sign, and encrypt PDF files. With Master PDF Editor you can add text with any format to documents in PDF or edit existing text. You can also insert images into your document, select and move the object, change the size of the object save image to a file and copy them to the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Luminar Neo 1.24.7 (15515)</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Sep 2025 18:02:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-luminar-neoo-7194.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-luminar-neoo-7194.html
</guid><description>
Luminar Neo is an innovative image editor powered by futuristic AI technologies that simplifies complex editing workflows and allows creators to turn their boldest ideas into reality. Luminar Neo calculates image depth and generates 3D maps, allowing you to naturally scatter light in 3D across a 2D image. This opens the door to unleash your creativity to bring your artistic vision to life.
MaskAI automates the masking process by identifying objects in the image and creating the correct...
</description></item><item><title>Download MAGIX VEGAS Pro 23.0.0.278</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Sep 2025 18:01:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-magix-vegas-pro-81.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-magix-vegas-pro-81.html
</guid><description>
MAGIX VEGAS Pro provides an interface fully customizable brings maximum flexibility. Full of new features, both inside and outside, MAGIX VEGAS Pro create the power for your creativity. Whether you work in HD or 4K, VEGAS Pro willing to become a partner of your creativity. Video / Audio production, and DVD / Blu-ray authoring all in one powerful software package.
FEATURES, CHARACTERISTICS MAGIX VEGAS Pro
VEGAS Pro provides all the tools you need to edit your video quickly. Coding...
</description></item><item><title>Download UniFab 3.0.2.8</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Sep 2025 18:01:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-unifab-10377.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-unifab-10377.html
</guid><description>
UniFab is software to efficiently convert, compress and edit more than 1000 video formats for playback on any device without losing quality. Enlarge video/audio to 1080p/DTS 7.1 and upgrade video to HDR10 or Dolby Vision with AI Enhancer. UniFab Pro provides the best AI-powered zoom tool that allows you to enlarge videos from low resolutions, such as 360p, 480p and 720p, to 1080p without losing any quality. Clearer and sharper image details will bring you an exceptional viewing...
</description></item><item><title>Download 4KSoftware 4K Downloader 5.17.5</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Sep 2025 18:00:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-downloader-3858.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-downloader-3858.html
</guid><description>
4K Downloader is a Windows application small but powerful to download and convert video in 4K and 8K Ultra HD from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion and thousands of other video-based websites. It speeds up your download by up to 5 times. Consider that most smart phones, TVS, computers, and tablets all support the high definition format, don't be surprised when many users want to enjoy quality content on their device. 4K Downloader is a lightweight software designed to help you grab videos...
</description></item><item><title>Download n-Track Studio Suite 10.2.2.10189</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Sep 2025 17:59:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-n-track-studio-2991.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-n-track-studio-2991.html
</guid><description>
n-Track Studio is a recording software allows you record and create MIDI music and sounds top quality. The software allows you to add effects, VST3, DirectX, AU (Mac), VST and ReWire different on each track or channel. This program also allows you to automatically fade out, fade in and fade out or increase the volume of the music to indicate the voice of the singer.
n-Track Studio can record and playback the number of audio, MIDI and sound unlimited. In addition, you can handle the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Power-user Premium 1.7.53.156</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Sep 2025 17:59:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-power-user-premium-3149.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-power-user-premium-3149.html
</guid><description>
Power-user is a plugin for software, Microsoft Excel, PowerPoint and Word help you to provide more visual content so you can create the spreadsheet attractive. It contains templates, icons, tables, drawings and charts, modern, professional, allows you to build professional looking documents. You can add custom content to your project just by a click of the mouse and surprise clients and colleagues with your skills on Excel, PowerPoint and Word.
Power-user Premium - Plugin Excel,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Print Artist Photo Projects 2 v25.0.3.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Sep 2025 17:58:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-print-artist-photo-projects-12683.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-print-artist-photo-projects-12683.html
</guid><description>
Print Artist Photo Projects is designed to help users create and print professional-quality photo projects quickly and easily. The software offers many templates and graphics to enhance creativity. Everything you need to create amazing photo projects for home, school or the office! The fast, easy and fun way to create spectacular print projects. Bring your photos to life with Print Artist Photo Projects 2.
Features of Print Artist Photo Projects 2
	Create and print...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Downloader 9.16.8</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Sep 2025 17:58:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html
</guid><description>
YTD Youtube Downloader is an application that reliable and intuitive, allowing you to quickly download YouTube videos and save them to your computer. You can also convert the media files to the format desired video or extract audio streams and save separately. YTD Youtube Downloader lets you save your favorite clips of yourself from Youtube, Facebook, Vimeo and Dailymotion to your desktop. The software supports URLS from many web site hosting, multimedia and allows you to download desired...
</description></item><item><title>Download QuadSpinner Gaea 2.2.3.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Sep 2025 17:58:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quadspinner-gaea-3870.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quadspinner-gaea-3870.html
</guid><description>
QuadSpinner Gaea is design software terrain, sophisticated and modern for results the top in moments. The top tools of QuadSpinner Gaea makes realism became the basis. Workflows are streamlined, allowing you to easily gain visibility and work in parallel with your team. Interface is extremely modern and our multitude of gadgets stimulate creativity, not limit it. Working at Gaea very interesting and can help you set a performance standard new.
QuadSpinner Gaea - design software...
</description></item><item><title>Download Visual Studio Code 1.104.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Sep 2025 17:57:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-visual-studio-code-3182.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-visual-studio-code-3182.html
</guid><description>
Visual Studio Code is the encryption tool of Microsoft has met most of the needs of the developer. Environment this encoding was introduced to compete with other products such as Sublime and Nodepad ++ . Microsoft, in its new product, has not been released in many years, has provided many features in a simple environment. In addition to the familiar with a dozen programming languages, the syntax and get to know coding language as soon as be encrypted and allows for syntax highlighting, it...
</description></item><item><title>Download Win Screen Recorder 2025 v10.0.0.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Sep 2025 17:57:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-win-screen-recorder-7793.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-win-screen-recorder-7793.html
</guid><description>
Win Screen Recorder 2022 is a convenient and easy to use screen recording software that allows you to record any part of the screen, record HD video and audio, and capture screenshot any time you want.
Features of Win Screen Recorder
	Includes Filmmaker and Video Editor.
	It's easy to create your own movies from images and video clips.
	Add Music, Text, Animation, Effects and Mosaic to your videos.
	Cut, join, crop and rotate your video.
	Publish your video to the Internet or DVD.
</description></item><item><title>Download Daemon Tools Lite 12.3.0.2357</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Sep 2025 17:56:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-daemon-tools-lite-3391.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-daemon-tools-lite-3391.html
</guid><description>
DAEMON Tools Lite is based on two key features, simulation of virtual disks and building the file disk image as iso. DAEMON Tools Lite can emulate up to 4 virtual drives, DVD, CD or Blu-ray on your computer. The virtual units will be present in your system the same as the unit. After you select the virtual drive you want, you will choose a disc image (nrg, iso, mdf, bin, cue, etc.) that you want to mount. Visit My Computer at the device have The mobile storage and you will find the disk...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tomabo MP4 Downloader Pro 5.7.6</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Sep 2025 17:52:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tomabo-mp4-downloader-pro-3602.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tomabo-mp4-downloader-pro-3602.html
</guid><description>
Tomabo MP4 Downloader Pro is the app designed exclusively for Windows users to help them download videos from the Internet. In addition, it also increase download speeds by up to 500%, or even more. Tomabo MP4 Downloader Pro, interface design, simple, well-organized, beautifully. Here, users can view a list of videos has download with gravatar, URL, quality, duration and size of them. Software allows download video series at the same time, at the same time, support create a list of clips...
</description></item></channel></rss>