<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 17:37:35 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 17:37:35 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Glary Utilities Pro 6.31.0.35</title><pubDate> Mon, 08 Sep 2025 20:08:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-utilities-pro-76.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-utilities-pro-76.html
</guid><description>
Glary Utilities Pro is a collection of tools and system utilities to fix, speed up, maintain and protect your computer. Glary Utilities Pro allows you to clean junk files, system downloads, as well as the subscriptions are not valid and Internet traces (that support the plug-in more for the 45+ program outside). You can also manage and delete add-ons of the browser, analyze the use of disk and find the file duplicate.
Glary Utilities Pro - optimized system
Key features Glary Utilities...
</description></item><item><title>Download FxSound (FxSound Enhancer Premium) 1.1.36 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Mon, 08 Sep 2025 20:07:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fxsound-enhancer-premium-2013.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fxsound-enhancer-premium-2013.html
</guid><description>
FxSound Enhancer Premium formerly DFX Audio Enhance, is accessories multimedia software most popular in the world with over 46 million downloads worldwide. FxSound enhances the sound of most of the music content and online video is live streaming on the Web, including the streaming service, YouTube, Pandora, Spotify and Apple Music. FxSound Enhancer Premium also implemented enhanced real-time audio on the player PC multimedia most popular include iTunes, Windows Media Player, Winamp and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Duplicate Files Fixer 1.2.1.1078</title><pubDate> Mon, 08 Sep 2025 20:06:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-duplicate-files-fixer-3417.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-duplicate-files-fixer-3417.html
</guid><description>
Duplicate Files Fixer - You know that your system usually accumulate too many files, duplicate occupy much storage capacity do not? Tool copy duplicate files is a simple tool designed to find and delete all the duplicate files that easily! This convenient tool makes your system more organized!
Duplicate Files Fixer - Find and delete duplicate files
Copy file duplicate identify exactly all the file formats are identical. Find the text, images, audio and video files identical it's easy...
</description></item><item><title>Download Stardock ObjectDock 3.01</title><pubDate> Mon, 08 Sep 2025 20:06:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stardock-objectdock-14105.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stardock-objectdock-14105.html
</guid><description>
Stardock ObjectDock is a software that helps customize the Windows computer interface by creating a dock like on the macOS operating system. This dock allows users to add frequently used application icons and folders for quick access, making the desktop screen more neat and convenient.
Features of ObjectDock
	Allows adding application icons and folders by dragging and dropping directly into the dock.
	There are many effects such as zooming in on the icon when hovering over...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinPE 11-10-8 Sergei Strelec 2025.09.07</title><pubDate> Mon, 08 Sep 2025 20:06:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winpe-10-8-sergei-strelec-8027.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winpe-10-8-sergei-strelec-8027.html
</guid><description>
WinPE 11-10-8 Sergei Strelec is a Windows 11, 10 and 8 PE boot disk for computer maintenance, hard disks and partitions, disk and partition backup and restore, computer diagnostics, data recovery, installation Windows.
Assembly components include:
	WinPE 11 x64
	WinPE 10 x64
	WinPE 10 x86
	WinPE 8 x86
	WinPE 8 x86 (Native)
System Requirements:
1. RAM 1 GB or more
2. PC can boot from CD/DVD or USB drive.
</description></item><item><title>Download 4K Tokkit Pro 25.3.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 08 Sep 2025 20:05:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-tokkit-pro-6753.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-tokkit-pro-6753.html
</guid><description>
4K Tokkit Pro is an application created to bulk download TikTok content., save TikTok videos, captions, entire accounts, hashtags and single videos in high quality. . Watch TikToks offline, browse your TikTok feed without ads, repost clips to other social networks.
Features of 4K Tokkit Pro
	Download videos in bulk from your TikTok account. Save all videos from profile and get TikTok user's profile picture.
	Automatically get updates from your favorite TikTok creators and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Dont Sleep 9.81</title><pubDate> Mon, 08 Sep 2025 20:01:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dont-sleep-89.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dont-sleep-89.html
</guid><description>
Don't Sleep allows you can set the date and custom time that you want to reactivate the feature manager usual sources or you can set a countdown fast to pause the power management in X hours.
Can temporarily disable the protection of your screen or off your computer at a certain time.
The main features of the Dont Sleep:
- Optimal power supply for computer
- Installation time power source according to
- Prevent computer reboot
Content update Dont Sleep 5.66:
The official website...
</description></item><item><title>Download AnyMP4 Blu-ray Copy Platinum 7.3.20</title><pubDate> Mon, 08 Sep 2025 20:00:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anymp4-blu-ray-copy-platinum-1972.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anymp4-blu-ray-copy-platinum-1972.html
</guid><description>
AnyMP4 Blu-ray Copy Platinumsoftware Blu-ray great and full of features, have the technology to copy and burn the most advanced to help users copy any Blu-ray disc (2D / 3D) how to Blu-ray disc / folder / ISO image file. Software Blu-ray Copy of this wonderful help copy a 1: 1 ratio perfectly, even supports compressing BD-50 to a BD-25 single performance with absolutely no error. That certainly is the right solution to make backups of Blu-ray movies and has been proven to be a trustworthy...
</description></item><item><title>Download FxSound Pro 1.1.36 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Mon, 08 Sep 2025 19:59:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fxsound-5966.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fxsound-5966.html
</guid><description>
FxSound Pro is a professional software that helps to enhance the quality of sound, volume, depth, and sound on your PC. FxSound brings you a great sound just with a downloadable download. After using FxSound, you will know if it is for you or not. Most people do n' t know what they ' re missing in their sound until they try their software/sound hardware better. It ' s hard to convey if you do n' t really experience yourself.
Reason to use FxSound Pro:
	The perfect sound on every...
</description></item><item><title>Download Glarysoft Malware Hunter Pro 1.205.0.836</title><pubDate> Mon, 08 Sep 2025 19:57:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glarysoft-malware-hunter-pro-235.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glarysoft-malware-hunter-pro-235.html
</guid><description>
Glarysoft Malware Hunter capabilities, comprehensive protection against threats, data protection and privacy, ensure the computer is no longer virus. It allows you against many types of viruses, trojans with the ability to super fast scanning to detect and remove the malware quickly. Glarysoft Malware Hunter has a simple design of the interface, but the pace of new work is the most important problem of this software.
Features Glarysoft Malware Hunter Pro
	Automatically search, detect,...
</description></item><item><title>Download RustDesk 1.4.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 08 Sep 2025 19:57:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rustdesk-12244.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rustdesk-12244.html
</guid><description>
RustDesk is a full-featured open source remote alternative for self-hosting and security with minimal configuration. It allows users to access and control their computers remotely from anywhere in the world, providing a convenient solution for remote work, technical support, or accessing files and applications on the go. transfer.
RustDesk is continuously updated and improved, providing a reliable and effective remote desktop solution. Whether you work remotely, need remote technical...
</description></item><item><title>Download SlickEdit Pro 2024 v29.0.3</title><pubDate> Mon, 08 Sep 2025 19:57:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-slickedit-pro-5576.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-slickedit-pro-5576.html
</guid><description>
SlickEdit Pro is designed by developers for developers, SlickEdit's award-winning source code and text editor is respected for its rich set of coding tools and programming features. a powerful time saver. As a true multi-language, cross-platform editor, SlickEdit offers programmers the ability to code in more than 70 languages ​​across 9 platforms.
SlickEdit Pro: Build and debug large or complex projects. Stay in sync with built-in version control and powerful file diff tools. All...
</description></item><item><title>Download Glary Malware Hunter PRO 1.205.0.836</title><pubDate> Mon, 08 Sep 2025 19:56:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-malware-hunter-pro-77.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-malware-hunter-pro-77.html
</guid><description>
Glary Malware Hunter PRO - detection of file malware on your computer and delete dangerous content, allowing you to run on-demand scan of the area, important system or specific files. As suggested by its name, Malware Hunter is designed to find and remove the files and components potential danger on your computer, keep it out of the virus and the type of threat other.
Glary Malware Hunter PRO - perfect protection of your equipment
Features Glary Malware Hunter PRO
- Scan ultrasound...
</description></item><item><title>Download Glary Tracks Eraser 6.0.1.25</title><pubDate> Mon, 08 Sep 2025 19:56:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-tracks-eraser-1342.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-tracks-eraser-1342.html
</guid><description>
Glary Tracks Eraser is security software privacy when browsing the web, allows you to delete all traces of network access and trace number, including browser cache, cookies, the website is already open, the URL has been entered, the document new mines, temporary files,... Glary Tracks Eraser that helps you free up space in hard disk drives, scan entire junk files in the drive with the speed of processing is extremely fast. Data deleted by Glary Tracks Eraser will not be able to restore,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Big Fish Games Keygen 2025.08.18</title><pubDate> Mon, 08 Sep 2025 19:55:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-big-fish-games-2043.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-big-fish-games-2043.html
</guid><description>
Big Fish Games that we share this software is provided by Vovan help provide Key for the game Big Fish Games without resorting to other software. As many people who love the game also know as Big Fish Games bring gaming experience great and attractive is built on the foundation of publishing exclusive of it. The company is headquartered in Seattle, WA, with a regional office in Oakland, CA, and is a part of Aristocrat Leisure Limited.
Big Fish Games - Provide Key for more than 4723...
</description></item><item><title>Download Silent Install Builder 6.4.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 08 Sep 2025 19:55:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-silent-install-builder-2391.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-silent-install-builder-2391.html
</guid><description>
Silent Install Builder is a great tool if you need to quickly install a set of software on multiple computers. The package created by this program can contain a number of settings belonging to the different categories is app automatically recognizes. InstallShield, Inno Setup, Wise and NSIS (Nullsoft Installer) are the supported. Get acquainted with the application absolutely not difficult, thanks to the interface is well organized, intuitive. The left panel displays the components of your...
</description></item><item><title>Download RSS Guard 4.8.6</title><pubDate> Mon, 08 Sep 2025 19:54:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rss-guard-4409.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rss-guard-4409.html
</guid><description>
RSS Guard is the program has ability to fetch the format data feeds, the most popular, including RSS and RDF and ATOM. RSS Guard is designed on the Qt libraries and is compatible with this os:
	Windows XP and newer,
	GNU / Linux
	Os / 2 (eComStation),
	Mac OS X,
	xBSD (possibly),
	Android (can),
	other platforms supported by Qt.
RSS Guard - Read RSS, RDF and ATOM
RSS Guard is written in C ++. It is quite fast even with tons of messages be download. The core features are:
	-...
</description></item><item><title>Download App Builder 2025.32</title><pubDate> Mon, 08 Sep 2025 19:53:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-app-builder-241.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-app-builder-241.html
</guid><description>
App Builder is a software application developer to help create and design apps, HTML5, web app, web app PWA on both platforms mobile and desktop. App Builder is professional software supports users to create the program HTML5 without writing code. It is very easy to use, suitable with all users who lack of professional knowledge in the field of programming and application design.
App Builder brings to 22 different themes that users can use to design for your app. You can choose 1 or a...
</description></item><item><title>Download VovSoft VCF to CSV Converter 4.6</title><pubDate> Mon, 08 Sep 2025 19:53:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-vcf-to-csv-converter-7020.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-vcf-to-csv-converter-7020.html
</guid><description>
Designed with simplicity in mind, VovSoft VCF to CSV Converter can only do one task: extract contacts from the input VCF container, then convert it to a newly created CSV file anywhere on your computer. In other words, you can simply select the input VCF file and choose to export it to CSV format, all with just a few clicks.
</description></item><item><title>Download Glary Disk Cleaner 6.0.1.32</title><pubDate> Mon, 08 Sep 2025 19:53:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-disk-cleaner-1341.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-disk-cleaner-1341.html
</guid><description>
Glary Disk Cleaner is the software helps to erase the file system temporarily, cleanup your browser cache, or release the folder. Glary Disk Cleaner show scan results in detail, help you pick exactly each file to delete. The list file is much more wide open, with temporary files, user-generated, or the file system, cache, bug report, log files, data in recycle bin, the shortcut expires.
Glary Disk Cleaner - garbage system
Glary Disk Cleaner is designed to be simple as possible in use....
</description></item><item><title>Download MiniMeters 1.0.18.1918</title><pubDate> Mon, 08 Sep 2025 19:52:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minimeters-9410.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minimeters-9410.html
</guid><description>
MiniMeters is a simple standalone sound meter application for Windows. Monitor your System Audio*, Any Input, or insert the MiniMeter Server Plug-in (VST3/AU/CLAP) at the end of your main channel in the DAW of your choice. Customize the layout in a horizontal bar (perfect for above or below the audio engine of your choice) or pop out into modules to create custom layouts.
Features of MiniMeters
	6 modules to choose from to build your perfect metering setup: Spectrogram, Waveform,...
</description></item><item><title>Download CameraFTP Virtual Security System 5.1.174</title><pubDate> Mon, 08 Sep 2025 19:52:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cameraftp-virtual-security-system-12406.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cameraftp-virtual-security-system-12406.html
</guid><description>
CameraFTP VSS is a powerful video surveillance program that can turn your PC/Laptop into a CCTV/DVR security system. It can display live scenes on the screen and record footage to the cloud. You can watch or play back footage anywhere, anytime. VSS also provides powerful screen recording features to monitor computer usage, record online classes/meetings, TV shows and games.
Features of CameraFTP VSS
	Common surveillance camera system features: Can view up to 25 cameras on one...
</description></item><item><title>Download ButterScroll 1.3.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 08 Sep 2025 19:51:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-butterscroll-13824.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-butterscroll-13824.html
</guid><description>
Smooth scrolling on Windows just got better. Smooth scrolling for Windows is what ButterScroll is all about. It improves the way your mouse scrolls using customizable speed and ease settings.
Smooth scrolling for all types of mice.
ButterScroll improves your everyday scrolling experience with smooth scrolling precision, customizable controls, and a satisfying feel across all your Windows apps — from browsers to spreadsheets.
ButterScroll Features
	Easy to set up and use
	Smooth,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Reuschtools CopyWin 4.68</title><pubDate> Mon, 08 Sep 2025 19:51:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reuschtools-copywin-14136.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reuschtools-copywin-14136.html
</guid><description>
Reuschtools CopyWin is a versatile program designed to copy the contents of your Windows drive, including all files and programs, to another drive, USB or MicroSD card. This is especially useful for upgrading or replacing storage hardware, as it simplifies the migration process. The tool does not require installation; it can be used by running the executable file, but requires administrative rights to operate. CopyWin also offers features like incremental backups after the initial backup,...
</description></item><item><title>Download HTML Compiler 2025.19</title><pubDate> Mon, 08 Sep 2025 19:51:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-html-compiler-2548.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-html-compiler-2548.html
</guid><description>
HTML Compiler is a program for Microsoft Windows (tm) allows you to put an entire HTML application (including HTML, CSS, JavaScript, images, etc.) into a Windows application independent can be executed like any other application window the application. HTML Compiler allows you to customize file real exam results by changing the icon of them and set some other options. For example, you can allow or not allow the ability to print the HTML pages, allow or disallow the text selection and many,...
</description></item></channel></rss>