<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 15:51:18 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 15:51:18 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Java SE Development Kit 25.0.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jan 2026 17:45:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-java-se-development-kit-6881.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-java-se-development-kit-6881.html
</guid><description>
Java allows you to play online games, chat with people around the world, and view images in 3D. These applications, written in the Java programming language and accessible from your browser, are called applets. Companies also use Java applications for intranet applications and other e-business solutions.
Java is used by companies in all major industries. Whether deployed on mobile phones, embedded devices, game consoles, laptops, or in data centers, Java provides rich user interfaces,...
</description></item><item><title>Download ShareX 19.0.1 + Portable</title><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jan 2026 17:44:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sharex-946.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sharex-946.html
</guid><description>
ShareX is a screen capture tool lets you capture an area on your desktop and automatically save to clipboard, your hard drive or download now up more than 25 file storage service different, including Imgur, Flickr , ImageShack, TinyPic, Dropbox and others.
With the "After Capture" allows you to choose whether you want to download snapshots of yourself up hosting service or keep it locally and support more action even adding watermarks to mark copyright photos.
ShareX - Capture screen...
</description></item><item><title>Download Q-Dir 12.46</title><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jan 2026 16:47:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-q-dir-348.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-q-dir-348.html
</guid><description>
Q-Dir is software to manage the entire file and folder on the computer, allowing to see file in same time 4 different positions (viewport quadro) while still maintaining all the standard features of the Explorer.
It also provides a variety of management features, additional files included the filter file color-coding, layouts and columns can be customized, quick access to file and folder favorites and more.
Other features of Q-Dir , including directory listings (.txt, .doc .html .csv),...
</description></item><item><title>Download AI Ebook to Audio Converter 1.1.28</title><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jan 2026 16:46:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ai-ebook-to-audio-converter-13863.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ai-ebook-to-audio-converter-13863.html
</guid><description>
AI Ebook to Audio Converter converts your ebooks into high-quality audiobooks with advanced AI voice technology. Convert EPUB, PDF, and TXT files to MP3 audiobooks with natural voices, all while working completely offline with no subscription fees.
Advanced voice technology
	High-quality AI voice synthesis with natural-sounding results
	Voice mixing system - blend multiple voices together to create custom sounds
	Save and load pre-set voice settings for consistent results
	Test voice...
</description></item><item><title>Download Google Chrome 144.0.7559.97</title><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jan 2026 16:46:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-chrome-1012.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-chrome-1012.html
</guid><description>
Google Chrome web browser is the most used today. Support surf the web, listen to music, watch movies, play web game effective no jerky lag with the internet connection stable. When you are surfing the web or performing an important task, whether it is operation big or small, work or entertainment, then Chrome has the smart features and the speed you need to make, create and explore on the net.
The latest version of Google Chrome is the third 114. But we are providing for users Google...
</description></item><item><title>Download CapCut PC 7.9.0.3294 / 8.0.0.3337 Beta 5</title><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jan 2026 16:45:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capcut-pc-9995.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capcut-pc-9995.html
</guid><description>
CapCut PC is a simple video editing tool that you can freely use anywhere. You can create videos on your browser, desktop and laptop, or on your phone. Versatile editing, magical AI tools, team collaboration, and built-in assets. Create videos in a whole new way.
You can edit videos based on editing the timeline, in the process you can add different elements and effects to the video to give the best effect to your work. It is a simple and intuitive set of editing tools and effects that...
</description></item><item><title>Download Rhinoceros 8.27.26019.16021</title><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jan 2026 16:45:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rhinoceros-179.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rhinoceros-179.html
</guid><description>
Rhinoceros is design software 3D easy to learn, easy to use and has range of application in various industries. Rhinoceros (or Rhino, Rhino3D) is a graphics software CAD and 3D developed by Robert McNeel &amp;amp; Associates, a private company established in the year 1980. Rhinoceros is developed according to the algorithm NURBS mathematical model, algorithm, focus on the correct presentation of curves and surfaces mathematics in computer graphics (in contrast to the application polygon...
</description></item><item><title>Download Picture Window Pro 8.0.545</title><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jan 2026 16:44:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-picture-window-pro-7452.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-picture-window-pro-7452.html
</guid><description>
Picture Window Pro is a powerful image editing tool designed for serious photographers with strict creative and quality standards. Its comprehensive set of photo editing and editing tools let you control and shape every aspect of your images.
Picture Window Pro 8 is a complete rewrite of Picture Window Pro 7. It features non-destructive image editing through a novel interface based on an image tree. It also fully supports large, high-resolution displays and can be used in dual monitor...
</description></item><item><title>Download Bitsum Process Lasso Pro 17.0.2.18</title><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jan 2026 16:44:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bitsum-process-lasso-pro-289.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bitsum-process-lasso-pro-289.html
</guid><description>
Bitsum Process Lasso Pro is software compact statistics and troubleshoot computer systems, such as crashes by control CPU. Technological process Lassos ProBalance (process balance) adjust the smart priority of running programs so that the process works poorly or too active will not affect the ability to use your computer!
Software Process Lasso to help manage the program or application will be managed and controlled to not have the ability to monopolize the CPU. Process Lasso also...
</description></item><item><title>Download MusConv 4.10.449 Lifetime</title><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jan 2026 16:43:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html
</guid><description>
MusConv transfers playlists, albums, followed artists and liked songs across a variety of services – Spotify, Apple Music, Amazon Music, YouTube, YouTube Music, iTunes, Deezer, Tidal, SoundCloud, Pandora and more 125 music services!
Features of MusConv Ultimate
	Transfer playlists, albums, followed artists and liked tracks between over 125 music servicesManage playlists (Delete, Merge, Split, Copy...)
	More than 125 music services supported
	Access DAILY updated music charts on...
</description></item><item><title>Download reaConverter Pro 8.0.184</title><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jan 2026 16:43:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html
</guid><description>
reaConverter Pro is software image processing feature with batch conversion and image editing periodically becomes simple. eaConverter also provide command line utilities allow you to process images automatically, thus helping you shorten the time for other work.
reaConverter Pro integrated powerful tool of Uber with many great features. It provides advanced solutions to process and adjust images. Management of the conversion process the base image with the latest version of...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube Downloader 3.9.18 (2001)</title><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jan 2026 16:43:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube Downloader  is a dedicated software that helps users  downloading youtube videos  Favorites on PC for offline viewing. With MediaHuman YouTube  Downloader  you can download videos from youtube website to your computer with  fast speed , with special software development technology that automatically receives videos from Websites, in addition to the ability to download videos from software websites, can convert downloaded video formats to various formats for the purpose...
</description></item><item><title>Download K-Lite Codec Pack Update 19.4.3</title><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jan 2026 16:42:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-update-5145.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-update-5145.html
</guid><description>
K-Lite Codec Pack Update is the update of the set of codecs and related tools. Codec stands for Compressor-decompressor. Codec is necessary to encode and decode (play) audio and video. K-Lite Codec Pack Update is designed as a user-friendly solution with users to play all movie files your. With Codec Pack K-Lite, you can play 99% of all the movies found on your computer. A number of packages codec is not friendly with computers, as they tend to slow down Windows, break down multimedia...
</description></item><item><title>Download E-Z Contact Book 6.0.0.20</title><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jan 2026 16:41:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-e-z-contact-book-10318.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-e-z-contact-book-10318.html
</guid><description>
E-Z Contact Book is a popular software program used to manage and organize contact information. It functions as a digital address book, allowing users to store and manage their contacts, including names, phone numbers, email addresses, mailing addresses, and more. E-Z Contact Book offers a variety of features that help you easily track contacts and communicate with them. You can maintain personal and business phone numbers, emails, websites, addresses, customer notes, and reminders about...
</description></item><item><title>Download ArmorTools Professional / Home 26.1.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jan 2026 16:41:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-armortools-7726.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-armortools-7726.html
</guid><description>
ArmorTools is a set of tools that extend the capabilities of the MS Windows operating system in the field of security and protection of user confidential information. ArmorTools allows you to create secure virtual disks encrypted with AES128/AES256 algorithms, encrypting files and folder contents using any file as a password.
ArmorTools erases the user's work traces on the computer, deletes the history of accessing websites, deletes confidential information without the possibility of...
</description></item><item><title>Download ChessBase 26.3</title><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jan 2026 16:41:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chessbase-13889.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chessbase-13889.html
</guid><description>
ChessBase is the personal, independent chess database that has become the world standard. Everyone uses ChessBase, from World Champions to the amateur player next door. It is the program of choice for anyone who loves the game and wants to learn more about it. Start your personal success story with ChessBase and enjoy the game even more.
Whether it's preparing for an individual opponent or tournament, managing and analyzing your own games, developing training materials for self-study or...
</description></item><item><title>Download EF File Catalog 26.01</title><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jan 2026 16:40:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ef-file-catalog-3214.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ef-file-catalog-3214.html
</guid><description>
EF File Catalog is software that listed the directory of the entire disk or just the folder only has the user interface like Explorer and make it available to browse and search offline.
EF File Catalog - file Manager and folder Explorer-like
The following languages are included in the package: English, German, Arabic, Bulgarian, Catalan, Chinese, Dutch, English, French, Hebrew, Hungarian, Italian, Japanese, Korean, Lithuanian, Macedonian, Portuguese, Romanian, Russian, Slovak, Spanish...
</description></item><item><title>Download XtraTools Pro 26.1.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jan 2026 16:40:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xtratools-pro-7168.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xtratools-pro-7168.html
</guid><description>
XtraTools Pro is a universal tool for MS Windows system optimization that takes care of all aspects of your computer like optimizing the registry and removing unnecessary program to establish network connection and increase RAM speed. It is a compact tool with an intuitive interface that gives you complete control over the boot process, memory monitoring and a huge set of system settings that control your computer. The current version of the software provides the following tools: Folder...
</description></item><item><title>Download Obsidian 1.11.5</title><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jan 2026 16:39:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-obsidian-10386.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-obsidian-10386.html
</guid><description>
Obsidian is a powerful knowledge base that operates on a local folder containing plain text Markdown files. It allows users to create internal links for notes and then display the connections as a graph. Additionally users can also organize and structure their thoughts and knowledge in a flexible, non-linear way.
Features of Obsidian
Personal notes:
	Links: Create connections between your notes.
	Graph: Visualize the relationships between your notes.
	Plugins: Build your ideal...
</description></item><item><title>Download Luanti 5.15.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jan 2026 16:39:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-luanti-13986.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-luanti-13986.html
</guid><description>
Luanti, formerly known as Minetest, is a free and open source voxel game engine, written primarily in C++. It uses a modified version of the Irrlicht Engine and allows users to create games and mods using the Lua programming language.
Player Features
	Choose from a Variety of Games: There are a variety of games to choose from. You can survive in harsh environments, build creatively, or fight other players. Just load the game or connect to the server.
	Huge map: With 62,000 × 62,000...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cutting Optimization Pro 5.18.19.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jan 2026 16:38:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cutting-optimization-pro-6573.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cutting-optimization-pro-6573.html
</guid><description>
Cutting Optimization Pro is a cutting software used to obtain the optimal cut layout for one-dimensional (1D) and two-dimensional (2D) pieces. The software also allows you to define and process complex products, such as desks, tables, cabinets, cabinets, bookshelves... Cutting Optimization Pro can be used to cut rectangular panels made of glass, wood, metal, plastic or any other material used in industrial applications.
Features of Cutting Optimization Pro
	Optimize 1D and 2D in the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft PIX 2601.15</title><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jan 2026 16:38:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-pix-4100.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-pix-4100.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft PIX is a free program designed for all game developers, professional and amateur, give them reviews, game performance, debugging and tuning applications. Microsoft PIX will optimize the resource consumption is essential, especially for the game that requires high resources. Microsoft PIX can provide insight about the whole process of the production and how it affects the performance of the server system. Therefore, it can prove to be a real asset in the toolbox of developers,...
</description></item><item><title>Download EF Commander 26.01</title><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jan 2026 16:37:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ef-commander-92.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ef-commander-92.html
</guid><description>
EF Commander is an application specialized software can help you to manage your files effectively can help you full control over the files and folders, suitable for both beginners to experts with interface according to the card format Tab. The application supports ID3 tags, enhanced sound quality and use less resources with the format OGG/ Vorbis, FLAC, WMA and WAV and other formats can be heard on Winamp,...
EF Commander - a file manager effectively 
With EF Commander : When starting...
</description></item><item><title>Download Disk Sorter Ultimate 17.7.14 + Server + Pro</title><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jan 2026 16:36:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-disk-sorter-ultimate-1464.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-disk-sorter-ultimate-1464.html
</guid><description>
Disk Sorter Ultimate is the utility classification file lightweight and simple helps people detect files on most types of drives, as well as manage them according to many different criteria to create more capacity on the disc. This app allows you to search through the 500,000 files, have storage capacity of 2TB. To start sorting, all what you have to do is select a directory, drive or server and click the button "Classification". You should know that you can search for the type specific...
</description></item><item><title>Download Money Manager Ex 1.9.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jan 2026 16:35:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-money-manager-ex-4382.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-money-manager-ex-4382.html
</guid><description>
Money Manager Ex is software personal finance provides a full range of features to manage finance, budget and your investment. It supports checking, credit card, savings, investment account securities as well as fixed assets with depreciation. You can manually enter transaction and also set reminders for payments or withdraw money periodically. The program supports multiple accounts and currencies and can create a report, chart and graph for spending / income and your budget.
Money...
</description></item></channel></rss>