<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 05:36:23 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 05:36:23 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Tails 7.3.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 01:07:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tails-3241.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tails-3241.html
</guid><description>
Tails is a live operating system that you can boot on almost any computer from a USB memory stick or DVD. Tails does this by using the distribution classic Gnome of Linux. The top navigation bar allows you quick access to "Applications" and "Places" so you can easily access what you need quickly and easily and not lost.
Tails - independent operating System for security
Menu "apps" provide shortcuts for bundled software, including graphics, audio and video, office, system tools, and...
</description></item><item><title>Download CyberLink PowerDirector Ultimate 2026 v24.0.1209.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 01:04:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-powerdirector-ultimate-425.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-powerdirector-ultimate-425.html
</guid><description>
CyberLink PowerDirector Ultimate is software editor, edit video and make movies on the computer from a variety of templates are made available, complete with effects, transitions, animations, and music. CyberLink PowerDirector 17 is a combination of video editing software with advanced video editing features powerful. Cblowing need to add your clips into the time line and click on 'Production'!
The tool design video in CyberLink PowerDirector have the ability to customize helps you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Macro Expert Enterprise 4.9.8.7</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 01:04:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-macro-expert-enterprise-3558.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-macro-expert-enterprise-3558.html
</guid><description>
Macro Expert Enterprise is a powerful tool that will help you save time and money by empowering you to automate fully the work repetitive and regular. Macro Expert Enterprise can simplify a lot of work your computer, providing more than 260 action will meet most all your needs, automate your task. To keep they have the ability to access and organize high Macro Expert Enterprise split these actions into separate groups: Email, Excel document, database, Text, window, FTP, Internet, File,...
</description></item><item><title>Download ManicTime Pro 2025.3.5.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 01:02:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-manictime-18.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-manictime-18.html
</guid><description>
ManicTime is a software automatically collect information about how to use your computer. It records the time of operation of the machine, see the change data in the machine, how much data you share, received on or moved away, what software you use, use at any time
ManicTime allows you to keep up the work of the staff, send progress reports accurately and manage your time better than ever. This type of software can help your business more efficient when it comes to the internal problems...
</description></item><item><title>Download NetSpeedTray 1.1.8 + Portable</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 01:02:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-netspeedtray-14068.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-netspeedtray-14068.html
</guid><description>
NetSpeedTray is a lightweight, open source network monitor for Windows that displays upload/download speeds directly on the Taskbar with a native look and feel.
Designed to blend seamlessly with Windows 10/11 user interface. Includes intelligent detection of light and dark themes on the taskbar to ensure text is always visible. Sits quietly in the system tray without hogging resources. Features "Dynamic Update Rate" that automatically reduces update frequency when the network is idle to...
</description></item><item><title>Download ASCOMP F-Rename Professional 2.112</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 00:55:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ascomp-f-rename-6327.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ascomp-f-rename-6327.html
</guid><description>
ASCOMP F-Rename allows you to rename the number of files at the same time. With it, you can assign the file names that mean a large amount of data that does n' t cost much work. Besides, it allows you to find all the files on your hard drive after this without having to send a search group.
Features of ASCOMP F-Rename
	The numbering or date for the entire file collection and name of your MP3 file is only a few clicks based on the ID3 card.
	The function of renaming the individual...
</description></item><item><title>Download Avast Clear 25.12.10659</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 00:55:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avast-clear-4437.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avast-clear-4437.html
</guid><description>
Avast Clear is a utility to remove accurately and completely line product anti-virus AVAST. Avast to leave a lot of garbage behind the computer and in the register. In particular, the registry hassle can, for example, can be an obstacle to install a program anti-virus Avast other then. In such cases, you can use a special utility Avast!
Avast Clear - Uninstall program Avast
Recommended avoid any inconvenience, should always engage the help of a dedicated tool to know where to search...
</description></item><item><title>Download AVG Clear 25.12.10659</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 00:54:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avg-clear-4945.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avg-clear-4945.html
</guid><description>
AVG Clear is free program help completely erase everything from installing AVG current your including the registry entries, file, settings, files, users, etc. AVG Clear is provided by AVG and is the last measure to use if you encounter a problem when deleting AVG current whether it is error repair, reinstall, or delete altogether.
Please note that all user settings AVG will be removed after the uninstall process is complete. The items should be deleted to include content from Virus...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cutting Optimization Pro 5.18.16.30</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 00:46:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cutting-optimization-pro-6573.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cutting-optimization-pro-6573.html
</guid><description>
Cutting Optimization Pro is a cutting software used to obtain the optimal cut layout for one-dimensional (1D) and two-dimensional (2D) pieces. The software also allows you to define and process complex products, such as desks, tables, cabinets, cabinets, bookshelves... Cutting Optimization Pro can be used to cut rectangular panels made of glass, wood, metal, plastic or any other material used in industrial applications.
Features of Cutting Optimization Pro
	Optimize 1D and 2D in the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Opera GX (Gaming Browser) 125.0.5729.22</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 00:45:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-gx-3170.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-gx-3170.html
</guid><description>
Opera GX is a special version of the Opera browser is built to complement gamers avid. Browser this game comes with the unique features to help users make maximum use of both the game and their browser. Opera GX is built specifically to support the game. This browser includes the unique features to help users have the best experience when gaming and surfing the web.
Opera GX - special browser for gamers
GX Control allows you to set a limit on the level of use RAM, CPU and network where...
</description></item><item><title>Download Opera One 125.0.5729.21</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 00:44:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-972.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-972.html
</guid><description>
Opera is a fast, safe, configurable and compliant intranet web browser, which includes both the reader and the application. The Opera browser supports web browsing, listening to music, watching high speed movies, you can open many tabs on the Opera without affecting your browsing speed. Opera now supports almost all devices and operating systems such as windows, IOS, Android, linux, MacOS ...
Opera is a beautiful interface and many interesting features, operating on both PCs and mobile,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Quick Clipboard Editor 3.1.2.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 00:43:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quick-clipboard-editor-9421.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quick-clipboard-editor-9421.html
</guid><description>
Quick Clipboard Editor is free software that provides direct access to the text stored in your clipboard, allowing you to quickly modify it to meet your needs. meet your needs before pasting the text into the app you want. It allows you to quickly retrieve previous clips from your clipboard history, find and replace specific words or phrases, insert new content into each line, trim unwanted pieces of text, keep or remove lines or characters based on different criteria, arrange text using...
</description></item><item><title>Download Drives Monitor 18.7</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 00:43:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-drives-monitor-6969.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-drives-monitor-6969.html
</guid><description>
Drives Monitor is a Windows 10 utility that provides a lot of useful information about the activity of each physical disk, and a real-time graph is also provided. With Drives Monitor, you can view detailed information about the physical drive type, capacity, type, number of partitions and more. If the free space is running low, the disk space usage bar will turn red, so let you know about the problem and take appropriate measures.
If you run CrystalDiskInfo in the background, the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Certificate Manager 18.45</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 00:42:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-certificate-manager-13958.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-certificate-manager-13958.html
</guid><description>
Certificate Manager provides an in-depth overview of your current certificates, allowing you to easily access detailed information. It also provides functions for both exporting existing certificates and importing new certificates, enhancing your certificate management capabilities.
Application certificates are often overlooked by most users until problems arise during application installation. For the average end user, there is little reason to focus on application certificates....
</description></item><item><title>Download Steinberg VST Live Pro 3.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 00:41:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-steinberg-vst-live-pro-7557.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-steinberg-vst-live-pro-7557.html
</guid><description>
Steinberg VST Live Pro is a unique, stable software solution designed for musicians who want to deliver a great performance, including sound, light and video, wherever they are. VST Live comes with a wide range of virtual instruments, sync features for music, text and chord symbols showing on other devices, video, Cubase import, MIDI tracks for lighting control Live DMX and more.
Features of Steinberg VST Live Pro
The core of your live production.
Has all the functionality needed to...
</description></item><item><title>Download SysGauge Ultimate 12.3.14 + Pro + Server</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 00:41:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sysgauge-1296.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sysgauge-1296.html
</guid><description>
SysGauge Ultimate / Server is software that provides the ability to display the chart type monitoring system, hosted report monitoring systems and results of monitoring system to a number of standard formats including HTML, PDF, Excel, text, CSV and XML. Advanced users and IT administrators are provided the ability to save recurring reports system status, set a limit specified by the user for the timer monitoring the system and then displayed error message or alert, play sound...
</description></item><item><title>Download PC Timer 18.45</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 00:28:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pc-timer-7519.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pc-timer-7519.html
</guid><description>
PC Timer is a simple tool to automatically shut down, log out, restart or lock your PC based on your scheduled time. A handy feature of the app is its ability to prevent unauthorized cancellation of a scheduled task. To do so, PC Timer .NET allows you to set a password that the user must provide to cancel the operation.
The advantage of the application is its simplicity, small footprint on the system and the fact that it does not require installation. Thanks to the ability to set tasks...
</description></item><item><title>Download SSD Booster .NET 18.45</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 00:26:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ssd-booster-net-7375.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ssd-booster-net-7375.html
</guid><description>
SSD Booster .NET is our perfect tool to optimize and adjust Windows for the SSD drive to increase performance and maintain the highest performance for your SSD. In addition, the app comes with the system information tab for information about the hardware and operating system of your machine. To check your specifications, move to the Introduction and find the System Information button.
Features of SSD Booster .NET
	The perfect tool to optimize and adjust Windows for the SSD drive to...
</description></item><item><title>Download jetAudio Basic 8.1.12</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 00:14:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jetaudio-basic-384.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jetaudio-basic-384.html
</guid><description>
jetAudio Basic is software listen to music, play videos on computer assisted recording, CD recording and convert audio formats various.  It is a full multimedia features with the ability to record and extract CD integrated. JetAudio Basic brings you a tool to listen to music in high quality using simple and many the ability to customize extremely flexible.
jetAudio Basic supports all media formats popular including MP3, OGG, MPG, AVI, WMA and many other formats. In addition to music...
</description></item><item><title>Download AskAvatar - AI Stream Assistant 0.3.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:59:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-askavatar-ai-stream-assistant-14332.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-askavatar-ai-stream-assistant-14332.html
</guid><description>
AskAvatar is a revolutionary new tool for live streamers. Our AI-powered avatars will listen to your donations, subscriptions, raids, Bits, followers, and more, then respond LIVE on stream with unique AI-generated voice and messages based on personality and characteristics that you can design yourself.
What's inside?
AskAvatar comes with 13 unique pre-made avatars, each with its own characteristics, personality, and comedic style. You can also create your own completely custom...
</description></item><item><title>Download Intuitibits WiFi Explorer Pro 1.1.11.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:52:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intuitibits-wifi-explorer-pro-14331.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intuitibits-wifi-explorer-pro-14331.html
</guid><description>
Use WiFi Explorer Pro to help design and validate wireless networks, identify channel conflicts and overlapping channels, low signal quality, and other issues that may affect the connectivity or performance of your home, office, or business wireless network.
Includes visual visibility of the Wi-Fi environment, support for Wi-Fi 4 through 7 across 2.4, 5, and 6 GHz bands, custom columns from over 850 data fields, advanced filtering features, and compatibility with remote sensors. It allows...
</description></item><item><title>Download Merge VM Enterprise 24.2.7</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:37:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-merge-vm-enterprise-14330.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-merge-vm-enterprise-14330.html
</guid><description>
Merge VM Enterprise is a top choice in the virtual machine field, renowned for its superior speed and wide compatibility. Meticulously designed to meet the demands of modern computing environments, this advanced platform stands out for many reasons.
Features of Merge VM Enterprise
Superior Speed: Merge VM Enterprise sets the gold standard for virtual machine performance, boasting rapid setup and processing capabilities.
Diverse Operating System Support: With the ability to virtualize...
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 7.5.6</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Dec 2025 19:20:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-11-7760.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-11-7760.html
</guid><description>
TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 is a program that allows users to discover hidden settings in Windows 11. This application is specially designed for Windows 11, groups many registry settings and distribute them from the easy and secure user interface. With TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 you can move the Windows taskbar to the top and resize the taskbar by editing the registry value. With any application that modifies the registry, we recommend that you have a backup copy...
</description></item><item><title>Download Total Commander 11.56 Extended 25.12 Full / Lite</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Dec 2025 19:20:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-total-commander-it-edition-7090.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-total-commander-it-edition-7090.html
</guid><description>
Total Commander is the most popular file manager with all necessary functions for both casual users and IT professionals. Total Commander will help you manage, change data, computer files allowing you to best manage your data. Total Commander tool has two parallel opening windows that allow you to move and copy data from one folder to another easily.
In addition to all the tools dedicated to file managers, Total Commander also contains very convenient viewers for multimedia and graphic...
</description></item><item><title>Download AITextTune 1.4.9.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Dec 2025 19:19:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aitexttune-12973.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aitexttune-12973.html
</guid><description>
AITextTune is an AI-powered tool designed to enhance and refine text content. It offers features such as improving clarity and coherence, generating summaries, and translating text into multiple languages. Users can easily adjust their writing style from formal to creative. This tool is very flexible and can be used on many different software and platforms.
AITextTune Features
	WRITE PERFECTLY: Improve the clarity and coherence of your writing! Create summaries and...
</description></item></channel></rss>