<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 09:32:05 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 09:32:05 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Glary Utilities Pro 6.37.0.41</title><pubDate> Mon, 19 Jan 2026 22:45:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-utilities-pro-76.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-utilities-pro-76.html
</guid><description>
Glary Utilities Pro is a collection of tools and system utilities to fix, speed up, maintain and protect your computer. Glary Utilities Pro allows you to clean junk files, system downloads, as well as the subscriptions are not valid and Internet traces (that support the plug-in more for the 45+ program outside). You can also manage and delete add-ons of the browser, analyze the use of disk and find the file duplicate.
Glary Utilities Pro - optimized system
Key features Glary Utilities...
</description></item><item><title>Download Glary File Recovery Pro 1.30.0.30</title><pubDate> Mon, 19 Jan 2026 22:44:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glarysoft-file-recovery-pro-6587.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glarysoft-file-recovery-pro-6587.html
</guid><description>
Glarysoft File Recovery Pro is professional software that helps you recover files from recycle bin, system crash, permanent deletion, virus loss, formatted driver and other external storage devices, such as camera memory cards. Glarysoft File Recovery Pro supports multiple file systems ie, NTFS + EFS, FAT, NTFS. Furthermore, it can recover files that users have compressed, fragmented, or even encrypted on the NTFS file system.
Also, it performs automatic sorting by name, size and...
</description></item><item><title>Download reaConverter Pro 8.0.183</title><pubDate> Mon, 19 Jan 2026 22:43:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html
</guid><description>
reaConverter Pro is software image processing feature with batch conversion and image editing periodically becomes simple. eaConverter also provide command line utilities allow you to process images automatically, thus helping you shorten the time for other work.
reaConverter Pro integrated powerful tool of Uber with many great features. It provides advanced solutions to process and adjust images. Management of the conversion process the base image with the latest version of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Gilisoft SnapID 8.7.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 19 Jan 2026 22:43:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-snapid-12712.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-snapid-12712.html
</guid><description>
Gilisoft SnapID offers a variety of features to help you enhance and transform your images. With Gilisoft SnapID, you can easily crop, resize and rotate images to get the perfect composition. The software also allows you to adjust the color, brightness, contrast, and saturation to bring out the best in your photos.
One of the standout features of Gilisoft SnapID is the ability to add filters and effects. You can choose from a variety of presets or customize your own settings to create a...
</description></item><item><title>Download Advanced Renamer Commercial 4.20</title><pubDate> Mon, 19 Jan 2026 22:42:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-renamer-2647.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-renamer-2647.html
</guid><description>
Advanced Renamer is a program to rename multiple files and folders at the same time. By configuring the method name change, the name can be manipulated in many different ways. It's easy to set up a batch job using multiple methods on a large number of files. 14 different modes allow you to change the name, attributes and timestamp of the file in once. The file can also be copied or moved to new location based on information in the file.
The program can rename files in many different ways,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Room Arranger 10.3.3.740</title><pubDate> Mon, 19 Jan 2026 22:42:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-room-arranger-3779.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-room-arranger-3779.html
</guid><description>
Room Arranger is a 3D application lets you easily plan for the room, office or his apartment just a few mouse clicks. The application comes with a simple interface will significantly simplify your work. You can draw many kinds of objects and items to create furniture of your own. This app also includes a library of object rich.
Software Room Arranger enables you to view your project in 3D form. You can also upload the 3D scene interact on your blog or your website. The application uses...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter 3.9.18 (1801)</title><pubDate> Mon, 19 Jan 2026 22:41:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-to-mp3-converter-1744.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-to-mp3-converter-1744.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter is the software support download youtube video and convert video to mp3 format fast and most simple. MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter allows you download and convert videos from YouTube and other websites to MP3 format by pasting the YouTube URL into the application. When you paste the URL, the program will display thumbnails for videos and you have the option to customize the title information, artist and album before you begin the process of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Glarysoft Malware Hunter Pro 1.211.0.842</title><pubDate> Mon, 19 Jan 2026 22:40:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glarysoft-malware-hunter-pro-235.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glarysoft-malware-hunter-pro-235.html
</guid><description>
Glarysoft Malware Hunter capabilities, comprehensive protection against threats, data protection and privacy, ensure the computer is no longer virus. It allows you against many types of viruses, trojans with the ability to super fast scanning to detect and remove the malware quickly. Glarysoft Malware Hunter has a simple design of the interface, but the pace of new work is the most important problem of this software.
Features Glarysoft Malware Hunter Pro
	Automatically search, detect,...
</description></item><item><title>Download O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro 22.1.238 / Server</title><pubDate> Mon, 19 Jan 2026 22:40:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-diskimage-pro-218.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-diskimage-pro-218.html
</guid><description>
O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro is software backup data comprehensive and effective is provided to protect the data of the computer system, it creates images for individual drives or the entire system that still does not affect your system.
O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro allows the user to backup the entire computer or drive, the and files whenever you want even while the computer is being used. Or can use O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro to create a copy chinh sac of computer disk drives, can be used instead of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Glary Malware Hunter PRO 1.211.0.842</title><pubDate> Mon, 19 Jan 2026 22:40:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-malware-hunter-pro-77.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-malware-hunter-pro-77.html
</guid><description>
Glary Malware Hunter PRO - detection of file malware on your computer and delete dangerous content, allowing you to run on-demand scan of the area, important system or specific files. As suggested by its name, Malware Hunter is designed to find and remove the files and components potential danger on your computer, keep it out of the virus and the type of threat other.
Glary Malware Hunter PRO - perfect protection of your equipment
Features Glary Malware Hunter PRO
- Scan ultrasound...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tecplot Focus 2025 R2 v2025.2.0.81941</title><pubDate> Mon, 19 Jan 2026 22:39:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tecplot-focus-6031.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tecplot-focus-6031.html
</guid><description>
Tecplot Focus allows you to quickly draw up your sugar and surface techniques as well as check the exact data in the way you want. You can analyze and explore complex data sets, organize lots of XY, 2D and 3D cells, and communicate your results to your colleagues with high quality output.
This application is very easy to use and is the perfect solution for all the needs of your image from the simple XY tiles to the complex dynamic images of the contaminant beam. This is a comprehensive...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tecplot RS 2025 R1 v2025.1.0.82070</title><pubDate> Mon, 19 Jan 2026 22:38:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tecplot-rs-5019.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tecplot-rs-5019.html
</guid><description>
Tecplot RS helps you manage and analyze large amounts of data, simulation reservoir, discover the knowledge about the behavior pattern of reservoir and convey your results to colleagues and management by image and animation professional. Tools analysis and visualization is very important in process simulation to help you fully understand his model. Work closely with the reservoir engineers in the past 15 years, our team has researched the process simulation reservoir typical.
The main...
</description></item><item><title>Download Unicodia 3.0.8</title><pubDate> Mon, 19 Jan 2026 22:37:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-unicodia-8521.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-unicodia-8521.html
</guid><description>
Unicodia is free, open source software that can be used as an alternative character map for your Windows machine. The interface contains everything you need, allowing you to easily cycle through all the available ASCII symbols and copy them to the clipboard. Uncicodia is a great alternative to your standard Unicode characters and is filled with symbols/characters that make it useful for a number of different uses.
Features of Unicodia
	In Windows 10/11 — all characters of Unicode 15...
</description></item><item><title>Download Becky! Internet Mail 2.83.01</title><pubDate> Mon, 19 Jan 2026 22:37:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-becky-internet-mail-3926.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-becky-internet-mail-3926.html
</guid><description>
Becky! Internet Mail is a client E-mail features dedicated to Windows and the Internet. Since its inception in 1996, Becky! Internet Mail is constantly improving its functions to listen to user feedback and it has become one of the products email share most successful. Becky! Internet Mail is an email application that creates multiple mailboxes. You will find many features to be expected for a software E-mail Internet and a number of features will exceed your expectations. It has almost...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tecplot 360 EX + Chorus 2025 R2 (2025.2.0.81941)</title><pubDate> Mon, 19 Jan 2026 22:36:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tecplot-360-ex-2202.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tecplot-360-ex-2202.html
</guid><description>
Tecplot is a software engineering with functionality XY, 2D and 3D extended. The program is designed to measure the performance data, construction of test data, mathematical analysis, and engineering construction in general. Users Tecplot is able to use many open source libraries available. Carry out any development project or scientific, use this software for drawing and visualization, it will help presenting your work under the most favorable light. And if you are thinking about...
</description></item><item><title>Download HttpMaster Pro 6.2.7</title><pubDate> Mon, 19 Jan 2026 22:36:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-httpmaster-pro-1925.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-httpmaster-pro-1925.html
</guid><description>
A useful application for web developers who need to automate the test the web application by requesting multiple resources from a specified site web-based application. The professional version httpMaster in order to meet the requirements of many people when related to the test application. When working with HttpMaster Pro, most of the time you will manage the attributes and properties of the project HttpMaster of the items required in project. Project properties provides the global options...
</description></item><item><title>Download Donemax Data Recovery Technician 2.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 19 Jan 2026 19:44:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-donemax-data-recovery-7666.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-donemax-data-recovery-7666.html
</guid><description>
Donemax Data Recovery is an easy-to-use data recovery software that helps you recover deleted, formatted or lost data from HDD, SSD, USB flash drives , memory card, digital camera, RAID, Server, etc. It will completely recover deleted, formatted or lost data within 3 easy steps.
Features of Donemax Data Recovery
	Easily recover data lost due to deletion, formatting, partition loss, virus infection, human error, logic error, hard drive failure, etc.
	Recover all types of lost files...
</description></item><item><title>Download GiliSoft USB Lock 11.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 19 Jan 2026 19:41:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-usb-lock-866.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-usb-lock-866.html
</guid><description>
GiliSoft USB Lock is a tool that prevents leakage of data to prevent leakage and copy of your data to USB Drives, external DRIVES, CD / DVD, or the other mobile device. GiliSoft USB Lock lets you block all the drives and devices do not belong to you. With USB Lock, you can share your PC with anyone without fear of data theft. This is a security software easy USB and Endpoint DLP Suite that helps you lock the usb port, making recording a dvd / cd read-only, block some websites, forbid some...
</description></item><item><title>Download Glary Disk Cleaner 6.0.1.40</title><pubDate> Mon, 19 Jan 2026 17:14:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-disk-cleaner-1341.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-disk-cleaner-1341.html
</guid><description>
Glary Disk Cleaner is the software helps to erase the file system temporarily, cleanup your browser cache, or release the folder. Glary Disk Cleaner show scan results in detail, help you pick exactly each file to delete. The list file is much more wide open, with temporary files, user-generated, or the file system, cache, bug report, log files, data in recycle bin, the shortcut expires.
Glary Disk Cleaner - garbage system
Glary Disk Cleaner is designed to be simple as possible in use....
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow QR Code Maker 4.0.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 19 Jan 2026 17:14:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qr-code-maker-9760.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qr-code-maker-9760.html
</guid><description>
QR Code Maker is a simple app to generate QR Code for text, link, email, Whatsapp, SMS, Call and Wifi. With QR Codes, you have complete flexibility, because only a short URL points to the encrypted content. So you can modify the links or stored files without having to generate and reprint the Codes. This will save resources and allow you to respond to any campaign changes as quickly as possible.
Features of QR Code Maker
	Generate QR Code for Text, Link, Email, Whatsapp, SMS, Call and...
</description></item><item><title>Download SecretDNS 3.8.4</title><pubDate> Mon, 19 Jan 2026 16:10:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secretdns-12481.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secretdns-12481.html
</guid><description>
SecretDNS provides a quick means to deploy DNS over HTPS, meaning it allows DNS (short for Domain Name Server) resolution to be performed remotely using the HTTPS protocol to encrypts data between the client and the DNS resolver. Its purpose, obviously, is related to data security and user privacy, to prevent unauthorized interception and manipulation of DNS data.
Default DNS settings in SecretDNS use CloudFlare to ensure security. You can change DNS configuration in the dedicated tab...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube Downloader 3.9.18 (1801)</title><pubDate> Mon, 19 Jan 2026 16:09:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube Downloader  is a dedicated software that helps users  downloading youtube videos  Favorites on PC for offline viewing. With MediaHuman YouTube  Downloader  you can download videos from youtube website to your computer with  fast speed , with special software development technology that automatically receives videos from Websites, in addition to the ability to download videos from software websites, can convert downloaded video formats to various formats for the purpose...
</description></item><item><title>Download FX Math Tools Manifest 26.01.14</title><pubDate> Mon, 19 Jan 2026 16:09:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fx-draw-tools-multidocs-8814.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fx-draw-tools-multidocs-8814.html
</guid><description>
MultiDocs is a new way to create self-modifying Word documents. MultiDocs' amazing new document reproduction features allow you to create reproducible tests and quizzes in minutes. Get new numbers, new diagrams and even brand new solutions! MultiDocs combines the power of Word with two leading products: FX Draw and FX Equation in a new and exciting way.
Features of FX Draw Tools MultiDocs
	Create multiple documents: The software allows users to create multiple math and evaluation...
</description></item><item><title>Download Batch Image Converter 2.2.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 19 Jan 2026 16:00:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-batch-image-converter-7430.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-batch-image-converter-7430.html
</guid><description>
Batch Image Converter is software that helps you batch convert image files. It can work with many image types (*.bmp, *.gif, *.jpg, *.png, *.tiff, *.tif, *.psd, *.pcx, *.pbm, *.pgm , *. ppm, *.tga, *.tpic, etc.).
Features of Batch Image Converter
	Easy, intuitive, one-click configuration.
	Save/load session for easy use again.
	Support command line execution.
	Execute automatically at specific time.
</description></item><item><title>Download ReShade 6.7.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 19 Jan 2026 15:59:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-450-3227.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-450-3227.html
</guid><description>
ReShade is an open Source tool help improve the look of the old games on modern video cards as well as allow additional display technology / new video over on the old game doesn't support the technology that.
ReShade, technically, is a tool processing general for the games and video software. Imagine you see your favorite game yourself with the obscure-around, effects market the true depth or color correction. Function ReShade by showing in an automatic way and general access to...
</description></item></channel></rss>