<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 12:06:16 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 12:06:16 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download WinToHDD Professional + Technician 6.9.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 04 Jan 2026 22:50:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wintohdd-professional-technician-4406.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wintohdd-professional-technician-4406.html
</guid><description>
WinToHDD is software Windows handy and useful allows you to install or re-install Windows without using CD / DVD drive or USB. With this software installed All-In-One Windows, you can easily re-install Windows, install Windows on another drive than the one where Windows operating system you installed, or is installing Windows operating system (Windows vista or later) to another disk.
WinToHDD Professional + Technician - Support install Windows
In addition to creating a USB drive that...
</description></item><item><title>Download Stellar Data Recovery Pro 12.4.0.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 04 Jan 2026 22:50:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stellar-phoenix-windows-data-recovery-professional-3312.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stellar-phoenix-windows-data-recovery-professional-3312.html
</guid><description>
Stellar Phoenix Windows Data Recovery Professional is an application that reliable and comprehensive, allowing you to recover quickly and easily the files lost or deleted from internal hard drive or any media outside any other. The program provides with an intuitive interface and no clutter, help you easily get back lost data without modifying the original structure.
Stellar Phoenix Windows Data Recovery Professional - Recover lost data
Stellar Phoenix Windows Data Recovery...
</description></item><item><title>Download Stellar Toolkit for Data Recovery 12.4.0.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 04 Jan 2026 22:50:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stellar-toolkit-for-data-recovery-3330.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stellar-toolkit-for-data-recovery-3330.html
</guid><description>
Stellar Toolkit for Data Recovery is recovery software lost data or can't access, can restore the file buffer is not full or corrupt, and the Windows operating system, Mac and Linux. Sometimes the data on the hard drive can be deleted due to a system error or malfunction. In such cases, use a recovery software can strongly increase the possibility of data recovery and save your important data from the risk of permanently deleted.
Stellar Toolkit for Data Recovery - recover lost...
</description></item><item><title>Download Stellar Data Recovery Technician 12.4.0.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 04 Jan 2026 22:49:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stellar-data-recovery-technician-3561.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stellar-data-recovery-technician-3561.html
</guid><description>
Stellar Data Recovery Technician is a other version helps you to recover lost data like files, photos, videos, emails and many other things from hard drive Windows storage media and RAID arrays. Technicians data recovery of Stellar smart detection parameters RAID key and rebuild the RAID virtual to recover data from the RAID 0 array, RAID 5 and RAID 6 faulty or damaged.
Software Stellar Data Recovery Technician provides advanced functions for recovering data from servers, RAID 0, 5 and 6...
</description></item><item><title>Download Fast File Encryptor 26.0.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 04 Jan 2026 22:48:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fast-file-encryptor-2606.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fast-file-encryptor-2606.html
</guid><description>
Fast File Encryptor is the encoder files fast designed for fast processing of the file very big. It can encrypt or decrypt files, contents of folders and contains a lot of additional tools. In addition, there is a tool responsible to completely remove files from the hard drive, you need it if you don't want to leave traces 100 percent in the system. You need to specify the password or key, then select the encryption method, remember remember everything, otherwise it will not work, then...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinToHDD Enterprise 6.9</title><pubDate> Sun, 04 Jan 2026 22:48:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wintohdd-enterprise-388.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wintohdd-enterprise-388.html
</guid><description>
WinToHDD Enterprise is useful software that allows you to install or reinstall Windows without using a CD/DVD or USB drive. This is the software that can set up all the settings of the windows in one. With WinToHDD Enterprise it is easy to reinstall Windows, install Windows on other disks with your Windows operating system settings or copy existing Windows OS settings.
In addition to creating a USB drive that contains all the setup files of the OS, you can use an app like WinToHDD. Its...
</description></item><item><title>Download Duplicate File Finder Professional 2026 v409</title><pubDate> Sun, 04 Jan 2026 22:47:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-duplicate-file-finder-professional-4425.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-duplicate-file-finder-professional-4425.html
</guid><description>
Duplicate File Finder Professional is a compact application helps you quickly find and remove files duplicate on the computer. With Duplicate File Finder Professional you can choose any folder on the hard drive or use the folder standard user and our app will analyze the deep content of the selected folder to copy. It will take only a few seconds. The files will be compared by the hash algorithm MD5, which means they will be compared by content, not by name. Then, use our convenient...
</description></item><item><title>Download Stellar Data Recovery Premium 12.4.0.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 04 Jan 2026 22:46:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stellar-data-recovery-premium-9617.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stellar-data-recovery-premium-9617.html
</guid><description>
Stellar Data Recovery Premium is software developed by Stellar, a company specializing in data recovery solutions. Stellar Data Recovery Premium is designed to help users recover lost or deleted data from various storage devices, including hard drives, SSDs, USB drives, SD cards, and more.
It allows you to save the scan information to continue the recovery process from the same point, at a later stage. It also has an option to create an image of a complete hard drive or a...
</description></item><item><title>Download Extra Subst Home 26.0.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 04 Jan 2026 22:46:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-extra-subst-2605.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-extra-subst-2605.html
</guid><description>
Extra Subst is program designed to help access to the folder is regular use of your computer easier. It is also used to create, edit and remove virtual drives of your computer. Extra Subst creates virtual drives on the basis of the selected folder. Physical drives remain unchanged and are not divided into additional partitions.
Create a new virtual disk is very simple, because you only need to specify the folder which will be connected to, then select the letters and go to it. New virtual...
</description></item><item><title>Download LuBan 3D 24.12.2025</title><pubDate> Sun, 04 Jan 2026 22:45:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-luban-3d-10427.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-luban-3d-10427.html
</guid><description>
LuBan 3D is creative design software that helps designers and manufacturers create their innovative products quickly. LuBan automatically creates 3D models in a variety of forms, such as lithophane, stacks, hashes, slabs, reliefs, modules, and wireframes. The resulting model can be fabricated by 3D printing, laser cutting and CNC milling. Model parts can be fabricated using laser cutting and 3D printing. LuBan does not depend on specific fabrication methods; instead, it can communicate...
</description></item><item><title>Download ExtraDisks Home 26.0.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 04 Jan 2026 22:44:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-extradisks-home-7758.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-extradisks-home-7758.html
</guid><description>
ExtraDisks is a set of tools for creating virtual disks on your computer physical drives that do not change and are not divided into additional partitions. The program contains tools for creating encrypted disks, file-based virtual disks and directory-based virtual disks. The current version includes the following tools: Encrypted Disks, Virtual Disks, Folder Disks, Startup Manager, System Tweaker.
Features of ExtraDisks
ExtraDisks: Encrypted Disk
This tool is used to create encrypted...
</description></item><item><title>Download MS SQL Maestro 25.12.0.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 04 Jan 2026 22:43:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ms-sql-maestro-10915.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ms-sql-maestro-10915.html
</guid><description>
MS SQL Maestro is the leading GUI administration tool for managing, controlling, and developing Microsoft SQL Server and MSDE. This application also provides you with a powerful set of tools to edit and execute SQL scripts, build visual diagrams for numerical data, compose OLAP cubes, and more.
With a friendly graphical interface and diverse features, MS SQL Maestro is a useful tool for database administrators or application developers working with SQL Server databases.
Features of MS...
</description></item><item><title>Download Disable Windows Defender 2.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 04 Jan 2026 17:43:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-disable-windows-defender-14217.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-disable-windows-defender-14217.html
</guid><description>
Usually, we need to disable Windows Defender to prevent it from deleting known files due to false positives. Sometimes, it can slow down your computer or interrupt your work. In such cases, you can easily disable it and enable it again later with just one click. We can also disable this feature (Real-time Monitoring) using the Defender Settings panel, but it will be automatically enabled after a period of time. This tool ensures that this feature is 100% disabled. It also disables all...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ant Download Manager Pro 2.16.5 Build 92283</title><pubDate> Sun, 04 Jan 2026 17:39:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ant-download-manager-pro-137.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ant-download-manager-pro-137.html
</guid><description>
Ant Download Manager Pro is software support download has the same features as IDM, even it has many prominent features, more user friendly more and have speed download data incredible. Ant Download Manager is a Internet content downloader quickly with support download at video! Function: fully Integrated with the web browsers most popular: Internet Explorer 8+, Mozilla Firefox 32 +, Google Chrome 31+ and the copies of them (Pale Moon, Opera, Vivaldi, Slimjet, ComodoDragon, etc.). you...
</description></item><item><title>Download CyberLink PowerDirector Ultimate 2026 v24.0.1302.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 04 Jan 2026 17:38:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-powerdirector-ultimate-425.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-powerdirector-ultimate-425.html
</guid><description>
CyberLink PowerDirector Ultimate is software editor, edit video and make movies on the computer from a variety of templates are made available, complete with effects, transitions, animations, and music. CyberLink PowerDirector 17 is a combination of video editing software with advanced video editing features powerful. Cblowing need to add your clips into the time line and click on 'Production'!
The tool design video in CyberLink PowerDirector have the ability to customize helps you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Easy English Platinum 11.0.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 04 Jan 2026 17:38:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easy-english-platinum-10850.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easy-english-platinum-10850.html
</guid><description>
Designed by university language experts, Easy English Platinum is an interactive learning system proven to teach you English quickly and easy. With progressive learning lessons, voice recognition technology, and immersive learning, you'll have everything you need to master English. Build your vocabulary, practice real-world conversations, and perfect your pronunciation.
This program will put you in real-life situations where you interact with native speakers to learn faster. Enter your...
</description></item><item><title>Download reaConverter Pro 8.0.175</title><pubDate> Sun, 04 Jan 2026 17:37:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html
</guid><description>
reaConverter Pro is software image processing feature with batch conversion and image editing periodically becomes simple. eaConverter also provide command line utilities allow you to process images automatically, thus helping you shorten the time for other work.
reaConverter Pro integrated powerful tool of Uber with many great features. It provides advanced solutions to process and adjust images. Management of the conversion process the base image with the latest version of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Telegram for Desktop 6.4.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 04 Jan 2026 17:37:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-telegram-3376.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-telegram-3376.html
</guid><description>
Telegram is an instant messaging service and voice over IP services on the cloud platform. Client application Telegram is available for Android, iOS, Windows Phone, Windows NT, macOS, and Linux. Users can send messages and exchange photos, videos, stickers, audio and files of any kind.
Telegram - Messaging and free phone calls
Telegram seamless sync across all your devices and can be used on desktop, tablet and phone. You can send unlimited amount of messages, photos, videos and files...
</description></item><item><title>Download Allavsoft Video Downloader Converter 3.28.8.9497</title><pubDate> Sun, 04 Jan 2026 17:37:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allavsoft-video-downloader-converter-248.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allavsoft-video-downloader-converter-248.html
</guid><description>
Allavsoft Video Downloader Converter software supports download movies, music videos, playlist, sport videos from video sharing website for free like Facebook, Youtube and over 100 video sharing sites.
Allavsoft is many users favorite thanks to the combined features simultaneous transmission of multiple videos and speed limit download video. Besides, the program also supports pause and resume data transmission, to help you interfere with the process of transmitting download data to...
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 7.6.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 04 Jan 2026 17:36:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-11-7760.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-11-7760.html
</guid><description>
TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 is a program that allows users to discover hidden settings in Windows 11. This application is specially designed for Windows 11, groups many registry settings and distribute them from the easy and secure user interface. With TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 you can move the Windows taskbar to the top and resize the taskbar by editing the registry value. With any application that modifies the registry, we recommend that you have a backup copy...
</description></item><item><title>Download NirLauncher Package 1.30.22</title><pubDate> Sun, 04 Jan 2026 17:36:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nirlauncher-152.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nirlauncher-152.html
</guid><description>
NirLauncher is a package of more than 200 freeware utilities developed by Nirsoft, the NirLauncher application is provided free of charge for easy selection, use by feature classification. . Popular Nirsoft Utilities (many of them listed separately on taiwebs.com) NirLauncher includes network tools, password recovery tools, security cleaners, system utilities, programming tools, command line utilities and more.
NirLauncher's Versatile Utility
With this NirLauncher utility, users can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Top Process Monitor 11.5</title><pubDate> Sun, 04 Jan 2026 17:36:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-top-process-monitor-2753.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-top-process-monitor-2753.html
</guid><description>
Top Process Monitor is a small utility that allows you to view the processes are using most CPU, memory and other important components in your system. It can be easily installed and configured, even by inexperienced users. The interface of the application is based on a small frame that you can move to any location on the screen. So, you can check the current CPU, along with the application and the total stream is included.
Top Process Monitor - View operation, the CPU, computer...
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 7.6.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 04 Jan 2026 17:35:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-10-7759.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-10-7759.html
</guid><description>
TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 is a utility that allows users to discover hidden settings in Windows 10. This application is specially designed for Windows 10, groups many registry settings and provide them from an easy and secure user interface. With TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 you can move the Windows taskbar to the top and resize the taskbar by editing the registry value. With any application that modifies the registry, we recommend that you have a backup copy to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Any Video Downloader Pro 10.1.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 04 Jan 2026 17:35:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-video-downloader-pro-3731.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-video-downloader-pro-3731.html
</guid><description>
Any Video Downloader Pro is software support you can download video HD 720p, 1080p, 2K, 4K and 8K from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion, Vimeo, Metacafe and thousands of video sharing sites, other. It is a tool to speed up multi-threading can speed up your download faster up to 5 times. This helpful program support download at the same time. Any Video Downloader Pro lets you download multiple videos at the same time. Moreover, it allows you to pause and resume downloads if you need more...
</description></item><item><title>Download DriverStore Explorer 0.12.135</title><pubDate> Sun, 04 Jan 2026 17:34:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-driverstore-explorer-2892.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-driverstore-explorer-2892.html
</guid><description>
DriverStore Explorer RAPR is software for dealing with drivers Windows more easily. The supported operations include enumeration, adding driver package (stage), add and install, delete and delete force from the store drivers.
DriverStore Explorer - drivers
The features of the DriverStore Explorer
	Listed / Listed all the packages are held in the store current drivers.
	Export the list as CSV.
	Added package drivers catalog drivers (called staging)
	Install &amp;amp; Add driver package...
</description></item></channel></rss>