<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 15:45:58 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 15:45:58 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Paint NET 5.1.9 + Portable</title><pubDate> Fri, 01 Aug 2025 16:40:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-paint-net-252.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-paint-net-252.html
</guid><description>
Paint.NET is software photo manipulation and image creation support, photo editing, simple but effective on the computer. With the additional help from Microsoft, and means free replacement for the software MS Paint. Users can totally create photo effects, 3D shadow effect for photo privacy Paint.Net without the need to resort to Photoshop too complicated.
Paint.NET has a clean interface and easy to understand includes all the tools edit downloads, as well as clone stamp and various...
</description></item><item><title>Download Android Studio 2025.1.2.11</title><pubDate> Fri, 01 Aug 2025 16:39:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-android-studio-3890.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-android-studio-3890.html
</guid><description>
Android Studio is an Android development environment, completely new, provides many improvements and new features compared to Eclipse ADT. This software solution will is IDE the official Android when is finishing. This tool provides many tools and features such as editing, layout, rich set of tools to capture usability, compatibility version, performance and other issues, create a lot APK, build system based on Gradle flexibility, extended support for Google Services, integrated support...
</description></item><item><title>Download Office Timeline Plus 11.17.00.00 Expert / Pro / Pro+ Edition</title><pubDate> Fri, 01 Aug 2025 16:38:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-timeline-2106.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-timeline-2106.html
</guid><description>
Office Timeline is an add-on very useful and powerful software for Microsoft PowerPoint. With add-ons, you can create PowerPoint documents look more beautiful. With add-ons, you can add the time Line on the project by yourself. Application time for the composition and different segments of the document, your PowerPoint will not only increase the beauty for your work, but also for customers and your manager. The people who created this product is also believe that add-ons this is the only...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare Repairit 6.5.12.5</title><pubDate> Fri, 01 Aug 2025 16:37:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-recoverit-video-repair-3889.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-recoverit-video-repair-3889.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare Recoverit Video Repair is a reliable application that helps you fix the broken video, Wondershare Recoverit Video Repair supports file formats MP4, MOV, M4V, M2TS, MKV, MTS, 3GP, AVI and FLV is corrupt and broken. Great service we provide. It fixes the video that there is corruption in the process of shooting, when done, file transfer, while editing, convert.
Wondershare Recoverit Video Repair - video repair broken
Features of Wondershare Recoverit Video Repair
	Repair...
</description></item><item><title>Download FastStone Image Viewer 8.1 Corporate</title><pubDate> Fri, 01 Aug 2025 16:36:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-faststone-image-viewer-278.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-faststone-image-viewer-278.html
</guid><description>
FastStone Image Viewer software is manager, converter and editor image fast, stable, user-friendly. FastStone Image Viewer has the features include image viewing, management, comparison, red-eye removal, emailing, resizing, cropping and color adjustments. Full screen mode innovative but intuitive its provides quick access to EXIF information, browse the thumbnails and the main functions via hidden toolbars that pop up when your mouse touch the four edges of the screen.
FastStone Image...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Photoshop 2025 v26.9.0.15 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Fri, 01 Aug 2025 16:36:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-0010-adobe-photoshop-737.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-0010-adobe-photoshop-737.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Photoshop is a powerful raster graphics editor developed by Adobe Systems, primarily used for image editing, photo editing, and graphic design. Currently,&amp;nbsp;Adobe Photoshop 2025 is considered a graphic design software, creating and enhancing images, illustrations, and 3D artwork. In addition, it also supports website and mobile app design, video editing, real-life painting simulation, and more.
Adobe Photoshop 2025 - Graphic design
When it comes to Adobe Photoshop, it is...
</description></item><item><title>Download MedCalc 22.3.3</title><pubDate> Fri, 01 Aug 2025 16:35:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-medcalc-1536.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-medcalc-1536.html
</guid><description>
MedCalc is a statistical software for biomedical research can analyze many performance curve system with a set of rich functionality, chart types and advanced module. MedCalc was designed to meet the needs and requirements of the study nature and aims to analyze the statistical calculations of the project. This software provides the tools and means essential to analyze the characteristic curve of the system (ROC), drawing data and perform the statistical calculations.
MedCalc -...
</description></item><item><title>Download Resolume Arena 7.23.1 rev 49731</title><pubDate> Fri, 01 Aug 2025 16:34:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-arena-760.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-arena-760.html
</guid><description>
Resolume Arena is software Visual Jockey for DJ help adjust, mix and match image combination screen displayed directly. Software control it from the lighting and synchronize with the DJ via SMPTE time code. Adjust the ratio and position of the clip to suit your needs. Apply effects to change the powerful interface of the video. Everything running on the card screen so you get fast performance and good image quality as possible.
Resolume Arena - software Visual Jockey for DJ
Features of...
</description></item><item><title>Download SoftPerfect Network Scanner 2025.8</title><pubDate> Fri, 01 Aug 2025 16:34:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-softperfect-network-scanner-465.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-softperfect-network-scanner-465.html
</guid><description>
SoftPerfect Network Scanner is software scan ip address fast with many features for the programmer. With SoftPerfect Network Scanner you can completely scan IPv4 / IPv6 universal fast with many options. Program this powerful can ping computers, scan ports, discover the folder is shared and comes with filtering options and flexible display. It can take practically any information about the network device through WMI, SNMP, HTTP, SSH , and PowerShell. In addition, it can scan the remote...
</description></item><item><title>Download PanoramaStudio Pro 4.1.5.441</title><pubDate> Fri, 01 Aug 2025 16:29:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-panoramastudio-pro-1604.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-panoramastudio-pro-1604.html
</guid><description>
PanoramaStudio Pro is software is the complete solution for creating panoramic images as matching images are arranged arbitrary in the panorama. PanoramaStudio Pro creates panoramic images in a row and multiple rows of up to 360x180 spherical full. In addition, this software provides viewer / player application HTML5 interactions are compatible with all web browsers and on multiple systems to display the panoramic image 3D, 360 degree images and image zoom on the site.
PanoramaStudio...
</description></item><item><title>Download Geometric Glovius Pro 6.6.10.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 01 Aug 2025 16:29:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-geometric-glovius-pro-754.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-geometric-glovius-pro-754.html
</guid><description>
Geometric Glovius Pro is viewer CAD 3D modern for files CATIA, NX, STEP, IGES, Pro/ENGINEER and Creo, SolidWorks, Inventor and Solid Edge. The work of Geometric Glovius Pro is made exact measurements, cut dynamic sections, compare differences between models and export to 3D PDF, STL and Glovius Mobile.
Geometric Glovius Pro - manager, and view CAD 3D
The features of Geometric Glovius Pro
	Modern interface, simple, easy to use
	Mobile app for free for iOS &amp;amp; Android powerful...
</description></item><item><title>Download Directory Opus Pro 13.17.4 Beta</title><pubDate> Fri, 01 Aug 2025 16:25:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-opus-pro-779.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-opus-pro-779.html
</guid><description>
Directory Opus Pro is a software replacement for Explorer with traditional strength and function more than any manager other files. Directory Opus Pro full support for high DPI screen (for example 4K and 5K) with the rename dialog is redesigned, with new features. Besides being a recording macro only allows you to perform mass renaming complex that don't need regular expressions. In addition, Directory Opus Pro also enhances the ability to script.Better handling of renaming recursive and...
</description></item><item><title>Download HTML Compiler 2025.10</title><pubDate> Fri, 01 Aug 2025 16:25:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-html-compiler-2548.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-html-compiler-2548.html
</guid><description>
HTML Compiler is a program for Microsoft Windows (tm) allows you to put an entire HTML application (including HTML, CSS, JavaScript, images, etc.) into a Windows application independent can be executed like any other application window the application. HTML Compiler allows you to customize file real exam results by changing the icon of them and set some other options. For example, you can allow or not allow the ability to print the HTML pages, allow or disallow the text selection and many,...
</description></item><item><title>Download RapidRAW 1.3.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 01 Aug 2025 16:24:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rapidraw-13957.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rapidraw-13957.html
</guid><description>
RapidRAW is a modern, high-performance, open-source RAW photo editor, designed to deliver a fast and clean editing experience with a lightweight footprint (under 30MB). Built with performance and usability in mind, the software is aimed at photographers who want a simple, efficient, and fun workflow without compromising performance.
Key Features
	GPU-accelerated processing: Uses a custom WGSL shader to process all image adjustments on the GPU, allowing for smooth, responsive editing...
</description></item><item><title>Download Software Companions GerbView 11.15.0.610</title><pubDate> Fri, 01 Aug 2025 16:24:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-software-companions-gerbview-1484.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-software-companions-gerbview-1484.html
</guid><description>
GerbView is a file, advanced, but easy to use, convert, print, and view files HPGL, HPGL / 2, Excellon and raster. It supports both RS274D and RS274X. You can use this software to convert the old format and RS274D standard to the new RS274X have default data. Gerbview is used to represent and illustrate the intricate design of you.
Software Companions GerbView - conversion, printing, and viewing HPGL, HPGL / 2, Excellon
You don't need to wait for rendered images to see the picture of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Alternate Timer 4.820</title><pubDate> Fri, 01 Aug 2025 16:23:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-alternate-timer-2732.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-alternate-timer-2732.html
</guid><description>
Alternate Timer is a program to manage / journaling time (daily work, using the internet, etc.). To achieve this time table is created monthly. Could use some table time every month and match the time table with the overview panel (For example, in a year). The program also can calculate the salary on the table that time. It requires Net-Framework 2.0 or higher (already included in the operating system since Windows Vista).
Alternate Timer - time Table
Alternate Timer can be exported as...
</description></item><item><title>Download Alternate Calculator 3.920</title><pubDate> Fri, 01 Aug 2025 16:23:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-alternate-calculator-2744.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-alternate-calculator-2744.html
</guid><description>
Alternate Calculator is a simple calculator also can be used to translate the currency (e.g. Euro). It has included a set of currencies is pre-determined and the exchange rate can also be modified individually. An editor internal is included can be used to re-encode and save the calculation steps were performed.
Alternate Calculator - Calculator and currency converter
Alternate Calculator also can be used the different number systems (decimal, hexadecimal, binary, client defined). This...
</description></item><item><title>Download Karaosoft Karma 2026.0.6</title><pubDate> Fri, 01 Aug 2025 16:19:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-karma-2379.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-karma-2379.html
</guid><description>
Karma is an enhancement program that helps you tune, karaoke can view the text of the files sound different. At first glance, after launch, the layout may seem complicated, unclear where to start. You can customize the display prompts to understand the function of each parameter is highlighted integrated.
Management program your karaoke a easy way. Search no need to click, drag and drop feature and many other unique features designed to bring you the easiest management for the program...
</description></item><item><title>Download App Builder 2025.17</title><pubDate> Fri, 01 Aug 2025 16:19:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-app-builder-241.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-app-builder-241.html
</guid><description>
App Builder is a software application developer to help create and design apps, HTML5, web app, web app PWA on both platforms mobile and desktop. App Builder is professional software supports users to create the program HTML5 without writing code. It is very easy to use, suitable with all users who lack of professional knowledge in the field of programming and application design.
App Builder brings to 22 different themes that users can use to design for your app. You can choose 1 or a...
</description></item><item><title>Download Awesome Miner Ultimate 11.1.8</title><pubDate> Fri, 01 Aug 2025 16:19:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-awesome-miner-9041.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-awesome-miner-9041.html
</guid><description>
Awesome Miner is a software application designed to manage and monitor cryptocurrency mining operations. It supports a wide variety of mining hardware, including ASICs and GPUs, and can be used to manage mining for a variety of cryptocurrencies, including Bitcoin, Ethereum, and Litecoin.
Powerful tool to manage and monitor cryptocurrency mining activities. With support for a wide variety of mining hardware and cryptocurrencies, mobile apps, and customizable alerting and performance...
</description></item><item><title>Download Zero Install 2.27.4</title><pubDate> Fri, 01 Aug 2025 16:18:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zero-install-1632.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zero-install-1632.html
</guid><description>
Zero Install is a system, install the software distribution cross africa focus. Other features include full support for shared libraries (with the SAT for resolution dependent), share between users, and integration with the package manager original foundation. Zero Install supports both binary packages and source and works on Linux systems , OS X , Unix and Windows. It is completely open source.
Zero Install - System software installation
Zero Install also has a number of interesting...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tray Weather 1.35.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 01 Aug 2025 16:18:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tray-weather-7091.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tray-weather-7091.html
</guid><description>
Tray Weather is a simple application to retrieve and display weather information for a given geographical location in a small dialog box and in the Windows OS system tray. Weather and map information is obtained from OpenWeatherMap. To get weather information from OpenWeatherMap you need to register on their website and enter the given API Key in Tray Weather configuration dialog.
when executed, the application will reside in the system tray, showing the current weather icon. Tooltip...
</description></item><item><title>Download VRGeoscience Virtual Reality Geological Studio 3.02 Build 31</title><pubDate> Fri, 01 Aug 2025 16:17:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vrgeoscience-virtual-reality-geological-studio-12732.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vrgeoscience-virtual-reality-geological-studio-12732.html
</guid><description>
VRGS (Virtual Reality Geological Studio) provides an integrated software solution for visualizing, interpreting and analyzing 3D geological datasets of virtual rock outcrops. It allows users to import large datasets from Lidar and Structure from Motion (SfM)/photogrammetry, create and visualize ultra-high-resolution models in 3D in VR or desktop mode, and deploy a comprehensive set of analytical tools to describe and interpret key geological features such as layers, faults, and...
</description></item><item><title>Download PACETEQ OneTiming 1.10.134</title><pubDate> Fri, 01 Aug 2025 16:17:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-paceteq-onetiming-12731.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-paceteq-onetiming-12731.html
</guid><description>
OneTiming integrates all important data sources, including all major timing protocols, GPS feeds, Race Control Messages, weather data and video feeds. The optimal balance of performance and durability is designed to be the benchmark for dynamic and complex racing environments.
Key Features of OneTiming
	Data Integration: OneTiming seamlessly combines information from multiple channels, including timekeeping, telemetry, weather data, and audio/video feeds. This integration supports all...
</description></item><item><title>Download W10Privacy 5.2.0.4</title><pubDate> Fri, 01 Aug 2025 16:16:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-w10privacy-2956.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-w10privacy-2956.html
</guid><description>
W10Privacy is a program lightweight and simple application that allows you to easily and quickly configure the privacy settings in system Windows its 10. Typically these options can be configured directly from the operating system, but they are hidden in some menu that the user can not normally access easily.
W10Privacy - Configure the options the right to privacy in Windows
The application will display the settings available clear, allowing you to configure the desired options...
</description></item></channel></rss>