<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 17:40:14 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 17:40:14 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download LibreOffice 25.8.3 / 7.6.7</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 19:45:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-libreoffice-391.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-libreoffice-391.html
</guid><description>
LibreOffice is editor free for office similar to MS Office and OpenOffice includes word processor, spreadsheet application, presentation tool, database and design diagrams. Here is the app code open source, multi-feature, to offer users many tools to draft documents and handle the office documents efficiently.
The program can open or import most Microsoft Office formats popular, including .doc .ppt and .csv as well as many document formats other. LibreOffice is a tool to be more user...
</description></item><item><title>Download LDPlayer 9.1.78.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 19:43:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ldplayer-2331.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ldplayer-2331.html
</guid><description>
LDPlayer is an Android emulator that allows users to play games and run applications on Windows computers. LDPlayer supports heavy gaming, running chat applications, editing photos, videos, and many other Android applications. LDPlayer is compatible with Android 5.1 and above, supporting multitasking for an experience that is not inferior to that of using on Mobile.
Installation is a simple and quick process that does not require any special attention from you, there are more. settings,...
</description></item><item><title>Download CalendarTask (formerly DesktopCal) 3.26.255.8188</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 19:41:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopcal-1831.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopcal-1831.html
</guid><description>
CalendarTask (formerly DesktopCal) is a simple desktop calendar that blends into your desktop without blocking access to your desktop icons. You can double-click on a date to quickly add notes and also jump to specific dates in the past or future.
CalendarTask - Computer calendar
CalendarTask can use your current wallpaper or loop through images from your folder and update your desktop every few minutes. The program helps you make appointments, make plans... Not only that, the Screen...
</description></item><item><title>Download reaConverter Pro 8.0.154</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 19:38:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html
</guid><description>
reaConverter Pro is software image processing feature with batch conversion and image editing periodically becomes simple. eaConverter also provide command line utilities allow you to process images automatically, thus helping you shorten the time for other work.
reaConverter Pro integrated powerful tool of Uber with many great features. It provides advanced solutions to process and adjust images. Management of the conversion process the base image with the latest version of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Shutter Encoder 19.6</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 19:38:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-shutter-encoder-6837.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-shutter-encoder-6837.html
</guid><description>
Shutter Encoder is an easy-to-use program to convert, edit and encode images, videos, audio files and more. Shutter Encoder is a video, audio and image converter based on FFmpeg and other great tools. It has been designed by video editors to be as accessible and effective as possible.
Features of Shutter Encoder:
	Cut without re-encoding, Replace Audio, Rewind, Edit, Merge, Extract, Subtitle, Insert Video
	Audio Converter: WAV, AIFF, FLAC, MP3, AAC, AC3, OPUS, OGG
	Edit codecs: DNxHD,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Abelssoft YouTube Song Downloader Plus 2026 v26.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 19:38:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-abelssoft-youtube-song-downloader-plus-111.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-abelssoft-youtube-song-downloader-plus-111.html
</guid><description>
Abelssoft YouTube Song Downloader Plus 2018.18.17 Program YouTube Song Downloader Plus will help you search the music and video files from YouTube, after you can download them at. To search for music you just need to enter song name in the required field and you will get results, then you can download all videos and audio files. The program can search the entire album, this function will help to find individual songs from separate albums, because of this we specify the name of the artist...
</description></item><item><title>Download GoodSync Enterprise 12.9.16.6</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 19:37:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-goodsync-enterprise-163.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-goodsync-enterprise-163.html
</guid><description>
GoodSync Enterprise is a software that saves files and files easily and is reliable. It automatically analyts, synchronize and backup your email, family photos, contacts, MP3, financial documentation and other important files-between desktop computers, laptops, servers, external drives and Windows Mobile devices as well as remotely via FTP , SFTP, WebDAV and more. The GoodSync synchronized software combines bulletproof reliability with an extremely easy interface to compare, synchronize...
</description></item><item><title>Download Aiseesoft FoneLab for Android 6.0.20</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 19:37:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aiseesoft-fonelab-for-android-3929.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aiseesoft-fonelab-for-android-3929.html
</guid><description>
Aiseesoft FoneLab for Android is one of the software Android data recovery best. Aiseesoft FoneLab for Android is recovery software data great for Android users that helps you recover text messages, deleted messages, attached, lost, contacts lost, call history and Photos, Photo, Videos, Music, documents on Android phone, tablet and your SD card. Regardless of whether you lost files due to mistakenly deletion, root, upgrade, format the memory card, attack of virus or due to you crashing,...
</description></item><item><title>Download SIW Technicians 2025 v15.10.1111</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 19:36:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-siw-technicians-3584.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-siw-technicians-3584.html
</guid><description>
SIW Technicians is an information tool complex system, for Microsoft Windows, check your PC and collect detailed data about the properties and system settings and displays it in a way very easy to understand. SIW Technicians can create a report file (JSON, HTML, TXT, CSV or XML) and you can use that file in batch mode (for Inventory computer inventory of hardware and software, asset inventory, security audit, license Management software, configuration Management server).
SIW Technicians...
</description></item><item><title>Download Iperius Backup Full 8.7.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 19:36:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iperius-backup-621.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iperius-backup-621.html
</guid><description>
Iperius Backup software supports backup and restore of data can be stored on a cloud service, and AES 256-bit. This is the perfect software to get the advantages of the many services that cloud storage is provided by the famous supplier like Google or Microsoft. With a single application, you will can easily save your files externally on Google Drive, Dropbox or Microsoft SkyDrive.
Iperius Backup uses the technology images Windows drive most advanced, allows to copy entire operating...
</description></item><item><title>Download BackUp Maker Pro 8.318</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 19:35:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-backup-maker-pro-480.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-backup-maker-pro-480.html
</guid><description>
BackUp Maker Pro is software backup, data recovery secure against hazards like virus attack, system error or due to the user mistakenly deleted data... BackUp Maker Pro security of your files regularly so that in case of emergency, data your computer you can still gain access. BackUp Maker automatically stores your data and at the same time provide intuitive operation: select your data, optionally set the automation to backup according to schedules, select the destination and immediately,...
</description></item><item><title>Download FileLocator Pro 2022 Build 3540</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 19:35:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-filelocator-pro-1056.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-filelocator-pro-1056.html
</guid><description>
FileLocator Pro is software manage files and search function the file quickly the software and data. FileLocator Pro helps you find things quickly. The unique feature of it allows the extraction of information in all file formats the most obscure.
FileLocator Pro - file Manager
The features of FileLocator Pro
	Search algorithm based on the C ++ multi-threading for ultra-fast
	Search for network drive by mapped drive or UNC paths
	Support regular expressions for file name and...
</description></item><item><title>Download CapCut PC 7.5.0.3053</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 19:34:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capcut-pc-9995.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capcut-pc-9995.html
</guid><description>
CapCut PC is a simple video editing tool that you can freely use anywhere. You can create videos on your browser, desktop and laptop, or on your phone. Versatile editing, magical AI tools, team collaboration, and built-in assets. Create videos in a whole new way.
You can edit videos based on editing the timeline, in the process you can add different elements and effects to the video to give the best effect to your work. It is a simple and intuitive set of editing tools and effects that...
</description></item><item><title>Download ExpanDrive 2025.11.10</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 19:33:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-expandrive-609.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-expandrive-609.html
</guid><description>
ExpanDrive is software sync cloud storage strong support BackBlaze B2, Google Team Drive, SMB / CIFS and new interface and easy user search file version, share links and much more.  ExpanDrive mapped network drives for macOS and Micosoft Windows connect with all the provide major cloud storage such as Dropbox, Google Drive, Google Team Drive, Amazon Drive, Box, OneDrive, OneDrive for Business, Sharepoint, Openstack Swift , BackBlaze B2, Amazon S3 or SFTP servers, FTP or WebDAV on your own...
</description></item><item><title>Download iFunia Video Converter 4.2.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 19:33:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ifunia-video-converter-10020.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ifunia-video-converter-10020.html
</guid><description>
iFunia Video Converter is a versatile video converter that supports more than 600 video and audio formats, including 4K/5K UHD video. It can extract audio from video and convert for popular devices and software. The application also has advanced editing functions, built-in media player and fast conversion speed. In addition, iFunia Video-Converter includes a DVD creator that can burn video to DVD with menus, subtitles and background music.
The application supports various DVD menu...
</description></item><item><title>Download 3D Youtube Downloader 1.24</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 19:33:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-3d-youtube-downloader-1631.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-3d-youtube-downloader-1631.html
</guid><description>
3D Youtube Downloader is application support users to download the videos from Youtube website with great quality. The advantage of this software is the ability to download the videos in 3D, make the download process is fully automated and the download speed is extremely fast. In addition to Youtube, this tool also allows to download videos from many other sites, so users can own any favorite videos yet. 3D Youtube Downloader is a downloads simple but powerful from Youtube, Vimeo,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Youtube Downloader HD 5.9.9.5</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 19:32:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-downloader-hd-3122.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-downloader-hd-3122.html
</guid><description>
Youtube Downloader HD is the best application to download and save Youtube videos. And it's completely free :) You can also convert the downloaded video into various formats easily. Youtube Downloader HD is the download at video free. Download at your videos easily and convert to AVI video format or into MP4 video format (compatible with iPad, iPhone). You can download high quality videos, high definition videos and Full HD from YouTube.
Youtube Downloader HD - Download Youtube videos...
</description></item><item><title>Download VSO ConvertXtoDVD 7.5.0.137</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 19:31:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vso-convertxtodvd-182.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vso-convertxtodvd-182.html
</guid><description>
VSO ConvertXtoDVD is specialized software used to convert video and burn to DVD with many formats including AVI, MKV, MOV, DivX, WMV, MTS, MPEG... and you can watch it on any player whatsoever, in general is convenient. ConvertXtoDVD supports work with a large number of video formats among them MPEG, AVI, DV, MOV and so on, you can see on the official website, also support working with video online.
VSO ConvertXtoDVD
In addition, the use of VSO ConvertXtoDVD to edit the audio files as...
</description></item><item><title>Download 4K Video Downloader Plus 25.4.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 19:31:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-video-downloader-617.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-video-downloader-617.html
</guid><description>
4K Video Downloader Plus is software support downloads video, audio and subtitles from YouTube with high quality up to 4K. Download process video is very simple: just copy the video link from your browser and click Paste Url. Done! If you want that video on your iPad, iPhone or other device, we have protected you.
The feature on 4K Video Downloader Plus
	Download entire playlists and channels from YouTube and save them in MP4, MKV, M4A, MP3, FLV, 3G, create a file .m3u for...
</description></item><item><title>Download NCH PicoPDF Plus 7.28</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 19:31:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nch-picopdf-plus-6856.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nch-picopdf-plus-6856.html
</guid><description>
NCH PicoPDF Plus is a simpler and lighter alternative to other popular PDF programs, such as Sumatra PDF and Foxit Reader. More, it can be used completely offline and not based on active internet connectivity to be able to perform some functions such as other similar software.
Features of NCH PicoPDF Plus
	Edit existing text or add new text
	Reorder text and graphics
	Add notes and comments to documents
	Delete or move embedded images
	Add an image to your PDF
	Enter in the space to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Hard Disk Sentinel Pro 6.30.5 Beta</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 19:30:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hard-disk-sentinel-pro-562.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hard-disk-sentinel-pro-562.html
</guid><description>
Hard Disk Sentinel Pro is a tool for monitoring and optimal performance for hard drive HDD and help diagnose the HDD as well as SSD. Version of Hard Disk Sentinel Pro is a professional version, the most advanced of Hard Disk with many advanced features that meet basic needs, check the hard drive for the user.
The goal of it is to find, test, diagnose and repair the malfunction, hard drive, report and display the health status of the SSD and hard drive failure, decreased performance and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Garmin Express 7.27.1.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 19:30:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-garmin-express-1579.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-garmin-express-1579.html
</guid><description>
Garmin Express is a tool developed by the company Garmin to enable you to manage equipment on your GPS from the computer. You can use this app to map updates, register the device, update software and even to create a backup. Garmin Express also allows you to install voices and vehicles for free, as well as download instructions for use product.
Garmin Express - Manage GPS devices
You can automatically update the map by only one click, so you always have accurate information when you go...
</description></item><item><title>Download MP3Studio YouTube Downloader 2.0.29</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 19:29:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mp3studio-youtube-downloader-6778.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mp3studio-youtube-downloader-6778.html
</guid><description>
MP3Studio YouTube Downloader is an efficient and user-friendly software developed to provide you with an easy means of getting all your favorite videos from the web and store them on your PC, in one of the available formats. With MP3Studio YouTube Downloader, you can download up to 99 songs at once in the background as you start your business.
Use this media editor to preload various songs via YouTube and other services. It will provide you with good quality music that you can listen to...
</description></item><item><title>Download ZD Soft Screen Recorder 12.0.8</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 19:29:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zd-soft-screen-recorder-136.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zd-soft-screen-recorder-136.html
</guid><description>
ZD Soft Screen Recorder supports user taping the game in 2D or 3D, film screen, the content is screened in the multimedia. The Videos are saved in a list and popular formats with best quality.
ZD Soft Screen Recorder is a program recording software screen high performance. It works just like a camera really. A camcorder can record many things in the real world including computer screen, while ZD Soft Screen Recorder can only record computer screen but can do much better than a camcorder...
</description></item><item><title>Download SoundVolumeView 2.48</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 19:29:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-soundvolumeview-2695.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-soundvolumeview-2695.html
</guid><description>
SoundVolumeView is a simple tool for Windows Vista / 7/8/2008/10, displays general information and current volume levels for all components sound activity on your system and allows you to mute and unmute them instantly. SoundVolumeView also allows you to save audio configuration to a file, containing the current volume level status and mute / unmute of all audio components, as well as the audio devices to default, then upload the same file to restore exactly the same file volume levels and...
</description></item></channel></rss>