<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 21:50:41 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 21:50:41 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download reaConverter Pro 8.0.187</title><pubDate> Mon, 26 Jan 2026 23:53:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html
</guid><description>
reaConverter Pro is software image processing feature with batch conversion and image editing periodically becomes simple. eaConverter also provide command line utilities allow you to process images automatically, thus helping you shorten the time for other work.
reaConverter Pro integrated powerful tool of Uber with many great features. It provides advanced solutions to process and adjust images. Management of the conversion process the base image with the latest version of...
</description></item><item><title>Download O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro 22.1.240 / Server</title><pubDate> Mon, 26 Jan 2026 23:53:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-diskimage-pro-218.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-diskimage-pro-218.html
</guid><description>
O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro is software backup data comprehensive and effective is provided to protect the data of the computer system, it creates images for individual drives or the entire system that still does not affect your system.
O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro allows the user to backup the entire computer or drive, the and files whenever you want even while the computer is being used. Or can use O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro to create a copy chinh sac of computer disk drives, can be used instead of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download GiliSoft Audio Toolbox Suite 13.3</title><pubDate> Mon, 26 Jan 2026 23:52:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-audio-toolbox-suite-856.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-audio-toolbox-suite-856.html
</guid><description>
GiliSoft Audio Toolbox Suite is software that contains 9 program powerful audio like Audio Recorder , Audio Cutter, Audio Joiner, Audio Converter, Video to Mp3,ID3 Tag Editor,Transfer to iTunes,CD Ripper,CD Burner. With GiliSoft Audio Toolbox Suite, you can easily convert and edit any audio file, how to extract, create and copy CD, convert audio files, burn music to CD, rip CD / DVD to the audio file to another, etc.
GiliSoft Audio Toolbox Suite - software sound synthesis
The main...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Dimension 4.1.7 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Mon, 26 Jan 2026 23:51:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-dimension-cc-254.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-dimension-cc-254.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Dimension CC 2019 is software for designing 2D and 3D to easily create 3D images are of high quality, made to combine the resources intuitive 2D and 3D in one product the actual environment. Purpose introduction of Adobe Dimension is to provide to developers the tools necessary to integrate assets in 2D and 3D without having to study the application complex and specialized. In other words, the program allows you to quickly and simple and creative image other combined 2D and 3D...
</description></item><item><title>Download The Bat! Professional 12.0.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 26 Jan 2026 23:51:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-the-bat-professional-3072.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-the-bat-professional-3072.html
</guid><description>
The Bat! Professional is an email program guest safety, developed to protect your correspondence against the side Tuesday. The Bat! Professional protection of your data through multi-threaded encoding with a choice encoding of your emails on disk and during communication through SSL / TLS connections. Free email providers global hosting your mail on the cloud and free for the Web clients, The Bat! ensure your data is kept private.
The Bat! Professional - mail application security
The...
</description></item><item><title>Download ExpanDrive 2026.01.22</title><pubDate> Mon, 26 Jan 2026 23:50:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-expandrive-609.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-expandrive-609.html
</guid><description>
ExpanDrive is software sync cloud storage strong support BackBlaze B2, Google Team Drive, SMB / CIFS and new interface and easy user search file version, share links and much more.  ExpanDrive mapped network drives for macOS and Micosoft Windows connect with all the provide major cloud storage such as Dropbox, Google Drive, Google Team Drive, Amazon Drive, Box, OneDrive, OneDrive for Business, Sharepoint, Openstack Swift , BackBlaze B2, Amazon S3 or SFTP servers, FTP or WebDAV on your own...
</description></item><item><title>Download GiliSoft Audio Recorder Pro 15.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 26 Jan 2026 23:44:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-audio-recorder-pro-855.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-audio-recorder-pro-855.html
</guid><description>
GiliSoft Audio Recorder Pro is software perfect recorder to record audio and microphone of your computer to AAC, AC3, AIFF, AMR, AU, FLAC, M4A, M4B, M4R, MKA, MP2, MP3, OGG, RA, VOC , WAV Files or WMA files on Windows 7/8. Recording the sound that goes through your sound card is not at all a difficult task, but GiliSoft Audio Recorder Pro promises to make everything a lot easier, even for those who do not have computer knowledge advanced.
GiliSoft Audio Recorder Pro - audio recording...
</description></item><item><title>Download KILHO AutoClick 1.4.8</title><pubDate> Mon, 26 Jan 2026 23:38:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kilho-autoclick-12515.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kilho-autoclick-12515.html
</guid><description>
AutoClick is a software or script designed to automate mouse clicking tasks, especially useful for repetitive actions in a variety of applications, including gaming and data entry. It allows users to define specific click points and automatically click at those locations. This tool is user-friendly and supports recording click sequences for repeated use.
AutoClick allows users to set precise time intervals and geographic coordinates for various click patterns. Additionally, AutoClick...
</description></item><item><title>Download gBurner Pro 5.7.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 26 Jan 2026 23:38:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gburner-5594.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gburner-5594.html
</guid><description>
gBurner is a powerful and easy-to-use CD / DVD burning tool, allows you to create and burn data, CD and DVD audio, create bootable data CDs and DVDs, create multi-session discs copy. Moreover, this software can be used as a disk image file processing tool, thus it will allow you to create, extract, open, edit, convert or burn ISO / BIN image files.
gBurner Features
	Easy and friendly interface. gBurner supports context menu, drag and drop, copy and paste clipboard…
	Create and burn...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinPane Home 1.0.3</title><pubDate> Mon, 26 Jan 2026 20:48:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winpane-home-14534.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winpane-home-14534.html
</guid><description>
Welcome to a desktop experience designed entirely for YOU. Whether you're a tech novice, a senior looking for a simpler interface, or a gamer seeking speed, this app will transform your Windows PC into a centralized, colorful, and user-friendly control center.
We believe that technology should be accessible to everyone. That's why we've replaced the clutter of traditional computer screens with a streamlined, app-like home screen. WinPane Home is a modern control panel with a simple...
</description></item><item><title>Download Hamaguri Blur 1.0.4</title><pubDate> Mon, 26 Jan 2026 20:42:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hamaguri-blur-14533.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hamaguri-blur-14533.html
</guid><description>
Hamaguri Blur is a productivity tool designed to help you focus on the task at hand by reducing "distractions" on your computer screen. It applies a customizable blurring overlay to the screen, blurring background windows, icons, and other distracting elements, allowing you to fully concentrate on the task at hand.
Enhanced concentration: Modern computer screens are often full of distractions. Hamaguri Blur lets you hide the clutter of inactive windows and wallpapers with a gentle,...
</description></item><item><title>Download UEFITool A73</title><pubDate> Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:02:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-uefitool-4063.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-uefitool-4063.html
</guid><description>
UEFITool allows edit, parse and extract images, UEFITool support analysis, pictures, BIOS full cover sets description flash or any binary files which contains the volume of UEFI; it is compatible with many types of image BIOS including ROM, BIN, FD, CAP, BIO, WPH and EFI, all of them will load and display convenient together with the appropriate details, including name, category / sub category and text such.
UEFITool - Extract images
UEFITool will allow you to extract data from an...
</description></item><item><title>Download KMPlayer (KMP) 2026.1.26.43 x64 / 4.2.3.31 x86</title><pubDate> Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:01:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kmplayer-kmp-902.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kmplayer-kmp-902.html
</guid><description>
KMPlayer (KMP) is software watch movies listen to music multi-function for video enthusiasts. KMPlayer development is many types of the format different. KMPlayer has improved on sound quality, images when listening to music and watching movies, the playback speed of video is faster, more codec player is added to the software video decoder is optimized.
KMPlayer also supports a variety of audio formats and video and offers a the interface can be customized with the preview coverflow and...
</description></item><item><title>Download RapidRAW 1.4.9</title><pubDate> Mon, 26 Jan 2026 16:54:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rapidraw-13957.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rapidraw-13957.html
</guid><description>
RapidRAW is a modern, high-performance, open-source RAW photo editor, designed to deliver a fast and clean editing experience with a lightweight footprint (under 30MB). Built with performance and usability in mind, the software is aimed at photographers who want a simple, efficient, and fun workflow without compromising performance.
Key Features
	GPU-accelerated processing: Uses a custom WGSL shader to process all image adjustments on the GPU, allowing for smooth, responsive editing...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinTools.one Professional / Home 26.1.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 26 Jan 2026 16:53:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wintoolsone-10808.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wintoolsone-10808.html
</guid><description>
WinTools.one is a program designed to help both regular and advanced users as well as computer engineers fine-tune the MS Windows operating system. It allows you to increase the performance of the operating system, maintain its performance at a high level, fix operating system errors, free up space on the computer's hard drive and control the operation of installed programs. In addition, the program allows you to store and protect your secret and confidential information, as well as work...
</description></item><item><title>Download O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Premium 22.2.1149</title><pubDate> Mon, 26 Jan 2026 16:53:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-diskimage-server-4547.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-diskimage-server-4547.html
</guid><description>
O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Server is software that is specially designed for use in enterprise environments, the software allows users to backup all the files you want and keep them safe from any incident or disaster computer. O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Server comes with a variety of easy to use utility that allows users to backup entire partitions of the specific files from their PC, as well as recover the version previous data of them, all from a simple interface.
O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Server - data...
</description></item><item><title>Download ExifTool 13.46</title><pubDate> Mon, 26 Jan 2026 16:52:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-exiftool-1685.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-exiftool-1685.html
</guid><description>
ExifTool is a library of Perl platform-independent plus a command line application for reading, writing, and editing meta information in various file types. ExifTool supports many metadata formats including EXIF , GPS , IPTC , XMP , JFIF , GeoTIFF , ICC Profile , Photoshop IRB , FlashPix , AFCP and ID3 , as well as notes of the manufacturer of many digital cameras by Canon , Casio , DJI , FLIR , FujiFilm , GE , GoPro , HP , JVC / Victor , Kodak , Leaf , Minolta / Konica-Minolta , Motorola...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinScript 1.4.7</title><pubDate> Mon, 26 Jan 2026 16:52:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winscript-12800.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winscript-12800.html
</guid><description>
WinScript is an open source tool built to help you build custom scripts for Windows 10 and 11. It includes scripts for debugging, privacy, performance, and more, along with the ability to install all your favorite apps with just one click.
Features
	Debloat: Remove Windows bloatware, CoPilot, Edge, OneDrive, and other pre-installed features preset.
	Privacy: Disable Windows and 3rd party data collection, tracking, app access, and telemetry.
	Performance: Set background services to...
</description></item><item><title>Download 4KSoftware 4K Downloader 6.1.6</title><pubDate> Mon, 26 Jan 2026 16:51:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-downloader-3858.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-downloader-3858.html
</guid><description>
4K Downloader is a Windows application small but powerful to download and convert video in 4K and 8K Ultra HD from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion and thousands of other video-based websites. It speeds up your download by up to 5 times. Consider that most smart phones, TVS, computers, and tablets all support the high definition format, don't be surprised when many users want to enjoy quality content on their device. 4K Downloader is a lightweight software designed to help you grab videos...
</description></item><item><title>Download Helium Music Manager Premium 17.4.564</title><pubDate> Mon, 26 Jan 2026 16:51:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-helium-music-manager-premium-164.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-helium-music-manager-premium-164.html
</guid><description>
Helium Music Manager is a music manager that can rip, tag, play, browse, search, rename, burn and synchronize your music with the mobile. You can control your music collection with Helium Music Manager. Stop using time looking for the file on your computer or looking through CDS, vinyl records and tapes - instead, simply enjoy and explore your music! Helium Music Manager can replace the ripper, the player, tag editor and related software to audio your other.
Helium Music Manager...
</description></item><item><title>Download Pepakura Designer 6.1.4</title><pubDate> Mon, 26 Jan 2026 16:51:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pepakura-designer-748.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pepakura-designer-748.html
</guid><description>
Pepakura Designer is software to create 2D models, 3D quick, easy and developed in Japan. Pepakura Designer helps easily design the template paper craft by importing data 3D model. No special knowledge is required to model papercraft. All you have to do is prepare the 3D model. You can use some software 3DCG released from other developers to make the 3D models for unfolding.
Pepakura Designer - Create model 2D 3D
Pepakura Designer to create the form of 2D images that you can share it...
</description></item><item><title>Download Eltima CloudMounter 3.6.2112</title><pubDate> Mon, 26 Jan 2026 16:49:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-eltima-cloudmounter-6553.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-eltima-cloudmounter-6553.html
</guid><description>
Eltima CloudMounter is a reliable system utility that allows mounting various cloud storages and web servers to your personal computer as a local disk . Connect to Microsoft OneDrive, Google Drive, Amazon S3, Dropbox, FTP, and WebDAV servers in Finder, just as if they were on your machine.
Eltima CloudMounter Features
	Mapping cloud storage as a network drive to manage files online the same way you manage files locally.
	Access the clouds easily with CloudMounter
	You can mount...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube Downloader 3.9.18 (2501)</title><pubDate> Mon, 26 Jan 2026 16:48:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube Downloader  is a dedicated software that helps users  downloading youtube videos  Favorites on PC for offline viewing. With MediaHuman YouTube  Downloader  you can download videos from youtube website to your computer with  fast speed , with special software development technology that automatically receives videos from Websites, in addition to the ability to download videos from software websites, can convert downloaded video formats to various formats for the purpose...
</description></item><item><title>Download Kotato All Video Downloader Pro 10.1.6</title><pubDate> Mon, 26 Jan 2026 16:48:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kotato-all-video-downloader-pro-5228.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kotato-all-video-downloader-pro-5228.html
</guid><description>
Kotato All Video Downloader Pro is a Windows application professional to download and convert your favorite videos from the video sharing website. It speeds up your downloads up to 5 times! Kotato All Video Downloader Pro can download videos from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion and hundreds of video sharing sites, other. After downloading, you will be able to play them smoother on your PC or your mobile device, even when you don't have Internet access.
The main features of Kotato All...
</description></item><item><title>Download Yellow Leads Extractor 9.3.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 26 Jan 2026 16:48:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yellow-leads-extractor-3729.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yellow-leads-extractor-3729.html
</guid><description>
Yellow Leads Extractor is the software that allows users to make 100% custom search in the browser. When you have this program then you don't need to do more work to retrieve information from the yellow pages. You just need to enter the category and location. After entering the information when you will click on the option data get then all the information will be extracted.
Yellow Leads Extractor - custom Search on the browser
The features of the Yellow Leads Extractor
	You can save...
</description></item></channel></rss>