<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 01:46:44 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 01:46:44 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Monkeys Audio 11.88</title><pubDate> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 00:01:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-monkeys-audio-949.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-monkeys-audio-949.html
</guid><description>
Monkey\'s Audio is software that compresses digital music without loss of quality. Supports high quality WAV files and CD ripping. Monkeys Audio will compress .wav tracks into .ape files to reduce their size without loss of sound quality, decompress .ape, convert files, check file integrity and manage tags.
Unlike traditional methods like MP3 and OGG, which permanently remove quality to save space, Monkey\'s Audio only creates perfect copies with the same sound quality as the originals....
</description></item><item><title>Download MSI Center 2.0.62.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 00:00:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-msi-center-12314.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-msi-center-12314.html
</guid><description>
The AI ​​era of computing: MSI laptops are equipped with MSI's exclusive AI technology capable of providing completely new smart features. The AI ​​revolution has arrived on MSI laptops. MSI AI Engine automatically recognizes various user situations, triggering appropriate adjustments in performance, sound effects, display modes and keyboard backlighting. Users do not need to make manual adjustments to achieve optimal situations.
MSI Center combines all of MSI's exclusive...
</description></item><item><title>Download JRiver Media Center 35.0.24</title><pubDate> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 00:00:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jriver-media-center-110.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jriver-media-center-110.html
</guid><description>
JRiver Media Center can help you strictly manage all your files media and enjoy them in a completely new way. Launching the application for the first time, users will be immediately impressed with the intuitive and eye-catching interface with many interesting features to explore. Most people who have used JRiver Media Center evaluate that the software interface design is youthful and modern.
The software for arranging cover art of music files is also extremely neat, especially Insert...
</description></item><item><title>Download HDCleaner 2.095</title><pubDate> Mon, 24 Nov 2025 23:59:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hdcleaner-1050.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hdcleaner-1050.html
</guid><description>
HDCleaner is optimization software system and perform other tasks as completely delete files, edit the shortcut errors, defragment the drive,... HDCleaner is the solution to support users who are looking for a measure, optimize your computer effectively without using too many other programs.
HDCleaner - Cleanup system optimization
HDCleaner includes four tabs different folders, allowing users to navigate through the remote operation and fast extraction of features. Tab Dashboard...
</description></item><item><title>Download Irix HDR Pro 2.3.54</title><pubDate> Mon, 24 Nov 2025 23:59:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-irix-hdr-pro-10653.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-irix-hdr-pro-10653.html
</guid><description>
Irix HDR Pro is an AI-powered photo editing application for Windows, it is available on Microsoft Store. This program has tons of professional HDR photo editing features including Sky Replacement, Face Sculpting &amp;amp; body, over 200 presets &amp;amp; AI powered tool' and is a Photo Editor in the category of photo &amp;amp; Graphics. It delivers true-to-life HDR photo editing, providing one-click edits for a full-scale professional editing toolkit.
Features of Irix HDR Pro
	Sky Replacement...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sandboxie 5.71.8</title><pubDate> Mon, 24 Nov 2025 23:58:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sandboxie-818.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sandboxie-818.html
</guid><description>
Sandboxie software to browse the Web securely while still keeping all the functionality your browser for content works against harmful agents such as sanbox up your computer. You may not know, when you browse the Web, the change will occur with the system of your computer. When you use Sandboxie, the software will protect the web browser of their own.
Sandboxie - web protection, safe browsing
The main features of Sandboxie
Stay safe on the Internet with Sandboxie
	Run the program in...
</description></item><item><title>Download Drive SnapShot 1.50.0.1766</title><pubDate> Mon, 24 Nov 2025 23:58:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-drive-snapshot-701.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-drive-snapshot-701.html
</guid><description>
Drive SnapShot is a backup software, Restore disk, including operating system, installed programs, your data and all security attributes - while windows is running and you continue to work. With Drive SnapShot you backup partition or hard drive and it can also create disk image of your system. If a disaster occurs (a virus, trojan or the fixed hard disk), the recover complete and accurate your system will be able to accomplish after only a few minutes. The image file can be mounted as...
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakPower 2.076</title><pubDate> Mon, 24 Nov 2025 23:58:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweakpower-1038.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweakpower-1038.html
</guid><description>
TweakPower is software, line up the system and tweak the operating system and your program to have optimal performance. The use of the computer for long periods can cause stress for performance. Surfing the web, uninstall the program or keep the computer clutter can all contribute to reduced performance or even errors. On the bright sid of things, you can rely on dedicated applications such as TweakPower to keep your computer in good state.
TweakPower - Cleanup system
TweakPower...
</description></item><item><title>Download Irix HDR Classic Pro 2.3.54</title><pubDate> Mon, 24 Nov 2025 23:57:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-irix-hdr-classic-pro-10652.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-irix-hdr-classic-pro-10652.html
</guid><description>
Irix HDR Classic Pro is an AI-powered photo editor that delivers true-to-life HDR photo editing, providing one-click edits to the editing toolkit professional at full scale with a highly cognitive user interface (UI).
Main features:
	Sky replacement (SkyXpress): replaces the sky and imports weather. Import custom skies and merge, blend, and integrate with your images for a natural look with AI Edge Detect.
	Presets &amp;amp; Filters: 200+ social media optimized presets with just one tap...
</description></item><item><title>Download RegCool 3.0.0.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 24 Nov 2025 23:57:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-regcool-42.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-regcool-42.html
</guid><description>
RegCool is a powerful and user-friendly registry editor for Windows operating systems. The registry is an important part of the Windows operating system, containing important settings and configurations that determine how your computer functions. With RegCool, users can easily navigate, edit, and manage registry keys and values, making it a valuable tool for advanced users and IT professionals.
RegCool's main features:
	User-friendly interface: RegCool has a clear and intuitive user...
</description></item><item><title>Download CopyWin 4.74</title><pubDate> Mon, 24 Nov 2025 23:56:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reuschtools-copywin-14136.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reuschtools-copywin-14136.html
</guid><description>
Reuschtools CopyWin is a versatile program designed to copy the contents of your Windows drive, including all files and programs, to another drive, USB or MicroSD card. This is especially useful for upgrading or replacing storage hardware, as it simplifies the migration process. The tool does not require installation; it can be used by running the executable file, but requires administrative rights to operate. CopyWin also offers features like incremental backups after the initial backup,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Auslogics Anti-Malware 1.23.0.3</title><pubDate> Mon, 24 Nov 2025 23:56:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-auslogics-anti-malware-788.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-auslogics-anti-malware-788.html
</guid><description>
Auslogics Anti-Malware is software antivirus, top protection against the threat of data security and malware. Auslogics Anti-Malware is the product of Auslogics, certified Microsoft® Gold Application Developer. The software is Microsoft appreciated in developing quality software to meet the increasing demand of the users.
Auslogics Anti-Malware - viruses and malware
Features of Auslogics Anti-Malware
	Detection of the toxic
	Schedule automatic scans flexible
	Keep your computer safe...
</description></item><item><title>Download Efficient Elements for presentations 4.4.5800.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 24 Nov 2025 23:55:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-efficient-elements-for-presentations-7748.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-efficient-elements-for-presentations-7748.html
</guid><description>
Efficient Elements for presentations is an add-in for Microsoft PowerPoint for creating professional-looking presentations in your corporate design. Automatic program slides. Comprehensive Slide Library. Format and Align with one click. Check out the powerful corporate design. Interactive Harvey Shadows, Traffic Lights,… Map of All Countries in the World that you can edit in Excel.
Features of Efficient Elements for presentations
	Calculate time intervals or pages...
</description></item><item><title>Download Far Manager 3.0 Build 6600</title><pubDate> Mon, 24 Nov 2025 23:55:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-far-manager-1609.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-far-manager-1609.html
</guid><description>
Far Manager is an application for managing files and archives in Windows operating systems. Far Manager works in text mode and provides a simple interface and intuitive to perform the action.
Far Manager - Manage file documents
The main features of Far Manager include:
	Viewing files and directories; editing, copying and renaming files; and many other actions.
	The function of Far Manager is significantly expanded by the module DLL outside - the plugin, created by a special...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinCatalog 2024.16.0.1124</title><pubDate> Mon, 24 Nov 2025 23:54:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wincatalog-615.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wincatalog-615.html
</guid><description>
WinCatalog 2018 is a software cataloguer multi-function for the disk, file, folder, and any objects not files. Not always easy to track the location of a number of files in your computer, especially if you have a huge collection of CD and DVD. If you are one of those users, then surely there will be appropriate tools to work with such a task. WinCatalog is a software utility designed to help you find documents and data from your computer by building an index that allows you immediate...
</description></item><item><title>Download Garden Planner 3.8.79</title><pubDate> Mon, 24 Nov 2025 23:53:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-garden-planner-186.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-garden-planner-186.html
</guid><description>
Garden Planner : If you want to create a garden plan, create a landscape by activity or simply be curious, then you can download Garden Planner .   Garden Planner is a program that helps the user to design a dream garden through the layout and arrangement of plants, plants, buildings and objects, creating living spaces. style is consistent with the user's criteria and standards.
Garden Planner application is very simple, just select bushes, other plants, trees, pond and drag them into...
</description></item><item><title>Download HttpMaster Pro 6.2.5</title><pubDate> Mon, 24 Nov 2025 23:53:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-httpmaster-pro-1925.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-httpmaster-pro-1925.html
</guid><description>
A useful application for web developers who need to automate the test the web application by requesting multiple resources from a specified site web-based application. The professional version httpMaster in order to meet the requirements of many people when related to the test application. When working with HttpMaster Pro, most of the time you will manage the attributes and properties of the project HttpMaster of the items required in project. Project properties provides the global options...
</description></item><item><title>Download BotMaster 26.0.0.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 24 Nov 2025 23:52:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-botmaster-12136.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-botmaster-12136.html
</guid><description>
BotMaster is a WhatsApp marketing tool for businesses and is designed to help businesses reach their target audience effectively. With advanced features and capabilities, BotMaster makes it easy for businesses to engage with customers on WhatsApp and improve their marketing efforts. Whether you're looking to send limited-time promotions, personalized offers, or important updates, BotMaster is the ultimate solution for businesses looking to leverage the marketing power of WhatsApp.
Main...
</description></item><item><title>Download LuBan 3D 16.11.2025</title><pubDate> Mon, 24 Nov 2025 23:52:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-luban-3d-10427.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-luban-3d-10427.html
</guid><description>
LuBan 3D is creative design software that helps designers and manufacturers create their innovative products quickly. LuBan automatically creates 3D models in a variety of forms, such as lithophane, stacks, hashes, slabs, reliefs, modules, and wireframes. The resulting model can be fabricated by 3D printing, laser cutting and CNC milling. Model parts can be fabricated using laser cutting and 3D printing. LuBan does not depend on specific fabrication methods; instead, it can communicate...
</description></item><item><title>Download AutoHideDesktopIcons 6.57</title><pubDate> Mon, 24 Nov 2025 23:51:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-autohidedesktopicons-1747.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-autohidedesktopicons-1747.html
</guid><description>
AutoHideDesktopIcons allows you to automatically hide the icons on his screen after some seconds of inactivity, certain to your screen is not cluttered and your wallpaper in full view. The program works very similar to the screen saver, but instead of making the desktop look your beautiful eyes, it makes it look clean.
AutoHideDesktopIcons - Hides icons on the Desktop
Must say that AutoHideDesktopIcons is software features auto hide and show on the computer screen. It has a lot of apps...
</description></item><item><title>Download AD FastReporter Pro 25.11.19</title><pubDate> Mon, 24 Nov 2025 23:51:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ad-fastreporter-pro-9439.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ad-fastreporter-pro-9439.html
</guid><description>
AD FastReporter Pro is a powerful tool for reporting and analyzing Active Directory (AD) data. It is designed to help administrators and IT professionals quickly and easily generate reports on AD users, computers, groups, and other objects.
With AD FastReporter Pro, you can generate many types of reports, including user account reports, team membership reports, computer inventory reports, security reports, and more. This tool allows you to customize your reports based on your specific...
</description></item><item><title>Download ChessBase 26.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 24 Nov 2025 23:50:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chessbase-13889.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chessbase-13889.html
</guid><description>
ChessBase is the personal, independent chess database that has become the world standard. Everyone uses ChessBase, from World Champions to the amateur player next door. It is the program of choice for anyone who loves the game and wants to learn more about it. Start your personal success story with ChessBase and enjoy the game even more.
Whether it's preparing for an individual opponent or tournament, managing and analyzing your own games, developing training materials for self-study or...
</description></item><item><title>Download Jim's Toolbox 7.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 24 Nov 2025 23:50:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jims-toolbox-9077.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jims-toolbox-9077.html
</guid><description>
Jim's Toolbox is a free utility to assist you in fixing Windows Installation errors, diagnosing Windows Installations, repairing registry, adding functions, fixing errors, installing quick install software after clean install, change the look and feel of Windows Setup. Diagnose and change your network settings. Many quick links to hidden functions in Windows Settings and even access to Windows GOD mode.
It includes tools to help you quickly learn information about your system, as well...
</description></item><item><title>Download Danil Pristupov Fork 2.14.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 24 Nov 2025 23:49:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fork-6879.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fork-6879.html
</guid><description>
Fork is a great Git client app that allows you to keep tabs on every file line so you can know who is the last person to make changes. The simple and intuitive design of this app helps the management of all of your warehouses much easier. The Fork interface is extremely friendly to users. There is a long list of repositories, branches, origins, tags and archives on the left side of the screen.
With Fork, you can also search and open any of the repositories quickly, from the top of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cash Register Pro 4.0.5</title><pubDate> Mon, 24 Nov 2025 23:48:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cash-register-pro-3853.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cash-register-pro-3853.html
</guid><description>
Cash Register Pro a software cash register full of features and creative for a Windows computer, it will help you to better handle all the activities of the computer money. The application comes with the user interface logical and user friendly allows you to work quickly and do not commit the common error. The program can be used on a number of computers and offers a wide range of authorization secure and reliable. Cash Register Pro will help you track products and goods remain...
</description></item></channel></rss>