<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 23:37:28 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 23:37:28 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download IObit Driver Booster Pro 13.0.0.138</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Sep 2025 23:25:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iobit-driver-booster-102.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iobit-driver-booster-102.html
</guid><description>
IObit Driver Booster Pro is the starting step to avoid hardware errors, the loss of the system and hidden security vulneruses. To update the regular driver is also an effective way to enhance your overall computer performance and maximize your gaming experience. While this process can be dangerous and frustrating if done manually. IObit Driver Booster Pro is introduced to download and update the driver for you automatically with only one click. Based on the cloud library, IObit Driver...
</description></item><item><title>Download MathType 7.9.1.454</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Sep 2025 23:24:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mathtype-478.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mathtype-478.html
</guid><description>
MathType software is to compose mathematical formulas, symbols, math for office applications such as mathematical equations, to handle text, web pages, desktop publishing, desktop presentations, elearning, and for TeX documents, LaTeX and MathML. MathType would be a great help for work as well as your learning.
When integrate MathType into the office software, you easily create the logo or any formula in Math will save a lot of time, work efficiency is highly increased.
Teachers,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Battery Monitor 10.6</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Sep 2025 23:24:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-battery-monitor-1049.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-battery-monitor-1049.html
</guid><description>
Battery Monitor is a small utility that display on the computer screen the details current battery of laptop your as its name. The interface is based on a small frame can be moved to any location on the screen, with the help of the mouse cursor.
Battery Monitor is not popular and you can quickly get overview of the battery details while working in other apps. The main frame displays the clock and percent level, battery status, remaining time, charging speed and charging current. Battery...
</description></item><item><title>Download Astute Graphics Plug-ins Elite Bundle 4.3.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Sep 2025 23:21:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-astute-graphics-plug-ins-elite-bundle-5523.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-astute-graphics-plug-ins-elite-bundle-5523.html
</guid><description>
Astute Graphics Plug-ins Elite Bundle is a set of graphics editing tools for Adobe Illustrator. It includes many unique tools like Phantasm, VectorScribe, WidthScribe and many others. Get the complete set of plug-ins and transform your workflow in Illustrator. Add speed, ease, and precision with all our plug-ins and become the Astute Graphics Plug-in Elite Package!
Astute Graphics Plug-ins Elite Bundle Features:
	Correct alignment + selection
	Sketching visual vector
	Instantly...
</description></item><item><title>Download Total Commander 11.56 Final Extended 25.9 (Full/Lite)</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Sep 2025 23:20:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-total-commander-it-edition-7090.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-total-commander-it-edition-7090.html
</guid><description>
Total Commander is the most popular file manager with all necessary functions for both casual users and IT professionals. Total Commander will help you manage, change data, computer files allowing you to best manage your data. Total Commander tool has two parallel opening windows that allow you to move and copy data from one folder to another easily.
In addition to all the tools dedicated to file managers, Total Commander also contains very convenient viewers for multimedia and graphic...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ashampoo Music Studio 12.0.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Sep 2025 23:19:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-music-studio-1207.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-music-studio-1207.html
</guid><description>
Ashampoo Music Studio is software to work with audio files. Includes the process of taking the disc recording CD, DVD and Blu-ray discs module to organize music collections, editing audio files, recording module and the tool to restore audio files broken.
Ashampoo Music Studio
Functions of Ashampoo Music Studio
	Edit audio files quickly
	Cut perfect slices including direct recording
	Convert to any format and listen anywhere
	The most convenient tool to extract CD
	Create a list from...
</description></item><item><title>Download Dropbox 232.4.5988</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Sep 2025 23:19:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dropbox-1313.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dropbox-1313.html
</guid><description>
Dropbox on taiwebs.com is free tool, the data synchronization across multiple PC become easier than never before: after installation, all what you have to do is enter your name, email address and password before opening the folder My Dropbox. If you install the software on a different computer, Dropbox will reflect the content of the online storage. So you exchange any data between the different computer is connected to Dropbox account. In addition the client is installed on the computer,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Metasequoia 4.9.0d</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Sep 2025 23:18:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tetraface-inc-metasequoia-1479.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tetraface-inc-metasequoia-1479.html
</guid><description>
Metasequoia is software designed three-dimensional model and create the characters the same person or animal, requires some knowledge in this field and most important is a set of tools suitable for the job. For those who have created a number of innovative 3D solutions dedicated software different and need to work with them without have to re-install each program, a utility like Metasequoia can be the right choice.
Tetraface Inc Metasequoia - designed three-dimensional model
This app...
</description></item><item><title>Download FX Science Tools MultiDocs 25.09.16</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Sep 2025 23:18:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fx-science-tools-3744.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fx-science-tools-3744.html
</guid><description>
FX Science Tools provided to teachers of chemistry and physics the effective means to create equations and chemical structures. Just type and create. FX Chem FX Chem makes writing chemical equations become simple. You just type and FX Chem know enough about chemistry to put all the components of the equation at the right point. FX Chem can even create the chemical equations for nuclear - a very difficult thing in the Word. FX ChemSturation FX ChemSturation made the organic structure, what...
</description></item><item><title>Download Avast Premium Security 25.9.10453</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Sep 2025 23:17:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avast-premier-antivirus-security-1359.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avast-premier-antivirus-security-1359.html
</guid><description>
Avast! Premier Antivirus is antivirus software famous by combining all the technologies and methods virus advanced. The developer software this anti-virus have invested in all their knowledge about fighting viruses to create one of the software anti-virus best. Program anti-virus this combines all the technology and advanced methods to get the level of computer security highest. This product is ideal for all the Windows operating system.
Avast! Premier Antivirus - antivirus...
</description></item><item><title>Download Avast Clear 25.9.10453</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Sep 2025 23:17:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avast-clear-4437.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avast-clear-4437.html
</guid><description>
Avast Clear is a utility to remove accurately and completely line product anti-virus AVAST. Avast to leave a lot of garbage behind the computer and in the register. In particular, the registry hassle can, for example, can be an obstacle to install a program anti-virus Avast other then. In such cases, you can use a special utility Avast!
Avast Clear - Uninstall program Avast
Recommended avoid any inconvenience, should always engage the help of a dedicated tool to know where to search...
</description></item><item><title>Download Coolmuster iOS Assistant 4.6.12</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Sep 2025 23:16:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-ios-assistant-2476.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-ios-assistant-2476.html
</guid><description>
You want to backup data from iPhone / iPad / iPod to computer? You want to import a file from your computer to your iOS device? You want to restore backup on your iDevices? You want to have full control over the data stored on your iDevices? This iOS Assistant pro integrates all these features in a and sure is the best manager for your iOS device.
Coolmuster iOS Assistant - backup for IOS devices
Coolmuster iOS Assistant is a whole program feature allows you to freely backup contacts,...
</description></item><item><title>Download BricsCad Ultimate 25.2.09.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Sep 2025 23:16:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bricscad-ultimate-3256.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bricscad-ultimate-3256.html
</guid><description>
BricsCad Ultimate is a software solution, CAD powerful and comprehensive, providing both tools advanced 2D and model 3D live smart on Linux and windows platform. Utility that allows you to sort the file DWG in hierarchical structures and allows you to easily assemble their products with the help of a set of tools and ingredients powerful 3D.
BricsCad Ultimate allows you to rotate and move any part of your model to solve all problems kinematics in real time. The program also allows you to...
</description></item><item><title>Download PentaLogix ViewMate Pro 11.24.58</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Sep 2025 23:15:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pentalogix-viewmate-pro-1008.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pentalogix-viewmate-pro-1008.html
</guid><description>
PentaLogix ViewMate Pro is software to view, edit and convert files from DXF to other formats such as Gerber. When using ViewMate Pro, with the DFM smart, you can check the data view there are mass violations or not. And not just a class once! Many violations, laminated with results quickly and accurately. The system provides an error report in ASCII, and in addition, create a file Gerber to help edit the file plot quickly.
PentaLogix ViewMate Pro - View and convert DXF
ViewMate Pro,...
</description></item><item><title>Download FX Math Tools MultiDocs 25.09.16</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Sep 2025 23:14:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fx-draw-tools-1909.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fx-draw-tools-1909.html
</guid><description>
FX Draw Tools to provide an environment to draw high productivity is exclusively designed for math teachers. Quickly create editable, high quality diagrams for the quiz, test, worksheets, web pages, presentations and demonstrations. FX Sketch, free extension of FX Draw Tools, allows you to sketch diagrams math and to them automatically converted into the drawing of professional quality can be edited by the power of FX Draw. Efofex also provides for the registration FX Draw three bonus...
</description></item><item><title>Download GSoft4U Music Collection 3.9.4.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Sep 2025 23:13:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gsoft4u-music-collection-2437.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gsoft4u-music-collection-2437.html
</guid><description>
GSoft4U Music Collection is a free software to help you fully organized music collection of an archive can search quality. Archiving process is very simple; put on details related to format, genre, release date, record label, as well as rating the 'why' of it. The artists will be divided up alphabetically for easy access.
GSoft4U Music Collection - Manage music collection
The app will allow you to add additional information into its music, as this of course you must have an Internet...
</description></item><item><title>Download MobiKin Assistant for iOS 3.6.10</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Sep 2025 23:09:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mobikin-assistant-for-ios-4865.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mobikin-assistant-for-ios-4865.html
</guid><description>
MobiKin Assistant for iOS is software assistant the world's most powerful apps for iPad users, iPhone and iPod, MobiKin Assistant for iOS allows users to transfer, backup and manage all content on your device just by a simple click. In case of losing data if your iPhone is stolen or accidentally damaged or you just want to share the movies on your iDevice with your friends in other ways you should regularly backup the files on iPhone, iPad or iPod to iTunes . However, there are still many...
</description></item><item><title>Download PentaLogix CAMMaster Designer 11.24.58</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Sep 2025 23:09:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pentalogix-cammaster-designer-13705.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pentalogix-cammaster-designer-13705.html
</guid><description>
CAMMaster Designer is the CAM software of choice for designers for their most demanding jobs. Experience the industry's best CAD companion to get your work done. Panelization is easy with all the features included in this package. Netlist and DRC extraction set the industry standard.
Highlights
	Contour-based netlist extraction
	Advanced DFM inspection
	Automatic aperture conversion
	Layer comparison
	Network conversion
	Automatic conversion from draw to flash
	Solder mask...
</description></item><item><title>Download AVG Clear 25.9.10453</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Sep 2025 23:09:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avg-clear-4945.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avg-clear-4945.html
</guid><description>
AVG Clear is free program help completely erase everything from installing AVG current your including the registry entries, file, settings, files, users, etc. AVG Clear is provided by AVG and is the last measure to use if you encounter a problem when deleting AVG current whether it is error repair, reinstall, or delete altogether.
Please note that all user settings AVG will be removed after the uninstall process is complete. The items should be deleted to include content from Virus...
</description></item><item><title>Download StructurePoint spColumn 10.20</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Sep 2025 23:08:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-structurepoint-spcolumn-10491.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-structurepoint-spcolumn-10491.html
</guid><description>
StructurePoint spColumn is structural engineering software used to design and study reinforced concrete sections subjected to combined axial and bending loads. spColumn provides a clear and simple interface for model editing and 3D visualization of nominal and coefficient damage surfaces. Batch processing and integration with AutoCAD and ETABS are some of the program's many features.
The most significant upgrade to spColumn since its inception features a pioneering interface for...
</description></item><item><title>Download Opera One 122.0.5643.24</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Sep 2025 23:07:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-972.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-972.html
</guid><description>
Opera is a fast, safe, configurable and compliant intranet web browser, which includes both the reader and the application. The Opera browser supports web browsing, listening to music, watching high speed movies, you can open many tabs on the Opera without affecting your browsing speed. Opera now supports almost all devices and operating systems such as windows, IOS, Android, linux, MacOS ...
Opera is a beautiful interface and many interesting features, operating on both PCs and mobile,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Psiphon 186.20250915</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Sep 2025 23:07:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-psiphon-7347.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-psiphon-7347.html
</guid><description>
Psiphon is a firewall bypass tool by Psiphon Inc. Uses VPN, SSH and HTTP Proxy technology to give you uncensored access to Internet content. Your Psiphon app automatically learns about new hotspots to maximize your chances of bypassing censorship.
The way the software works is that Psiphon constantly changes the proxy, so the user's IP address is also constantly changing, the server will not detect the user's real address, so you can feel free. roof. access to websites and software...
</description></item><item><title>Download StructurePoint spWall 10.20</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Sep 2025 23:06:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-structurepoint-spwall-10479.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-structurepoint-spwall-10479.html
</guid><description>
StructurePoint spWall is a computer program for the design and analysis of cast-in-place reinforced concrete walls, inclined walls, ICF walls and architectural and bearing panels precast force. It uses a graphical interface that allows users to easily create complex wall models. The shape of the wall (including any number of openings and barriers), material properties, loads (point, line and area) and support conditions are specified graphically by the user.
Features of StructurePoint...
</description></item><item><title>Download PentaLogix CAMMaster 11.24.58</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Sep 2025 23:06:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pentalogix-cammaster-5559.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pentalogix-cammaster-5559.html
</guid><description>
CAMMaster Designer is CAM software of choice by the Designer for the most demanding jobs. Experience the industry's best CAD companion to get your work done. The disinfection process is fast with all the features available in this package. Exploiting Netlist and DRC sets industry standards. Basically, CamMaster provides many functions depending on the relevant needs of the user. It also provides nearly five free technical support. Furthermore, net list comparison and class comparison make...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Bridge 2025 v15.1.2.737 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Sep 2025 20:22:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-bridge-0003-1338.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-bridge-0003-1338.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Bridge is a versatile digital asset management application developed by Adobe Inc., first released in 2005 as part of the Adobe Creative Suite. It acts as a powerful tool for organizing, previewing, and managing creative assets across various Adobe applications. By downloading the program on taiwebs.com, you can easily edit elements in batch mode, add watermarks and even set color options centrally - Adobe Bridge CC will simplify your work and help maintain order.
Adobe Bridge...
</description></item></channel></rss>