<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 22:04:47 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 22:04:47 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Metasequoia 4.9.0f</title><pubDate> Tue, 17 Feb 2026 01:04:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tetraface-inc-metasequoia-1479.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tetraface-inc-metasequoia-1479.html
</guid><description>
Metasequoia is software designed three-dimensional model and create the characters the same person or animal, requires some knowledge in this field and most important is a set of tools suitable for the job. For those who have created a number of innovative 3D solutions dedicated software different and need to work with them without have to re-install each program, a utility like Metasequoia can be the right choice.
Tetraface Inc Metasequoia - designed three-dimensional model
This app...
</description></item><item><title>Download Fluke TruTest 1.2.0.7</title><pubDate> Tue, 17 Feb 2026 01:02:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fluke-trutest-12626.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fluke-trutest-12626.html
</guid><description>
Fluke TruTest software is designed to eliminate the hassle associated with traditional power system data management and reporting. Whether you are testing fixed wiring systems or equipment in the office, verifying repairs in the workshop or carrying out annual inspections, proper data management is critical to creating Produce easy-to-understand reports for customers. Compatible with a growing list of Fluke and Beha-Amprobe test and measurement devices TruTest software allows you to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Hard Disk Sentinel Pro 6.40 Final</title><pubDate> Mon, 16 Feb 2026 19:54:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hard-disk-sentinel-pro-562.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hard-disk-sentinel-pro-562.html
</guid><description>
Hard Disk Sentinel Pro is a tool for monitoring and optimal performance for hard drive HDD and help diagnose the HDD as well as SSD. Version of Hard Disk Sentinel Pro is a professional version, the most advanced of Hard Disk with many advanced features that meet basic needs, check the hard drive for the user.
The goal of it is to find, test, diagnose and repair the malfunction, hard drive, report and display the health status of the SSD and hard drive failure, decreased performance and...
</description></item><item><title>Download tinyMediaManager 5.2.7.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 16 Feb 2026 19:54:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tinymediamanager-1819.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tinymediamanager-1819.html
</guid><description>
tinyMediaManager is a media manager full-featured to arrange and cleanup your media library your. Just choose (s) the folder containing your movies and the program can automatically get all meta data required for movies and program your TV from TheMovieDB.org, Imdb.com, OFDb.de and other online sources. tinyMediaManager download at artwork, film, cast, plot and details of other communication. Each film or program is presented with a unique art background, category, and appropriate...
</description></item><item><title>Download Helium Music Manager Premium 18.0.686</title><pubDate> Mon, 16 Feb 2026 19:53:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-helium-music-manager-premium-164.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-helium-music-manager-premium-164.html
</guid><description>
Helium Music Manager is a music manager that can rip, tag, play, browse, search, rename, burn and synchronize your music with the mobile. You can control your music collection with Helium Music Manager. Stop using time looking for the file on your computer or looking through CDS, vinyl records and tapes - instead, simply enjoy and explore your music! Helium Music Manager can replace the ripper, the player, tag editor and related software to audio your other.
Helium Music Manager...
</description></item><item><title>Download reaConverter Pro 8.0.198</title><pubDate> Mon, 16 Feb 2026 19:52:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html
</guid><description>
reaConverter Pro is software image processing feature with batch conversion and image editing periodically becomes simple. eaConverter also provide command line utilities allow you to process images automatically, thus helping you shorten the time for other work.
reaConverter Pro integrated powerful tool of Uber with many great features. It provides advanced solutions to process and adjust images. Management of the conversion process the base image with the latest version of...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter 3.9.18 (1502)</title><pubDate> Mon, 16 Feb 2026 19:50:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-to-mp3-converter-1744.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-to-mp3-converter-1744.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter is the software support download youtube video and convert video to mp3 format fast and most simple. MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter allows you download and convert videos from YouTube and other websites to MP3 format by pasting the YouTube URL into the application. When you paste the URL, the program will display thumbnails for videos and you have the option to customize the title information, artist and album before you begin the process of...
</description></item><item><title>Download NTFS Permissions Reporter Enterprise 5.2.655</title><pubDate> Mon, 16 Feb 2026 19:50:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ntfs-permissions-reporter-enterprise-6370.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ntfs-permissions-reporter-enterprise-6370.html
</guid><description>
System administrators are constantly required to check user rights for specific files and folders. This is often a time-consuming work, with multiple NTFS classes and repetitive adjustments over time creating a security maze. NTFS Permissions Reporter Enterprise allows you to confirm the security status of the entire file system quickly and efficiently. All have multiple export formats, command line support, integration scheduling, advanced filtration, and more.
Features of NTFS...
</description></item><item><title>Download Directory Opus Pro 13.21.4 Beta</title><pubDate> Mon, 16 Feb 2026 19:49:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-opus-pro-779.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-opus-pro-779.html
</guid><description>
Directory Opus Pro is a software replacement for Explorer with traditional strength and function more than any manager other files. Directory Opus Pro full support for high DPI screen (for example 4K and 5K) with the rename dialog is redesigned, with new features. Besides being a recording macro only allows you to perform mass renaming complex that don't need regular expressions. In addition, Directory Opus Pro also enhances the ability to script.Better handling of renaming recursive and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Helium Streamer Premium 8.0.0.1805</title><pubDate> Mon, 16 Feb 2026 19:49:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-helium-streamer-premium-1363.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-helium-streamer-premium-1363.html
</guid><description>
Helium Streamer Premium is the music from the collection of Helium helps you to enjoy your music by yourself anywhere you want. Helium Streamer Premium will use Wi-Fi connection to get music streaming from anywhere in and around your home and 3G / 4G if you're out. You easily download the software on taiwebs.com and constant updates latest.
Helium Streamer Premium - stream music from the collection of Helium
Software Helium Streamer Premium support you more ways to browse music...
</description></item><item><title>Download Text Editor Pro 35.4.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 16 Feb 2026 17:23:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-text-editor-pro-800.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-text-editor-pro-800.html
</guid><description>
Text Editor Pro is software to handle text, HTML, Perl, Ruby, or Fortran with features syntax highlighting, professional. Text Editor provides syntax highlighting for over 50 scripts and has a simple interface and easy access. In addition, the Text Editor Pro also supports more than 50 programming languages like C ++, COBOL, graph DOT, DSP, DWScript, Fortran, Foxpro, Java, Perl, Python, Ruby, SQL and many other languages.
Text Editor Pro - text Processing professional
The software can...
</description></item><item><title>Download DesktopOK 12.29</title><pubDate> Mon, 16 Feb 2026 17:23:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopok-1635.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopok-1635.html
</guid><description>
DesktopOK is software save and restore the positions of icons. DesktopOK also offers a solution small but effective for the user to change the screen resolution often. DesktopOK is not installed and can be executed easily from the desktop, and can be carried on a small USB or memory device to another. Start of the program. The first time you use the program, the program will show you screen license. Free program and license info is only displayed the first time (on each PC).
DesktopOK -...
</description></item><item><title>Download EFI Boot Editor 1.5.6</title><pubDate> Mon, 16 Feb 2026 17:22:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-efi-boot-editor-7475.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-efi-boot-editor-7475.html
</guid><description>
EFI Boot Editor is a program that provides you with a graphical interface to check your current boot settings and make modifications to the EFI Boot Manager. With Windows Boot Manager you can check Description, path, category, general settings like timeout and whether properties are active or hidden. Optionally, the application can provide the same information in other formats, namel HEX, BASE64, UTF-8 or UTF-16.
Features of EFI Boot Editor
	Edit startup items.
	Add, remove, and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Certificate Manager 19.3</title><pubDate> Mon, 16 Feb 2026 17:21:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-certificate-manager-13958.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-certificate-manager-13958.html
</guid><description>
Certificate Manager provides an in-depth overview of your current certificates, allowing you to easily access detailed information. It also provides functions for both exporting existing certificates and importing new certificates, enhancing your certificate management capabilities.
Application certificates are often overlooked by most users until problems arise during application installation. For the average end user, there is little reason to focus on application certificates....
</description></item><item><title>Download ReShade 6.7.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 16 Feb 2026 17:20:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-450-3227.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-450-3227.html
</guid><description>
ReShade is an open Source tool help improve the look of the old games on modern video cards as well as allow additional display technology / new video over on the old game doesn't support the technology that.
ReShade, technically, is a tool processing general for the games and video software. Imagine you see your favorite game yourself with the obscure-around, effects market the true depth or color correction. Function ReShade by showing in an automatic way and general access to...
</description></item><item><title>Download CoolUtils Total Doc Converter 5.1.0.374/146</title><pubDate> Mon, 16 Feb 2026 17:18:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-total-doc-converter-84.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-total-doc-converter-84.html
</guid><description>
CoolUtils Total Doc Converter Program that will allow you to document conversion DOC to others, the list can be viewed on the official website or you can watch carefully the screenshot, I think the question would no longer can download CoolUtils Total Doc Converter below. There is batch processing,in general, everything is convenient, I hope you like it.
Total Doc Converter is conversion tools text comprehensive and multi-featured, very necessary when storing or printing the text. It also...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinScript 1.4.8</title><pubDate> Mon, 16 Feb 2026 17:17:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winscript-12800.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winscript-12800.html
</guid><description>
WinScript is an open source tool built to help you build custom scripts for Windows 10 and 11. It includes scripts for debugging, privacy, performance, and more, along with the ability to install all your favorite apps with just one click.
Features
	Debloat: Remove Windows bloatware, CoPilot, Edge, OneDrive, and other pre-installed features preset.
	Privacy: Disable Windows and 3rd party data collection, tracking, app access, and telemetry.
	Performance: Set background services to...
</description></item><item><title>Download PortableApps.com Installer 3.9.9</title><pubDate> Mon, 16 Feb 2026 17:16:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-portableappscom-installer-7673.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-portableappscom-installer-7673.html
</guid><description>
PortableApps.com Installer is an easy-to-use multilingual installer that allows you to package your portable applications without writing code. PortableApps.com Installer can be run from a cloud folder, an external drive or a local folder without installing to Windows. It's even better with the PortableApps.com Platform for easy installation and automatic updates.
Features of PortableApps.com Installer
	Proven NSIS Installer Core
	Excellent compression for distribution
	Easy...
</description></item><item><title>Download NIUBI Partition Editor Technician WinPE 10.3.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 16 Feb 2026 17:14:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-niubi-partition-editor-enterprise-edition-3461.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-niubi-partition-editor-enterprise-edition-3461.html
</guid><description>
NIUBI Partition Editor Enterprise Edition is designed for organizations medium and large. It supports Windows Server 2019/2016/2012/2008/2003, small business server 2011/2008/2003 and Windows 10/8/7 / Vista / XP (32 &amp;amp; 64 bit). Hard drive local / mobile, VMware, Hyper-V and all kinds of RAID array hardware are supported.
The enterprise version can be registered on the PC and unlimited servers belong to your organization, regardless of location. Partition manager enterprise helps you to...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube Downloader 3.9.18 (1502)</title><pubDate> Mon, 16 Feb 2026 17:13:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube Downloader  is a dedicated software that helps users  downloading youtube videos  Favorites on PC for offline viewing. With MediaHuman YouTube  Downloader  you can download videos from youtube website to your computer with  fast speed , with special software development technology that automatically receives videos from Websites, in addition to the ability to download videos from software websites, can convert downloaded video formats to various formats for the purpose...
</description></item><item><title>Download Snappy Driver Installer 1.26.1 (R2601)</title><pubDate> Mon, 16 Feb 2026 17:12:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-snappy-driver-installer-9472.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-snappy-driver-installer-9472.html
</guid><description>
Snappy Driver Installer is a free and open source software tool designed to help users install and update device drivers on Windows operating systems. Device drivers are software programs that allow the operating system to communicate with and control hardware devices such as graphics cards, sound cards, network adapters, etc.
It's important to note that while Snappy Driver Installer can be a useful tool for managing drivers on Windows systems, we always recommend caution when...
</description></item><item><title>Download MetaProducts Portable Offline Browser 8.8.0.5012</title><pubDate> Mon, 16 Feb 2026 17:11:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-metaproducts-portable-offline-browser-4701.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-metaproducts-portable-offline-browser-4701.html
</guid><description>
MetaProducts Portable Offline Browser is the leading app in the industry to store and download at website, MetaProducts Portable Offline Browser provides technology download at high level and strong features. Hosting your website automatically on a regular basis. Copy the website downloaded directly to your hard drive or to external media to another, such as a Flash drive or DVD. Storing downloaded content in any format: ZIP, CHM, EXE.
It's easy to download the website large amount or...
</description></item><item><title>Download Psiphon 186.20260215</title><pubDate> Mon, 16 Feb 2026 17:10:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-psiphon-7347.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-psiphon-7347.html
</guid><description>
Psiphon is a firewall bypass tool by Psiphon Inc. Uses VPN, SSH and HTTP Proxy technology to give you uncensored access to Internet content. Your Psiphon app automatically learns about new hotspots to maximize your chances of bypassing censorship.
The way the software works is that Psiphon constantly changes the proxy, so the user's IP address is also constantly changing, the server will not detect the user's real address, so you can feel free. roof. access to websites and software...
</description></item><item><title>Download MyLanViewer Enterprise 6.7.6</title><pubDate> Mon, 16 Feb 2026 17:09:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mylanviewer-enterprise-1274.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mylanviewer-enterprise-1274.html
</guid><description>
MyLanViewer is a program for scanning IP address, Netbios and LAN / Network powerful for Windows tool whois and traceroute, remote shutdown and process management Wake On LAN (WOL), scan and monitor wireless networks. This app will help you find all IP addresses, MAC addresses and shared folders of computers on the network wired or wireless (Wi-Fi).
MyLanViewer Enterprise - Scan IP address LAN/Network
The program scans network and displays the computer network in your window, friends...
</description></item><item><title>Download Executor 2.2.4.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 16 Feb 2026 17:09:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-executor-271.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-executor-271.html
</guid><description>
Executor for windows is a software alternative premium customization features for the Windows "Run" and "Search Programs". When you press WIN + Z and provides the search results instant, as-you-type for any keywords you enter. By default, Executor will index all the Desktop and Start Menu and you can easily expand the search range by adding the folder location additional.
Executor for windows
The program comes with a list of commands built in which you can use to quickly access many...
</description></item></channel></rss>