<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 13:49:28 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 13:49:28 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Aiarty Image Enhancer 3.7</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Dec 2025 16:02:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aiarty-image-enhancer-12181.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aiarty-image-enhancer-12181.html
</guid><description>
Aiarty Image Enhancer is an AI-powered image enhancement software to de-noise, de-blur, enhance images and create more image details. It uses advanced deep learning technologies to enhance and upscale images while creating realistic details. Whether you want to enlarge low-resolution images by 200%, 400% or 800% for printing, deliver 2K/4K/8K images while preserving realistic details, correcting low-quality photos , remove blur and noise or restore compressed JPEGs, Aiarty Image Enhancer...
</description></item><item><title>Download SoftMaker Office NX Universal 2024 Rev S1230.1206</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Dec 2025 16:02:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-softmaker-office-professional-819.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-softmaker-office-professional-819.html
</guid><description>
SoftMaker Office Professional version, professional office support in terms of writing, calculation, presentation, E-mail, tasks,.. When using SoftMaker Office documents, calculations and presentations are handled as fast as e-mail or appointment and task planning. From the simple work daily to these documents, the most demanding, SoftMaker Office 2018 is the indispensable help of you.
SoftMaker Office is compatible with all the Microsoft Office. It edit Microsoft Office documents true to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Digiarty Aiarty Video Enhancer 3.3</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:58:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-digiarty-aiarty-video-enhancer-13862.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-digiarty-aiarty-video-enhancer-13862.html
</guid><description>
Digiarty Aiarty Video Enhancer is an AI-powered desktop software designed to upscale, denoise, deblur, and enhance videos up to 4K resolution with professional quality and speed. It uses advanced AI models optimized for GPU acceleration and Turbo mode, enabling real-time or near-real-time video processing, including frame interpolation for smooth motion up to 90fps, 120fps, or higher. This tool is effective in restoring low-resolution, old, blurry, jerky or underexposed footage,...
</description></item><item><title>Download 4DDiG Partition Manager 3.9.1.9</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:57:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4ddig-partition-manager-2024-9781.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4ddig-partition-manager-2024-9781.html
</guid><description>
4DDiG Partition Manager is a powerful Windows disk partition software expert in system migration, disk cloning and disk partition management. It can effectively clone your entire disk or partition, providing a reliable solution for data backup.
This is Windows 10 fast system and data transfer solution &amp;amp; 11. 4DDiG Partition Manager can move the system and large files or folders from one disk partition to a larger one with just one click. Or you can use it to move the system and large...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube Downloader 3.9.18 (0412)</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:57:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube Downloader  is a dedicated software that helps users  downloading youtube videos  Favorites on PC for offline viewing. With MediaHuman YouTube  Downloader  you can download videos from youtube website to your computer with  fast speed , with special software development technology that automatically receives videos from Websites, in addition to the ability to download videos from software websites, can convert downloaded video formats to various formats for the purpose...
</description></item><item><title>Download StaxRip 2.50.5</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:56:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-staxrip-2930.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-staxrip-2930.html
</guid><description>
StaxRip app is a comprehensive and powerful, allowing you to convert all video files DVB, DVD, or DV video into a variety of file formats. The program is open Source, meaning completely free to download and use. StaxRip can support many video formats such as x264, MPEG-4, DivX, XviD, MPEG-2 and many other formats. The format sounds different also be supported, including MP2 / MPA, AAC, WAV, Ogg Vorbis, MP3, AC3, DTS and other formats. Moreover, the program also supports a variety of...
</description></item><item><title>Download reaConverter Pro 8.0.173</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:56:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html
</guid><description>
reaConverter Pro is software image processing feature with batch conversion and image editing periodically becomes simple. eaConverter also provide command line utilities allow you to process images automatically, thus helping you shorten the time for other work.
reaConverter Pro integrated powerful tool of Uber with many great features. It provides advanced solutions to process and adjust images. Management of the conversion process the base image with the latest version of...
</description></item><item><title>Download VovSoft Http Requester 6.4</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:52:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-http-requester-6570.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-http-requester-6570.html
</guid><description>
VovSoft Http Requester is a simple tool for asking POST and GET queries. The POST and GET are the two basic requirements in HTTP, each with its own role, but both are based on the demand-feedback protocol. A list of URLs that can be filled in manually or glued to a private school, while the input name and corresponding values also have a reserved area.
The user can add new input data in a manual manner, but there is also an option to import that data from the CSV file. Right next to,...
</description></item><item><title>Download PassFab 4EasyPartition 3.9.1.9</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:45:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-passfab-4easypartition-7983.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-passfab-4easypartition-7983.html
</guid><description>
After using your PC for many years, there are bound to be many files you want to transfer to your new PC. PassFab 4EasyPartition can perform a one-click migration saving you hours of reinstalling operating systems and applications. It has an intuitive interface and step-by-step wizard that makes migrating the system in just a few steps. PassFab 4EasyPartition will effectively solve the problem of low disk space, speed up your computer and make it run faster.
Features of PassFab...
</description></item><item><title>Download thilmera7 0b184 Rev.3</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:39:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thilmera7-2918.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thilmera7-2918.html
</guid><description>
thilmera7 is an application capable of performing this task and perform it quite well. This is an app that tracks real-time which you can put anywhere on the screen of his computer application and to forward detailed information about memory, disk, network, CPU, GPU, processes, sound and other aspects miscellaneous.
All the controls and options for the application is provided from the context menu right-click. There you can find the table 'properties' from where you can switch and see all...
</description></item><item><title>Download RyTuneX 1.5.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:38:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rytunex-11852.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rytunex-11852.html
</guid><description>
RyTuneX is an advanced optimizer built on the WinUI 3 framework, designed to enhance the performance of Windows devices. Designed for Windows 10 and 11, RyTuneX empowers users to easily remove stubborn pre-installed apps and optimize system resources.
RyTuneX Features
	Selectively remove apps: Easily uninstall unwanted pre-installed apps.
	Background services management: Streamline your system by disabling unnecessary services.
	Privacy enhancements: Strengthen your privacy by...
</description></item><item><title>Download Pazu Spotify Music Converter 4.9.9</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:38:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pazu-spotify-music-converter-11024.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pazu-spotify-music-converter-11024.html
</guid><description>
Pazu Spotify Music Converter for Windows allows you to download and convert Spotify music to MP3, M4A, AAC, FLAC, WAV and AIFF in high quality. Use it to download Spotify songs, albums, playlists, podcasts, and audiobooks with a free or paid Spotify account. You can then transfer them to any device, such as an MP3 player, and play them without restrictions.
Why should you use Pazu Spotify Music Converter?
Premium Spotify users can save albums, playlists for offline playback, but unlike...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft Power BI Report Server September 2025 v15.0.1119.121</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:37:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-power-bi-report-server-11324.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-power-bi-report-server-11324.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft Power BI Report Server gives your users access to the rich, interactive reports and enterprise reporting capabilities of SQL Server Reporting Services. Explore data visually and quickly discover patterns to make better decisions, faster. And create the pixel-perfect paginated reports your business needs. You also have the ability to confidently scale to thousands of users because Power BI Report Server is based on a proven enterprise-grade platform.
Create, publish and...
</description></item><item><title>Download PostgreSQL Maestro 25.9.0.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:37:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-postgresql-maestro-5267.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-postgresql-maestro-5267.html
</guid><description>
PostgreSQL Maestro is the premier tool to manage, control and develop databases. It provides a set of GUI tools rich for anyone using PostgreSQL, including the developer, database, DBA, and data analyst. Browse, create, edit, copy, rename, and drop all the object schema as tables, view, function, or trigger in the simplest way possible.
Use PostgreSQL Maestro to admin any server version PostgreSQL from 7.3 to 10! PostgreSQL Maestro supports features version server latest as debugging PL /...
</description></item><item><title>Download CrushFTP 11.3.7.74</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:36:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-crushftp-13882.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-crushftp-13882.html
</guid><description>
CrushFTP is an extremely powerful, easy-to-use solution that runs on almost any operating system: macOS 10.9+/11/12+, Win2012+, Linux, Solaris, BSD, Unix, etc! Any operating system that can run Java 8 at a minimum can run CrushFTP. It supports multiple protocols including FTP, FTPS, SFTP, HTTP, HTTPS, WebDAV, and WebDAV SSL, making it flexible for secure file transfers across a variety of environments.
Key features of CrushFTP include:
	Cross-platform compatibility: Runs on macOS,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tier1App yCrash 3.1.3.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:36:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tier1app-ycrash-13868.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tier1app-ycrash-13868.html
</guid><description>
yCrash is a root cause analysis tool developed by Tier1App that helps identify the source of complex manufacturing issues. The tool is designed to quickly determine why issues like CPU spikes, memory degradation, or increased response times occur, rather than simply identifying what the problem is.
Key features and functionality of yCrash include:
	Automatic data collection and analysis The tool collects and analyzes over 18 different artifacts, including GC logs, stream backups, and...
</description></item><item><title>Download File Manager 3.6.7</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:33:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-file-manager-8886.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-file-manager-8886.html
</guid><description>
File Manager+ is an easy and powerful file browser for Android devices. It's free, fast, and full-featured. Because of its simple user interface, it is extremely easy to use. With File Manager+, you can easily manage files and folders on your devices, NAS (Network Attached Storage), and cloud storage. What's more, you can quickly see how many files and apps you have on your device right after opening File Manager+.
It supports all file management actions (opening, searching, navigating...
</description></item><item><title>Download Multi language Translator Text 98.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:33:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-multi-language-translator-text-11918.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-multi-language-translator-text-11918.html
</guid><description>
In today's globalized world, it is normal to communicate with people who speak different languages. Whether you are traveling abroad, conducting business with international customers, or simply trying to connect with people from different cultures, the ability to quickly and accurately translate text is essential. necessity. This is where a multilingual text translation app can become a valuable tool.
Multi language Translator Text is a mobile application that allows users to translate...
</description></item><item><title>Download AR Ruler App: Tape Measure Cam 3.1.7</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:33:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ar-ruler-app-tape-measure-cam-8721.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ar-ruler-app-tape-measure-cam-8721.html
</guid><description>
AR Ruler app is a mobile app that uses augmented reality (AR) technology to measure distances, angles, and sizes of objects in real-world environments. This app works by using the device's camera and sensors to create a virtual 3D representation of a real-life environment.
The AR Ruler app uses augmented reality (AR) technology to measure the real world using your smartphone's camera. Target the detected plane and start using the AR
tape measure tool
Features of AR Ruler...
</description></item><item><title>Download Service Freezer (Root) 2.0.3</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:33:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-service-freezer-root-11462.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-service-freezer-root-11462.html
</guid><description>
Service Freezer makes it possible for you to freeze unwanted Services or Packages (Installed, Bloatware or System) on your Rooted devices. It works with most Rooted devices: Samsung, Sony, LG, Xiaomi, Oppo, HTC, etc.
Service Freezer Features
	Freeze Unwanted Services or Packages - freeze installed services or packages, Bloatware or Unwanted System
	Custom Bloatware list feature - edit and customize the Bloatware list yourself (supported by [Set Non-Bloat] and [Set As Bloat]...
</description></item><item><title>Download AdGuard Ad Blocker 4.14.32 Nightly</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:32:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-adguard-block-ads-without-root-8215.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-adguard-block-ads-without-root-8215.html
</guid><description>
AdGuard for Android is the only root-free ad blocker for Android that removes ads in apps and browsers, protects your privacy, and helps you manage your apps. Adguard is designed to block unwanted ads, pop-ups and banners while you browse the web on your device. It uses a combination of local VPN technology and a custom DNS server to block ads, meaning it can block ads in apps as well as in web browsers.
In addition, Adguard also blocks tracking scripts from collecting information about...
</description></item><item><title>Download Construction Calc Pro 7.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:32:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-construction-calc-pro-9627.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-construction-calc-pro-9627.html
</guid><description>
Save money with quick material estimates. Save time by calculating angles, measurements and quantities. The ideal handy companion for anyone in the construction industry. Construction Calc Pro took 12 months and 21,500 lines of code to develop and is the easiest-to-use construction calculation and estimating app available on any mobile platform. There are no complicated instructions to master or instructions to follow – just enter data and get accurate results.
Calculator and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Quick Volume Control 1.5</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:32:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-quick-volume-control-11302.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-quick-volume-control-11302.html
</guid><description>
Control the volume from the notification bar without pressing the physical volume key. This is small mini app (150 kb size) without any annoying permissions or background services. It offers maximum customization options with a simple, clean user interface. The app allows toggling notifications for the volume slider: Ringer, Notifications, Alarm, Music, In-call and system (dialing tone).
	Customizable notification toggle with background color and icon.
	Select the volume switch you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Video Converter, Compressor 17.0.3</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:31:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-video-converter-compressor-13301.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-video-converter-compressor-13301.html
</guid><description>
The fastest video converter and compressor on the market supports almost all video formats: MP4, MKV, AVI, 3GP, MOV, MTS, MPEG, MPG, WMV, M4V, VOB, FLV, etc. This converter and compressor supports converting, compressing, changing resolution, Frame Rate (FPS), bitrate of video files. It can also convert video files to audio formats like MP3, AAC, AC3, OGG, M4A, WAV, etc.
Key Features
	Convert and compress your videos to almost any video and audio format. Choose from predefined 4K to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Passport Photo: ID Photo Print 1.2.15</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:31:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-passport-photo-id-photo-print-11981.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-passport-photo-id-photo-print-11981.html
</guid><description>
Passport Photo: ID Photo Print is a powerful passport photo editor that will adjust your passport size photos properly. It's the easiest way for you to create passport photos and visa photos at home. With passport size photo maker, you can quickly access high quality passport photos, visa photos that meet all government requirements.
Passport Photo: ID Photo Print has all the premium features that make it the ideal passport size photo solution for conveniently editing visa or passport...
</description></item></channel></rss>