<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 15:42:37 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 15:42:37 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download ColorCatcher 4.6</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 18:06:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-colorcatcher-14269.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-colorcatcher-14269.html
</guid><description>
ColorCatcher is a small but powerful free Windows program that allows you to extract colors from your screen using the built-in magnifier and save them to your own color lists, which are easy to edit. Moreover, you can use ColorCatcher as a portable program, for example on a USB drive. This way you can take your color list with you.
ColorCatcher's Highlight Features
	ColorCatcher can copy colors as Hex, Decimal, RGB, HSV or Integer values ​​and save them to a stack for later...
</description></item><item><title>Download Firewall Rule Creator 0.3</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 18:03:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-firewall-rule-creator-12854.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-firewall-rule-creator-12854.html
</guid><description>
Firewall Rule Creator is a simple Windows tool that allows you to quickly add or remove firewall rules without manually navigating through advanced firewall settings.
Key Features
	Block or allow connections to any .exe file
	Supports inbound, outbound, or both
	Choose a profile: Domain, Private, Public
	Prevent duplicate rules by checking existing rules
	Simple and clean user interface when using CustomTkinter
</description></item><item><title>Download CyberLink PowerDirector Ultimate 2026 v24.0.1112.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 17:00:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-powerdirector-ultimate-425.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-powerdirector-ultimate-425.html
</guid><description>
CyberLink PowerDirector Ultimate is software editor, edit video and make movies on the computer from a variety of templates are made available, complete with effects, transitions, animations, and music. CyberLink PowerDirector 17 is a combination of video editing software with advanced video editing features powerful. Cblowing need to add your clips into the time line and click on 'Production'!
The tool design video in CyberLink PowerDirector have the ability to customize helps you...
</description></item><item><title>Download dslrBooth Photo Booth Software Pro 7.49.3.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 16:59:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dslrbooth-photo-booth-software-666.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dslrbooth-photo-booth-software-666.html
</guid><description>
Photo Booth Software is a software to create, list and combine the images back together in the same theme as travel, haloween. Created by the professional photographer for the operator photo booth at all skill levels, photo booth software dslrBooth built from scratch with the sole purpose of running the photo booth. The software uses the latest technology to provide you and your guests, high quality prints and the ability to share photos and GIF on the means of social media including...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ashampoo Photo Commander 19.0.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 16:58:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-photo-commander-273.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-photo-commander-273.html
</guid><description>
Ashampoo Photo Commander software brings user photo management tool effectively cover view, sort, edit, convert photos and images to the web. Ashampoo Photo Commander 16 will surprise you immediately! Interface modern user will quickly learn the features of your favorite and adjust accordingly for faster access. The slideshow images appear in the mode 4K stunning and the panoramic feature will steals the show.
Ashampoo Photo Commander - photo editing
Software Ashampoo Photo Commander...
</description></item><item><title>Download AnyDesk 9.6.5</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 16:57:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anydesk-1321.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anydesk-1321.html
</guid><description>
AnyDesk is software computer control remote, easy connection with remote computer management and manipulation on the computer. After installing the AnyDesk up 2 the computer then you can easily use the software to provide technical support for a friend or family member or you have access to your computer while you away from home or office.
AnyDesk - control your computer remotely
The process of using very simple software, want to allow access to his computer, only need to provide for...
</description></item><item><title>Download Draftable Desktop 25.11.100</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 16:57:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-draftable-desktop-3749.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-draftable-desktop-3749.html
</guid><description>
Draftable Desktop is comparison tool documents the fastest. Compare over 300 pages in a few seconds. Draftable Desktop 2.0 is now available - faster and stronger than ever! See all the changes in your documents, locally and online. Take your work to the next level. Compare secret and private do not use the internet and your documents never leave your computer. Specifically, Draftable Desktop compatible with .xls, .xlsx, .xlsxm. With Office 2013, 2016 or 365, you can compare text in...
</description></item><item><title>Download Print Artist Platinum 25.0.3.4</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 16:56:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-print-artist-platinum-9808.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-print-artist-platinum-9808.html
</guid><description>
Print Artist Platinum is a software application developed by Nova Development that allows users to create and design various print projects. It offers a wide range of templates, graphics, and design tools to assist in creating personalized projects like greeting cards, banners, brochures, calendars, labels, and more.
Impress friends, family and customers with the creative edge that only Print Artist Platinum can offer with over 28,000 professionally designed templates, 377,000+...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cisdem Duplicate Finder 4.5.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 16:56:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cisdem-duplicate-finder-6973.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cisdem-duplicate-finder-6973.html
</guid><description>
Cisdem Duplicate Finder is software that supports you to find and delete duplicate files quickly and accurately and retrieve more content on your computer. Cisdem Duplicate Finder uses advanced scanning algorithms to compare files based on content, not only name, time or size. With the advanced scanning engine and you can configure, you can easily control the location and file type that will be scanned.
With advanced scanning algorithms, Cisdem Duplicate Finder can quickly filter out...
</description></item><item><title>Download O&amp;amp;O Defrag Pro 30.5.1211</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 16:55:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-o-o-defrag-pro-149.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-o-o-defrag-pro-149.html
</guid><description>
O&amp;amp;O Defrag Pro is the professional software has the ability to defragment the hard disk and can work with the file system different from FAT / 32 to NTFS / 5, and support for the different arrays Volume / Stripe Sets. You can also set the schedule which O &amp;amp; O Defrag will be booted and perform a number of manipulation certain. Regular defragmentation of the disk partition optimized performance of your computer. The user interface is very easy to use. It has a ribbon bar displays all...
</description></item><item><title>Download O&amp;amp;O Defrag Server 30.5.1211</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 16:55:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-defrag-server-2521.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-defrag-server-2521.html
</guid><description>
O&amp;amp;O Defrag Server professional software has the ability to defragment the hard disk and can work with the file system different from FAT / 32 to NTFS / 5, and support for the different arrays Volume / Stripe Sets. You can also set the schedule which O &amp;amp; O Defrag will be booted and perform a number of manipulation certain. Regular defragmentation of the disk partition optimized performance of your computer. The user interface is very easy to use. It has a ribbon bar displays all the...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinMute 2.5.4.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 16:54:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winmute-7446.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winmute-7446.html
</guid><description>
WinMute can automatically mute all audio devices on your PC when:
	you lock your PC.
	screensaver turns on.
	screen off
	you are logged out
	Your PC is off
	Your PC goes to sleep
	Your PC is connected to a specific wireless network
This is useful, for example, if you are away from your desk and don't want to disturb your co-workers with random sounds or music from your computer, or don't want music coming from your speakers , the next time you turn on your computer during a...
</description></item><item><title>Download TreeSize Free 4.8.0.608</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 16:54:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-treesize-free-10656.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-treesize-free-10656.html
</guid><description>
TreeSize Free is a free disk space manager for Windows, it will show you the size of folders including its subfolders in a similar fashion like Explorer. Large folders can be identified at a glance thanks to the gradient bar displayed in the background. All scan results can be detailed at the file level and filters, e.g. for files of a certain type, can be applied.
Features of TreeSize Free
	Search space: clean up hard drive space
	Break down hard drive space usage to file level:...
</description></item><item><title>Download Renee PassNow Pro 2025.11.08.153</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 16:54:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-renee-passnow-pro-3975.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-renee-passnow-pro-3975.html
</guid><description>
Renee PassNow Pro is the application used to reset BIOS passwords, a feature quite useful when users need to make changes there but can't access the BIOS because the login information is forgotten. Users can take advantage of Renee PassNow to discover the faults of Windows and fix them, as long as they can not boot into the operating system anymore.
Renee PassNow Pro - password Recovery system
This tool can create direct means to recover data with just a few mouse clicks, as it can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tomabo MP4 Downloader Pro 5.9.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 16:53:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tomabo-mp4-downloader-pro-3602.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tomabo-mp4-downloader-pro-3602.html
</guid><description>
Tomabo MP4 Downloader Pro is the app designed exclusively for Windows users to help them download videos from the Internet. In addition, it also increase download speeds by up to 500%, or even more. Tomabo MP4 Downloader Pro, interface design, simple, well-organized, beautifully. Here, users can view a list of videos has download with gravatar, URL, quality, duration and size of them. Software allows download video series at the same time, at the same time, support create a list of clips...
</description></item><item><title>Download Coolmuster PDF Creator Pro 2.7.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 16:53:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-pdf-creator-pro-4200.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-pdf-creator-pro-4200.html
</guid><description>
Coolmuster PDF Creator Pro is a tool to create PDF files of your own easily and manage the different files on the computer and convert all the file similar or related into a PDF file large. With Coolmuster PDF Creator Pro you can create your own PDF from 4 different formats so you can share and manage files on computer more effectively. You can create PDF files from 7 major formats, including Microsoft Word (.docx), Text (.txt), image (.jpg, .png, .gif, .bmp, etc.), MOBI (.mobi .prc),...
</description></item><item><title>Download Coder Technologies Coder 2.27.5</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 16:52:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coder-oss-enterprise-8726.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coder-oss-enterprise-8726.html
</guid><description>
Coder OSS Enterprise is a development platform that provides a complete cloud-based solution for software development, testing and deployment. It is designed to simplify the software development process by providing developers with a collaborative and streamlined environment.
Coder offloads development from local workstations to your on-premises infrastructure and public cloud. Boost developer productivity with powerful server resources and instant integration. Keep the code and data...
</description></item><item><title>Download Coolmuster PDF Image Extractor 2.3.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 16:52:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-pdf-image-extractor-4846.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-pdf-image-extractor-4846.html
</guid><description>
Coolmuster PDF Image Extractor is an effective tool to support users to extract images from PDF files very easily and quickly. After extract, you can add these images into PowerPoint slideshows, photo collage or use them for other purposes without any restrictions.
You feel tired when to extract photos from multiple PDF files different? Try function extract batch this to get images from all PDF documents in just one single operation.
	Provide 3 different ways to download all PDF file...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cisdem Video Converter 4.2.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 16:51:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cisdem-video-converter-9557.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cisdem-video-converter-9557.html
</guid><description>
Cisdem Video Converter is an all-in-one solution for converting video and audio files of any format, ripping DVD movies and converting online videos. The converter provides support for more than 150 audio and video file formats, and helps you download or share content with others. Cisdem Video Converter gives you the ability to make audio or video content compatible with almost any device.
Save videos and music from 1000+ hosting sites for offline viewing, including YouTube, Facebook,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Lansweeper 12.6.0.11</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 16:45:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lansweeper-2011.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lansweeper-2011.html
</guid><description>
Lansweeper is an application to manage IT assets and the scanning device is connected to the network. This software can scan and identify all network devices have workstation IP and Windows, Linux and Mac and indexing for them. Deep Scan Engine this software uses a set of protocols to detect and receive data from any device connected to the network. All data received can be stored in database SQL Compact or SQL Server.
Lansweeper - Scan system Internet
Software Lansweeper design open...
</description></item><item><title>Download 510k PEACH 1.0.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 16:44:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-510k-peach-14199.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-510k-peach-14199.html
</guid><description>
PEACH 510k is a next-generation polyphonic MIDI plugin designed to create rhythmically-bending, variable polyphonic arpeggiator sequences in digital audio workstations (DAWs). Unlike traditional arpeggiators that follow fixed up/down cycle patterns, PEACH allows each lane of the arpeggiator to run at an independent step length. This feature turns simple chords into complex, variable polyphonic patterns, full of rhythm and variation.
Key Features
Polymetric Lanes — Each lane (Gate,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Audio Damage AD055 Quanta 2 v2.1.4</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 16:44:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-audio-damage-ad055-quanta-9492.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-audio-damage-ad055-quanta-9492.html
</guid><description>
Quanta is a full-featured, easy-to-use detail synthesizer for AAX, AudioUnits, VST and VST3 servers. The user interface has been cleaned, modernized and offers clear and consistent controls with the new controls.
Features of Audio Damage AD055 Quanta
	Multi-format Template Loader
	Grain Engine
	Two virtual analog oscillators
	Noise Source
	Dual Multi-Mode Filter
	Flexible Envelope Generator (FEG) x 4
	Flexible Low Frequency Oscillator (FLFO) x 2
	Sampling and holding
	Modulation...
</description></item><item><title>Download TubeDownload Pro 6.31.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 16:43:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubedownload-pro-12035.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubedownload-pro-12035.html
</guid><description>
TubeDownload Pro is a professional Windows application for downloading your favorite videos from YouTube and hundreds of other video sites. TubeDownload Pro can increase download speed up to 500% or even more.
Features of TubeDownload Pro
	Download your favorite videos from YouTube and hundreds of other video sites.
	Increase download speed up to 500% or even more.
	Download 720p, 1080p, 2K, 4K and 8K HD videos from YouTube.
	Download entire playlists in just a few clicks.
	Download...
</description></item><item><title>Download Coolmuster PDF Password Remover 2.3.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 16:43:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-pdf-password-remover-4203.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-pdf-password-remover-4203.html
</guid><description>
Coolmuster PDF Password Remover is software password unlock PDF files protected Click people like to use password to protect copyright PDF of their work out of copying, printing, editing or stealing by others. So, sometimes you need to delete password from PDF to edit, copy, or share. Under this situation, Coolmuster PDF Password Remover can be an ideal assistant to you can remove password as you like.
Coolmuster PDF Password Remover - Remove password protected PDF
Forget the PDF...
</description></item><item><title>Download Algonaut Atlas 2.6.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 16:40:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-algonaut-atlas-7328.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-algonaut-atlas-7328.html
</guid><description>
Algonaut Atlas is an Artificial Intelligence-powered sampler that will change the way you find sounds and create rhythms. See all of your own templates curated in one place with style and feature-based maps. Find inspiration by creating an instant drum kit using your own templates. Speed ​​up your workflow by dragging and dropping into any application.
Features of Algonaut Atlas
	Export to MIDI and Audio Loops.
	Built for drums, fast and flexible. The best parts of the...
</description></item></channel></rss>