<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 16:03:58 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 16:03:58 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Bulk Image Downloader 6.62</title><pubDate> Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:25:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bulk-image-downloader-121.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bulk-image-downloader-121.html
</guid><description>
Bulk Image Downloader is an application specially developed to help you download the images in full size from the Bulk Image Downloader most of the web gallery or web forum.
Bulk Image Downloader what?
Support image storage - BID works with almost every archive page popular images, such as flickr, imagevenue, imagefap, imagebam, etc.
Social networking sites - BID supports downloading from sites such as facebook, myspace, and twitter as tweetphoto.com, twitpic.com, yfrog.com
Images are...
</description></item><item><title>Download DesktopNoteOK 4.44</title><pubDate> Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:24:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopnoteok-4076.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopnoteok-4076.html
</guid><description>
DesktopNoteOK is a software to create quick notes on desktop Windows, with the random options and the custom options different. The notes on the desktop created at the request of users, mainly because Windows 10, here it only available via MS Store. About privacy, users doubt here and ask me a tool desktop pure. Is a mobile version and / or maybe install!
DesktopNoteOK - notes on your Desktop
The features of DesktopNoteOK
	Many themes for the desktop notes random background and font...
</description></item><item><title>Download AVS Video Editor 26.0.1.176</title><pubDate> Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:24:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs-video-editor-426.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs-video-editor-426.html
</guid><description>
AVS Video Editor is software professional video editing for windows with full features useful, easy-to-use.  When using AVS Video Editor you can record a video, to impose various effects, create and burn DVD, export movies to various video formats, convert video to iPod, PSP, mobile phones and the other portable device.
Features AVS Video Editor
Format support
	AVS Video Editor supports all major video formats. Edit and save the video file in the codec AVI, VOB, MP4, DVD, WMV, 3GP,...
</description></item><item><title>Download ScanFS 1.0.1.405</title><pubDate> Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:23:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-scanfs-1750.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-scanfs-1750.html
</guid><description>
ScanFS is a tool to locate files and add the directory of the disc allows you to quickly find files matching his criteria. Program ScanFS offers a real-time search (default) as well as an option to create a catalog disc storing all the information files in the database to search offline. Search options database get results from the directory of the disk instead scans your hard drive, allows you to search removable media, even when media is not connected (for example, files stored on USB...
</description></item><item><title>Download VueScan Pro 9.8.51</title><pubDate> Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:22:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vuescan-pro-75.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vuescan-pro-75.html
</guid><description>
VueScan Pro l  is one of the software  Scan quality pictures  First and appeared quite soon,  VueScan Pro  always asserted its No. 1 position on the technology pages, awards as well as user reviews. Through many versions, VueScan Pro 9 is greatly improved in terms of interface and features. Supporting most popular image formats today, this software will help you scan images quickly, easy to use and high quality output. With the color balance mode, you won't have to worry about blurring the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Obsidian 1.11.7</title><pubDate> Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:22:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-obsidian-10386.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-obsidian-10386.html
</guid><description>
Obsidian is a powerful knowledge base that operates on a local folder containing plain text Markdown files. It allows users to create internal links for notes and then display the connections as a graph. Additionally users can also organize and structure their thoughts and knowledge in a flexible, non-linear way.
Features of Obsidian
Personal notes:
	Links: Create connections between your notes.
	Graph: Visualize the relationships between your notes.
	Plugins: Build your ideal...
</description></item><item><title>Download Calibre 9.2.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:21:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-calibre-1669.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-calibre-1669.html
</guid><description>
Calibre  is an eBook library management application that allows you to manage your eBook collection, convert eBooks between different formats, Sync with popular e-reading devices and read your e-books with included viewer. You can sort books by author, title, date and other details, download meta information and book covers, add personalized tags and comments, and view your images in the cover display.
Collection of essential tools for adding metadata editing books or managing your...
</description></item><item><title>Download Fast Screen Recorder 2.1.0.18</title><pubDate> Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:21:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fast-screen-recorder-7132.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fast-screen-recorder-7132.html
</guid><description>
With the Fast Screen Recorder app, you can capture any moment on your screen. Fast Screen Recorder helps capture your online conferences, meetings, tutorials, gaming moments and more. You can only record audio, video and both with or without a voice mic.
Fast Screen Recorder provides an option to enable/disable your microphone before recording begins. So you can make videos with your voice. This is useful for recording tutorials and presentations. After recording video or audio from...
</description></item><item><title>Download Navicat Premium 17.3.9 Enterprise</title><pubDate> Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:20:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-navicat-premium-87.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-navicat-premium-87.html
</guid><description>
Navicat Premium is a developer tool database allows you to connect simultaneously with the MySQL database, MariaDB, SQL Server, Oracle, PostgreSQL and SQLite from a single application. Navicat Premium is compatible with the database cloud such as Amazon RDS, Amazon Aurora, Amazon Redshift, SQL Azure, Oracle Cloud and Google Cloud. You can quickly and easily build, manage and maintain database of your.
Features, characteristics, Navicat Premium:
Move data seamlessly
Data transfer, data...
</description></item><item><title>Download HitmanPro 3.8.50 Build 346</title><pubDate> Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:20:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hitmanpro-5529.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hitmanpro-5529.html
</guid><description>
HitmanPro is the fastest solution to see if your computer is infected with a virus. The software is also portable and can be run from a USB Flash Drive, CD / DVD, network or local hard drive. Hitman Pro 3 is a quick all-in-one tool for locating, identifying, and removing viruses, spyware, trojans, rootkits and other malware. Hitman Pro 3 will quickly show up if your PC is infected with malware.
Research shows that many computers are infected, even when they have an up-to-date security...
</description></item><item><title>Download AVS Audio Converter 26.0.1.176</title><pubDate> Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:19:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs-audio-converter-1195.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs-audio-converter-1195.html
</guid><description>
AVS Audio Converter is a program that convert audio files from this format to other formats support many different formats. Support converting WAV, OGG Vorbis, MP3, MP2, Microsoft ADPCM, WMA, VOX, AAC, M4A, AMR and other audio formats. Before transition, the program determines the frequency, number of channels and other parameters of audio files. In addition, the AVS Audio Converter allows you to make settings for the format MP3 and OGG formats when converting audio files and change the...
</description></item><item><title>Download USB Safely Remove 7.3.1.1334</title><pubDate> Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:19:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-usb-safely-remove-122.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-usb-safely-remove-122.html
</guid><description>
USB Safely Remove is a great program to automate work with devices your mobile. For example, you can easily specify the launch the program you need when disconnecting or connecting equipment, plus you have access to the command line, you can download USB Safely Remove in the full news. I would like to note an interesting feature of the program is that you can stop the USB device by pressing the hot key and the unique technology of the program will allow you to know why the device you...
</description></item><item><title>Download XMedia Recode 3.6.2.5</title><pubDate> Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:18:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xmedia-recode-919.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xmedia-recode-919.html
</guid><description>
XMedia Recode is software to change the quality for video files on windows operating system, it has the ability to change quality, video format. XMedia Recode supports the format conversion such as 3GP, 3GPP, 3GPP2, AAC, AC3, AIFF, AMR, ASF, AU, AVI, DIVX, DTS, DVR-MS, FLV, H. 261, H. 263, H. 264, M4A, M1V, M2V, M4V, MKV.
Parameters advanced
The user can step into the more advanced and modify bitrate, frame interval the frame rate, modes, speed control and many other settings regarding...
</description></item><item><title>Download AVS4YOU Software AIO Installation Package 26.0.1.176</title><pubDate> Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:17:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs4you-software-aio-installation-package-1200.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs4you-software-aio-installation-package-1200.html
</guid><description>
AVS4YOU Software AIO Installation Package is the package includes programs to work with video, audio, graphics, documents, and system cleaning. You can install as a complete package, or separate. Which program are presented: AVS Video Editor, AVS Video Converter, AVS Video ReMaker, AVS Media Player, AVS Audio Editor, AVS Audio Converter, AVS Disc Converter, AVS Image Converter, AVS Document Converter, AVS Registry Cleaner.
AVS4YOU Software AIO Installation Package - Full set of tools,...
</description></item><item><title>Download ASUS GPU Tweak III 2.4.0.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:17:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-asus-gpu-tweak-3252.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-asus-gpu-tweak-3252.html
</guid><description>
ASUS GPU Tweak is a tools overclocking powerful and full-featured allows you to significantly enhance the performance of the graphics processor ASUS. Utility that allows you to get the best results just by few mouse clicks. ASUS GPU Tweak has a number mode allows you to adjust the parameters of graphics according to the specific needs of his. Mode OC allows you to benefit from maximum performance supplied by your graphics card. Game play mode allows you to play the game using the default...
</description></item><item><title>Download Zortam Mp3 Media Studio Pro 33.80</title><pubDate> Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:14:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zortam-mp3-media-studio-pro-135.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zortam-mp3-media-studio-pro-135.html
</guid><description>
Zortam Mp3 Media Studio Pro brings you rich processing tools music includes extract and convert music from CD to Mp3 format, edit, music cards, music download....You can also create discs CD high-quality music, with Zortam Mp3 Media Studio search music files duplicated to remove them from the system, rename music files, switch back and forth between formats.
Zortam Mp3 Media Studio Pro is rated as perfect software in the processing of the MP3 files on the computer. First of all, you can...
</description></item><item><title>Download O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro 22.1.243 / Server</title><pubDate> Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:13:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-diskimage-pro-218.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-diskimage-pro-218.html
</guid><description>
O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro is software backup data comprehensive and effective is provided to protect the data of the computer system, it creates images for individual drives or the entire system that still does not affect your system.
O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro allows the user to backup the entire computer or drive, the and files whenever you want even while the computer is being used. Or can use O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro to create a copy chinh sac of computer disk drives, can be used instead of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download AVS Media Player 26.0.1.176</title><pubDate> Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:13:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs-media-player-1890.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs-media-player-1890.html
</guid><description>
AVS Media Player is software media player brings you a space to enjoy music, video, vivid. AVS Media Player supports all audio formats, different image is a necessity. AVS Media Player allows you can open to near 100 format sounds, different images from common to most rare. Name the audio format, video, audio that programs can read, including: .AVI, .MPEG, .MP3, or .FLV, .JPG, .PNG ... and so very many other formats again.
AVS Media Player - The Media player
Features of AVS Media...
</description></item><item><title>Download Darktable 5.4.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:12:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-darktable-3959.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-darktable-3959.html
</guid><description>
Darktable is an application process work, photography, open source and developer rough. A lighttable virtual and Darktable for the photographer. It manages the negative of your digital in the database, lets you view them through a lamp can zoom and allows you to develop raw images and enhance them. Original image of you never be modified! Features color management professional to ensure fidelity in all the way in and handle GPU acceleration means you can speed up the process of his work by...
</description></item><item><title>Download AVS Video ReMaker 26.0.1.176</title><pubDate> Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:10:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs-video-remaker-1196.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs-video-remaker-1196.html
</guid><description>
AVS Video ReMaker is software that support quick editing of video files without reducing the video quality. Detection algorithm scenes used in AVS Video ReMaker will save time when processing video images and split it into the set. So, no need to preview every frame of the video file to find the transitions manually. With the help of AVS Video ReMaker, you can delete the unwanted parts and TV commercials from video files or file format DVD, recorded by various cameras, various video...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ahnenblatt 4.42.0.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:10:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ahnenblatt-3844.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ahnenblatt-3844.html
</guid><description>
Ahnenblatt is a genealogy software full-featured, easy to use suitable for beginners and even pedigree has the experience to organize genealogy research by you. Use plausibility checks to find out the inaccuracies in your family and create the chart impressive with just a few mouse clicks.
Ahnenblatt - Create family tree,
Recently, there has been strong increase of the general interest of the public for genealogical tree. Users who desire to track their heritage have many tools at...
</description></item><item><title>Download AVS Image Converter 26.0.1.176</title><pubDate> Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:09:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs-image-converter-4021.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs-image-converter-4021.html
</guid><description>
AVS Image Converter is a comprehensive application and have the ability to allow you to switch quickly and easily the digital images of yourself between many formats, including RAW, JPEG, GIF, TGA, PNG, PDF, TIFF, RAS, JPEG 2000. and many other types . The application comes with a variety of presets to change image size will allow you to easily resize your photos to the different print formats. You can also use the presets this to adjust their images for slideshows can be shared on social...
</description></item><item><title>Download Zentimo xStorage Manager 3.3.1.1303</title><pubDate> Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:09:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zentimo-xstorage-manager-33.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zentimo-xstorage-manager-33.html
</guid><description>
Zentimo xStorage Manager comprehensive management of your devices on the manage drive letter, launch the mobile app is installed on device, custom functions run automatically, more convenient. Besides, users can check the speed for the drive in ability file, including the file capacity from small to large, at the same time watch information, total capacity and available space on the drive.
</description></item><item><title>Download UWPSpy 1.5.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:08:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-uwpspy-10357.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-uwpspy-10357.html
</guid><description>
UWPSpy is a testing tool for UWP and WinUI 3 applications. Seamlessly view and manipulate UI elements and their properties in real time.
It allows users to observe how changes affect the structure and functionality of their UWP app. This is beneficial for helping with user interface design tasks during application development. When you select specific properties, the associated elements will be highlighted and any changes will update in real time.
How to use:
	Run UWPSpy.exe and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Bondware Poser Pro 14.0.227</title><pubDate> Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:08:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-smith-micro-poser-pro-526.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-smith-micro-poser-pro-526.html
</guid><description>
Smith Micro Poser Pro provides tools to create character and animation powerful 3D and includes models Poser the 3D character. The image is built so that the artist can click and drag to create the body parts, sculpting the face. Thousands of pose, shape, clothing, hair, materials and accessories are included.
Poser brings the power of design, interactive 3D animation, brings limitless opportunities to portray the diversity, form and expression of the human. Design with the human form...
</description></item></channel></rss>