<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 02:05:41 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 02:05:41 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download 4K Video Downloader Plus 26.0.4</title><pubDate> Tue, 17 Feb 2026 02:54:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-video-downloader-617.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-video-downloader-617.html
</guid><description>
4K Video Downloader Plus is software support downloads video, audio and subtitles from YouTube with high quality up to 4K. Download process video is very simple: just copy the video link from your browser and click Paste Url. Done! If you want that video on your iPad, iPhone or other device, we have protected you.
The feature on 4K Video Downloader Plus
	Download entire playlists and channels from YouTube and save them in MP4, MKV, M4A, MP3, FLV, 3G, create a file .m3u for...
</description></item><item><title>Download Freemake Video Converter Gold 5.0.0.35</title><pubDate> Tue, 17 Feb 2026 02:53:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-freemake-video-converter-gold-167.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-freemake-video-converter-gold-167.html
</guid><description>
Freemake Video Converter Gold is a software to help convert tail high quality videos with many different formats on many devices. Freemake Video Converter - convert video to AVI, MP4, WMV, MKV, 3GP, DVD, MP3, iPad, iPhone, PSP, Android phone. Video to MP3 just with one click! Rip and burn DVD. Convert YouTube to MP4, AVI, etc. with Freemake! Results guaranteed. Freemake Video Converter has fast conversion speed, guarantee the output quality,support create HTML5 videos have the embed code...
</description></item><item><title>Download Draftable Desktop 26.2.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 17 Feb 2026 02:53:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-draftable-desktop-3749.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-draftable-desktop-3749.html
</guid><description>
Draftable Desktop is comparison tool documents the fastest. Compare over 300 pages in a few seconds. Draftable Desktop 2.0 is now available - faster and stronger than ever! See all the changes in your documents, locally and online. Take your work to the next level. Compare secret and private do not use the internet and your documents never leave your computer. Specifically, Draftable Desktop compatible with .xls, .xlsx, .xlsxm. With Office 2013, 2016 or 365, you can compare text in...
</description></item><item><title>Download HitmanPro.Alert 3.21.1 Build 2039</title><pubDate> Tue, 17 Feb 2026 02:52:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hitmanpro-alert-112.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hitmanpro-alert-112.html
</guid><description>
HitmanPro is a lightweight application that can monitor your browser activity and detect the hidden threats may include security systems. Tool HitmanPro is built specifically to add an additional layer of security for system of you, to protect you whenever you shop on the Internet , or perform banking activities online. It offers computer protection in real time against the exploitation of software, download at in drive, encryption software, online fraud and identity...
</description></item><item><title>Download 4K YouTube to MP3 26.0.4</title><pubDate> Tue, 17 Feb 2026 02:50:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-youtube-to-mp3-622.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-youtube-to-mp3-622.html
</guid><description>
4K YouTube to MP3 is a software to convert video youtube to mp3 quickly and easily by the manipulation drag-and-drop simple. With 4K YouTube to MP3 you just drag and drop the link to the favorite songs of you and get the MP3 files to your computer, as easy as that. Transfer songs directly to iPod, iPhone and iPad everywhere you go. No install annoying and complex to solve, just a clean interface, user friendly and functional.
When using 4K YouTube to MP3, users will get the playlists,...
</description></item><item><title>Download DP Animation Maker 3.5.47</title><pubDate> Tue, 17 Feb 2026 02:48:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dp-animation-maker-2860.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dp-animation-maker-2860.html
</guid><description>
DP Animation Maker - 2D animation software smart allows you to turn static images into motion directly. The world is a living, breathing from your still images with minimal effort. DP Animation Maker lets you make natural scenes burst with vibrancy and bring out the motion to people and objects.
DP Animation Maker - Create and edit animated GIF
Animation Maker has the tools rich that you need to put all the pieces together. When you select pictures of yourself, it's easy to move from...
</description></item><item><title>Download Q-Dir 12.49</title><pubDate> Tue, 17 Feb 2026 01:17:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-q-dir-348.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-q-dir-348.html
</guid><description>
Q-Dir is software to manage the entire file and folder on the computer, allowing to see file in same time 4 different positions (viewport quadro) while still maintaining all the standard features of the Explorer.
It also provides a variety of management features, additional files included the filter file color-coding, layouts and columns can be customized, quick access to file and folder favorites and more.
Other features of Q-Dir , including directory listings (.txt, .doc .html .csv),...
</description></item><item><title>Download Code VBA 11.0.0.29</title><pubDate> Tue, 17 Feb 2026 01:16:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-code-vba-7207.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-code-vba-7207.html
</guid><description>
Code VBA allows professional software developers and MS Office users to write VBA code faster and take less time to search for online solutions. Find and insert VBA for Excel, Access and Word according to the application object model. The tool annotation explains what classes and procedures perform and grant direct access (F1) to the relevant documentation on Office MSDN online. In addition, the VBA code creator supports the writing of larger code blocks.
Features of Code VBA:
	The...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sublime Merge 2 Build 2122 Dev</title><pubDate> Tue, 17 Feb 2026 01:15:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sublime-merge-3957.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sublime-merge-3957.html
</guid><description>
Sublime Merge is the name of the application software and of course very useful for the programmer. In fact, the software in front of you is a text editor and the code light on the mass, and of course is strong. When using this software, you can view and edit multiple page text and his code at the same time and edit and complete them. User interface with great editing tools will give you experience coding very interesting.
Sublime Merge - source Editor and write the Code
Software...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mozilla Firefox 147.0.4</title><pubDate> Tue, 17 Feb 2026 01:14:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-firefox-quantum-501.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-firefox-quantum-501.html
</guid><description>
Firefox Quantum is a web browser independently provide the tabbed browsing combined with numerous handy features like pop-up blocker, Bookmarks, direct (integrated RSS), password manager, and more. Functionality can be extended with dozens of plugins available for free (extensions).
Firefox Quantum are interface completely new, beautiful, neat, minimalistic and delicate, eats less RAM to 30% compared with the old version and solve the condition consuming capacity
Firefox can import all...
</description></item><item><title>Download Pepakura Designer 6.1.6</title><pubDate> Tue, 17 Feb 2026 01:13:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pepakura-designer-748.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pepakura-designer-748.html
</guid><description>
Pepakura Designer is software to create 2D models, 3D quick, easy and developed in Japan. Pepakura Designer helps easily design the template paper craft by importing data 3D model. No special knowledge is required to model papercraft. All you have to do is prepare the 3D model. You can use some software 3DCG released from other developers to make the 3D models for unfolding.
Pepakura Designer - Create model 2D 3D
Pepakura Designer to create the form of 2D images that you can share it...
</description></item><item><title>Download CrystalDiskMark 9.0.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 17 Feb 2026 01:12:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-crystaldiskmark-1682.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-crystaldiskmark-1682.html
</guid><description>
CrystalDiskMark is software reviews active disk by the most simple method to check the performance and assess the quality of hard drive. CrystalDiskMark allows users to perform the test to review the performance of the hard drive. The simple reason you should use software like this is because the hard drive is the core for data storage on your computer, however each machine configuration different the performance of the hard drive. CrystalDiskMark gives you the tools to check the hard...
</description></item><item><title>Download Zortam Mp3 Media Studio Pro 33.81</title><pubDate> Tue, 17 Feb 2026 01:11:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zortam-mp3-media-studio-pro-135.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zortam-mp3-media-studio-pro-135.html
</guid><description>
Zortam Mp3 Media Studio Pro brings you rich processing tools music includes extract and convert music from CD to Mp3 format, edit, music cards, music download....You can also create discs CD high-quality music, with Zortam Mp3 Media Studio search music files duplicated to remove them from the system, rename music files, switch back and forth between formats.
Zortam Mp3 Media Studio Pro is rated as perfect software in the processing of the MP3 files on the computer. First of all, you can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Notepad++ 8.9.2 + Portable</title><pubDate> Tue, 17 Feb 2026 01:11:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-notepad-1062.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-notepad-1062.html
</guid><description>
Notepad++ is software editor programming editor and edit source code support on Windows platform, working with many other programming languages like ASP, PHP, Java, C#, Python, Jsp... Notepad++ is a source code editor is many programmers choice with many functions than men of it is Notepad.
Notepad++ - tool editor programming
Notepad++ has many features, simple interface, and can combine with many programming languages different. Notepad++ supports you to automatically perform various...
</description></item><item><title>Download NetSpot Unlimited Enterprise 5.1.0.706</title><pubDate> Tue, 17 Feb 2026 01:10:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-netspot-unlimited-enterprise-3952.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-netspot-unlimited-enterprise-3952.html
</guid><description>
NetSpot Unlimited Enterprise is a professional application only to the site survey, wireless, Wi-Fi and troubleshooting on Mac OS X and Windows. It is a analysis, FREE Wi-Fi. No need to be an expert network to improve the Wi-Fi at home or your office today! All you need is your MacBook running Mac OS X 10.10+, or any laptop with Windows 7/8/10 and NetSpot Unlimited Enterprise that operates on any 802.11 network.
NetSpot Unlimited Enterprise - Wifi network analysis
When working on a...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sandboxie 5.72.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 17 Feb 2026 01:08:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sandboxie-818.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sandboxie-818.html
</guid><description>
Sandboxie software to browse the Web securely while still keeping all the functionality your browser for content works against harmful agents such as sanbox up your computer. You may not know, when you browse the Web, the change will occur with the system of your computer. When you use Sandboxie, the software will protect the web browser of their own.
Sandboxie - web protection, safe browsing
The main features of Sandboxie
Stay safe on the Internet with Sandboxie
	Run the program in...
</description></item><item><title>Download Modbus Poll 13.0.0.2522</title><pubDate> Tue, 17 Feb 2026 01:08:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-modbus-poll-3852.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-modbus-poll-3852.html
</guid><description>
Modbus Poll is the simulator the Modbus is designed primarily to help developers device Modbus or others want to test and simulate the Modbus protocol. With the multiple document interface you can monitor a number of slave Modbus and / or the zone data at the same time. For each window you simply specify the ID slave, Modbus, function, address, size, and proportion of poll. You can read and write registers and coils from any window. If you want to change a register, just double-click the...
</description></item><item><title>Download priPrinter Professional 7.0.0.2616 Beta</title><pubDate> Tue, 17 Feb 2026 01:07:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-priprinter-professional-633.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-priprinter-professional-633.html
</guid><description>
priPrinter Professional is the printer driver allows you to manipulate the output of the printer before being printed. PriPrinter is installed and select the same as the printer driver other. After printing it automatically displays the preview in where you can preview his print, change the layout, page position back, cut them, and much more. Then, you print it to printer or save your document for later use. With PriPrinter you will always be sure his prints will look like. You can measure...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sandboxie Plus 1.17.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 17 Feb 2026 01:06:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sandboxie-plus-4962.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sandboxie-plus-4962.html
</guid><description>
Sandboxie Plus is an application version of the open source project on Github, equipped with software to protect your information while browsing the web or running valuable software. doubt. Web browsing, downloading or running software can affect system security. To prevent this from happening, a high user experience and strong layers of protection are needed to prevent malware from spreading to the system. For example, by opening an unknown application, malware in flash memory can...
</description></item><item><title>Download dbForge Studio for SQL Server Enterprise 2025.3.93</title><pubDate> Tue, 17 Feb 2026 01:04:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbforge-studio-for-sql-server-4710.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbforge-studio-for-sql-server-4710.html
</guid><description>
dbForge Studio 2019 for SQL Server is the program that will help the developer SQL management database, change database version control in the source control system downloads, speed up routine tasks, as well as perform the change database complicated.
A handy tool to analyze the status of the index SQL and troubleshoot issues with fragmentation index. dbForge Studio 2019 for SQL Server allows you to quickly collect statistical data fragmentation index and the current database needs...
</description></item><item><title>Download Metasequoia 4.9.0f</title><pubDate> Tue, 17 Feb 2026 01:04:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tetraface-inc-metasequoia-1479.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tetraface-inc-metasequoia-1479.html
</guid><description>
Metasequoia is software designed three-dimensional model and create the characters the same person or animal, requires some knowledge in this field and most important is a set of tools suitable for the job. For those who have created a number of innovative 3D solutions dedicated software different and need to work with them without have to re-install each program, a utility like Metasequoia can be the right choice.
Tetraface Inc Metasequoia - designed three-dimensional model
This app...
</description></item><item><title>Download Fluke TruTest 1.2.0.7</title><pubDate> Tue, 17 Feb 2026 01:02:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fluke-trutest-12626.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fluke-trutest-12626.html
</guid><description>
Fluke TruTest software is designed to eliminate the hassle associated with traditional power system data management and reporting. Whether you are testing fixed wiring systems or equipment in the office, verifying repairs in the workshop or carrying out annual inspections, proper data management is critical to creating Produce easy-to-understand reports for customers. Compatible with a growing list of Fluke and Beha-Amprobe test and measurement devices TruTest software allows you to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Hard Disk Sentinel Pro 6.40 Final</title><pubDate> Mon, 16 Feb 2026 19:54:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hard-disk-sentinel-pro-562.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hard-disk-sentinel-pro-562.html
</guid><description>
Hard Disk Sentinel Pro is a tool for monitoring and optimal performance for hard drive HDD and help diagnose the HDD as well as SSD. Version of Hard Disk Sentinel Pro is a professional version, the most advanced of Hard Disk with many advanced features that meet basic needs, check the hard drive for the user.
The goal of it is to find, test, diagnose and repair the malfunction, hard drive, report and display the health status of the SSD and hard drive failure, decreased performance and...
</description></item><item><title>Download tinyMediaManager 5.2.7.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 16 Feb 2026 19:54:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tinymediamanager-1819.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tinymediamanager-1819.html
</guid><description>
tinyMediaManager is a media manager full-featured to arrange and cleanup your media library your. Just choose (s) the folder containing your movies and the program can automatically get all meta data required for movies and program your TV from TheMovieDB.org, Imdb.com, OFDb.de and other online sources. tinyMediaManager download at artwork, film, cast, plot and details of other communication. Each film or program is presented with a unique art background, category, and appropriate...
</description></item><item><title>Download Helium Music Manager Premium 18.0.686</title><pubDate> Mon, 16 Feb 2026 19:53:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-helium-music-manager-premium-164.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-helium-music-manager-premium-164.html
</guid><description>
Helium Music Manager is a music manager that can rip, tag, play, browse, search, rename, burn and synchronize your music with the mobile. You can control your music collection with Helium Music Manager. Stop using time looking for the file on your computer or looking through CDS, vinyl records and tapes - instead, simply enjoy and explore your music! Helium Music Manager can replace the ripper, the player, tag editor and related software to audio your other.
Helium Music Manager...
</description></item></channel></rss>