<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 15:42:52 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 15:42:52 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download FxSound Pro 1.2.3 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 18:21:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fxsound-5966.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fxsound-5966.html
</guid><description>
FxSound Pro is a professional software that helps to enhance the quality of sound, volume, depth, and sound on your PC. FxSound brings you a great sound just with a downloadable download. After using FxSound, you will know if it is for you or not. Most people do n' t know what they ' re missing in their sound until they try their software/sound hardware better. It ' s hard to convey if you do n' t really experience yourself.
Reason to use FxSound Pro:
	The perfect sound on every...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinScan2PDF 9.46 + Portable</title><pubDate> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 18:14:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winscan2pdf-2117.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winscan2pdf-2117.html
</guid><description>
WinScan2PDF is a simple tool that allows you to scan documents from scanner and save them as PDF files. The program also supports multi-page scanning, then will be combined into one PDF document. Useful if your scanning software does not provide PDF conversion.
WinScan2PDF - Scan document to computer
WinScan2PDF allows users to perform scans the entire text or document at the same time to serve for the saved PDF format. Not only that, you also can choose the page any of a text to...
</description></item><item><title>Download StartAllBack 3.9.18.5338</title><pubDate> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 18:11:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-startallback-6857.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-startallback-6857.html
</guid><description>
With the official release of Windows 11, chances are that most of you want to try it out. As the name suggests, StartAllBack is a small, lightweight tool that can help you enjoy the power of the new operating system while keeping the look and feel, especially because main work area, desktop of Windows 7, Windows 10 as taskbars and start menu styles.
StartAllBack is specially designed for Windows 11 and will not work on any older operating systems. If you want to get the start menu back...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube Downloader 3.9.18 (1711)</title><pubDate> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 18:10:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube Downloader  is a dedicated software that helps users  downloading youtube videos  Favorites on PC for offline viewing. With MediaHuman YouTube  Downloader  you can download videos from youtube website to your computer with  fast speed , with special software development technology that automatically receives videos from Websites, in addition to the ability to download videos from software websites, can convert downloaded video formats to various formats for the purpose...
</description></item><item><title>Download XYplorer (32 Bit) 27.20.0500</title><pubDate> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 18:10:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-portable-12066.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-portable-12066.html
</guid><description>
XYplorer Portable is a file management software application that provides a comprehensive set of features for organizing and managing files and folders on your computer. This is a portable version of XYplorer that you can run directly from a portable storage device, such as a USB drive, without installation.
XYplorer Portable Features
	File Management: XYplorer Portable provides a two-window interface, allowing you to view and work with two folders at the same time. It provides easy...
</description></item><item><title>Download Global Mapper Pro 26.2.1 Build 111825</title><pubDate> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 18:09:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-global-mapper-professional-3563.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-global-mapper-professional-3563.html
</guid><description>
Global Mapper is a GIS application affordable and easy-to-use application that provides access to a great variety of spatial data sets and provides just the right level functionality to satisfy both GIS experts and experience users started. Also similar to a tool management data space independently and as an integral component of a GIS system enterprise-wide, Global Mapper is the tool mandatory for anyone working with maps or spatial data.
Global Mapper - GIS application
Global Mapper...
</description></item><item><title>Download Notepad++ 8.8.8 + Portable</title><pubDate> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 18:09:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-notepad-1062.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-notepad-1062.html
</guid><description>
Notepad++ is software editor programming editor and edit source code support on Windows platform, working with many other programming languages like ASP, PHP, Java, C#, Python, Jsp... Notepad++ is a source code editor is many programmers choice with many functions than men of it is Notepad.
Notepad++ - tool editor programming
Notepad++ has many features, simple interface, and can combine with many programming languages different. Notepad++ supports you to automatically perform various...
</description></item><item><title>Download ON1 Photo RAW 2026.1 v20.1.0.17725</title><pubDate> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 18:08:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-on1-photo-raw-1791.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-on1-photo-raw-1791.html
</guid><description>
ON1 Photo RAW 2023  includes the essential tools and features every photographer needs in their workflow. Our state-of-the-art, super-fast, non-destructive processing engine gives you an extremely smooth and efficient editing experience.
ON1 Photo RAW focuses on letting you get the most out of every photo. Photographers now have a quick photo management engine, hundreds of customizable photo effects, fast and beautiful HDR, masking and selection tools, layers and more in one app. Quickly...
</description></item><item><title>Download A4ScanDoc 2.0.9.31</title><pubDate> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 18:07:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-a4scandoc-4421.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-a4scandoc-4421.html
</guid><description>
A4ScanDoc is a software solution useful provide you with a set of features reasonable and support the document feeder and two-sided printing, at the same time provides a fast scanning engine handy based on the profile of users to create. It is very easy to use, and it has a minimalist interface, while somewhat outdated, has intuitive layout. However, the application does not provide materials to help first-time users.
A4ScanDoc - Scan and print documents
When one or more documents have...
</description></item><item><title>Download Smadav Pro 2025 v15.6</title><pubDate> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 18:07:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-smadav-pro-2443.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-smadav-pro-2443.html
</guid><description>
Smadav is an antivirus powerful virus for Windows operating system. Like any program anti-virus any other, this program will provide insurance on your system in order to prevent attacks and security threats. In addition to detecting viruses and malware like worms, Trojans, advertising, spammers, ransomware, etc., this program has good ability to protect and detect all type of virus Autorun. These viruses are often found in flash memory and storage media, mobile. You attach and copy the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft Edge 142.0.3595.90</title><pubDate> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 18:06:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-edge-3940.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-edge-3940.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft Edge is web browser developed specifically for Windows operating system 10 alternatives to Internet Explorer is the default browser on Windows. Browser Microsoft Edge built-in assistant Cortana brings content and website based on the user's preferences, there are also system utilities quite extensive help you to customize according to individual. Microsoft Edge has the similarity with Google Chrome quite large, except the target is marked more of the interface and the rounded...
</description></item><item><title>Download Text Editor Pro 35.0.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 18:06:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-text-editor-pro-800.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-text-editor-pro-800.html
</guid><description>
Text Editor Pro is software to handle text, HTML, Perl, Ruby, or Fortran with features syntax highlighting, professional. Text Editor provides syntax highlighting for over 50 scripts and has a simple interface and easy access. In addition, the Text Editor Pro also supports more than 50 programming languages like C ++, COBOL, graph DOT, DSP, DWScript, Fortran, Foxpro, Java, Perl, Python, Ruby, SQL and many other languages.
Text Editor Pro - text Processing professional
The software can...
</description></item><item><title>Download ON1 Photo RAW MAX 2026.1 v20.1.0.17725</title><pubDate> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 18:05:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-on1-photo-raw-max-10717.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-on1-photo-raw-max-10717.html
</guid><description>
ON1 Photo RAW MAX 2024 is powerful photo editing software that provides photographers with many tools and features to enhance and edit their images. With a user-friendly interface, it offers advanced editing capabilities, including non-destructive editing, AI-powered adjustments, and precise control over color and tone. It also supports raw files from over 800 cameras and works with JPEG, TIF, PSD, PSB, PNG and DNG files. Additionally, it also includes photo organization tools to manage...
</description></item><item><title>Download KMPlayer (KMP) 2025.11.14.11 x64 / 4.2.3.28 x86</title><pubDate> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 18:05:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kmplayer-kmp-902.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kmplayer-kmp-902.html
</guid><description>
KMPlayer (KMP) is software watch movies listen to music multi-function for video enthusiasts. KMPlayer development is many types of the format different. KMPlayer has improved on sound quality, images when listening to music and watching movies, the playback speed of video is faster, more codec player is added to the software video decoder is optimized.
KMPlayer also supports a variety of audio formats and video and offers a the interface can be customized with the preview coverflow and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Macro Express Pro 6.7.0.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 18:04:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-macro-express-pro-14053.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-macro-express-pro-14053.html
</guid><description>
Macro Express Pro is a Windows automation utility developed by Insight Software Solutions. It allows users to automate common computer tasks such as filling out web forms, opening programs, performing mouse clicks, and other repetitive actions.
Why use macros?
A macro is a way to automate a task that you perform repeatedly or frequently. It is a series of commands and actions that can be stored and run whenever you need to perform the task. You can record or create a macro, then run...
</description></item><item><title>Download Inno Setup Unpacker 2.1.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 18:04:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-inno-setup-unpacker-12546.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-inno-setup-unpacker-12546.html
</guid><description>
Inno Setup is a popular and reliable application that creates program installers by helping you create scripts. Extracting the installation files from their container, resulting from compiling code with Inno Setup, can only be done through self-extracting files. In other words, you need to create a self-extracting executable to shell the installation documents.
Inno Setup Unpacker can help you avoid such actions, which is especially useful because some system security protocols block...
</description></item><item><title>Download Windows and Office Genuine ISO Verifier 12.28.50.25</title><pubDate> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 18:03:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-and-office-genuine-iso-verifier-542.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-and-office-genuine-iso-verifier-542.html
</guid><description>
Windows and Office Genuine ISO Verifier is a small utility used to check for Microsoft Office and Windows ISO genuine or not by carrying out verification fast SHA-1 and MD5. The software has a friendly interface with the user and not cause you any real trouble whatsoever while navigating.
Users use tool requires to specify the file input and the application will automatically perform the rest of the work. Windows and Office Genuine ISO Verifier can compare the file SHA-1 with the...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDF Annotator 10.0.0.1002</title><pubDate> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 18:03:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-annotator-178.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-annotator-178.html
</guid><description>
PDF Annotator software user open any PDF file and add annotations, using the mouse or pen Tablet PC, directly on the Page of the PDF file. PDF Annotator allows users to perform editing operations on PDF files such as: add notes, edit signature, highlight, insert images or text... From the this useful tool, you can completely modify PDF files as you like in order to meet the different work.
PDF Annotator
With the PDF Annotator the document has annotations can then be saved directly back...
</description></item><item><title>Download JWIZARD Cleaner 1.9.7</title><pubDate> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 18:01:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jwizard-cleaner-12853.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jwizard-cleaner-12853.html
</guid><description>
Effective Windows cleaning software to remove unnecessary files from your PC. JWIZARD Cleaner for Windows quickly frees up disk space and keeps your system in an optimal state, ensuring your PC runs stably and efficiently. This application is designed to provide you with a comprehensive tool to analyze and optimize your PC by performing a comprehensive cleanup or a more detailed cleanup, targeting specific areas such as system, browser, mail, etc.
Features of JWIZARD Cleaner
	Clean...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Downloader 9.18.8</title><pubDate> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 18:01:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html
</guid><description>
YTD Youtube Downloader is an application that reliable and intuitive, allowing you to quickly download YouTube videos and save them to your computer. You can also convert the media files to the format desired video or extract audio streams and save separately. YTD Youtube Downloader lets you save your favorite clips of yourself from Youtube, Facebook, Vimeo and Dailymotion to your desktop. The software supports URLS from many web site hosting, multimedia and allows you to download desired...
</description></item><item><title>Download QOwnNotes 25.11.3</title><pubDate> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 18:00:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qownnotes-3178.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qownnotes-3178.html
</guid><description>
QOwnNotes is notes bookmark file simple text (GPL) open source application for GNU / Linux , Mac OS X and Windows of Patrizio Bekerle ( pbek on GitHub and IRC) (optional) activity along with the notes application of ownCloud or Nextcloud. QOwnNote store your notes as plain text files and can be synchronized with synchronization function file of ownCloud / Nextcloud. You can also use other apps like Syncthing or Dropbox . Just write out your thoughts as they appear, and edit them if...
</description></item><item><title>Download Executor 2.1.8</title><pubDate> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 18:00:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-executor-271.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-executor-271.html
</guid><description>
Executor for windows is a software alternative premium customization features for the Windows "Run" and "Search Programs". When you press WIN + Z and provides the search results instant, as-you-type for any keywords you enter. By default, Executor will index all the Desktop and Start Menu and you can easily expand the search range by adding the folder location additional.
Executor for windows
The program comes with a list of commands built in which you can use to quickly access many...
</description></item><item><title>Download Alternate TextBrowser 4.380</title><pubDate> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 18:00:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-alternate-textbrowser-2743.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-alternate-textbrowser-2743.html
</guid><description>
Alternate TextBrowser is a text editor, markup syntax, reliable and useful, useful for users that need to browse through a number of documents TXT and HTML in few minutes. Alternate TextBrowser will syntax highlighting for some programming languages / file types are available and can be configured for the file extensions different. The program includes the memorandum replaced and the Computer replaced as the additional tool. It is free software and requires Net-Framework 2.0 or higher...
</description></item><item><title>Download Dropbox 237.4.5655</title><pubDate> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 17:59:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dropbox-1313.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dropbox-1313.html
</guid><description>
Dropbox on taiwebs.com is free tool, the data synchronization across multiple PC become easier than never before: after installation, all what you have to do is enter your name, email address and password before opening the folder My Dropbox. If you install the software on a different computer, Dropbox will reflect the content of the online storage. So you exchange any data between the different computer is connected to Dropbox account. In addition the client is installed on the computer,...
</description></item><item><title>Download XYplorer 28.00.0700 Beta</title><pubDate> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 17:58:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-533.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-533.html
</guid><description>
XYplorer - File Manager for Windows is software that supports users to manage files on the Window quickly and to arrange the folder tidy. XYplorer features tabbed browsing, search, files, powerful, preview, flexible, highly customizable interface, dual frame options and a variety of unique ways to automate effective tasks often repeat. It's fast, lightweight, and portable.
Features XYplorer
	XYplorer is a file manager mobile. It does not require any settings, store all configuration...
</description></item></channel></rss>