<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 10:20:16 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 10:20:16 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Wondershare PDFelement Pro 12.1.1.3852</title><pubDate> Fri, 28 Nov 2025 01:44:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-pdfelement-pro-105.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-pdfelement-pro-105.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare PDFelement Pro support users to convert PDF to office documents for easier use, modify in every situation. Is one of the software conversion material is rated best today, integrated with many features. We recommend that you should use experience software many useful features this.
Wondershare PDFelement Pro - conversion Fie PDF more features, multi-language
Wondershare PDFelement Pro what?
Convert PDF into Word, Excel, PowerPoint...
• Convert PDF and protected PDF into...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare UniConverter 17.1.0.454</title><pubDate> Fri, 28 Nov 2025 01:43:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-uniconverter-4808.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-uniconverter-4808.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare UniConverter ( old name is Wondershare Video Converter Ultimate) which allows you to convert the video format. You can cut, splice, move, or add effects, subtitles a easy way. When using software you easily cut, splice, move, as well as add the effects, the subtitles to the video.... Or can switch the clods SD, HD video to any format popular for use with iPod (Classic, Nano and Touch), iPhone, Apple TV, Zune, PSP, Pocket PC...
Wondershare UniConverter helps convert formats...
</description></item><item><title>Download EaseUS Fixo Technician 4.1.0 Build 20251124</title><pubDate> Fri, 28 Nov 2025 01:42:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-fixo-9814.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-fixo-9814.html
</guid><description>
Video is corrupted or inaccessible after power failure and sudden blackout, whole system crash, update failure, wrong file handling or some other reason? EaseUS Fixo allows you to repair many different video file formats including MOV, MP4, M2TS, MKV, MTS, 3GP, etc. easier no matter how broken it is.
It can intelligently and intelligently repair damaged and damaged photos from computers or other external storage devices such as USB flash drives, memory cards, SD cards, digital cameras...
</description></item><item><title>Download reaConverter Pro 8.0.161</title><pubDate> Fri, 28 Nov 2025 01:42:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html
</guid><description>
reaConverter Pro is software image processing feature with batch conversion and image editing periodically becomes simple. eaConverter also provide command line utilities allow you to process images automatically, thus helping you shorten the time for other work.
reaConverter Pro integrated powerful tool of Uber with many great features. It provides advanced solutions to process and adjust images. Management of the conversion process the base image with the latest version of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Atlantis Word Processor 5.0.0.11</title><pubDate> Fri, 28 Nov 2025 01:41:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-atlantis-word-processor-585.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-atlantis-word-processor-585.html
</guid><description>
Atlantis Word Processor is a word processor app with features format, standard text, autocorrect, and spell check.  Atlantis is a word processor in accordance with most of the tasks handled daily text. The interface is very easy to use and offers the toolbars, hotkeys and sound effects thanh can customize (can turn off). It includes a clip library for quick access to the text or images used regular preview, font format and many other features aimed at improving the process of your...
</description></item><item><title>Download O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Premium 22.0.1123</title><pubDate> Fri, 28 Nov 2025 01:41:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-diskimage-server-4547.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-diskimage-server-4547.html
</guid><description>
O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Server is software that is specially designed for use in enterprise environments, the software allows users to backup all the files you want and keep them safe from any incident or disaster computer. O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Server comes with a variety of easy to use utility that allows users to backup entire partitions of the specific files from their PC, as well as recover the version previous data of them, all from a simple interface.
O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Server - data...
</description></item><item><title>Download Opera One 124.0.5705.65</title><pubDate> Fri, 28 Nov 2025 01:40:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-972.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-972.html
</guid><description>
Opera is a fast, safe, configurable and compliant intranet web browser, which includes both the reader and the application. The Opera browser supports web browsing, listening to music, watching high speed movies, you can open many tabs on the Opera without affecting your browsing speed. Opera now supports almost all devices and operating systems such as windows, IOS, Android, linux, MacOS ...
Opera is a beautiful interface and many interesting features, operating on both PCs and mobile,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Zoner Studio 19.2509.2.665</title><pubDate> Fri, 28 Nov 2025 01:40:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zoner-photo-studio-x-95.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zoner-photo-studio-x-95.html
</guid><description>
Zoner Photo Studio X Pro helps you to control your photos. Zoner Photo Studio is a complete toolbox for managing and processing digital photos. Get photos from your camera, organize your archive, and edit and share your photos - never been easier! Zoner Photo Studio is useful for beginners, advanced users and photographers with experience, who can choose one of four different variations. Zoner Photo Studio is made for every user of digital cameras, scanners, and mobile devices. It contains...
</description></item><item><title>Download lessmsi 2.10.7</title><pubDate> Fri, 28 Nov 2025 01:39:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lessmsi-12392.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lessmsi-12392.html
</guid><description>
Lessmsi (Less MSIerables) is a free and portable application that allows users to view and extract the contents of MSI files.
How does it work? Files with the .msi extension are not as widely used as their .exe cousins, but both contain programs for Windows. The main difference between them is that the latter does not always come with an installer, while it comes standard with the former. However, there will be cases where you just need to view or want to extract specific content from...
</description></item><item><title>Download Secret Video Downloader 1.0.7</title><pubDate> Fri, 28 Nov 2025 01:38:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secret-video-downloader-13775.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secret-video-downloader-13775.html
</guid><description>
Secret Video Downloader is a free application designed to facilitate easy video downloading from various websites. It leverages the yt-dlp command line program to efficiently grab video content, allowing users to save videos in the highest quality available without complicated installation or configuration. The tool has a minimalist interface focused on simplicity: the user pastes the video URL into the built-in browser, clicks the Download button, and the video is added to the download...
</description></item><item><title>Download Big Fish Games Keygen 2025.11.15</title><pubDate> Fri, 28 Nov 2025 01:27:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-big-fish-games-2043.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-big-fish-games-2043.html
</guid><description>
Big Fish Games that we share this software is provided by Vovan help provide Key for the game Big Fish Games without resorting to other software. As many people who love the game also know as Big Fish Games bring gaming experience great and attractive is built on the foundation of publishing exclusive of it. The company is headquartered in Seattle, WA, with a regional office in Oakland, CA, and is a part of Aristocrat Leisure Limited.
Big Fish Games - Provide Key for more than 4723...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinScript 1.4.3</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 23:23:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winscript-12800.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winscript-12800.html
</guid><description>
WinScript is an open source tool built to help you build custom scripts for Windows 10 and 11. It includes scripts for debugging, privacy, performance, and more, along with the ability to install all your favorite apps with just one click.
Features
	Debloat: Remove Windows bloatware, CoPilot, Edge, OneDrive, and other pre-installed features preset.
	Privacy: Disable Windows and 3rd party data collection, tracking, app access, and telemetry.
	Performance: Set background services to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Opera GX (Gaming Browser) 124.0.5705.61</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 23:22:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-gx-3170.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-gx-3170.html
</guid><description>
Opera GX is a special version of the Opera browser is built to complement gamers avid. Browser this game comes with the unique features to help users make maximum use of both the game and their browser. Opera GX is built specifically to support the game. This browser includes the unique features to help users have the best experience when gaming and surfing the web.
Opera GX - special browser for gamers
GX Control allows you to set a limit on the level of use RAM, CPU and network where...
</description></item><item><title>Download R-Wipe &amp;amp; Clean 20.0 Build 2537</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 23:21:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-wipe-clean-891.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-wipe-clean-891.html
</guid><description>
R-Wipe &amp;amp; Clean is software to delete junk files, unnecessary files from your computer to release the storage space and speed up your computer. In addition, R-Wipe &amp;amp; Clean also unleash the capacity of your drive and delete information invasion of privacy on different operations online and offline including your internet history and cookies, the list of downloaded files and documents were open, buffer different data, temporary files and many other items, created by the operating...
</description></item><item><title>Download XYplorer 28.00.0900 Beta</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 23:15:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-533.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-533.html
</guid><description>
XYplorer - File Manager for Windows is software that supports users to manage files on the Window quickly and to arrange the folder tidy. XYplorer features tabbed browsing, search, files, powerful, preview, flexible, highly customizable interface, dual frame options and a variety of unique ways to automate effective tasks often repeat. It's fast, lightweight, and portable.
Features XYplorer
	XYplorer is a file manager mobile. It does not require any settings, store all configuration...
</description></item><item><title>Download System Info 18.42</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 23:14:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-system-info-11391.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-system-info-11391.html
</guid><description>
System Info is a simple piece of software that displays various information about your system, including its hardware, operating system, and more. Having everything presented in a single interface, where you can copy and share that data elsewhere, can finally become convenient for regular users. That's what System Information does: it gives you various data about your system, including hardware specifications, operating system, network, and more. without installation.
This application...
</description></item><item><title>Download OCCT 15.0.8.99</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 23:14:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-occt-perestroika-1680.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-occt-perestroika-1680.html
</guid><description>
OCCT is a free application designed to benchmark and overclock system components. Test tool OverClock includes 4 different tests to assess the stability of your computer. CPU and CPU: Linpack to test the processor, GPU: 3D to check stability of the graphics processor and power supply combination of CPU: Linpack and GPU: 3D to download power of you up to the maximum.
OCCT - Measuring system components
The features of OCCT
	Support is enabled for a maximum of 16 cores.
	All the tests...
</description></item><item><title>Download uTorrent Pro 3.6.0 Build 47228</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 23:13:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-utorrent-pro-79.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-utorrent-pro-79.html
</guid><description>
uTorrent - Download the torrent file
uTorrent Pro is an application BitTorrent efficient for Windows. Most of the features in the BitTorrent client and others have in uTorrent, including priority bandwidth, scheduling, automatic download at RSS and Mainline DHT. Additionally, uTorrent supports specification joint protocol encryption and peer exchange of goods. Unlike many torrent clients, it does not hog system resources have value - typically using less than 6MB of memory, allowing you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tenorshare 4DDiG Windows Backup 1.1.1.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 23:13:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tenorshare-4ddig-windows-backup-14219.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tenorshare-4ddig-windows-backup-14219.html
</guid><description>
Backup files, partitions, or computers to computers or external devices. Full system backup to keep your system safe. Restore a specific partition from a full backup to save time. Task management console for easy backup.
Backup data with just one click
	PC backup: Delete, overwrite, corruption, or sudden crash can cause data loss. To keep your data safe, easily create a backup of your files, partitions, drives, or system with 4DDiG Windows Backup. Create a backup task, choose what you...
</description></item><item><title>Download ffMediaMaster (formerly myFFmpeg) 1.1.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 23:13:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-myffmpeg-2894.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-myffmpeg-2894.html
</guid><description>
ffMediaMaster is a communication tool designed with simple ideas, which will bring in a creative way to use FFmpeg. You can use this app to easily create high quality videos without having to write code. The utility will help you handle and convert a range of media files with just a few simple steps. ffMediaMaster supports a wide variety of multimedia formats, such as H264, Matroska, DNxHD, MPEG TS, XAVS, Theora, OGG, Animated GIF, VP9, MXF, MPEG-4, H265 HEVC, PRORES, DVVideo, MPEG FLV,...
</description></item><item><title>Download CalendarTask (formerly DesktopCal) 3.26.259.8213</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 23:12:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopcal-1831.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopcal-1831.html
</guid><description>
CalendarTask (formerly DesktopCal) is a simple desktop calendar that blends into your desktop without blocking access to your desktop icons. You can double-click on a date to quickly add notes and also jump to specific dates in the past or future.
CalendarTask - Computer calendar
CalendarTask can use your current wallpaper or loop through images from your folder and update your desktop every few minutes. The program helps you make appointments, make plans... Not only that, the Screen...
</description></item><item><title>Download GibbsCAM 2026 v26.0.51</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 23:12:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gibbscam-001-732.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gibbscam-001-732.html
</guid><description>
GibbsCAM is a full-featured CAM system that provides powerful CNC programming capabilities to optimize manufacturing production.GibbsCAM 12 introduces a modern, updated system Updated interface designed to increase efficiency and improve overall user experience.
GibbsCAM
GibbsCAM updates with a new interface that gives users the ability to customize, along with the ease-of-use features users expect, while still maintaining character, personality and traditional workflows. by...
</description></item><item><title>Download Pixel Composer 1.20.0.8</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 23:07:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pixel-composer-13321.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pixel-composer-13321.html
</guid><description>
Pixel Composer is a Node-based visual effects (VFX) software designed specifically for pixel art. It allows users to create, edit, and composite pixel art effects in a non-destructive and procedural way. The software features a powerful node and graph system that allows users to mix, stack, and combine multiple effects without altering the original file.
It supports animation of any parameter using keyframes, curves, and expressions, and includes simulation capabilities such as rigid...
</description></item><item><title>Download Vovsoft PDF Reader 5.7</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 23:07:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-pdf-reader-6226.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-pdf-reader-6226.html
</guid><description>
Vovsoft PDF Reader is a simple, lightweight PDF viewing application. There is no complex configuration to view your PDF files from the desktop. The minimus interface provides all the necessary elements. The unique design PDF reader does not tax the system resources of your computer.
Features of Vovsoft PDF Reader
	The interaction is PDF document
	Lightweight and easy to use
	Simple interface.
System requirements:
	The operating system was supported: Windows 10 /8.1/8/7/Vista/XP...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mountain Duck 5.1.0.28309</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 23:06:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mountain-duck-4115.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mountain-duck-4115.html
</guid><description>
Mountain Duck allows you to mount servers and cloud storage as the disk on the computer to your desk. Open the file remotely with any application and act as on a local disk without the need to synchronize the file. Based on the platform open source solid of Cyberduck, all of the main protocols are supported to connect to any server you want, including FTP, SFTP, WebDAV, Azure Cloud Storage, Amazon S3, Google Cloud Storage, Google Drive, Dropbox, Backblaze B2 &amp;amp; OpenStack Swift. Transfer...
</description></item></channel></rss>