<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 13:53:30 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 13:53:30 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Quick Clipboard Editor 3.1.1.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 21 Aug 2025 15:47:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quick-clipboard-editor-9421.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quick-clipboard-editor-9421.html
</guid><description>
Quick Clipboard Editor is free software that provides direct access to the text stored in your clipboard, allowing you to quickly modify it to meet your needs. meet your needs before pasting the text into the app you want. It allows you to quickly retrieve previous clips from your clipboard history, find and replace specific words or phrases, insert new content into each line, trim unwanted pieces of text, keep or remove lines or characters based on different criteria, arrange text using...
</description></item><item><title>Download DesktopOK 11.96</title><pubDate> Thu, 21 Aug 2025 15:47:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopok-1635.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopok-1635.html
</guid><description>
DesktopOK is software save and restore the positions of icons. DesktopOK also offers a solution small but effective for the user to change the screen resolution often. DesktopOK is not installed and can be executed easily from the desktop, and can be carried on a small USB or memory device to another. Start of the program. The first time you use the program, the program will show you screen license. Free program and license info is only displayed the first time (on each PC).
DesktopOK -...
</description></item><item><title>Download Office Timeline Plus 11.20.00.00 Expert / Pro / Pro+ Edition</title><pubDate> Thu, 21 Aug 2025 15:46:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-timeline-2106.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-timeline-2106.html
</guid><description>
Office Timeline is an add-on very useful and powerful software for Microsoft PowerPoint. With add-ons, you can create PowerPoint documents look more beautiful. With add-ons, you can add the time Line on the project by yourself. Application time for the composition and different segments of the document, your PowerPoint will not only increase the beauty for your work, but also for customers and your manager. The people who created this product is also believe that add-ons this is the only...
</description></item><item><title>Download Futuremark SystemInfo 5.87.1376</title><pubDate> Thu, 21 Aug 2025 15:45:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-futuremark-systeminfo-2568.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-futuremark-systeminfo-2568.html
</guid><description>
Futuremark SystemInfo is a small program created to conduct diagnostic analysis complete all kinds of processes, as well as equipment used on a personal computer of you. According to the author, you can use this tool as a component reference in the application be supported, it will determine the version of your operating system and other information about the hardware.
Note that Windows XP, 3DMark06, and PCMark05 are no longer be Futuremark support. Function SystemInfo on Windows XP is...
</description></item><item><title>Download Claris FileMaker Pro 22.0.2.202</title><pubDate> Thu, 21 Aug 2025 15:45:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-filemaker-pro-advanced-487.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-filemaker-pro-advanced-487.html
</guid><description>
FileMaker Pro Advanced is software via internet easy manager database, contacts, projects and inventory data, and generate reports. FileMaker Pro will help users to build database customize and design them to fit with the activities and profile of their business. More than a million people around the world use platform FileMaker every day to complete the work faster and more efficient in work.
Features on FileMaker Pro Advanced
Anywhere access
	Use one unified platform to create the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Fort Firewall 3.19.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 21 Aug 2025 15:44:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fort-firewall-6439.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fort-firewall-6439.html
</guid><description>
Fort Firewall is a network security system that monitors and controls network traffic and goes based on predefined security rules. A firewall often establishes a barrier between a trusted internal network and untrusted external networks, such as the Internet.
Features of Fort Firewall
	Filter by network address, application group
	Support of representative characters in the name path name
	Application group speed limit
	Access Traffic Statistics
	Display bandwidth
	Based on the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Marvelous Designer Enterprise 2025.1.107</title><pubDate> Thu, 21 Aug 2025 15:44:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-marvelous-designer-1339.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-marvelous-designer-1339.html
</guid><description>
Marvelous Designer is one of the program best designed to help the 3D design and fashion design. A simulation system revolutionary use of physics. Now, you can create the correct clothes only using Marvelous Designer without help of the other CAD app. Marvelous Designer supports polylines, draw the curved lines connected for free. Any amendments and / or modifications will be displayed immediately on the model clothing 3D in real time.
Marvelous Designer - fashion design
The main...
</description></item><item><title>Download ACleaner 5.5</title><pubDate> Thu, 21 Aug 2025 15:43:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-acleaner-6867.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-acleaner-6867.html
</guid><description>
ACleaner is a safe and easy to use privacy protection tool that allows you to erase common Internet and computer traces, including browser caches. browsing, cookies, sites visited, URLs entered, recent documents, index.dat file and more. You can also easily remove traces of up to 100 popular apps. It also includes an option to overwrite deleted data multiple times, so it cannot be easily recovered. Cookie cleaning allows you to specify which cookies to keep so you don't delete your...
</description></item><item><title>Download n-Track Studio Suite 10.2.2.10172</title><pubDate> Thu, 21 Aug 2025 15:43:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-n-track-studio-2991.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-n-track-studio-2991.html
</guid><description>
n-Track Studio is a recording software allows you record and create MIDI music and sounds top quality. The software allows you to add effects, VST3, DirectX, AU (Mac), VST and ReWire different on each track or channel. This program also allows you to automatically fade out, fade in and fade out or increase the volume of the music to indicate the voice of the singer.
n-Track Studio can record and playback the number of audio, MIDI and sound unlimited. In addition, you can handle the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Free PDF Password Remover 14.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 21 Aug 2025 15:42:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-pdf-password-remover-5455.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-pdf-password-remover-5455.html
</guid><description>
Free PDF Password Remover is a FREE tool to instantly unlock your PDF file by removing password and all restrictions. It can remove both User and Owner passwords along with all PDF file restrictions like Copy, Print, Screen Reader, etc. Free PDF Password Remover allows users to import PDF documents into the editor's window with a drag-and-drop tool. This feature helps users to choose the correct PDF file that needs to be removed, and saves time and manipulation when working with a large...
</description></item><item><title>Download XYplorer 27.10.0600</title><pubDate> Thu, 21 Aug 2025 15:42:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-533.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-533.html
</guid><description>
XYplorer - File Manager for Windows is software that supports users to manage files on the Window quickly and to arrange the folder tidy. XYplorer features tabbed browsing, search, files, powerful, preview, flexible, highly customizable interface, dual frame options and a variety of unique ways to automate effective tasks often repeat. It's fast, lightweight, and portable.
Features XYplorer
	XYplorer is a file manager mobile. It does not require any settings, store all configuration...
</description></item><item><title>Download SyMenu 8.9.9363</title><pubDate> Thu, 21 Aug 2025 15:42:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-symenu-2726.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-symenu-2726.html
</guid><description>
SyMenu is a menu USB mobile that you can use to quickly access applications and documents from a USB drive its mobile. The program runs as an icon in your system tray from which you can activate the custom menu allows you to launch your apps. To create your menu, just drag - drop the folder from drive on your mobile or browse to find the file you want to link. You can arrange the shortcuts according to the hierarchical structure with folders, icons and separator and also can configure the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Avast Premium Security 25.8.10387</title><pubDate> Thu, 21 Aug 2025 15:41:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avast-premier-antivirus-security-1359.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avast-premier-antivirus-security-1359.html
</guid><description>
Avast! Premier Antivirus is antivirus software famous by combining all the technologies and methods virus advanced. The developer software this anti-virus have invested in all their knowledge about fighting viruses to create one of the software anti-virus best. Program anti-virus this combines all the technology and advanced methods to get the level of computer security highest. This product is ideal for all the Windows operating system.
Avast! Premier Antivirus - antivirus...
</description></item><item><title>Download Stepwise 2.2.6</title><pubDate> Thu, 21 Aug 2025 15:40:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stepwise-11853.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stepwise-11853.html
</guid><description>
Stepwise is a user-friendly automation tool for Windows. This utility provides the means to automate various repetitive tasks through a simple process that does not require much programming. Set up, name, and save workflows through an intuitive interface to save time and keystrokes. There are numerous tutorials available on the author's site that illustrate the setup and use of Stepwise. The interface is clearly laid out and provides tips as you move through automating your chosen...
</description></item><item><title>Download Abelssoft PC Fresh 2026 v12.0.64497</title><pubDate> Thu, 21 Aug 2025 15:40:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-abelssoft-pc-fresh-508.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-abelssoft-pc-fresh-508.html
</guid><description>
Abelssoft PC Fresh is a software compact and quite simple. Its function is to help users optimize the computer by stopping the processes do not need and defragmenting your hard disk. Dedicated application PC Fresh aims to keep your pc in good state so you can use the full potential of it.
Features of Abelssoft PC Fresh
With modern interface and is well organized, you will know what to do when to the main window. Some areas can be managed, such as services, startup items, speed, the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Grub2Win 2.4.3.3</title><pubDate> Thu, 21 Aug 2025 15:39:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-grub2win-3177.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-grub2win-3177.html
</guid><description>
Grub2Win is a open source program to dual boot Windows and Linux safely. Grub2Win boot code the GNU Grub version 2.04. Everything is in a folder of 20 MB on Windows drive C: On the EFI system, a few small modules to be installed into the EFI partition of your.
Grub2Win - Boot system, Windows
Using GUI Windows and simple instructions you can install Grub2Win quickly and safely. Notice the boot time and help can be displayed in multiple languages. After installing interface, it's easy to...
</description></item><item><title>Download PhotoPad Image Editor Pro 14.39 Beta</title><pubDate> Thu, 21 Aug 2025 15:39:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photopad-image-editor-572.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photopad-image-editor-572.html
</guid><description>
PhotoPad Image Editor is a software to help edit photos and supports lots of features like edit, cut, rotate, resize and flip digital photos. With PhotoPad Image Editor, you can freely perform the basic editing for their images and also can add some neat effect. It has the option to create a photo collage and mosaic images from your photos, and you can also add text and captions. If you prefer, you can complete your masterpiece by adding the frame or contour is simple.
The main features...
</description></item><item><title>Download Monkeys Audio 11.38</title><pubDate> Thu, 21 Aug 2025 15:39:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-monkeys-audio-949.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-monkeys-audio-949.html
</guid><description>
Monkey\'s Audio is software that compresses digital music without loss of quality. Supports high quality WAV files and CD ripping. Monkeys Audio will compress .wav tracks into .ape files to reduce their size without loss of sound quality, decompress .ape, convert files, check file integrity and manage tags.
Unlike traditional methods like MP3 and OGG, which permanently remove quality to save space, Monkey\'s Audio only creates perfect copies with the same sound quality as the originals....
</description></item><item><title>Download QILING Disk Master Technician WinPE v8.5</title><pubDate> Thu, 21 Aug 2025 15:38:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qiling-disk-master-technician-winpe-4831.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qiling-disk-master-technician-winpe-4831.html
</guid><description>
QILING Disk Master Technician WinPE is programs backup and restore data on WinPE for programmers and administrators, QILING Disk Master Technician WinPE meet all the needs to recover data your lost and restore the broken system in few minutes. There is software to restore data &amp;amp; backup systems, reliable and advanced system for desktop and laptops at homes and businesses. It allows the user to perform the operation backup service and backup the entire / difference / increase in...
</description></item><item><title>Download Syncovery Premium 11.7.2.87</title><pubDate> Thu, 21 Aug 2025 15:37:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncovery-pro-enterprise-232.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncovery-pro-enterprise-232.html
</guid><description>
Syncovery Pro Enterprise is a great application used to back up data and to synchronize personal computers, servers, laptops, notepads and storage online. The software comes with support for FTP and secure FTP servers, SSH, WebDAV, Amazon S3, http, update the part file, ZIP compression, data encryption, and schedule automatic backups.
Syncovery Pro Enterprise have the ability to freely select files and folders across the whole folder hierarchy in tree view and supports email...
</description></item><item><title>Download TunnelBear 4.14.0.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 21 Aug 2025 15:37:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tunnelbear-4601.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tunnelbear-4601.html
</guid><description>
TunnelBear is a VPN app for the Internet connection to help you protect your identity, allow you to select the IP address that author for you to easily access other Internet services. The purpose of TunnelBear is to help you add an additional layer of security to the data communication occurs between the PC and a remote server by using the service anonymous to encrypt information. With the help of it you can navigate on the Internet without having to worry that your data can be blocked by...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wave Arts Power Suite 7.2025.8.21</title><pubDate> Thu, 21 Aug 2025 15:37:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wave-arts-power-suite-4713.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wave-arts-power-suite-4713.html
</guid><description>
Wave Arts Power Suite is a sound plugin are appreciated by we are currently ranked first in class, sound quality outstanding, efficient CPU in particular, interface design, visually stunning, customer support, world-class and great value. The plugin Power Suite Native run in any application music production or audio editing based on Mac OS X (AU / VST / MAS / RTAS) or Windows (DX / VST / RTAS).
The features of Wave Arts Power Suite
	Plug-in channel strip last
	Sounder multi-algorithm...
</description></item><item><title>Download Alternate Calculator 3.920</title><pubDate> Thu, 21 Aug 2025 15:36:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-alternate-calculator-2744.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-alternate-calculator-2744.html
</guid><description>
Alternate Calculator is a simple calculator also can be used to translate the currency (e.g. Euro). It has included a set of currencies is pre-determined and the exchange rate can also be modified individually. An editor internal is included can be used to re-encode and save the calculation steps were performed.
Alternate Calculator - Calculator and currency converter
Alternate Calculator also can be used the different number systems (decimal, hexadecimal, binary, client defined). This...
</description></item><item><title>Download AndroidDrive 2.4.6</title><pubDate> Thu, 21 Aug 2025 15:36:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-androiddrive-10400.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-androiddrive-10400.html
</guid><description>
AndroidDrive is a program that allows mounting Android smartphones/tablets as drives on Windows. When AndroidDrive is running and you connect an Android device, AndroidDrive automatically mounts the drive containing that device's internal storage (files, folders).
Once you have started AndroidDrive, the connected Android smartphone/tablet will be recognized as a new drive in Windows Explorer. This way, any files, photos, or other media can be moved back and forth between your Windows...
</description></item><item><title>Download Viber for PC 26.0.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 21 Aug 2025 15:35:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-viber-2406.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-viber-2406.html
</guid><description>
Viber is a software of instant messaging, based on VoIP protocols, multi-platform due to the Viber Media development for smart phones used to send sms and make calls over the internet. Along with text messaging, users can exchange images, video and audio.
Viber - software news message, chat online
This is a program that is quite popular is mainly designed for mobile phones, but now we are talking about the version for Windows, so immediately. It will allow you to send messages to other...
</description></item></channel></rss>