<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 13:47:29 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 13:47:29 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download HomeBank 5.9.7</title><pubDate> Sat, 27 Dec 2025 16:22:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-homebank-1160.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-homebank-1160.html
</guid><description>
HomeBank is a software personal accounting helps you manage finances, track expenses and manage your budget. HomeBank can nerd the interface is quite simple but the program back offers all the features that most people need to manage personal finance their.
HomeBank - Manage personal finance
In addition, you can import your bank statements from the file OFX / QFX, customize the type of spending and income, set a limit personal budget and create a custom report (with chart) to know you...
</description></item><item><title>Download CPUID HWMonitor Free 1.61</title><pubDate> Sat, 27 Dec 2025 16:21:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cpuid-hwmonitor-free-8486.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cpuid-hwmonitor-free-8486.html
</guid><description>
CPUID HWMonitor Free is a free system monitoring software that allows users to monitor various hardware components in their computer, such as CPU, GPU, memory memory and temperature. It can be used to monitor performance and troubleshoot problems with the system. The software is compatible with the Windows operating system and can be downloaded from the CPUID website.
Features of CPUID HWMonitor Free
	Real-time monitoring of various hardware components such as CPU, GPU, memory and...
</description></item><item><title>Download R-Wipe &amp;amp; Clean 20.0 Build 2541</title><pubDate> Sat, 27 Dec 2025 16:14:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-wipe-clean-891.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-wipe-clean-891.html
</guid><description>
R-Wipe &amp;amp; Clean is software to delete junk files, unnecessary files from your computer to release the storage space and speed up your computer. In addition, R-Wipe &amp;amp; Clean also unleash the capacity of your drive and delete information invasion of privacy on different operations online and offline including your internet history and cookies, the list of downloaded files and documents were open, buffer different data, temporary files and many other items, created by the operating...
</description></item><item><title>Download XYplorer (32 Bit) 27.20.0800</title><pubDate> Sat, 27 Dec 2025 16:14:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-portable-12066.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-portable-12066.html
</guid><description>
XYplorer Portable is a file management software application that provides a comprehensive set of features for organizing and managing files and folders on your computer. This is a portable version of XYplorer that you can run directly from a portable storage device, such as a USB drive, without installation.
XYplorer Portable Features
	File Management: XYplorer Portable provides a two-window interface, allowing you to view and work with two folders at the same time. It provides easy...
</description></item><item><title>Download ExifTool 13.45</title><pubDate> Sat, 27 Dec 2025 16:13:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-exiftool-1685.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-exiftool-1685.html
</guid><description>
ExifTool is a library of Perl platform-independent plus a command line application for reading, writing, and editing meta information in various file types. ExifTool supports many metadata formats including EXIF , GPS , IPTC , XMP , JFIF , GeoTIFF , ICC Profile , Photoshop IRB , FlashPix , AFCP and ID3 , as well as notes of the manufacturer of many digital cameras by Canon , Casio , DJI , FLIR , FujiFilm , GE , GoPro , HP , JVC / Victor , Kodak , Leaf , Minolta / Konica-Minolta , Motorola...
</description></item><item><title>Download thilmera7 0b184 Rev.5</title><pubDate> Sat, 27 Dec 2025 16:13:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thilmera7-2918.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thilmera7-2918.html
</guid><description>
thilmera7 is an application capable of performing this task and perform it quite well. This is an app that tracks real-time which you can put anywhere on the screen of his computer application and to forward detailed information about memory, disk, network, CPU, GPU, processes, sound and other aspects miscellaneous.
All the controls and options for the application is provided from the context menu right-click. There you can find the table 'properties' from where you can switch and see all...
</description></item><item><title>Download RoboTask 10.6.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 27 Dec 2025 16:11:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-robotask-6157.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-robotask-6157.html
</guid><description>
RoboTask is software that allows you to automate any task combination on your computer, from just launching applications, checking your email, moving or backup files to upload or download, email and more. The program allows easy task to create simple tasks, as well as highly complex automation, involving the IF/ELSE statements that have conditions, loops, customization variables, and other advanced options.
Just a few minutes with RoboTask will give you a lot of ideas about how you can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tenorshare 4DDiG 10.6.11.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 27 Dec 2025 16:11:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tenorshare-4ddigs-pro-5629.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tenorshare-4ddigs-pro-5629.html
</guid><description>
Tenorshare 4DDiG is software to recover data from laptop / PC, external drive or USB flash disk. Recover Windows partitions, such as raw partitions, formatted partitions, damaged partitions, etc. Recover lost or deleted photos, videos, audio, videos, documents, etc.
With 4DDiG, you can recover many different types of data from this powerful Windows Data Recovery Tool feature. No matter what you have lost, 4DDiG is capable of recovering deleted files Windows 10 / 8.1 / 8/7 /...
</description></item><item><title>Download Moneyspire 2026 v26.0.7</title><pubDate> Sat, 27 Dec 2025 16:10:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-moneyspire-14310.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-moneyspire-14310.html
</guid><description>
Moneyspire is a personal and small business finance management program that lets you track your basic accounts, budgets, bills, loans, and investments. Categorize your spending and income into customizable categories. Track bills so you never forget to pay and avoid late fees. Set budgets to track spending and avoid overspending in specific categories like eating out. Forecast account balances to avoid overdrafts and cash shortages. Balance your checkbook and compare it to your bank...
</description></item><item><title>Download Inkscape 1.4.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 27 Dec 2025 16:10:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-inkscape-4219.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-inkscape-4219.html
</guid><description>
Inkscape is a free app and powerful tool designed for the task edit vector, which can support many features SVN advanced, such as cloning, marker, mixed alpha and many more. The program will help you easily design the logical interface, and enhance images, apply effects, add various objects, etc., Inkscape allows you to easily edit nodes, trace bitmaps and perform a variety of activities, links complex. This program is very similar to the popular software others, such as Corel Draw, Adobe...
</description></item><item><title>Download MailWasher Pro 8.0.96 Beta</title><pubDate> Sat, 27 Dec 2025 16:08:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-firetrust-mailwasher-pro-825.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-firetrust-mailwasher-pro-825.html
</guid><description>
MailWasher Pro software is ready to filter all of your email accounts and blocked, remove the spam from the list of email. MailWasher allows you to preview all your email before to your computer or your mobile device, you allows you to read all your email securely, and instantly delete any unwanted emails or suspicious. Email good rest of you is download at PC or mobile devices, to help you not get any virus, spam or any email.
Firetrust MailWasher Pro - Blocker remove spam
The...
</description></item><item><title>Download Thimeo Stereo Tool 10.74</title><pubDate> Sat, 27 Dec 2025 16:07:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stereo-tool-4066.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stereo-tool-4066.html
</guid><description>
Stereo Tool is an audio processor based on software, provide sound quality superior and comes with many unique features. It is used by over 1500 FM stations, from the station of the small local to the station 50 - 100 kW and nationwide network with dozens of generators, thousands of stations online and many radio DAB +, HD, AM and TV. Stereo Tool can make recordings sound equal and consistent in volume and sound color, highlight details and increase the stereo effect is there. It can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Firebird Maestro 24.2.0.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 27 Dec 2025 16:07:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-firebird-maestro-1459.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-firebird-maestro-1459.html
</guid><description>
Firebird Maestro is the tool superiority of Firebird to manage, control and develop databases. It provides powerful tools to manage users and the task, edit and execute the SQL scripts, create visual charts for numerical data, building the OLAP cubes, etc. With all the features this software Firebird Maestro will be daily assistant for server database Firebird your.
Firebird Maestro - database Management, data
Features and functionality of Firebird Maestro
	Supports all versions of...
</description></item><item><title>Download CCExtractor 0.96.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 27 Dec 2025 16:06:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ccextractor-6675.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ccextractor-6675.html
</guid><description>
CCExtractor is a tool used to produce subtitles for TV recordings from almost anywhere in the world. We plan to update all sources and formats. Subtitles are very important to many people. If you're learning a new language, subtitles are a great way to learn it from movies or TV shows. If you're hard of hearing, subtitles can help you better understand what's happening on screen. We aim to make it easy to create subtitles using command line tools or Windows GUI.
Features of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Thimeo ST-Enterprise 10.74</title><pubDate> Sat, 27 Dec 2025 16:05:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thimeo-st-enterprise-10422.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thimeo-st-enterprise-10422.html
</guid><description>
Thimeo ST-Enterprise is for larger media groups running multiple stations or channels. It does everything that Stereo Tools does and more! With ST-Enterprise, you can run up to 50(*) FM and/or HD processors on a single computer, with a single interface to control them and an overview screen showing the status of them all. incoming and outgoing signals.
Features of Thimeo ST-Enterprise
	It makes more efficient use of available resources, mainly processing power, and allows you to share...
</description></item><item><title>Download Thimeo Relay 10.74</title><pubDate> Sat, 27 Dec 2025 16:05:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thimeo-relay-10423.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thimeo-relay-10423.html
</guid><description>
Thimeo Relay uses your sound card (internal or external) as a Relay detector and converts on/off signals into RDS commands that can be sent to most devices. RDS encoders, including those in Stereo Engine and STXtreme.
Features of Thimeo Relay
	It minimizes audio latency, ensuring real-time audio processing and synchronization with video content or virtual instruments.
	It offers multiple connection options to meet different audio needs.
	Use your sound card (internal or external) as a...
</description></item><item><title>Download WPS Office - PDF, Word, Excel, PPT 18.24</title><pubDate> Sat, 27 Dec 2025 15:27:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wps-office-pdf-word-excel-ppt-8244.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wps-office-pdf-word-excel-ppt-8244.html
</guid><description>
WPS Office is a mobile office suite app that allows users to view, edit and create documents, spreadsheets, and presentations on their Android device. The app is available for download from the Google Play Store and is compatible with a wide range of file formats, including Microsoft Office documents.
WPS Office - Free Office suite for Word, PDF, Excel, is an all-in-one office suite that integrates Word, PDF, Excel, PowerPoint, Forms, Cloud Storage, Online Editing, Template library and...
</description></item><item><title>Download PhotoDirector: AI Photo Editor 20.8.8</title><pubDate> Sat, 27 Dec 2025 15:27:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-photodirector-photo-editor-8144.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-photodirector-photo-editor-8144.html
</guid><description>
PhotoDirector is a photo editing app for Android devices that allows you to edit and enhance your photos with a variety of tools and effects. With PhotoDirector, you can adjust your photo's color and lighting, remove blemishes and other imperfections, and apply filters to give your photos a unique look. You can also use PhotoDirector to create photo collages and slideshows, add text and stickers to photos, and share your edited photos on social networks or through other sharing...
</description></item><item><title>Download QuickPic Gallery 9.7 build 9700000</title><pubDate> Sat, 27 Dec 2025 15:27:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-quickpic-gallery-13688.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-quickpic-gallery-13688.html
</guid><description>
QuickPic Gallery is a popular Android application designed to manage and edit photos and videos with a fast, lightweight and user-friendly interface. The application displays all image and video files in a gallery format, allowing users to copy, move, rename, hide and delete files and folders. Users can also create new files and folders and move media between them.
QuickPic includes basic editing tools like cropping, flipping, rotating, resizing, and trendy filters for quick image...
</description></item><item><title>Download MiXplorer Silver File Manager 6.69.2-Silver</title><pubDate> Sat, 27 Dec 2025 15:26:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-mixplorer-silver-file-manager-8516.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-mixplorer-silver-file-manager-8516.html
</guid><description>
MiXplorer Silver File Manager is a file management application for mobile devices. It offers a user-friendly interface and a host of features to help you manage files and folders on your phone or tablet. MiX Silver is a bundle of the MiXplorer file manager and Archiver, Image, Tagger and PDF add-ons as a paid application to support MiXplorer development.
MiXplorer Silver File Manager Features
	Easily create themes with customization options that let you choose any color you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Firewall Security AI - No Root 2.5.9 build 2590</title><pubDate> Sat, 27 Dec 2025 15:26:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-firewall-no-root-8224.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-firewall-no-root-8224.html
</guid><description>
No Root Firewall is an Android application that allows users to block Internet access to specific applications on their device without requiring root access. Blocks internet attacks and protects you from unwanted access to the internet. Determine which applications can and cannot access the internet. With powerful firewall technology, secure filter lists and artificial intelligence, you protect your privacy comprehensively and also stay informed about what is being shared with the...
</description></item><item><title>Download SnapTube for Android 7.52.0.75250210</title><pubDate> Sat, 27 Dec 2025 15:25:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-snaptube-youtube-downloader-hd-video-8351.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-snaptube-youtube-downloader-hd-video-8351.html
</guid><description>
SnapTube is a mobile application that allows users to download videos from various platforms, such as YouTube, Vimeo, and Dailymotion. It provides video resolution in multiple formats 144p, 720p, 1080p HD, 2K HD, 4K HD and audio formats MP3 and M4A. With Snaptube, users can search for content across all their platforms without using multiple apps.
Features of SnapTube for Android
Download in multiple resolutions
	MP4 videos are available in resolutions: choose small 360 pixels or...
</description></item><item><title>Download Baby: Breastfeeding Tracker 6.28.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 27 Dec 2025 15:24:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-baby-breastfeeding-tracker-13388.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-baby-breastfeeding-tracker-13388.html
</guid><description>
This app is a convenient and reliable assistant for your newborn's breastfeeding. You can track breastfeeding, bottle feeding, solid feeding, and pumping. You can save your baby's diaper changes, sleep times, and height and weight measurements. This baby tracker will help parents get through the wonderful weeks.
App features
	Track breastfeeding on one side or both sides, if you feed from both sides at once
	Track bottle feedings
	Measure solids for breastfeeding - type and amount
	If...
</description></item><item><title>Download SketchUp Pro 2026 v26.1.189</title><pubDate> Sat, 27 Dec 2025 13:12:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sketchup-01en-1336.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sketchup-01en-1336.html
</guid><description>
SketchUp is a 3D modeling tool powerful and convenient is designed for architects, designers, builders, engineers and manufacturers of various products. SketchUp provides a variety of tools to draw and create drawings, palette of materials (vegetation, metal and glass), the color palette of the installation ball and more. Models created in SketchUp can be saved and then edited at any time, add new parts on them, change the size, texture, etc. this approach allows you to create complex...
</description></item><item><title>Download OnlyOffice Desktop Editors 9.2.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Dec 2025 23:37:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-onlyoffice-7488.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-onlyoffice-7488.html
</guid><description>
OnlyOffice is a free office suite that can open documents, presentations, and spreadsheets in different tabs of the same window, providing interoperability Compatible with the most popular file formats. With an attractive intuitive interface and intuitive controls, OnlyOffice allows users to open documents, spreadsheets and presentations, or create new ones from scratch. It comes with support for the most common file formats, even those native to Microsoft's office suite. Moreover, it can...
</description></item></channel></rss>