<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 15:33:05 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 15:33:05 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Wondershare PDFelement Pro 12.0.7.3749</title><pubDate> Sat, 27 Sep 2025 17:14:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-pdfelement-pro-105.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-pdfelement-pro-105.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare PDFelement Pro support users to convert PDF to office documents for easier use, modify in every situation. Is one of the software conversion material is rated best today, integrated with many features. We recommend that you should use experience software many useful features this.
Wondershare PDFelement Pro - conversion Fie PDF more features, multi-language
Wondershare PDFelement Pro what?
Convert PDF into Word, Excel, PowerPoint...
• Convert PDF and protected PDF into...
</description></item><item><title>Download PrivaZer Pro Donors 4.0.111</title><pubDate> Sat, 27 Sep 2025 17:14:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-privazer-donors-198.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-privazer-donors-198.html
</guid><description>
PrivaZer Donors  cleans and removes filth traces from the system. Intensive cleaning of unwanted traces of what you've done, viewed, downloaded, deleted, etc. Take ownership of your security and freedom - Free up disk space. Keep your PC snug and secure !!!
With one click, PrivaZer can safely clean: Internet browsers, Index.dat, Cookies, Tor Cookies, Flash Cookies, Silverlight Cookies, DOM Storing, IndexedDB, AppCache Registry, RAM, Pagefile.sys and Hiberfil.sys files.  PrivaZer  can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Topaz Video AI Pro 7.1.6 / 1.0.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 27 Sep 2025 17:13:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-video-enhance-ai-3733.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-video-enhance-ai-3733.html
</guid><description>
Topaz Video Enhance AI is a tool to increase video quality with this great technology ONE. Topaz Video Enhance WHO wide open your video to resolutions up to 8K with the details and consistency of motion. Until the present, there is no way to re-create a perfect high resolution video from the footage is low resolution. From the family film to SD low quality to DVD quality and more than that, Video Enhance WHO will convert your video into the footage is upgrade clear with resolutions up to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Photoshop 2025 v26.11.0 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Sat, 27 Sep 2025 17:12:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-0010-adobe-photoshop-737.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-0010-adobe-photoshop-737.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Photoshop is a powerful raster graphics editor developed by Adobe Systems, primarily used for image editing, photo editing, and graphic design. Currently,&amp;nbsp;Adobe Photoshop 2025 is considered a graphic design software, creating and enhancing images, illustrations, and 3D artwork. In addition, it also supports website and mobile app design, video editing, real-life painting simulation, and more.
Adobe Photoshop 2025 - Graphic design
When it comes to Adobe Photoshop, it is...
</description></item><item><title>Download OBS Studio 32.0.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 27 Sep 2025 17:12:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-open-broadcaster-software-2451.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-open-broadcaster-software-2451.html
</guid><description>
Open Broadcaster Software is abbreviated as OBS is a program to detect the type of multimedia content to the internet. It is worth noting that a simple interface and the presence of a good tool. You can adjust the quality of the audio and video before starting the broadcast, you can specify the URL, choose the resolution of the screen, etc. With strong desire, videos which you found can be saved to your hard drive.
Open Broadcaster Software - LiveStream on PC
The basic features of Open...
</description></item><item><title>Download yt-dlp 2025.09.26</title><pubDate> Sat, 27 Sep 2025 17:11:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-dlp-6802.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-dlp-6802.html
</guid><description>
yt-dlp is a youtube-dl branch based on youtube-dlc currently not working. The main focus of this project is the addition of new features and patches while still updating the original project.
</description></item><item><title>Download Cockos REAPER 7.47</title><pubDate> Sat, 27 Sep 2025 17:10:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cockos-reaper-889.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cockos-reaper-889.html
</guid><description>
Cockos REAPER is a powerful software for for windows, chp lets you record, arrange, edit, and display the audio waveform multi-track. Cockos REAPER offers an extensive feature set includes many effects and a sample project. REAPER supports ASIO, Kernel Streaming, WaveOut, and DirectSound for playback and recording. It reads the files in WAV, OGG and MP3 files and records WAV files. You can arrange any number of items in any number of tracks and use plug-in sound processing (DirectX and...
</description></item><item><title>Download n-Track Studio Suite 10.2.2.10223</title><pubDate> Sat, 27 Sep 2025 17:10:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-n-track-studio-2991.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-n-track-studio-2991.html
</guid><description>
n-Track Studio is a recording software allows you record and create MIDI music and sounds top quality. The software allows you to add effects, VST3, DirectX, AU (Mac), VST and ReWire different on each track or channel. This program also allows you to automatically fade out, fade in and fade out or increase the volume of the music to indicate the voice of the singer.
n-Track Studio can record and playback the number of audio, MIDI and sound unlimited. In addition, you can handle the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Internet Download Manager Portable 6.42 Build 47</title><pubDate> Sat, 27 Sep 2025 17:09:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-internet-download-manager-portable-11965.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-internet-download-manager-portable-11965.html
</guid><description>
Internet Download Manager (IDM) is a popular software tool that helps users download files from the internet at faster speeds. It is designed to increase download speeds up to five times, resume and schedule downloads, and support multiple download queues. IDM also has many features that make it easy to use and customize to fit your needs.
IDM has a simple and friendly interface that makes it easy to use. The software integrates seamlessly with popular web browsers such as Google Chrome,...
</description></item><item><title>Download PingPlotter Professional 5.25.19.9087</title><pubDate> Sat, 27 Sep 2025 17:08:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pingplotter-professional-4090.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pingplotter-professional-4090.html
</guid><description>
PingPlotter Professional is monitoring software network graphics, drawing graphs latency and data packet loss for maximum hundreds of targets at the same time. It includes everything in PingPlotter Standard, plus tools to monitor multi-targets, communicating with other systems, and collect data remotely. PingPlotter Professional is accessed through interface like web browser. PingPlotter Pro check out hundreds of targets at the same time. Summary chart available to the organization goals...
</description></item><item><title>Download R-Wipe &amp;amp; Clean 20.0 Build 2528</title><pubDate> Sat, 27 Sep 2025 17:08:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-wipe-clean-891.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-wipe-clean-891.html
</guid><description>
R-Wipe &amp;amp; Clean is software to delete junk files, unnecessary files from your computer to release the storage space and speed up your computer. In addition, R-Wipe &amp;amp; Clean also unleash the capacity of your drive and delete information invasion of privacy on different operations online and offline including your internet history and cookies, the list of downloaded files and documents were open, buffer different data, temporary files and many other items, created by the operating...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinScan2PDF 9.41 + Portable</title><pubDate> Sat, 27 Sep 2025 17:07:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winscan2pdf-2117.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winscan2pdf-2117.html
</guid><description>
WinScan2PDF is a simple tool that allows you to scan documents from scanner and save them as PDF files. The program also supports multi-page scanning, then will be combined into one PDF document. Useful if your scanning software does not provide PDF conversion.
WinScan2PDF - Scan document to computer
WinScan2PDF allows users to perform scans the entire text or document at the same time to serve for the saved PDF format. Not only that, you also can choose the page any of a text to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wing IDE Pro 11.0.5</title><pubDate> Sat, 27 Sep 2025 17:07:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wing-ide-pro-2080.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wing-ide-pro-2080.html
</guid><description>
Wing IDE Pro is a integrated development environment to create applications using the Python language. Wing IDE Pro provides a code editor professional, in which you can use the keyboard shortcuts vi and emacs, auto-complete code re-structure, follow up calls, reminders, contextual. A code debugger graphics to debug locally and remotely, an interface to version control system, a test unit, a search tool flexibility available.
Wing IDE Pro - programming language Python
Features of Wing...
</description></item><item><title>Download BandiView Pro (Honeyview) 7.23</title><pubDate> Sat, 27 Sep 2025 17:06:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-honeyview-4871.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-honeyview-4871.html
</guid><description>
HoneyView is an image viewer, comic book archive support with formats such as zip, cbz, rar....and support the photo format display, such as JPG, GIF, TIFF, PNG,... can see the photos automatically change after a period of time, adjust the time from 1 to 90 seconds and the options like repeat or random. In addition, support photo editing basics like rotate, add effects, zoom and pan or zoom display frame.
Features of HoneyView
	Operating system supported: Windows XP / Vista / 7/8 /...
</description></item><item><title>Download Monkeys Audio 11.54</title><pubDate> Sat, 27 Sep 2025 17:06:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-monkeys-audio-949.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-monkeys-audio-949.html
</guid><description>
Monkey\'s Audio is software that compresses digital music without loss of quality. Supports high quality WAV files and CD ripping. Monkeys Audio will compress .wav tracks into .ape files to reduce their size without loss of sound quality, decompress .ape, convert files, check file integrity and manage tags.
Unlike traditional methods like MP3 and OGG, which permanently remove quality to save space, Monkey\'s Audio only creates perfect copies with the same sound quality as the originals....
</description></item><item><title>Download Tracktion Software Waveform Pro 13 v13.5.13</title><pubDate> Sat, 27 Sep 2025 17:05:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tracktion-software-waveform-5037.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tracktion-software-waveform-5037.html
</guid><description>
Waveform is tools includes a set of greater than 80 plugins to be built in FX. Also includes a set of virtual musical instruments is extremely strong, Collective provides a wide variety of different instruments for every genre of music, Multi Sampler revolutionary is a playground, sound design and Subtractive brings similar sound for your works.
Specializing in workflow creative and inspired and avoid the unnecessary features clearly allows the app to maintain the fun and visually...
</description></item><item><title>Download MassTube 2026 v21.0.3.167 Ultra</title><pubDate> Sat, 27 Sep 2025 17:05:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-masstube-plus-461.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-masstube-plus-461.html
</guid><description>
MassTube Plus is a small utility used to download the favorite videos of you on youtube on your computer. This is a software compact, has a simple design with few options to download videos fastest. The you complete peace of mind because the software is easy to use, built exclusively for a single goal: to retrieve the video file from YouTube, so it doesn't pack the other useful features such as search engine integrated and a download audio file.
MassTube can work with multiple output...
</description></item><item><title>Download Imaginando VS 2.0.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 27 Sep 2025 17:00:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-imaginando-vs-11117.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-imaginando-vs-11117.html
</guid><description>
Take your music to another dimension with a captivating visual world. VS - Visual Synthesizer makes it easy to represent your sounds optically in a highly customizable way. At the core of Imaginando VS is a set of graphics shaders called materials, which render procedurally generated geometry in real time, based on each material's unique set of parameters. VS comes equipped with 50 beautifully hypnotic materials for you to customize and combine to create mesmerizing performances.
Visual...
</description></item><item><title>Download MusConv 4.10.422 Lifetime</title><pubDate> Sat, 27 Sep 2025 17:00:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html
</guid><description>
MusConv transfers playlists, albums, followed artists and liked songs across a variety of services – Spotify, Apple Music, Amazon Music, YouTube, YouTube Music, iTunes, Deezer, Tidal, SoundCloud, Pandora and more 125 music services!
Features of MusConv Ultimate
	Transfer playlists, albums, followed artists and liked tracks between over 125 music servicesManage playlists (Delete, Merge, Split, Copy...)
	More than 125 music services supported
	Access DAILY updated music charts on...
</description></item><item><title>Download PHPRunner Enterprise 11.1.43785</title><pubDate> Sat, 27 Sep 2025 16:59:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-phprunner-2572.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-phprunner-2572.html
</guid><description>
PHPRunner build the web interface visually appealing for all database MySQL, MS Access, SQL Server, Postgre and Oracle locally or remotely. A program convenient and simple will create multiple PHP pages to access and modify any database locally or remotely such as MySQL. First and foremost, software created for web developers who need to create various PHP pages in order to modify any database locally or remotely how.
The program allows you to create a web app complete with a number of...
</description></item><item><title>Download PrivaZer 4.0.111</title><pubDate> Sat, 27 Sep 2025 16:58:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-privazer-66.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-privazer-66.html
</guid><description>
PrivaZer : the program performs the scan is very thorough not only includes the trace downloads like registration, Internet history, cookies, etc but also find the traces of potential in the field of free disk space of you. PrivaZer can permanently delete all traces by using the method of secure erase and also re-establish the sector disk free to 0 to remove all traces from the delete operation earlier. The process of scanning and cleaning the original can spend less time (20-30 minutes),...
</description></item><item><title>Download Imaginando FRMS 1.12.4</title><pubDate> Sat, 27 Sep 2025 16:57:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-imaginando-frms-granular-synthesizer-9030.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-imaginando-frms-granular-synthesizer-9030.html
</guid><description>
Imaginando FRMS Granular Synthesizer is a software synthesizer designed for digital audio workstations (DAWs) that allows users to create complex and textured sounds using engineering techniques. detailed summary. The synthesizer is designed to be flexible and easy to use, with many intuitive controls and a graphical user interface that allows users to quickly and easily shape their sound.
The synthesizer also includes a variety of presets and a sound bank that gives users a starting...
</description></item><item><title>Download KeepMouseSpeedOK 3.44</title><pubDate> Sat, 27 Sep 2025 16:56:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-keepmousespeedok-2762.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-keepmousespeedok-2762.html
</guid><description>
KeepMouseSpeedOK is a simple app for those who often change the mouse speed and are looking for ways to do this from the system tray icon instead of mouse settings Windows. In addition to changing the cursor speed, the program also can lock the speed setting to ensure that the application of the Tuesday not changed. If you need access tot he full the mouse settings, a shortcut is provided in the tray icon and the file menu.
KeepMouseSpeedOK - control mouse speed
Program is suitable...
</description></item><item><title>Download Calcpad 7.4.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 27 Sep 2025 16:56:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-calcpad-12576.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-calcpad-12576.html
</guid><description>
Calcpad is free software for mathematical and engineering calculations. It is a flexible and modern programmable calculator with Html report generator. Calcpad uses a simple programming language that is fast and easy to learn. It does not require any special programming skills, which makes it suitable for engineers without any computer programming background. You can create calculation notes simply by writing your formula and text, enclosed in 'quotation marks'.
The program includes...
</description></item><item><title>Download ASPRunner.NET Enterprise 11.1.43785</title><pubDate> Sat, 27 Sep 2025 14:04:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-asprunnernet-enterprise-14178.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-asprunnernet-enterprise-14178.html
</guid><description>
ASPRunner.NET builds sophisticated, custom web database applications with the ASPRunner.NET low-code platform. ASPRunner.NET lets you create powerful, dynamic, and secure applications up to 20 times faster than traditional software coding.
With ASPRunner.NET, out of the box, you have a complete web application with a set of interconnected web pages. All pages are professionally designed but highly customizable and offer a lot of functionality.
Features of ASPRunner.NET
	Many skins...
</description></item></channel></rss>