<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 21:36:59 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 21:36:59 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Adobe-GenP 3.7.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 03 Nov 2025 17:12:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-genp-0013-9964.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-genp-0013-9964.html
</guid><description>
Adobe-GenP is a patch developed to unlock the latest versions of Adobe Creative Cloud applications 2019, 2020, 2021, 2022, 2023, 2024, 2024, 2025 (such as Photoshop, Premiere Pro) , After Effect....) easily and effectively. GenP is easy to use, works after your one click.
List of supported products:
	Adobe Acrobat DC 2023 - 2025
	Adobe After Effects CC 2019 – 2025, 2026
	Adobe Animate CC 2019 – 2025, 2026
	Adobe Audition CC 2019 – 2025, 2026
	Adobe Bridge CC 2019 – 2025,...
</description></item><item><title>Download DesktopSnowOK 6.76</title><pubDate> Mon, 03 Nov 2025 17:09:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopsnowok-1950.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopsnowok-1950.html
</guid><description>
DesktopSnowOK is an application to create snow fall effect interesting, DesktopSnowOK allows you to animate your desktop with the flakes of snow virtual. You can choose from many types of scales, configure the number of flakes (5-64) and the speed of them. The interface of DesktopSnowOK is quite simple but allows you to make more customization. At any time you can also choose to activate or deactivate DesktopSnowOK by the Activate/ Deactivate, click on Start with Windows to launch the app...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mozilla SeaMonkey 2.53.22</title><pubDate> Mon, 03 Nov 2025 17:09:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mozilla-seamonkey-4426.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mozilla-seamonkey-4426.html
</guid><description>
SeaMonkey is a comprehensive software suite will meet all your needs related to your Internet while you surf the web. The application is promoted by the platform, Netscape and Mozilla, allows the group SeaMonkey continuous project development to provide the high-quality updates to this concept. The software package, a chat application, email &amp;amp; news groups IRC has RSS reader, HTML editor, Internet browser and other web development tools different.
Mozilla SeaMonkey - The essential...
</description></item><item><title>Download VidCoder 12.11 + Portable</title><pubDate> Mon, 03 Nov 2025 17:06:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vidcoder-534.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vidcoder-534.html
</guid><description>
VidCoder is software to convert movies to MKV and MP4, as well as extract video content from DVDS and Blu-ray. This is a software utility to help people extract the video content from the BD and DVD as well as convert the clips specific to MKV and MP4.
VidCoder has an interface that includes a clear design, including a menu bar, several buttons and a panel to display the queue. The file can be added with the help of the file browser or drag and drop-out.
Features VidCoder
	VidCoder...
</description></item><item><title>Download Fast Screen Recorder 2.1.0.16</title><pubDate> Mon, 03 Nov 2025 17:05:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fast-screen-recorder-7132.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fast-screen-recorder-7132.html
</guid><description>
With the Fast Screen Recorder app, you can capture any moment on your screen. Fast Screen Recorder helps capture your online conferences, meetings, tutorials, gaming moments and more. You can only record audio, video and both with or without a voice mic.
Fast Screen Recorder provides an option to enable/disable your microphone before recording begins. So you can make videos with your voice. This is useful for recording tutorials and presentations. After recording video or audio from...
</description></item><item><title>Download DVDFab 13.0.5.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 03 Nov 2025 17:04:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dvdfab-67.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dvdfab-67.html
</guid><description>
DVDFab All-In-One is a multi-purpose combo of nearly all powerful DVDFab products-DVD replication, Ripper DVD, Blu-ray Ripper, Blu-ray Ripper, Copy UHD, Blu-ray to DVD, DVD to Blu-ray Transaction, DVD Creator, Blu-ray Creator, video conversion, Cinavia DVD removal, Windows DVD removal, DRM elimination for Apple, Screen Recorder and Editor for iOS, Hi-Fi Sound and File Transfer. It provides a complete solution to all of your DVD/Blu-ray/video problems and the perfect execution.
DvDFab -...
</description></item><item><title>Download Easy Duplicate Finder 7.35.0.74</title><pubDate> Mon, 03 Nov 2025 17:04:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easy-duplicate-finder-2768.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easy-duplicate-finder-2768.html
</guid><description>
Easy Duplicate Finder is software to find and remove files duplicate on the computer. With this tool, you can restore gigabyte of capacity, make your computer faster and arrange your files. Manage duplicate files with Easy Duplicate Finder™ on your computer or Mac fast, simple and fun.
Easy Duplicate Finder has powerful features that will help you to find and delete the photos, documents, MP3, videos, emails and many more. It is fast to the incredible, accurate and easy to use. Just...
</description></item><item><title>Download AllMapSoft Universal Maps Downloader 10.230</title><pubDate> Mon, 03 Nov 2025 17:03:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-universal-maps-downloader-736.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-universal-maps-downloader-736.html
</guid><description>
AllMapSoft Universal Maps Downloader is software download map images on the computer for offline viewing support many types such as Google Maps, Yahoo maps, Bing maps, OpenStreet Maps, Yandex Maps, Ovi Maps, MapQuest Maps. All the downloaded photos will be saved on disk. You can view downloaded maps by Maps Viewer Or you can combine them into one big bmp, or jpg file tif by Maps Combiner, and also you can export all the tiles into a database format MBTiles.
AllMapSoft Universal Maps...
</description></item><item><title>Download RapidRAW 1.4.4</title><pubDate> Mon, 03 Nov 2025 17:03:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rapidraw-13957.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rapidraw-13957.html
</guid><description>
RapidRAW is a modern, high-performance, open-source RAW photo editor, designed to deliver a fast and clean editing experience with a lightweight footprint (under 30MB). Built with performance and usability in mind, the software is aimed at photographers who want a simple, efficient, and fun workflow without compromising performance.
Key Features
	GPU-accelerated processing: Uses a custom WGSL shader to process all image adjustments on the GPU, allowing for smooth, responsive editing...
</description></item><item><title>Download Playnite 10.43</title><pubDate> Mon, 03 Nov 2025 17:02:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-playnite-6972.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-playnite-6972.html
</guid><description>
Playnite is an open-source video game library manager and manager with support for third-party libraries such as Steam, GOG, Origin, Battle.net and Uplay. Includes supporting the game, providing a unified interface for your game. With Playnite, you can comfortably enter the game from Steam, Battle.net, Origin, GOG and Uplay services, including uninstalled games.
You have three options to view when using Playnite. You also have the custom game option or add any game or program with...
</description></item><item><title>Download Homedale 2.22</title><pubDate> Mon, 03 Nov 2025 17:02:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-homedale-1914.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-homedale-1914.html
</guid><description>
Homedale is a screen wireless network simple allows you to view the status and signal strength of nearby access points. In addition to displaying technical information like infrastructure, channels and bitrate are supported, the program also includes a chart signals allows you to monitor signal strength of multiple access points in real time.
Because this is a mobile program, it is important to mention that it does not leave any traces in the Windows Registry. You can copy it on any USB...
</description></item><item><title>Download Automatic Email Processor 3.8.17</title><pubDate> Mon, 03 Nov 2025 17:02:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-automatic-email-processor-702.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-automatic-email-processor-702.html
</guid><description>
Automatic Email Processor is a software for managing Email in Outlook efficiency by automatically working with predefined settings. The user interface is divided into two main parts, which is the area allows you to view a list of profiles that you have created and their status and the filters located in the lower part of the interface.
Automatic Email Processor is a comprehensive solution in the archive and print emails and attachments on Outlook fully-automatic. Therefore, you can create...
</description></item><item><title>Download SoftPerfect NetWorx 25.11</title><pubDate> Mon, 03 Nov 2025 17:01:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-softperfect-networx-1592.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-softperfect-networx-1592.html
</guid><description>
SoftPerfect NetWorx is a software simple and effective way to manage traffic and bandwidth consumption in Windows. If we ignore traffic not regular, and occasionally of the operating system to update itself, as well as updates for the different drivers, one of the important factors in the job vacancy Internet soon is the use of the Internet is hidden by the software is installed on your system. . If you are the user settings clock software and you don't pay attention to it, the existence...
</description></item><item><title>Download Flyby11 1.50.627</title><pubDate> Mon, 03 Nov 2025 17:01:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-flyby11-12467.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-flyby11-12467.html
</guid><description>
Flyby11 is a simple patcher that removes annoying restrictions that prevent you from installing Windows 11 (24H2) on unsupported hardware. Do you have an old PC? No TPM, Secure Boot or your processor is not supported? Flyby11 allows you to install Windows 11 24H2. There are no complicated steps. Just run the tool and you'll be running Windows 11 on your outdated machine in no time.
Technical overview
Flyby11 takes advantage of a feature of the Windows 11 setup process that uses the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Flyoobe 1.50.627</title><pubDate> Mon, 03 Nov 2025 17:00:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oobelux-13956.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oobelux-13956.html
</guid><description>
Flyoobe was born out of the frustration many users felt with the Windows 11 setup experience. Whether it was the mandatory online account, the endless "Next, next, next..." screens, or the incomplete configuration options when you finally reached the desktop, the current setup lacked focus on what users really wanted.
Why choose Flyoobe?
	Simplifies the Windows 11 setup process right out of the box.
	Allows easy local account creation without need to hunt for hidden options.
	Includes...
</description></item><item><title>Download AllMapSoft Offline Map Maker 8.361</title><pubDate> Mon, 03 Nov 2025 17:00:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-offline-map-maker-656.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-offline-map-maker-656.html
</guid><description>
AllMapSoft Offline Map Maker is software create, organize, offline map from Google Maps, Yahoo maps, Bing maps and Openstreetmap. You can view offline maps downloaded with map viewer offline. And you can zoom out or zoom in the offline map or export map under the file format .BMP with file world xxx.bpw, and can output files xxx.map for OziExplorer. If you want to make a offline map of your city by yourself, it is very useful for you.
Features AllMapSoft Offline Map Maker
	You can...
</description></item><item><title>Download DoNotSpy11 Pro 1.3.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 02 Nov 2025 22:30:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-donotspy11-pro-10596.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-donotspy11-pro-10596.html
</guid><description>
DoNotSpy11 Pro is the professional successor to DoNotSpy10, the world's first anti-spy tool for Windows 10. Its simple user interface allows you to manage explains how Windows 10, Windows 11, Microsoft Edge, and Microsoft Office respect your privacy.
DoNotSpy11 gives you the opportunity to easily manage what you want to share and what not. While many of the settings represent what you can configure using Settings and many other apps, there are also adjustments that aren't easily...
</description></item><item><title>Download Simple Cutting Software X 2025.11.02</title><pubDate> Sun, 02 Nov 2025 22:29:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-simple-cutting-software-x-12810.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-simple-cutting-software-x-12810.html
</guid><description>
Simple Cutting Software X is a lightweight and practical program that helps you maximize the potential of a material, be it wood, metal, glass or other. It gives you the best cutting options for the parts you need, while minimizing waste.
Key Features
	2D Cutter Optimization: The cuts are made from one side to the other of the material. This feature is useful for glass, wood, tempered glass, etc.
	Adjustable blade thickness: For diamond glass cutting, the blade thickness is 0, but for...
</description></item><item><title>Download Album TD 4.9.0.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 02 Nov 2025 22:28:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-album-td-3968.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-album-td-3968.html
</guid><description>
Album TD has the full name is "Album Turbo Design" can help you design a wedding album album family photo album, with friends, etc.; any theme album with the great entertainment in just a few seconds. Album TD is equipped with fishing features from Album DS design software album for Photoshop, a new tool has been developed: Album Turbo Design. All the power to pull and drop-at services, album design, tools design new of, we will immediately create layouts for both page count and paging...
</description></item><item><title>Download XYplorer (32 Bit) 27.20.0200</title><pubDate> Sun, 02 Nov 2025 22:28:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-portable-12066.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-portable-12066.html
</guid><description>
XYplorer Portable is a file management software application that provides a comprehensive set of features for organizing and managing files and folders on your computer. This is a portable version of XYplorer that you can run directly from a portable storage device, such as a USB drive, without installation.
XYplorer Portable Features
	File Management: XYplorer Portable provides a two-window interface, allowing you to view and work with two folders at the same time. It provides easy...
</description></item><item><title>Download Nobe OmniScope 1.10.168</title><pubDate> Sun, 02 Nov 2025 22:27:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nobe-omniscope-10985.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nobe-omniscope-10985.html
</guid><description>
Nobe OmniScope is a powerful and flexible video monitoring and analysis tool used by professionals in the film, television and post-production industries. It provides a comprehensive set of features and tools for monitoring, analyzing, and editing video footage. Nobe OmniScope is equipped with many powerful features to help classify colors easily. GPU acceleration, HDR support, StreamDeck. Use the benefits of GPU acceleration and monitor your images in real time with virtually no...
</description></item><item><title>Download dbForge Studio for SQL Server Enterprise 2025.2.91</title><pubDate> Sun, 02 Nov 2025 22:26:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbforge-studio-for-sql-server-4710.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbforge-studio-for-sql-server-4710.html
</guid><description>
dbForge Studio 2019 for SQL Server is the program that will help the developer SQL management database, change database version control in the source control system downloads, speed up routine tasks, as well as perform the change database complicated.
A handy tool to analyze the status of the index SQL and troubleshoot issues with fragmentation index. dbForge Studio 2019 for SQL Server allows you to quickly collect statistical data fragmentation index and the current database needs...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft Office Pro Plus - Online Installer 3.3.8</title><pubDate> Sun, 02 Nov 2025 22:26:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-office-professional-plus-x86-x64-online-installer-7661.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-office-professional-plus-x86-x64-online-installer-7661.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft Office 2021 Professional Plus x86-x64 - Online Installer is a small script that helps users to download and install Microsoft Office 2021 Professional Plus including all updates directly from Microsoft CDN Server.
The version of Office 2021 downloaded and installed on your computer will include the following programs: Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Outlook, OneNote, Publisher, Access, Visio, Project, ProofingTools, OneDrive Desktop.
Usage:
Unzip the downloaded ZIP Archive...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cutting Optimization Pro 5.18.16</title><pubDate> Sun, 02 Nov 2025 22:25:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cutting-optimization-pro-6573.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cutting-optimization-pro-6573.html
</guid><description>
Cutting Optimization Pro is a cutting software used to obtain the optimal cut layout for one-dimensional (1D) and two-dimensional (2D) pieces. The software also allows you to define and process complex products, such as desks, tables, cabinets, cabinets, bookshelves... Cutting Optimization Pro can be used to cut rectangular panels made of glass, wood, metal, plastic or any other material used in industrial applications.
Features of Cutting Optimization Pro
	Optimize 1D and 2D in the...
</description></item><item><title>Download High-Logic FontCreator Professional 15.0.0.3035</title><pubDate> Sun, 02 Nov 2025 22:24:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-high-logic-fontcreator-professional-1533.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-high-logic-fontcreator-professional-1533.html
</guid><description>
High-Logic FontCreator Professional allows you to create and edit TrueType fonts and OpenType. It has the powerful drawing tools that typographers and graphic designers require, and an intuitive interface that allows beginners to become productive immediately.
When you create or open a font, FontCreator displays an overview of all available characters. You can only add the characters missing, or select an existing character, and modify its appearance. You can import (scanned) signature...
</description></item></channel></rss>