<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 17:36:43 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 17:36:43 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Visual C++ Redistributable Runtimes AIO Repack 0.101.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Sep 2025 19:01:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-visual-c-redistributable-runtimes-aio-repack-7825.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-visual-c-redistributable-runtimes-aio-repack-7825.html
</guid><description>
Visual C++ Redistributable Runtimes AIO Repack is a setup package that includes all the latest Microsoft Visual C++ Redistribution Runtimes without the initial setup payload.
	Built on VBCRedis_AIO_x86_x64.exe
	This process is handled by a command set of windows command, which runs hidden in the background by default.
	Before installation, the script will check and remove the existing Visual C + + runtime settings, including the original EXE or MSI setup or the older MSI package...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft Visual C++ 2015-2022 Redistributable 14.50.35615</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Sep 2025 18:57:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-visual-c-4856.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-visual-c-4856.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft Visual C++ Redistributable Package contains the component run-time libraries of Visual C ++ required to run the application on a PC without installed Visual C ++. Microsoft Visual C++ or also known as MSVC development environment integrated (IDE) for the programming language C, C++, at the same time integrated tools for developing and debugging C++ source code. Microsoft Visual C++ supports the function of automatic completion of the coding and the debugging function...
</description></item><item><title>Download Glary Utilities Pro 6.32.0.36</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Sep 2025 18:57:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-utilities-pro-76.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-utilities-pro-76.html
</guid><description>
Glary Utilities Pro is a collection of tools and system utilities to fix, speed up, maintain and protect your computer. Glary Utilities Pro allows you to clean junk files, system downloads, as well as the subscriptions are not valid and Internet traces (that support the plug-in more for the 45+ program outside). You can also manage and delete add-ons of the browser, analyze the use of disk and find the file duplicate.
Glary Utilities Pro - optimized system
Key features Glary Utilities...
</description></item><item><title>Download Topaz Video AI Pro 7.1.6 / 1.0.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Sep 2025 18:56:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-video-enhance-ai-3733.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-video-enhance-ai-3733.html
</guid><description>
Topaz Video Enhance AI is a tool to increase video quality with this great technology ONE. Topaz Video Enhance WHO wide open your video to resolutions up to 8K with the details and consistency of motion. Until the present, there is no way to re-create a perfect high resolution video from the footage is low resolution. From the family film to SD low quality to DVD quality and more than that, Video Enhance WHO will convert your video into the footage is upgrade clear with resolutions up to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ant Download Manager Pro 2.15.11 Build 91423</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Sep 2025 18:55:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ant-download-manager-pro-137.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ant-download-manager-pro-137.html
</guid><description>
Ant Download Manager Pro is software support download has the same features as IDM, even it has many prominent features, more user friendly more and have speed download data incredible. Ant Download Manager is a Internet content downloader quickly with support download at video! Function: fully Integrated with the web browsers most popular: Internet Explorer 8+, Mozilla Firefox 32 +, Google Chrome 31+ and the copies of them (Pale Moon, Opera, Vivaldi, Slimjet, ComodoDragon, etc.). you...
</description></item><item><title>Download UPDF 2.0.9.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Sep 2025 18:54:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-updf-14160.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-updf-14160.html
</guid><description>
UPDF for Windows is easy-to-use PDF software for Windows! Enjoy powerful editing tools for text, images, links, and more in your PDFs. Customize backgrounds, watermarks, and page sizes as easily as in Word. AI-powered PDF editor and manager that offers a wide range of features including editing, annotating, converting, OCR (Optical Character Recognition), organizing, protecting, sharing, printing, summarizing, translating, and interpreting PDF files.
Features of UPDF
Analyze PDFs with...
</description></item><item><title>Download Zortam Mp3 Media Studio Pro 33.35</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Sep 2025 18:53:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zortam-mp3-media-studio-pro-135.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zortam-mp3-media-studio-pro-135.html
</guid><description>
Zortam Mp3 Media Studio Pro brings you rich processing tools music includes extract and convert music from CD to Mp3 format, edit, music cards, music download....You can also create discs CD high-quality music, with Zortam Mp3 Media Studio search music files duplicated to remove them from the system, rename music files, switch back and forth between formats.
Zortam Mp3 Media Studio Pro is rated as perfect software in the processing of the MP3 files on the computer. First of all, you can...
</description></item><item><title>Download SynthFont2 2.9.1.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Sep 2025 18:48:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-synthfont-3896.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-synthfont-3896.html
</guid><description>
SynthFont is a tool to play and edit the midi file with many documents, audio sources such as files, GigaSampler, SoundFonts, files, SFZ and more. Tools VST can also be used as a substitute for a material source of the sound. A midi file other with - for example - a songs MP3 in that file does not include any audio data whatsoever. The file is a set of notes and instructions on how to play them. SynthFont mixing this information with the audio data in a SoundFont to produce ("render") a...
</description></item><item><title>Download Glarysoft Malware Hunter Pro 1.206.0.837</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Sep 2025 18:48:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glarysoft-malware-hunter-pro-235.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glarysoft-malware-hunter-pro-235.html
</guid><description>
Glarysoft Malware Hunter capabilities, comprehensive protection against threats, data protection and privacy, ensure the computer is no longer virus. It allows you against many types of viruses, trojans with the ability to super fast scanning to detect and remove the malware quickly. Glarysoft Malware Hunter has a simple design of the interface, but the pace of new work is the most important problem of this software.
Features Glarysoft Malware Hunter Pro
	Automatically search, detect,...
</description></item><item><title>Download XnViewMP 1.9.4</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Sep 2025 18:48:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xnview-mp-1074.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xnview-mp-1074.html
</guid><description>
XnViewMP "XnView MP" is the enhanced version of XnView Classic. This is the view and convert images multi-platform powerful, compatible with more than 500 image formats, different today. XnView MP easily export images to about 70 file format is different. Similar to XnConvert, XnView MP also features integrated switch at the same time batch file to help you process photos faster. XnView is another version of the photo viewer but with the ability to support formats more limited.
XnView...
</description></item><item><title>Download Glary Malware Hunter PRO 1.206.0.837</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Sep 2025 18:47:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-malware-hunter-pro-77.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-malware-hunter-pro-77.html
</guid><description>
Glary Malware Hunter PRO - detection of file malware on your computer and delete dangerous content, allowing you to run on-demand scan of the area, important system or specific files. As suggested by its name, Malware Hunter is designed to find and remove the files and components potential danger on your computer, keep it out of the virus and the type of threat other.
Glary Malware Hunter PRO - perfect protection of your equipment
Features Glary Malware Hunter PRO
- Scan ultrasound...
</description></item><item><title>Download RapidRAW 1.4.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Sep 2025 18:03:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rapidraw-13957.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rapidraw-13957.html
</guid><description>
RapidRAW is a modern, high-performance, open-source RAW photo editor, designed to deliver a fast and clean editing experience with a lightweight footprint (under 30MB). Built with performance and usability in mind, the software is aimed at photographers who want a simple, efficient, and fun workflow without compromising performance.
Key Features
	GPU-accelerated processing: Uses a custom WGSL shader to process all image adjustments on the GPU, allowing for smooth, responsive editing...
</description></item><item><title>Download Battery Monitor 10.7</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Sep 2025 18:03:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-battery-monitor-1049.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-battery-monitor-1049.html
</guid><description>
Battery Monitor is a small utility that display on the computer screen the details current battery of laptop your as its name. The interface is based on a small frame can be moved to any location on the screen, with the help of the mouse cursor.
Battery Monitor is not popular and you can quickly get overview of the battery details while working in other apps. The main frame displays the clock and percent level, battery status, remaining time, charging speed and charging current. Battery...
</description></item><item><title>Download miniToggle 1.4.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Sep 2025 18:00:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minitoggle-12243.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minitoggle-12243.html
</guid><description>
miniToggle provides you with a user-friendly application designed to further simplify the process of modifying Explorer settings. With miniToggle, users can conveniently toggle the visibility of hidden files, show or hide file extensions, and empty the trash.
On the extended screen, you will be able to choose one of the three options above to do so by clicking the tray icon. It also has the option to toggle the Windows 11 context menu between the new and classic design.
With...
</description></item><item><title>Download ScreenToGif 2.42</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Sep 2025 17:58:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-screentogif-499.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-screentogif-499.html
</guid><description>
ScreenToGif is a software that allows you to capture anything on your screen and save it as animated GIF. Besides, ScreenToGif allows you can freely move the frame to record a video on your website or activity on the screen on the computer to your desk.
The recording can be paused and resumed and once you finish recording, the program will display a simple editing allows you to preview the recording and delete every frame is not necessary.
The downside is: Because ScreenToGif does not...
</description></item><item><title>Download BackUp Maker Pro 8.316</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Sep 2025 17:57:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-backup-maker-pro-480.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-backup-maker-pro-480.html
</guid><description>
BackUp Maker Pro is software backup, data recovery secure against hazards like virus attack, system error or due to the user mistakenly deleted data... BackUp Maker Pro security of your files regularly so that in case of emergency, data your computer you can still gain access. BackUp Maker automatically stores your data and at the same time provide intuitive operation: select your data, optionally set the automation to backup according to schedules, select the destination and immediately,...
</description></item><item><title>Download NewFileTime 8.11</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Sep 2025 17:56:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-newfiletime-1918.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-newfiletime-1918.html
</guid><description>
NewFileTime is a small utility independence allows you to change date modified, Created and Accessed of any file. You can modify the dates for one or multiple files, even entire folder structures at the same time. The date can be changed to a date and time specific or you can choose to make each file "older" or "younger," according to a certain number of days.
NewFileTime - edit time files
You can add files simply via Drag and Drop or by import from a folder. In any case, it opens...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinPE 11-10-8 Sergei Strelec 2025.09.29</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Sep 2025 17:56:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winpe-10-8-sergei-strelec-8027.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winpe-10-8-sergei-strelec-8027.html
</guid><description>
WinPE 11-10-8 Sergei Strelec is a Windows 11, 10 and 8 PE boot disk for computer maintenance, hard disks and partitions, disk and partition backup and restore, computer diagnostics, data recovery, installation Windows.
Assembly components include:
	WinPE 11 x64
	WinPE 10 x64
	WinPE 10 x86
	WinPE 8 x86
	WinPE 8 x86 (Native)
System Requirements:
1. RAM 1 GB or more
2. PC can boot from CD/DVD or USB drive.
</description></item><item><title>Download reaConverter Pro 8.0.138</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Sep 2025 17:55:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html
</guid><description>
reaConverter Pro is software image processing feature with batch conversion and image editing periodically becomes simple. eaConverter also provide command line utilities allow you to process images automatically, thus helping you shorten the time for other work.
reaConverter Pro integrated powerful tool of Uber with many great features. It provides advanced solutions to process and adjust images. Management of the conversion process the base image with the latest version of...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Downloader 9.17.7</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Sep 2025 17:55:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html
</guid><description>
YTD Youtube Downloader is an application that reliable and intuitive, allowing you to quickly download YouTube videos and save them to your computer. You can also convert the media files to the format desired video or extract audio streams and save separately. YTD Youtube Downloader lets you save your favorite clips of yourself from Youtube, Facebook, Vimeo and Dailymotion to your desktop. The software supports URLS from many web site hosting, multimedia and allows you to download desired...
</description></item><item><title>Download VidCoder 12.10 + Portable</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Sep 2025 17:54:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vidcoder-534.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vidcoder-534.html
</guid><description>
VidCoder is software to convert movies to MKV and MP4, as well as extract video content from DVDS and Blu-ray. This is a software utility to help people extract the video content from the BD and DVD as well as convert the clips specific to MKV and MP4.
VidCoder has an interface that includes a clear design, including a menu bar, several buttons and a panel to display the queue. The file can be added with the help of the file browser or drag and drop-out.
Features VidCoder
	VidCoder...
</description></item><item><title>Download Windows Repair Toolbox 3.0.4.8</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Sep 2025 17:54:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-repair-toolbox-2225.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-repair-toolbox-2225.html
</guid><description>
Windows Repair Toolbox is a development that will solve almost all the problems with Windows. There is a mobile version in the repository, after the folder launch of it will be created in program files, but after you close it, everything will be deleted.
Windows Repair Toolbox - diagnose the problem on windows
Utilities can diagnose and solve a number of problems about your video Windows at the same time. All the tools are divided into categories. In The tools section, you can view a...
</description></item><item><title>Download Dassault Systemes DraftSight Enterprise Plus 2025 SP4</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Sep 2025 17:53:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-draftsight-enterprise-plus-4057.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-draftsight-enterprise-plus-4057.html
</guid><description>
DraftSight Enterprise Plus solution is a 2D and 3D CAD feature-rich for architects, engineers and suppliers of construction services, as well as user professional CAD designers, educators and hobbyists. Options, options and tools consistent with the needs and specific interests of you. Freedom of design is really lets you work the way you want to work. It is the ability to easily switch from 2D sketch to 3D models and back to optimize and maximize the design.
DraftSight Enterprise Plus...
</description></item><item><title>Download Desktop Info 3.21.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Sep 2025 17:53:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktop-info-11667.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktop-info-11667.html
</guid><description>
Desktop Info is a free application for Windows that allows users to display system information and important parameters directly on their desktop. This application provides a convenient way to monitor parameters such as CPU, memory, hard drive, network, and many other information that users want to monitor continuously.
With a simple and easy-to-use interface, Desktop Info allows users to customize the information displayed according to their wishes. Users can select...
</description></item><item><title>Download AnyTrans for iOS 8.9.12.20250928</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Sep 2025 17:52:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anytrans-for-ios-755.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anytrans-for-ios-755.html
</guid><description>
AnyTrans for iOS is content manager essential fully managed iPhone, Android and content of your cloud. Including all mobile devices, all cloud drives from your iPhone, iPad, iPod touch to phones and tablets. From local disk to cloud storage. AnyTrans has protected them all, providing you convenient management for all data and your files, regardless of whether they are stored where.
AnyTrans is the one stop solution to meet all the management needs of your data. For the first time, you can...
</description></item></channel></rss>