<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 17:37:35 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 17:37:35 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download WinRAR 7.20 Beta 1 / 7.13 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 20:32:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winrar-127.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winrar-127.html
</guid><description>
WinRAR is a compression utility data advanced supports multiple formats including RAR, ZIP, CAB, ARJ, LZH, ACE, TAR, GZip, UUE, ISO, BZIP2, Z and 7-Zip. It allows you to create, organize and manage archives in a comfortable way and quickly. WinRAR naturally are is a leading software currently in the compression and decompression of data. With the enhanced algorithm is applied, the software allows users to compress bulk files in different formats into synthetic 1 single file to facilitate...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare PDFelement Pro 12.0.8.3784</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 20:30:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-pdfelement-pro-105.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-pdfelement-pro-105.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare PDFelement Pro support users to convert PDF to office documents for easier use, modify in every situation. Is one of the software conversion material is rated best today, integrated with many features. We recommend that you should use experience software many useful features this.
Wondershare PDFelement Pro - conversion Fie PDF more features, multi-language
Wondershare PDFelement Pro what?
Convert PDF into Word, Excel, PowerPoint...
• Convert PDF and protected PDF into...
</description></item><item><title>Download Winxvideo AI 4.5.0.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 20:29:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winxvideo-ai-10981.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winxvideo-ai-10981.html
</guid><description>
Winxvideo AI is an innovative video editing app that leverages the power of artificial intelligence to provide users with advanced video editing capabilities. With advanced features and a user-friendly interface, Winxvideo AI is designed to streamline the video editing process and empower creators to create professional-quality videos.
Winxvideo AI meets all your audio/video conversion needs and compresses your 4K/8K footage from GB to MB without compromising on quality, powered by...
</description></item><item><title>Download Enolsoft PDF Password Remover 2.2.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 20:28:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-enolsoft-pdf-password-remover-14100.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-enolsoft-pdf-password-remover-14100.html
</guid><description>
Enolsoft PDF Password Remover helps users remove password protection from both user password protected PDF and owner password protected PDF, allowing you to edit, copy and print files freely.
What are Permission Password and Open Password?
There are two types of PDF passwords that can protect PDF files.
	Open/User Password: The PDF's open/user password is always used to control the access rights of PDF files to ensure security. If you forget the password, brute force attack will be...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cisdem PDF Compressor 3.3.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 20:28:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cisdem-pdf-compressor-8690.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cisdem-pdf-compressor-8690.html
</guid><description>
Cisdem PDF Compressor is a software application that allows users to compress PDF files without losing content quality. The software can reduce the size of PDF files by up to 90%, making it easier to share and store them across multiple devices or online platforms. In addition, Cisdem PDF Compressor has a batch processing function, allowing users to compress multiple PDF files at the same time. The software also includes several compression settings that can be customized to achieve the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Zoom Player Max 22.0 Beta 3</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 20:27:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zoom-player-max-104.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zoom-player-max-104.html
</guid><description>
Zoom Player MAX help you to see the film on DVD, Blu-ray, Flash movies and HD format with high quality and the ability to display subtitles in English very well. The advantage of software is that takes up very little system resources to play the movie with quick speed, change the wallpaper options while viewing movies.
Zoom Player MAX is the movies, browse high-quality photos on the computer with the advantages such as compact size, quick start, built-in codec. The application supports...
</description></item><item><title>Download Enolsoft PDF Compressor 2.2.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 20:27:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-enolsoft-pdf-compressor-14099.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-enolsoft-pdf-compressor-14099.html
</guid><description>
Enolsoft PDF Compressor is a software tool designed to significantly reduce the size of PDF files without losing the original quality. After reducing the size of the PDF file, the storage requirements will automatically decrease. As a result, you can store more files easily! Usually, when we receive a notification that the drive is low on space, we often choose to delete unnecessary files or increase storage capacity.
With Enolsoft PDF Compressor, you can set the compression size...
</description></item><item><title>Download ToDoList 9.1.5.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 20:27:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-todolist-1637.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-todolist-1637.html
</guid><description>
ToDoList is an application note and task management with multiple options, set up help you to easily split and track the progress of the work. Todolist helps millions of people feel in control of their lives more and be the leader in a number of organizations inspired the world to believe. Todolist keep all to-dos of I in one place and perfectly integrated with the other tools that I use. It helps me turn everything faster.
ToDoList - management software job
Every day you have to...
</description></item><item><title>Download DesktopOK 12.21</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 20:26:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopok-1635.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopok-1635.html
</guid><description>
DesktopOK is software save and restore the positions of icons. DesktopOK also offers a solution small but effective for the user to change the screen resolution often. DesktopOK is not installed and can be executed easily from the desktop, and can be carried on a small USB or memory device to another. Start of the program. The first time you use the program, the program will show you screen license. Free program and license info is only displayed the first time (on each PC).
DesktopOK -...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cisdem PDF Password Remover 2.4.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 20:23:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cisdem-pdf-password-remover-9223.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cisdem-pdf-password-remover-9223.html
</guid><description>
Cisdem PDF Password Remover is a software tool designed to help users remove passwords and restrictions from PDF files. It is an easy to use PDF password remover to help users unlock password protected PDF files, removing restrictions on opening, printing, editing and copying instantly. No loss of quality of the original files.
Overall, Cisdem PDF Password Remover is a useful tool for users who need to remove passwords and restrictions from PDF files quickly and easily. Its batch...
</description></item><item><title>Download Pulsar Audio IPA 25 1.0.14</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 20:22:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pulsar-audio-ipa-25-14071.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pulsar-audio-ipa-25-14071.html
</guid><description>
Pulsar Audio's IPA 25 is a classic VCA compressor emulation plugin, specifically inspired by the API 2500, providing a flexible multi-VCA dynamics system with modern control options for the engineer.
Key Features
	Faithful VCA modeling delivers classic tone with advanced control beyond the hardware limits.
	Modular signal flow and intuitive controls, allowing allows users to switch between different VCA circuits for more diverse sounds.
	Multi-circuit design: Provides both native...
</description></item><item><title>Download WiFi Direct + 10.0.20</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 19:48:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wifi-direct-10153.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wifi-direct-10153.html
</guid><description>
Wi-Fi Direct is a Wi-Fi standard for peer-to-peer wireless connections that allows two devices to establish a direct Wi-Fi connection without the need for an intermediate wireless access point, router, or Internet connection.
Features of WiFi Direct +
	Fast
	Completely free, no intrusive ads.
	Supports all file transfers.
	Supports multiple file transfers.
	Supports folder transfer.
	Supports file transfer to and from external sdcard.
	Tested on many devices.
	Advanced file chooser.
</description></item><item><title>Download FBReader Premium 3.8.20</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 19:47:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-fbreader-premium-8512.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-fbreader-premium-8512.html
</guid><description>
FBReader Premium is an e-book reading application for mobile devices. It provides a convenient way to read e-books on your phone or tablet and offers several features to enhance your reading experience. FBReader supports synchronization of your library and/or reading locations with the FBReader book network (https://books.fbreader.org/), a cloud service based on Google Drive™. Sync is disabled by default; To enable and configure it, use the options dialog.
This reader also includes a...
</description></item><item><title>Download Duolingo: language lessons 6.53.3</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 19:47:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-duolingo-language-lessons-8265.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-duolingo-language-lessons-8265.html
</guid><description>
Duolingo is a popular language learning app that offers interactive lessons to help users learn new languages. This application offers many languages for you to choose from, including Spanish, French, German, Italian, Portuguese, Chinese, Japanese and many more.
This app offers an gamified learning experience with interactive lessons, exercises, and quizzes designed to help users learn new words, phrases, and grammar rules. This app is designed to be easy to use and suitable for people...
</description></item><item><title>Download Bluetooth Codec Changer 1.7.3 build 1091</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 19:47:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-bluetooth-codec-changer-8542.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-bluetooth-codec-changer-8542.html
</guid><description>
Bluetooth Codec Changer is a technology used to encode and decode audio data transmitted over a Bluetooth connection. Improve audio quality and latency by controlling the Bluetooth device decoder. You have complete control over the A2DP Profile Decoder for your Bluetooth headset.
Features of Bluetooth Codec Changer
	Automatically switch codecs when you connect a Bluetooth device.
	Manage your different devices with different codec profiles and swap between them without any...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sound meter: SPL &amp;amp; dB meter 11.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 19:47:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sound-meter-spl-db-meter-12187.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sound-meter-spl-db-meter-12187.html
</guid><description>
Sound meter: SPL &amp;amp; dB meter is a sound pressure level meter (SPL meter), noise level meter, decibel meter (dB meter), sound level meter or sound meter. This is a very useful application for performing sound tests or measuring environmental noise (noise testing). It uses a smartphone or tablet's microphone to measure environmental noise in decibels (dB). The decibel(dB) value of this noise meter or sound meter may differ from the actual Sound Meter (DB Meter). Now you can easily...
</description></item><item><title>Download AVG Cleaner - Storage Cleaner 25.21.0 build 800011284</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 19:46:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-avg-cleaner-storage-cleaner-9005.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-avg-cleaner-storage-cleaner-9005.html
</guid><description>
AVG Cleaner is a memory cleaning and optimization application developed by AVG Technologies. It is designed to help users reclaim space on their Android devices by deleting unnecessary files and optimizing system performance.
The app can scan your device for junk files, including temporary files, cache files, and outdated APK files, and help you delete them safely. Additionally, AVG Cleaner can analyze your device's battery consumption and provide suggestions on how to improve your...
</description></item><item><title>Download FotMob - Soccer Live Scores 217.14873.20251022.rc</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 19:46:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-fotmob-soccer-live-scores-8241.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-fotmob-soccer-live-scores-8241.html
</guid><description>
FotMob gives you all the live scores, stats and storylines to help you keep up with the world of football. Personalized news and notifications make it easy to follow your favorite teams and players. And lightning-fast match updates ensure you never miss a goal, no matter where you are.
Features of FotMob - Live soccer scores
	Live match score
	Results, schedule, standings and lineup
	Detailed statistics, including expected goals (xG) and expected assists (xA)
	Capture map
	Player...
</description></item><item><title>Download 9GAG: Funny GIF, Meme &amp;amp; Video 8.16.3</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 19:46:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-9gag-funny-gif-meme-video-11500.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-9gag-funny-gif-meme-video-11500.html
</guid><description>
9GAG has the best funny, cute, weird, wacky, cosplay photos, GIFs, videos, memes, photos on the web. We are your greatest and happiest source. With millions of visitors every day, 9GAG is an application that helps you play LOL, kill time and make new friends around the world.
9GAG features
	The 9GAG app loads quickly and allows for easy scrolling. Don't waste time picking me up or just having a good laugh.
	Carry unlimited fun in your pocket. Enjoy 9GAG anytime, anywhere and...
</description></item><item><title>Download BSPlayer Pro 3.24.253-20251027</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 19:45:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-bsplayer-pro-10820.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-bsplayer-pro-10820.html
</guid><description>
This is the full version of BSPlayer for Android media player with full functionality. BSPlayer is a media player for Android devices: smartphones and tablets, supporting hardware accelerated video decoding, automatic subtitle search and buffered network playback from SMB shares.
BSPlayer Pro main features
	Available ONLY in the full version: experimental support for Chromecast (most mp4s are supported)
	NO ADS
	Hardware accelerated video playback - significantly increases playback...
</description></item><item><title>Download Elevate - Brain Training Games 5.212.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 19:44:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-elevate-brain-training-games-8564.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-elevate-brain-training-games-8564.html
</guid><description>
Elevate is a brain training program designed to improve speech, processing speed, memory skills, mental math, and more. Each person is provided with their own personalized learning program, which is adjusted over time to maximize results.
The more you practice with Elevate, the more you'll improve key cognitive skills proven to increase productivity, earning potential, and confidence. More than 90% said their vocabulary, memory, math skills and overall acuity improved when they...
</description></item><item><title>Download Screen Recorder: Facecam Audio 2.7.3</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 19:44:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-screen-recorder-facecam-audio-14043.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-screen-recorder-facecam-audio-14043.html
</guid><description>
Facecam, the all-in-one screen recording solution for anyone who wants to easily record and share content, apps, gaming actions and even their reactions in real-time! With a host of powerful features and a user-friendly interface, this video recording app has revolutionized video recording, making it faster and easier than ever!
Screen Recorder - Facetime Recorder!
Screen Recorder: Facetime Recorder lets you record what you're playing and yourself with a real-time camera recorder. With...
</description></item><item><title>Download Stick - Remote Control For TV 3.13</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 19:44:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-stick-remote-control-for-tv-12980.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-stick-remote-control-for-tv-12980.html
</guid><description>
Stick is a TV remote control app that turns your phone into a TV remote control! Now you have a universal TV remote that you can connect to TV models like Samsung TV remote, LG TV remote, Sony TV remote, Vizio TV remote, TCL TV remote, Insignia TV remote, Hisense TV remote, Roku TV remote, etc.
Some notable features
	Perfect for LG TV remote, TCL TV remote, Android TV remote and Samsung TV remote: Easily change channels, adjust volume and use menus on LG remote and Samsung TV...
</description></item><item><title>Download Hermit - Lite Apps Browser 31.0.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 19:43:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-hermit-lite-apps-browser-9896.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-hermit-lite-apps-browser-9896.html
</guid><description>
Hermit APK is a professional web browser with great built-in features that extend users' operations and productivity to new heights by allowing them to explore optimized applications and functions. good optimization. In addition, it automatically helps users search for Lite version specialized applications that they can use in the browser to save a lot of performance. It also includes integration of more extensions to take user personalization to the next level while exploring or...
</description></item><item><title>Download Money Manager Expense &amp;amp; Budget 4.10.3 GF build 1123</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 19:43:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-money-manager-expense-budget-13837.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-money-manager-expense-budget-13837.html
</guid><description>
Money Manager - the #1 financial planning, budgeting, expense tracking and personal wealth management app for Android! Money Manager makes managing your personal finances as easy as pie! Now you can easily record personal and business financial transactions, generate spending reports, review daily, weekly and monthly financial data and manage your assets with Money Manager's spending tracker and budget planner.
Key Features
- Adopt double-entry bookkeeping system
Money Manager...
</description></item></channel></rss>