<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 23:52:09 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 23:52:09 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download CrystalDiskInfo 9.8.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 16 Feb 2026 00:41:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-crystaldiskinfo-1683.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-crystaldiskinfo-1683.html
</guid><description>
CrystalDiskInfo is a software to monitor and evaluate status of hard drive a way the most accurate, simple, fast and compact. CrystalDiskInfo will help you complete peace of mind when always know hard drive of his computer are in any situation. The software let you know the status of the hard drive, how when operating, to avoid the risks that can be foreseen, most discs contain important data.
CrystalDiskInfo - See information hard drive
Some function information of...
</description></item><item><title>Download HFS: HTTP File Server (version 3) 3.0.3</title><pubDate> Mon, 16 Feb 2026 00:39:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hfs-http-file-server-11851.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hfs-http-file-server-11851.html
</guid><description>
HFS is a web file server to run on your computer. Share a folder or even a file thanks to the virtual file system. Essentially, this application turns your computer into an HTTP server and all users who want to connect and download files can do so by loading a simple website in their browser. HFS includes many configuration settings, so you can basically change each part of the application, starting with how users download files and ending with the appearance of the created website.
HFS...
</description></item><item><title>Download Prevent Restore Pro 2026 v118</title><pubDate> Mon, 16 Feb 2026 00:38:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-prevent-restore-pro-1473.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-prevent-restore-pro-1473.html
</guid><description>
Prevent Restore Pro is software prevent restore files deleted in any drive: external hard drives and hard drives mounted in hard drive, SSD, Flash drives, except CD-ROM and CD-RW. The software uses many security algorithms can be used to get data.Our program includes some of the most reliable and accepted as standard.
Prevent Restore Pro - Prevent restore files deleted
The features of Prevent Restore Pro
Mode to clean up quickly
	In this mode, the program will not overwrite the free...
</description></item><item><title>Download NIUBI Partition Editor Technician Edition 10.3.0 Pro / Enterprise / Server / Unlimited</title><pubDate> Mon, 16 Feb 2026 00:37:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-niubi-partition-editor-technician-edition-3332.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-niubi-partition-editor-technician-edition-3332.html
</guid><description>
System drive C becomes full and no free space to install Updates or applications? Don't worry, NIUBI Partition Editor Technician Edition helps you solve this problem easily. Better other utilities, management software partition magic this integrated technology, data protection, Roll-Back, unique, can automatically put the computer back to the state before the change size in A second, if error occurs, software or hardware malfunction, so you don't need to worry about data safety. Algorithm...
</description></item><item><title>Download PortKiller 3.3.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 16 Feb 2026 00:36:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-portkiller-14468.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-portkiller-14468.html
</guid><description>
PortKiller is not just a tool for closing ports — it's a cross-platform solution for monitoring and managing ports with powerful functionality. It listens to all TCP ports, identifies active processes, and displays detailed information about each process. Specifically designed for software developers and network administrators, PortKiller goes beyond simple port monitoring and process termination: it lets you filter by process type, simplify process management, handle Kubernetes port...
</description></item><item><title>Download Personal Backup 6.4.7.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 16 Feb 2026 00:35:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-personal-backup-1117.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-personal-backup-1117.html
</guid><description>
Personal Backup is software to backup data on computer hard drive professional with the ability to copy data on the hard drive and save any folder. Personal Backup is the most optimal solutions to ensure safety for data on avoid computer viruses, malicious code, intrusion and data loss because you can restore lost data at any time if it has to be backed up and stored on the folder of the computer.
Personal Backup - backup computer data
Features of Personal Backup
	Backup cross data...
</description></item><item><title>Download Let It Be Light 2.0.13</title><pubDate> Mon, 16 Feb 2026 00:33:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-let-it-be-light-13761.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-let-it-be-light-13761.html
</guid><description>
Let It Be Light – Illuminate the Invisible, Unleash Infinite Content! Tired of dark, underexposed footage that could be your next viral hit? Say hello to Let It Be Light – revolutionary AI image and video processing software that turns dull clips into beautiful, well-lit masterpieces!
Why Let It Be Light?
	Unlock Hidden Content – ​​Turn dark, grainy, or underexposed footage from film, old archives, or social media into crisp, bright, and useful content. No more discarding...
</description></item><item><title>Download eM Client Pro 10.4.4756</title><pubDate> Mon, 16 Feb 2026 00:33:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-em-client-pro-953.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-em-client-pro-953.html
</guid><description>
eM Client Pro is an email app full features with modern interface. eM Client offers calendar, tasks, contacts and chat. Software is best Email app for windows today. eM Client supports all major services including Gmail, Exchange, iCloud and Outlook.com. You can find more information in the server part on our website.
eM Client Pro - the best email App for windows
eM Client is very simple , can automatically set everything up for most of the services. It is also effective to import...
</description></item><item><title>Download Scale Photo Up 2.0.13</title><pubDate> Mon, 16 Feb 2026 00:32:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-scale-photo-up-13763.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-scale-photo-up-13763.html
</guid><description>
Are you tired of low-resolution, pixelated footage that stifles your creativity? Say goodbye to grainy memories and say hello to Scale Photo Up – groundbreaking AI software that doubles resolution, enhances detail, and smooths out imperfections in your photos and videos with stunning clarity!
Why Scale Photo Up?
	Upscale 2x – No loss of quality! – Turn blurry, low-resolution photos and videos into sharp, high-resolution masterpieces. Perfect for breathing new life into old...
</description></item><item><title>Download Retail Barcode 5.8</title><pubDate> Mon, 16 Feb 2026 00:31:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-retail-barcode-2586.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-retail-barcode-2586.html
</guid><description>
Retail Barcode a product of genuine VovSoft, is a cashier app can help users track product sales. This tool allows a person to identify customers, as well as affiliate sales of credit products to individual customers. This utility has value to any who are trading in the management of small shops. It is an ideal solution for the small shop faced with many types of products to be processed. Stores that don't stock items with barcodes can avoid this problem by simply creating a custom code...
</description></item><item><title>Download Secure Eraser Pro 7.101</title><pubDate> Mon, 16 Feb 2026 00:30:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secure-eraser-1003.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secure-eraser-1003.html
</guid><description>
Secure Eraser is a software to delete data permanently on the folder of the hard drive to data can not be recovered by any software. Secure Eraser is software delete data completely best. The software has simple interface and very small capacity. In addition, the software Secure Eraser also helps to tidy and clean the system, prevent the fragmentation of the hard drive.
Secure Eraser - Tool To Delete Data Permanently
Secure Eraser supports 4 standard delete data (US DoD 5220,22-ME, US...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sononym Sample Browser 1.6.4</title><pubDate> Mon, 16 Feb 2026 00:29:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sononym-7921.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sononym-7921.html
</guid><description>
Sononym is a sample browser that offers a fresh look at how sounds can be discovered and organized. Sononym analyzes a folder and all available information like: tempo, pitch, amount of noise, content, etc. - is collected from your file and stored in the database. This ensures quick accessibility as you search, filter, and sort your way through a large variety of templates.
Sononym supports similarity search allowing you to find samples with similar sounds in your sample collection....
</description></item><item><title>Download X1 Search Enterprise 10.2 Revision 19</title><pubDate> Mon, 16 Feb 2026 00:29:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-x1-search-enterprise-11828.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-x1-search-enterprise-11828.html
</guid><description>
Why should you use X1 Search?
Do you spend valuable time individually searching through Microsoft Outlook, OneDrive, SharePoint, Teams, Google Drive, Gmail and more without being able to find what you're looking for? With X1 Search, you can instantly search across emails, attachments, documents, local files, M365 data, including Teams Chat and Channels, and more, and find the exact information you need. with a single command, across all your data sources, saving you hours every...
</description></item><item><title>Download Spencer 1.36</title><pubDate> Mon, 16 Feb 2026 00:28:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-spencer-1881.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-spencer-1881.html
</guid><description>
Spencer provide an easy way to bring start Menu Windows XP classic for Windows 8 your. This program is a standalone application and requires no installation. Just copy the file spencer.exe to desktop your and click that file to display a menu with all Menu items, start your current.
Spencer - Create Menu Windows XP classic
If you want to integrate it into your taskbar to make it look like the start Button is actually more, you can choose the option "Pin to taskbar" from right click...
</description></item><item><title>Download Display Driver Uninstaller (DDU) 18.1.4.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 15 Feb 2026 14:57:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-display-driver-uninstaller-1999.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-display-driver-uninstaller-1999.html
</guid><description>
Display Driver Uninstaller (DDU) help to easily completely remove the packages and drivers graphics cards AMD, NVIDIA and Intel from your system without leaving any rest whatsoever. Display Driver Uninstaller will automatically detect your current GPU and allows you to delete drivers, registry and files related only by the click of a button. It will also prevent Windows automatically re-install drivers when you reboot your computer, leaving you a drivers graphics common until you install...
</description></item><item><title>Download K-Lite Codec Pack Update 19.4.9</title><pubDate> Sun, 15 Feb 2026 14:56:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-update-5145.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-update-5145.html
</guid><description>
K-Lite Codec Pack Update is the update of the set of codecs and related tools. Codec stands for Compressor-decompressor. Codec is necessary to encode and decode (play) audio and video. K-Lite Codec Pack Update is designed as a user-friendly solution with users to play all movie files your. With Codec Pack K-Lite, you can play 99% of all the movies found on your computer. A number of packages codec is not friendly with computers, as they tend to slow down Windows, break down multimedia...
</description></item><item><title>Download Alfa eBooks Manager Pro / Web 9.4.20.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 15 Feb 2026 14:55:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-alfa-ebooks-manager-web-981.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-alfa-ebooks-manager-web-981.html
</guid><description>
Alfa eBooks Manager Web is a program that enables to arrange the electronic books and paper of you in a single electronic library. eBooks Manager Website will host the electronic books and print in an electronic library. Group, filter and sort books by multiple parameters. Find any book in just a second by title, author or ISBN.
Alfa eBooks Manager Web - ebook library
Alfa eBooks Manager Web provides comprehensive set of fields, including the author, category, publisher, series, ISBN,...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube Downloader 3.9.18 (1402)</title><pubDate> Sun, 15 Feb 2026 14:54:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube Downloader  is a dedicated software that helps users  downloading youtube videos  Favorites on PC for offline viewing. With MediaHuman YouTube  Downloader  you can download videos from youtube website to your computer with  fast speed , with special software development technology that automatically receives videos from Websites, in addition to the ability to download videos from software websites, can convert downloaded video formats to various formats for the purpose...
</description></item><item><title>Download iZotope RX 11 Audio Editor Advanced 11.4.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 15 Feb 2026 14:53:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-izotope-rx-audio-editor-advanced-8619.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-izotope-rx-audio-editor-advanced-8619.html
</guid><description>
iZotope RX10 Audio Editor Advanced is professional audio editing software designed for sound restoration, post-production and sound design. It provides users with advanced tools and technologies to clean, repair and enhance recordings. The software's combination of advanced tools and technologies makes it a valuable tool for professional sound engineers and post-production professionals.
Features of iZotope RX10 Audio Editor Advanced
	Audio Restoration: The ability to repair and...
</description></item><item><title>Download NTFS Permissions Reporter Enterprise 5.2.653</title><pubDate> Sun, 15 Feb 2026 14:52:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ntfs-permissions-reporter-enterprise-6370.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ntfs-permissions-reporter-enterprise-6370.html
</guid><description>
System administrators are constantly required to check user rights for specific files and folders. This is often a time-consuming work, with multiple NTFS classes and repetitive adjustments over time creating a security maze. NTFS Permissions Reporter Enterprise allows you to confirm the security status of the entire file system quickly and efficiently. All have multiple export formats, command line support, integration scheduling, advanced filtration, and more.
Features of NTFS...
</description></item><item><title>Download DBF Recovery 4.66</title><pubDate> Sun, 15 Feb 2026 14:52:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbf-recovery-7931.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbf-recovery-7931.html
</guid><description>
DBF Recovery is software that gives users the ability to restore a damaged database back to its original condition without the expertise required to complete that task. It fixes headers and data structures in an automated process that doesn't involve user interaction. With DBF Recovery, you will truly have a lean, honest DBF repair machine without any functionality.
Features of DBF Recovery
	Quick and simple to use DBF file repair software.
	Repair almost any DBF...
</description></item><item><title>Download MSI Afterburner 4.6.7.16935 Beta 2</title><pubDate> Sun, 15 Feb 2026 14:50:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-msi-afterburner-1075.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-msi-afterburner-1075.html
</guid><description>
MSI Afterburner is overclocking software to speed up computer graphics card to increase gaming performance, support for spin off video card downloads. MSI Afterburner is a utility graphics card that supports users to track the status of the GPU and use the GPU with the maximum performance. Core application MSI Afterburner is based on RivaTuner - software overclocking graphics card top. The program is designed to enhance the performance of the GPU and support multiple graphics cards MSI...
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 7.9.9</title><pubDate> Sun, 15 Feb 2026 14:49:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-11-7760.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-11-7760.html
</guid><description>
TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 is a program that allows users to discover hidden settings in Windows 11. This application is specially designed for Windows 11, groups many registry settings and distribute them from the easy and secure user interface. With TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 you can move the Windows taskbar to the top and resize the taskbar by editing the registry value. With any application that modifies the registry, we recommend that you have a backup copy...
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 7.9.9</title><pubDate> Sun, 15 Feb 2026 14:49:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-10-7759.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-10-7759.html
</guid><description>
TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 is a utility that allows users to discover hidden settings in Windows 10. This application is specially designed for Windows 10, groups many registry settings and provide them from an easy and secure user interface. With TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 you can move the Windows taskbar to the top and resize the taskbar by editing the registry value. With any application that modifies the registry, we recommend that you have a backup copy to...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter 3.9.18 (1402)</title><pubDate> Sun, 15 Feb 2026 14:48:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-to-mp3-converter-1744.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-to-mp3-converter-1744.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter is the software support download youtube video and convert video to mp3 format fast and most simple. MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter allows you download and convert videos from YouTube and other websites to MP3 format by pasting the YouTube URL into the application. When you paste the URL, the program will display thumbnails for videos and you have the option to customize the title information, artist and album before you begin the process of...
</description></item></channel></rss>