<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 19:57:01 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 19:57:01 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Download Master 7.1.3.1735</title><pubDate> Fri, 29 Aug 2025 22:51:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-download-master-2005.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-download-master-2005.html
</guid><description>
Download Master is a software to improve the speed of file download from the Internet. Download Master replace the standard module of the load in the popular browsers such as Google Chrome, Firefox, Safari, Yandex.Browser, Opera, Internet Explorer etc. The software support download the file from the current position after the break of the network connection. Download Master lets you download videos or music from various services and have the priority function of the load. The software...
</description></item><item><title>Download Broot 1.48.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 29 Aug 2025 22:48:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-broot-8588.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-broot-8588.html
</guid><description>
Broot is an open source command line tool for browsing and navigating file systems. Broot provides a fast and intuitive way to navigate the file system with a tree-like interactive interface. It provides various features like searching for files, opening files and folders, copying file paths to clipboard, etc. It also supports customizing keys and color themes.
Features of Broot
	Fast file browsing: Lets you quickly navigate through large directory structures with a tree-like...
</description></item><item><title>Download Realtek High Definition Audio Drivers 6.0.9865.1 WHQL</title><pubDate> Fri, 29 Aug 2025 22:44:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-realtek-high-definition-audio-drivers-r282-32bit-64bit-442.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-realtek-high-definition-audio-drivers-r282-32bit-64bit-442.html
</guid><description>
Realtek High Definition Audio Drivers is audio drivers Realtek high-quality latest for windows operating systems, virgin audio controller is based on Realtek for Windows 7/8/8.1/10. When the window is integrated this Driver will make the sound of computer, laptop, your back up crisp, and the sound output for the highest quality possible.
Realtek High Definition Audio Drivers and devices are supported :
ALC880, ALC882, ALC883, ALC885, ALC888, ALC889, ALC861VC, ALC861VD, ALC892, ALC663,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare UniConverter 16.7.0.368</title><pubDate> Fri, 29 Aug 2025 22:44:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-uniconverter-4808.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-uniconverter-4808.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare UniConverter ( old name is Wondershare Video Converter Ultimate) which allows you to convert the video format. You can cut, splice, move, or add effects, subtitles a easy way. When using software you easily cut, splice, move, as well as add the effects, the subtitles to the video.... Or can switch the clods SD, HD video to any format popular for use with iPod (Classic, Nano and Touch), iPhone, Apple TV, Zune, PSP, Pocket PC...
Wondershare UniConverter helps convert formats...
</description></item><item><title>Download iTubeGo YouTube Downloader 10.8.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 29 Aug 2025 22:43:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-itubego-youtube-downloader-3681.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-itubego-youtube-downloader-3681.html
</guid><description>
iTubeGo YouTube Downloader  is the best way to download live video from 1000+ streaming sites. iTubeGo YouTube Downloader is a powerful download tool that allows you to save video and audio for free. The output format of high speed converter is high quality MP4, MP3. Fully compatible with iPhone, iPad, iTunes, iMovie, Android Phone and more.
iTubeGo YouTube Downloader - Solution for downloading high quality Youtube video 
Features of iTubeGo YouTube Downloader
	Download videos from...
</description></item><item><title>Download XYplorer 27.10.0700</title><pubDate> Fri, 29 Aug 2025 22:43:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-533.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-533.html
</guid><description>
XYplorer - File Manager for Windows is software that supports users to manage files on the Window quickly and to arrange the folder tidy. XYplorer features tabbed browsing, search, files, powerful, preview, flexible, highly customizable interface, dual frame options and a variety of unique ways to automate effective tasks often repeat. It's fast, lightweight, and portable.
Features XYplorer
	XYplorer is a file manager mobile. It does not require any settings, store all configuration...
</description></item><item><title>Download HFS: HTTP File Server (version 3) 0.57.14</title><pubDate> Fri, 29 Aug 2025 22:42:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hfs-http-file-server-11851.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hfs-http-file-server-11851.html
</guid><description>
HFS is a web file server to run on your computer. Share a folder or even a file thanks to the virtual file system. Essentially, this application turns your computer into an HTTP server and all users who want to connect and download files can do so by loading a simple website in their browser. HFS includes many configuration settings, so you can basically change each part of the application, starting with how users download files and ending with the appearance of the created website.
HFS...
</description></item><item><title>Download HE - Hardware Read and Write Utility 1.25.08.29</title><pubDate> Fri, 29 Aug 2025 22:42:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-he-hardware-read-and-write-utility-4287.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-he-hardware-read-and-write-utility-4287.html
</guid><description>
HE - Hardware Read and Write Utility is a powerful utility intended for hardware engineer, engineer, BIOS developer, driver, engineer, QA engineers, performance test engineers, diagnostic, etc., this utility access almost all the computer hardware, including PCI (PCI Express), index / Data, PCI, memory, index memory / Data space I / O, Index I / O / Data, Super I / O, DIMM SPD, CPU The registers MSR, screen, SMART, physical area of the hard drive identification data, ATA, dump tables ACPI...
</description></item><item><title>Download LibreOffice 25.8.1 / 7.6.7</title><pubDate> Fri, 29 Aug 2025 22:41:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-libreoffice-391.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-libreoffice-391.html
</guid><description>
LibreOffice is editor free for office similar to MS Office and OpenOffice includes word processor, spreadsheet application, presentation tool, database and design diagrams. Here is the app code open source, multi-feature, to offer users many tools to draft documents and handle the office documents efficiently.
The program can open or import most Microsoft Office formats popular, including .doc .ppt and .csv as well as many document formats other. LibreOffice is a tool to be more user...
</description></item><item><title>Download Aiseesoft Screen Recorder 3.1.32</title><pubDate> Fri, 29 Aug 2025 22:41:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aiseesoft-screen-recorder-631.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aiseesoft-screen-recorder-631.html
</guid><description>
Aiseesoft Screen Recorder is the software supports recording, take a screenshot with any videos and save them back with high quality. Apps screen recording video strong this can help you get online movies and radio, game capture, make video tutorials, record videos, capture screenshot, etc. on Windows 10/8/7.
Screen capture software helps you record almost any video screen you want. You can use it to record online video, game, podcast, webinars, lectures, presentations, Skype calls,...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Saver Pro 10.8.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 29 Aug 2025 22:40:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-saver-6830.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-saver-6830.html
</guid><description>
YT Saver is a software that supports downloading Video, Audio, Playlist from 10,000+ websites, Convert Video to MP4, MOV, AAC, WAV and more. YT Saver is a powerful downloader that allows you to save video and audio for free. The output format of the high-speed converter is high-quality MP4, MP3. Fully compatible with iPhone, iPad, iTunes, iMovie, Android Phone and more.
Supported Input Formats:
	Video: MP4, M4V, 3GP, MPEG, DAT, AVI, ASF, WMV, VOB, MKV, FLV, 3GS, 3G2, F4V, WEBM, TS,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Aiseesoft FoneLab for Android 6.0.8</title><pubDate> Fri, 29 Aug 2025 22:39:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aiseesoft-fonelab-for-android-3929.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aiseesoft-fonelab-for-android-3929.html
</guid><description>
Aiseesoft FoneLab for Android is one of the software Android data recovery best. Aiseesoft FoneLab for Android is recovery software data great for Android users that helps you recover text messages, deleted messages, attached, lost, contacts lost, call history and Photos, Photo, Videos, Music, documents on Android phone, tablet and your SD card. Regardless of whether you lost files due to mistakenly deletion, root, upgrade, format the memory card, attack of virus or due to you crashing,...
</description></item><item><title>Download ActivePresenter Pro 10.0.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 29 Aug 2025 22:38:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-activepresenter-pro-598.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-activepresenter-pro-598.html
</guid><description>
ActivePresenter Pro is a solution to create a video screencast, development, manuals, documents and training presentations interactive. With the full editing features, ActivePresenter allows you to edit audio / video adjust interface content and specify the script branching with ease and efficiency. HTML5 support latest web standards and ability to integrate with management Systems, learning content created with ActivePresenter can be sent virtually to any device and any...
</description></item><item><title>Download Musify 4.4.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 29 Aug 2025 22:38:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musify-4422.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musify-4422.html
</guid><description>
Musify is the convert YouTube Music best can download music from more than 1000 website share music to listen to offline without reducing sound quality. Such as: YouTube, Spotify, SoundCloud, Facebook, Instragram, and more. Easily convert music files mp3 to iPhone, iPad, iPod, Samsung and iOS devices and other Android. High speed and high quality. Musify is a YouTube converter is very efficient and fast, support format converting YouTube to MP3. You can batch convert mp3 files at the same...
</description></item><item><title>Download PPTube 10.8.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 29 Aug 2025 22:38:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pptube-12556.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pptube-12556.html
</guid><description>
PPTube Video Downloader allows you to download HD videos easily, from 720p, 1080p, 2K, 4K and 8K. You can save multiple videos at the same time. Just copy multiple video URLs from various websites and paste them into PPTube Downloader, then you can download multiple videos in seconds.
In addition, you can download HD videos from Instagram, TikTok, Facebook, Apple Music, Vimeo, adult websites, etc. and convert them to MP4, MP3, MOV, AAC and more than 20 other output formats. PPTube...
</description></item><item><title>Download Photo Supreme 2025.3.3.8069</title><pubDate> Fri, 29 Aug 2025 22:37:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photo-supreme-430.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photo-supreme-430.html
</guid><description>
Photo Supreme is a software product management professional pictures of idimager. With Photo Supreme you can arrange, manage back stock photo archive of yourself and share them with you here and relatives easily via Email or Facebook. Photo Supreme provides users method to sort images effective, logical, as well as edit and share your photos with friends and relatives in the family. Especially the Photo Supreme allows to work with multiple image formats and support mounting support,...
</description></item><item><title>Download ActivePresenter Professional 10.0.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 29 Aug 2025 22:36:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-activepresenter-professional-895.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-activepresenter-professional-895.html
</guid><description>
ActivePresenter Professional is a professional software to create video screencast, development, instructions for use, documents, and presentations, interactive training. In addition, ActivePresenter allows you to edit audio / video adjust interface content and specify the script branching with ease and efficiency. HTML5 support latest web standards and ability to integrate with management systems, learning content created with activepresenter can be delivered to virtually any device and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Pazu Tidal Music Converter 1.6.9</title><pubDate> Fri, 29 Aug 2025 22:35:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pazu-tidal-music-converter-11450.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pazu-tidal-music-converter-11450.html
</guid><description>
Pazu Tidal Music Converter: The ultimate guide to downloading Tidal music
Tidal is a popular music streaming service that offers a wide variety of music, including exclusive content and high-quality audio. However, one of Tidal's disadvantages is that it does not allow users to download music for offline listening. This can be a major inconvenience for users who want to listen to music without using data or want to have a backup of their music library.
Pazu Tidal Music Converter is a...
</description></item><item><title>Download iDownerGo 10.8.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 29 Aug 2025 22:34:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idownergo-12439.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idownergo-12439.html
</guid><description>
iDownerGo is the best tool that allows users to download videos, music and playlists from more than 10,000 streaming sites. It can easily convert videos to MP4, MOV, MKV, 3GP, AAC, WAV, FLAC and other formats on PC and Mac. With this amazing program, users can enjoy their favorite media content without restrictions.
iDownerGo Features
	Download any video up to 8K resolution
	Download 1080p videos online from over 10,000 popular streaming sites easily.
	Save any video in various...
</description></item><item><title>Download Waterfox 6.6.2 / 2022.11</title><pubDate> Fri, 29 Aug 2025 22:34:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-waterfox-114.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-waterfox-114.html
</guid><description>
Waterfox is a 64-bit version of the foundation Firefox was built and the compiler Intel is optimized for speed and performance on Windows systems.Waterfox does not add any additional features or bling, in fact, it will automatically import all the gadgets and install is have of you, so you will feel like at home when you run it the first time.All the add-on your Firefox will work with Waterfox, however, only support the plug-in more 64-bit, is includes Adobe Flash, Oracle Java and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Liberty Street HomeManage 2025 v25.0.8.22</title><pubDate> Fri, 29 Aug 2025 22:33:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-liberty-street-homemanage-5694.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-liberty-street-homemanage-5694.html
</guid><description>
Liberty Street HomeManage is new integrated report design software for creating and editing your own reports. Easily generate reports with graphs, images, totals, and more. Save and print reports or export to one of a variety of formats, including PDF, HTML, Excel, RTF, XML, text, and more. But that's not all, our report designer also lets you create labels and "File tags". You can even print out barcode labels to attach to your properties. Scan the bar code then to display the AssetManage...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cogin QueueMonitor Professional 1.6.35</title><pubDate> Fri, 29 Aug 2025 22:33:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cogin-queuemonitor-professional-9072.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cogin-queuemonitor-professional-9072.html
</guid><description>
QueueMonitor continuously monitors your MSMQ and its queues, and sends alerts or performs automatic fixes whenever something goes wrong. QueueMonitor Professional allows you to automate mail processing and integrate various external systems using files, HTTP, SQL databases, FTP without any coding on your part.
QueueMonitor is not a general monitoring tool with some simple MSMQ checks added later, it is made specifically for MSMQ monitoring and can detect and handle specific problems...
</description></item><item><title>Download QuadSpinner Gaea 2.2.1.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 29 Aug 2025 22:33:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quadspinner-gaea-3870.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quadspinner-gaea-3870.html
</guid><description>
QuadSpinner Gaea is design software terrain, sophisticated and modern for results the top in moments. The top tools of QuadSpinner Gaea makes realism became the basis. Workflows are streamlined, allowing you to easily gain visibility and work in parallel with your team. Interface is extremely modern and our multitude of gadgets stimulate creativity, not limit it. Working at Gaea very interesting and can help you set a performance standard new.
QuadSpinner Gaea - design software...
</description></item><item><title>Download FlashBack Express 7.6.423</title><pubDate> Fri, 29 Aug 2025 22:32:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-flashback-express-260.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-flashback-express-260.html
</guid><description>
BB FlashBack Express screen recording software allows you to capture activity on the computer in real time, such as film, video then export them out to Flash format (FLV and SWF) or an AVI. When using FlashBack Express we easily capture the entire screen, a particular window or area has the frame and also include sound from a microphone and even the video from the webcam is attached in the form of PIP images.
Features FlashBack Express includes :
	Record screen video in...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ampere 4.35.9</title><pubDate> Fri, 29 Aug 2025 21:00:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ampere-10520.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ampere-10520.html
</guid><description>
Have you ever felt that one charger/USB cable charges your device very fast and the other one doesn't? Now, you can prove this with Ampere. Measure the charging and discharging current of the battery.
Basic information: Application to measure battery charge/discharge current. If your phone is not connected to the charger, you will see a negative current. If you connect a charger, the current provided by the charger will be used to supply your phone and the remaining electricity will be...
</description></item></channel></rss>