<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 19:59:24 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 19:59:24 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download PictureThis - Plant Identifier 5.10.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 09 Aug 2025 22:59:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-picturethis-plant-identifier-10533.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-picturethis-plant-identifier-10533.html
</guid><description>
PictureThis identifies over 1,000,000 plants every day with 98% accuracy - better than most human experts. Get answers to your gardening questions and become a “green thumb” with PictureThis's plant identification capabilities! Identify any plant, flower, herb or tree by photo and get helpful plant care tips. Set timely reminders to water plants on time. Take photos to detect plant diseases and get quick treatment. Chat with experts to receive professional tree planting guidance....
</description></item><item><title>Download Flashlight Plus: Bright Light 2.8.9</title><pubDate> Sat, 09 Aug 2025 22:58:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-flashlight-plus-bright-light-12999.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-flashlight-plus-bright-light-12999.html
</guid><description>
Turn your mobile phone into a flashlight and a magnifying glass! This is a new flashlight app. This smart two-in-one app has both a flashlight and a magnifying glass. OpticView™ lets you see what you're lighting on the screen, turning your phone into one of the most compact and powerful gadgets you've ever owned!
Features
	A simple and free flashlight app, great for emergencies
	Use your device's LED as a torch and bring the brightest flashlight on your phone!
	Turn on the...
</description></item><item><title>Download PrintHand Mobile Print 14.4.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 09 Aug 2025 22:58:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-printhand-mobile-print-11658.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-printhand-mobile-print-11658.html
</guid><description>
PrintHand Mobile Print is a convenient and multifunctional mobile printing application that allows users to print photos, documents and other files from mobile phones or tablets. This application supports direct printing from mobile devices via Wi-Fi or Bluetooth connection to the printer for printing without using an intermediary computer.
With PrintHand Mobile Print, users can easily print from any application on their mobile device, including Email, Dropbox, Google Drive and more....
</description></item><item><title>Download Math Tricks Workout 2.7.1.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 09 Aug 2025 22:58:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-math-tricks-workout-8232.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-math-tricks-workout-8232.html
</guid><description>
Math Tricks Exercises can be an Android app designed to help users improve their math skills and speed through the use of various tricks and techniques. Math Tricks Exercises is one of the best math tricks app that brings you the most interesting exercises and practice to test and improve your math skills. Inspired by Vedic Maths, This is the most fun and free math learning app ever!
Features of Math Tricks Workout
	Various math problems, including addition, subtraction,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sound meter: SPL &amp;amp; dB meter 10.8</title><pubDate> Sat, 09 Aug 2025 22:57:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sound-meter-spl-db-meter-12187.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sound-meter-spl-db-meter-12187.html
</guid><description>
Sound meter: SPL &amp;amp; dB meter is a sound pressure level meter (SPL meter), noise level meter, decibel meter (dB meter), sound level meter or sound meter. This is a very useful application for performing sound tests or measuring environmental noise (noise testing). It uses a smartphone or tablet's microphone to measure environmental noise in decibels (dB). The decibel(dB) value of this noise meter or sound meter may differ from the actual Sound Meter (DB Meter). Now you can easily...
</description></item><item><title>Download Rain Alarm 6.0.0 build 701</title><pubDate> Sat, 09 Aug 2025 22:57:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-rain-alarm-8639.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-rain-alarm-8639.html
</guid><description>
This weather app alerts you when rain is approaching. Alerts are a reliable short-term forecast based on near real-time data. This app is more accurate and reliable than a traditional forecast. It is useful for all outdoor activities - including cycling, motorcycling, hiking, gardening, BBQs, picnics, dog walking and DIY.
Features of Rain Alarm for Android
	Alerts for all types of precipitation, whether rain, snow or hail
	Alerts as a notification with vibration and/or sound
	Simple...
</description></item><item><title>Download Smart MP3 Tag Editor 25.7.14</title><pubDate> Sat, 09 Aug 2025 22:57:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-smart-mp3-tag-editor-10706.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-smart-mp3-tag-editor-10706.html
</guid><description>
id3 tag editor for all your music. The app provides Smart Tagger function that will automatically find the best match for your music instantly. Embed lyrics into audio file to play it back offline. Support built-in Lyric search tab. Download Hi-res cover image to embed into audio file.
Smart mp3 tag editor features
	Batch tagging. Select multiple audio files for auto tagging.
	Edit entire album files or multiple files at once. Set them to have the same artist, album, genre, .... all...
</description></item><item><title>Download Blood Pressure &amp;amp; BP Tracker 3.6.4</title><pubDate> Sat, 09 Aug 2025 22:56:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-blood-pressure-cardio-journal-11674.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-blood-pressure-cardio-journal-11674.html
</guid><description>
Blood Pressure is an indispensable application that allows you to record high (or low) blood pressure, pulse or heart rate measurements and ultimately control hypertension or hypotension. With the help of a heart diary, you can easily take care of your heart health. All data in the log can be quickly and easily analyzed on various graphs, showing trends, changes, average values ​​over daily, weekly, 2-week and monthly periods, etc.
Main features:
	Add one-touch tonometer readings...
</description></item><item><title>Download IELTS Practice Test 5.17</title><pubDate> Sat, 09 Aug 2025 22:55:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ielts-practice-test-13333.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ielts-practice-test-13333.html
</guid><description>
Are you aiming for a high IELTS score? IELTS Practice Test is the complete solution for comprehensive exam preparation. Whether you are aiming for a band 7 or higher, our app provides the tools and resources you need to succeed. It covers all four sections of the IELTS exam, ensuring you are fully prepared for either the Academic or General Training test.
Key Features
	Realistic Practice Tests: Simulate the real IELTS exam with full practice tests in Listening, Reading, Writing and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Remote for All TV! 1.7.8</title><pubDate> Sat, 09 Aug 2025 22:55:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-remote-for-all-tv-13504.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-remote-for-all-tv-13504.html
</guid><description>
Remote for All TV! is an application that turns your smartphone into a universal remote control, helping you easily control most types of TVs on the market. This Universal Remote Control app gives you a convenient and modern experience, completely replacing the traditional or lost remote control.
Advantages of "Remote for All TV!":
	Support: compatible with many popular TV brands such as Samsung, LG, Sony, Panasonic, Xiaomi, Fire TV, Vizio, TCL, Roku TV, Android TV, etc.
	Easy to set...
</description></item><item><title>Download Call Recorder - Cube ACR 2.4.275</title><pubDate> Sat, 09 Aug 2025 22:55:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-call-recorder-cube-acr-11263.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-call-recorder-cube-acr-11263.html
</guid><description>
Call Recorder Cube ACR is an application that records phone and VoIP calls. Supports call recording for most versions of Android devices. If you have tried recording calls using other call recording apps and not getting satisfactory results, try Cube ACR Call Recording, it works best. Cube ACR call recording allows you to easily record incoming and outgoing phone calls as well as VoIP conversations.
Main features:
	Automatically record every call. Record each conversation as it...
</description></item><item><title>Download Yoga &amp;amp; Meditation | Gotta Yoga 2.1.20</title><pubDate> Sat, 09 Aug 2025 22:54:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-yoga-meditation-gotta-yoga-13510.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-yoga-meditation-gotta-yoga-13510.html
</guid><description>
Gotta Yoga is a versatile yoga and meditation app designed for users of all levels, from beginners to advanced practitioners. The app offers over 350 classes, including styles like Vinyasa, Yin, Hatha, Ashtanga, Iyengar, meditation and pranayama, with session lengths ranging from 5 to 90 minutes, many of which can be taken offline.
Key features include:
	Live classes via Zoom with certified yoga teachers, providing real-time interaction and feedback.
	Integrated with Apple Health and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Dumbbell Workout at Home &amp;amp; Gym 5.13</title><pubDate> Sat, 09 Aug 2025 22:54:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-dumbbell-home-workout-8634.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-dumbbell-home-workout-8634.html
</guid><description>
Dumbbell Workout at Home is a fitness app for Android devices that offers users a variety of workout routines that can be done at home using only weights. This app is designed for people who want to stay fit and healthy but don't have access to a gym or workout equipment.
Features of Weightlifting at Home for Android
	Customizable workout routines: The app offers users a variety of workout routines that can be customized based on their fitness level, goals, and the amount of time they...
</description></item><item><title>Download ChromePass 1.61</title><pubDate> Sat, 09 Aug 2025 18:03:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chromepass-3315.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chromepass-3315.html
</guid><description>
ChromePass is a tool to recover password for Windows, allows you to view user names and passwords stored by Google Chrome browser Web. For each password entry, the following information is displayed: the root URL, action URL, username Field, password Field, user Name, password and Time created. It allows you to retrieve the password from the system running your current or from a user profile stored on the external drive. You can select one or more items and then save them into text / html...
</description></item><item><title>Download Custom Context Menu 5.6.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 09 Aug 2025 17:55:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-custom-context-menu-12534.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-custom-context-menu-12534.html
</guid><description>
Custom Context Menu is a handy tool that allows you to customize the right-click context menu on Windows 11 system. This means you can add, remove or modify context menu items for quick access to your favorite apps, settings, or websites.
Features:
	Add new menus to execute the commands you need
	Customize the title and icon of the new custom menu
	Supports sharing and importing custom menu configurations
	Various configurations are provided for easy menu command...
</description></item><item><title>Download NxFilter 4.7.3.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 09 Aug 2025 17:53:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nxfilter-50.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nxfilter-50.html
</guid><description>
NxFilter is a server filter DNS have the ability to filter Internet traffic based on domain names and content types. In addition, it can use check package DNS to protect your network from malware and botnet activity.
NxFilter is installed on a single computer, where it acts as a proxy server, DNS. To route Internet traffic through NxFilter, you will need to change the DNS settings on all the machines that you want to protect to use the IP address of the individual NxFilter (instead of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download ON1 Resize AI 2026 v20.0.0.17265</title><pubDate> Sat, 09 Aug 2025 17:51:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-on1-resize-2055.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-on1-resize-2055.html
</guid><description>
ON1 Resize 2019 is the edited final image when you need to zoom in the highest quality - with technology genuine Fractals® - to resize your photo to print. You can quickly change the image size without losing sharpness or detail. ON1 Resize also includes one of the fastest ways to view, remove and edit photos.
ON1 Resize - Zoom, change photo size
The features of ON1 Resize
	ON1 Resize using interpolation algorithm based on fractal - helps quickly change the image size without losing...
</description></item><item><title>Download Easy Gamer Utility Pro 1.3.79</title><pubDate> Sat, 09 Aug 2025 17:51:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easy-gamer-utility-pro-12381.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easy-gamer-utility-pro-12381.html
</guid><description>
Easy Gamer Utility Pro is an easy-to-use program for Windows that can do a lot on your PC to help fix gaming problems, performance problems, and general optimization! The best tool to improve your Windows gaming experience! Is your game laggy and slow? If so, you can use the built-in game accelerator in Easy Gamer Utility, which boosts system performance, makes games run smoother, and increases FPS.
Additionally, this handy utility deletes and cleans unwanted and unnecessary temporary...
</description></item><item><title>Download Room Arranger 10.2.0.727</title><pubDate> Sat, 09 Aug 2025 17:50:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-room-arranger-3779.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-room-arranger-3779.html
</guid><description>
Room Arranger is a 3D application lets you easily plan for the room, office or his apartment just a few mouse clicks. The application comes with a simple interface will significantly simplify your work. You can draw many kinds of objects and items to create furniture of your own. This app also includes a library of object rich.
Software Room Arranger enables you to view your project in 3D form. You can also upload the 3D scene interact on your blog or your website. The application uses...
</description></item><item><title>Download Bforartists 4.5.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 09 Aug 2025 17:50:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bforartists-7643.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bforartists-7643.html
</guid><description>
Bforartists is a complete, free and open source 3D suite for creating CG content. It gives you the full 3D art pipeline for creating game graphics, pre-rendered movies, and stills. From modeling, sculpting, texturing, design, animation, rendering, to post processing. The main goal of Bforartists is to provide a refined graphical user interface and better usability. This means a complete shift in usage philosophy away from hotkey-focused usage towards an intuitive and user-friendly...
</description></item><item><title>Download Magic Data Recovery Pack 4.9</title><pubDate> Sat, 09 Aug 2025 17:44:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-magic-data-recovery-pack-5146.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-magic-data-recovery-pack-5146.html
</guid><description>
Magic Data Recovery Pack is a program that provides the ability to recover data fast, easy, and powerful in one convenient package. Provides the ability to restore data from the drive is broken, broken, broken and is re-partition the deleted partitions and formatted, the hard drive is corrupt and can not visit, Magic Data Recovery Pack helps recovering documents, compressed archives and many other types of data in just few clicks. Photo recovery tool comes allows recovering digital...
</description></item><item><title>Download Rainbow Analyst add-in Professional 25.08.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 09 Aug 2025 17:44:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rainbow-analyst-add-in-professional-11122.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rainbow-analyst-add-in-professional-11122.html
</guid><description>
Rainbow Analyst add-in Professional is a powerful tool designed to enhance data analysis in Microsoft Excel. This add-on provides many advanced features and visualizations to help users gain valuable insights from their data.
One of the key features of Rainbow Analyst is the ability to create color-coded reports and charts. Users can assign specific colors to different data values, making it easier to identify patterns, trends, and outliers. This visual representation of data enhances...
</description></item><item><title>Download Magic Photo Recovery 6.9</title><pubDate> Sat, 09 Aug 2025 17:43:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-magic-photo-recovery-3275.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-magic-photo-recovery-3275.html
</guid><description>
Magic Photo Recovery is a powerful application and features provide you the ability to recover digital images and RAW images of camera be lost. The program allows you to get back photos from memory card or hard drive is formatted with minimal effort. The program supports a variety of image formats, including RAW images. Using Magic Photo Recovery, you will be able to recover digital photos from local drive, many different memory cards or directly from internal memory of camera. The program...
</description></item><item><title>Download Magic Partition Recovery 5.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 09 Aug 2025 17:40:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-magic-partition-recovery-5155.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-magic-partition-recovery-5155.html
</guid><description>
Magic Partition Recovery is the software helps to recover files and restore information from the disk is damaged, formatted, corrupted and inaccessible media and solid state storage formatted with any version of FAT or NTFS. Restore files and folders, repair the partition broken, and rebuilt the file system is damaged and missing in the automatic mode completely. With both analysis modes, quick and comprehensive, Magic Partition Recovery restore be careful of your files and rebuild the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Comfy Photo Recovery 6.9</title><pubDate> Sat, 09 Aug 2025 17:37:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-comfy-photo-recovery-3292.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-comfy-photo-recovery-3292.html
</guid><description>
Comfy Photo Recovery is a comprehensive application and strong allows you to recover the deleted photos accidentally, lost images after format hard drive, USB drive or memory card photos lost due to system malfunction, etc. Comfy Photo Recovery is very easy to use interface, accessible to both novice and expert. The step by step instructions integration will help you to restore digital photos with just a few simple steps. Using this program, you will be able to easily search, recover and...
</description></item></channel></rss>