<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 21:28:59 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 21:28:59 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download HE - Hardware Read and Write Utility 1.25.09.05</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Sep 2025 17:46:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-he-hardware-read-and-write-utility-4287.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-he-hardware-read-and-write-utility-4287.html
</guid><description>
HE - Hardware Read and Write Utility is a powerful utility intended for hardware engineer, engineer, BIOS developer, driver, engineer, QA engineers, performance test engineers, diagnostic, etc., this utility access almost all the computer hardware, including PCI (PCI Express), index / Data, PCI, memory, index memory / Data space I / O, Index I / O / Data, Super I / O, DIMM SPD, CPU The registers MSR, screen, SMART, physical area of the hard drive identification data, ATA, dump tables ACPI...
</description></item><item><title>Download R-Studio 9.5 Build 191603 Network / Technician</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Sep 2025 17:45:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-studio-1415.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-studio-1415.html
</guid><description>
R-Studio is a group of software data recovery and data recovery powerful and effective. -STUDIO is the solution to recover most comprehensive data for the file restored from the variants NTFS, NTFS5, ReFS, FAT12 / 16/32, exFAT, HFS / HFS + (Macintosh), Little and Big Endian of UFS1 / UFS2 (FreeBSD / OpenBSD / NetBSD / Solaris) and Ext2 / Ext3 / Ext4 partition FS (Linux).
R-Studio is also used to recover file raw (scan known file types) for the file system is damaged or not determined. It...
</description></item><item><title>Download Balabolka 2.15.0.905</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Sep 2025 17:44:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-balaboka-142.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-balaboka-142.html
</guid><description>
Balabolka is a text-to-speech (TTS) program. It can read text on your screen in a human-like voice. You can use Balabolka to listen to text from a variety of file formats, convert text to spoken audio files, and adjust speech parameters such as speed and pitch. It is often used for accessibility purposes, helping people who have difficulty reading or multi-tasking by listening to text while doing other activities. Balabolka supports multiple languages and uses different TTS engines,...
</description></item><item><title>Download FanControl v235</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Sep 2025 17:44:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fancontrol-5749.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fancontrol-5749.html
</guid><description>
FanControl is a highly customizable fan control software for Windows. Stay in control of every aspect of your PC's GPU and CPU fan with the help of this highly customizable fan control app.
Features of FanControl
	Save, edit and load multiple configurations
	Multiple temperature sources (CPU, GPU, motherboard, hard drive, ".sensor" files)
	Custom fan curve
	Fine tune fan control response with steps,% start,% stop, response time and delay
	Mix different curves and sensors...
</description></item><item><title>Download Windows Memory Cleaner 3.0.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Sep 2025 17:43:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-memory-cleaner-9959.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-memory-cleaner-9959.html
</guid><description>
Sometimes programs don't release the memory they used, making the computer slow, but you don't want to restart the system to get the used memory back. This is where you use Windows Memory Cleaner to clean up memory so you can continue working without having to restart Windows.
How to clean RAM of Windows Memory Cleaner
	Clean Combined Page List Removes blocks from the combined page list. Valid only when site merge is enabled.
	Clean Modified Page List Clears memory from the Modified...
</description></item><item><title>Download GoodSync Enterprise 12.9.8.8</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Sep 2025 17:43:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-goodsync-enterprise-163.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-goodsync-enterprise-163.html
</guid><description>
GoodSync Enterprise is a software that saves files and files easily and is reliable. It automatically analyts, synchronize and backup your email, family photos, contacts, MP3, financial documentation and other important files-between desktop computers, laptops, servers, external drives and Windows Mobile devices as well as remotely via FTP , SFTP, WebDAV and more. The GoodSync synchronized software combines bulletproof reliability with an extremely easy interface to compare, synchronize...
</description></item><item><title>Download PointerStick 6.79</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Sep 2025 17:42:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pointerstick-1743.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pointerstick-1743.html
</guid><description>
PulumStick is a presentation tool, mobile simple to turn your mouse pointer into a pointer larger. The software is designed to be used with presentations on a large screen, it allows to emphasize the operation of the computer desktop and helps users easily track the cursor over. You can adjust the size of the pointer, choose from a number of cursor interface, and can also move the mouse cursor usually your through mouse click or keyboard hotkeys.
PointerStick - virtual cursor
This is a...
</description></item><item><title>Download EZ CD Audio Converter 12.2.0.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Sep 2025 17:42:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ez-cd-audio-converter-174.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ez-cd-audio-converter-174.html
</guid><description>
EZ CD Audio Converter is a software application advanced with purpose helps you extract audio tracks from CDS, convert files to different formats and burn them to disc. When using functions separate the audio from the disc, you are also edit the type of metadata and specify the file name to be separated.
EZ CD Audio Converter Ultimate has the ability to convert between multiple audio formats with high output quality assured, supported input formats, including 3GA, 3GP, AAC, AIF, AIFF,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Calcpad 7.3.7</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Sep 2025 17:41:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-calcpad-12576.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-calcpad-12576.html
</guid><description>
Calcpad is free software for mathematical and engineering calculations. It is a flexible and modern programmable calculator with Html report generator. Calcpad uses a simple programming language that is fast and easy to learn. It does not require any special programming skills, which makes it suitable for engineers without any computer programming background. You can create calculation notes simply by writing your formula and text, enclosed in 'quotation marks'.
The program includes...
</description></item><item><title>Download XRECODE3 v1.171 Final</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Sep 2025 17:41:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xrecode-iii-2915.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xrecode-iii-2915.html
</guid><description>
"Xrecode II" is the switch and grab the audio allows you to convert from mp2, mp3, ac3, aiff, wma, amr, ogg, ape, flac, cue, mpc, wv, tak, mid, cue, m4b, tta, wav, dts , wav (rf64), m4a, mp4, ra, shn, rm, avi, aac, mpg, vob, mka, mkv, flv, Mov, swf, ofr, divx, wmv, spx, mp3, m4v, 3gp, m2v, 3g2, m4v, m2ts, ts, adts, tak, xm, mod, it, s3m, alac, umx, mtm, mlp to m4a, ape, flac, mp4 (using NeroAAC), raw, ogg, wav, wav (rf64) , wma, mpc, WavPack, mp2, ofr, Speex, ac3, tak, aiff, snd, Shorten...
</description></item><item><title>Download Picture Window Pro 8.0.528</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Sep 2025 17:40:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-picture-window-pro-7452.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-picture-window-pro-7452.html
</guid><description>
Picture Window Pro is a powerful image editing tool designed for serious photographers with strict creative and quality standards. Its comprehensive set of photo editing and editing tools let you control and shape every aspect of your images.
Picture Window Pro 8 is a complete rewrite of Picture Window Pro 7. It features non-destructive image editing through a novel interface based on an image tree. It also fully supports large, high-resolution displays and can be used in dual monitor...
</description></item><item><title>Download Vov Music Player 11.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Sep 2025 17:40:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vov-music-player-2512.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vov-music-player-2512.html
</guid><description>
Vov Music Player is a program very easy to use, can play all your favourite music from the desired folder directly from the taskbar. Listening to music is an enjoyable activity, we often do it when sitting in front of computer just to dilute the situation, that is, this is not the main purpose of the in PC. Usually listen to music to as a complement for those moments when you are busy, for example, doing something more interesting, work or play. With this in mind, program Vov Music Player...
</description></item><item><title>Download AllMapSoft Offline Map Maker 8.349</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Sep 2025 17:40:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-offline-map-maker-656.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-offline-map-maker-656.html
</guid><description>
AllMapSoft Offline Map Maker is software create, organize, offline map from Google Maps, Yahoo maps, Bing maps and Openstreetmap. You can view offline maps downloaded with map viewer offline. And you can zoom out or zoom in the offline map or export map under the file format .BMP with file world xxx.bpw, and can output files xxx.map for OziExplorer. If you want to make a offline map of your city by yourself, it is very useful for you.
Features AllMapSoft Offline Map Maker
	You can...
</description></item><item><title>Download ExifTool 13.35</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Sep 2025 17:39:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-exiftool-1685.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-exiftool-1685.html
</guid><description>
ExifTool is a library of Perl platform-independent plus a command line application for reading, writing, and editing meta information in various file types. ExifTool supports many metadata formats including EXIF , GPS , IPTC , XMP , JFIF , GeoTIFF , ICC Profile , Photoshop IRB , FlashPix , AFCP and ID3 , as well as notes of the manufacturer of many digital cameras by Canon , Casio , DJI , FLIR , FujiFilm , GE , GoPro , HP , JVC / Victor , Kodak , Leaf , Minolta / Konica-Minolta , Motorola...
</description></item><item><title>Download Black Menu for Google 26.2.6</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Sep 2025 17:39:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-black-menu-for-google-3231.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-black-menu-for-google-3231.html
</guid><description>
Black Menu for Google (Firefox) gives you fast access to Google services with your favorite drop-down menu conveniently allows you to use Search, Google+ and many other services without leaving the page you are visiting. Click on the menu item to get a preview small window or click the open button to the right to open them in a new tab.
Customize the menu by just entering ‘Add to, and drag / click on the service you want from the list of comprehensive services. To delete a service, drag...
</description></item><item><title>Download RiDoc 5.0.14.22</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Sep 2025 17:38:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ridoc-3999.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ridoc-3999.html
</guid><description>
RiDoc is a program to grab images from a scanner and reduce the size of the image file. This program reduces the file size of documents or electronic images without reducing image quality. With the help of the assembly function, the frame images in accordance with page format A4 size and an image file is reduced without reducing image quality. The convergence of documents into graphical format to help protect these documents from unauthorized copying. To increase the level of protective...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cleaning Suite Professional 4.020</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Sep 2025 17:38:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cleaning-suite-professional-4623.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cleaning-suite-professional-4623.html
</guid><description>
Cleaning Suite Professional is software support you clean the system from unnecessary data with a total of six effective tool. If the system boots increasingly slow and hard drive is full, then it is high time to clean the system thoroughly. With software Cleaning Suite Professional this, you can delete temporary files, delete browser history, cache and cookies from all the popular Internet browsers and security applications and tools are installed automatically start when the system...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Substance 3D Modeler 1.22.4 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Sep 2025 17:37:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-substance-3d-modeler-7876.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-substance-3d-modeler-7876.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Substance 3D Modeler is a 3D sculpting and modeling application that helps you create on both desktop and VR. Modelers aim to make working in 3D as intuitive as working with clay in real life. To help achieve this, with Adobe Substance 3D Modeler you don't have to worry about adjusting vertices or managing UVs, you can instead focus on the creative process.
With its intuitive design, Adobe Substance 3D Modeler frees you from the technical constraints of traditional 3D modeling....
</description></item><item><title>Download Anki 25.09</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Sep 2025 17:37:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anki-1765.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anki-1765.html
</guid><description>
Anki is a program flashcards customizable to help you learn vocabulary, study tests, capture knowledge of the geography of you and more. The program provides access to a library of free flashcards (which are called `Decks`) on a variety of topics, and you can also create your own deck to help you study pretty much the theme you want.
Anki software - Support vocabulary learning
The possibilities are almost endless, you can create flashcards based on simple text or include audio / video,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Windows 10 Network Fix and Optimizer Utility 1.4</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Sep 2025 17:37:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-10-network-fix-and-optimizer-utility-11475.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-10-network-fix-and-optimizer-utility-11475.html
</guid><description>
Windows 10 Network Fix and Optimizer Utility is a tool that can help you repair and optimize Windows 10 network settings easily. It is displayed from a user-friendly interface, allowing you to select various options from the "Options" menu without wasting time checking each option manually.
Windows 10 Network Fix and Optimizer Utility displays essential network details such as LAN IP address, subnet, computer name, port used, and workgroup. You can also access System Properties with a...
</description></item><item><title>Download OneCommander Pro 3.101.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Sep 2025 17:36:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-one-commander-4232.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-one-commander-4232.html
</guid><description>
One Commander is a file manager for Microsoft Windows with function improved user interface and navigation experience, system file and manipulating the files. Utilities use the tree view to sort the folder, subfolders, and files your, make sure that the current location of you always clear. It supports multiple tabs, allowing you to easily switch between them and access the folder you need.
One Commander - a filemanager for Windows
Depending on the format of the files, some files can...
</description></item><item><title>Download AllMapSoft Bing Maps Downloader 7.533</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Sep 2025 17:36:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-bing-maps-downloader-6063.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-bing-maps-downloader-6063.html
</guid><description>
AllMapSoft Bing Maps Downloader is a tool that can automatically download Bing Maps down your PC. It can download small squares and save them into your hard disk, including the usual map, satellite map, hybrid map. After downloading, you can view the offline map with its Viewer Maps tool, or you can combine small images into a large map image. If you want to make a map of your own city, it is very useful for you.
Features of AllMapSoft Bing Maps Downloader
	Light software and easy to...
</description></item><item><title>Download PC Internals Pro 2.001</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Sep 2025 17:35:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pc-internals-pro-13002.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pc-internals-pro-13002.html
</guid><description>
PC Internals Pro is a new solution that allows Windows users to comprehensively analyze the system components and reliable monitoring of the hard drive. This software is aimed at individual users as well as IT experts and retail agents attach importance to transparency, early detection and data security. PC Internals provides detailed information about the processor, RAM, graphics card, drive and other system components. The chart directly displays the current load, while the specific...
</description></item><item><title>Download Hot Alarm Clock 6.4.3.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Sep 2025 17:35:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hot-alarm-clock-7070.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hot-alarm-clock-7070.html
</guid><description>
Hot Alarm Clock is a desktop clock for alarms, timer, stopwatch, countdown timer, birthday reminder, to-do list and everything other to organize and prioritize your time. With Hot Alarm Clock you can set a daily wake-up or configure multiple complex alarms that trigger on certain days of the week, day or month.
This alarm clock app can play your favorite music or online radio station, use fixed or incremental alarm volume, launch your favorite app and open Website when wake up. It will...
</description></item><item><title>Download iZotope Neutron 5.1.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Sep 2025 17:34:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-izotope-neutron-advanced-1727.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-izotope-neutron-advanced-1727.html
</guid><description>
iZotope Neutron Advanced is software audio control perfect reach blend clear, balanced with analysis tools and mixing new creative of the Neutron. Control every aspect of your music, from the visual field of music of your number of mixture-all of you with signal processing, digital award-winning iZotope.
iZotope Neutron 3 Advanced
iZotope Neutron 3 new introduction visual analytics, the first in the industry and communicate with all versions of neutron, so you can shape a mixture of...
</description></item></channel></rss>