<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 21:28:39 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 21:28:39 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download MobiPDF: PDF Editor &amp;amp; Scanner 11.9.267330</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:07:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pdf-extra-scan-edit-sign-8390.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pdf-extra-scan-edit-sign-8390.html
</guid><description>
PDF Extra PDF Editor &amp;amp; Scanner is a mobile application that allows users to create, edit and sign PDF documents on their Android or iOS devices. It includes many tools and features that make it easy to work with PDF files, including scanning, editing, and signing. This application also allows users to combine multiple PDF files into a single document and export PDF files in various file formats, such as JPEG, PNG, and Microsoft Word.
Features of PDF Extra PDF Editor &amp;amp;...
</description></item><item><title>Download Solid Explorer File Manager 3.0.2 beta</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:07:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-solid-explorer-file-manager-8924.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-solid-explorer-file-manager-8924.html
</guid><description>
Solid Explorer is a file management application inspired by old file management applications. Solid Explorer is a popular file management app for Android devices that allows users to manage and organize their files and folders in an intuitive and user-friendly interface. It offers many features that make it stand out from other file management apps.
Solid Explorer allows you to navigate to files stored on your device and automatically organize them into collections. You can view,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Lightroom Photo &amp;amp; Video Editor 10.5.3</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:07:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-adobe-lightroom-photo-video-editor-8401.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-adobe-lightroom-photo-video-editor-8401.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Photoshop Lightroom is a powerful, free camera app and photo editor that empowers your photography, helping you capture and edit stunning images. Easy image editing tools like sliders and filters simplify photo editing. Edit full-resolution photos, apply photo filters, or start editing photos anytime, anywhere.
It offers a variety of editing tools, including basic adjustments like cropping, rotation, and brightness control as well as advanced features like color grading, selective...
</description></item><item><title>Download HiEdu Calculator Pro 1.7.6</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:07:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-hiedu-calculator-pro-8218.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-hiedu-calculator-pro-8218.html
</guid><description>
HiEdu Calculator Pro is a simple yet powerful calculator that includes standard, scientific and programming modes, as well as unit converters, Mathematical, Physical and Chemical Formulas, Graphing and Equation Solver. It is the perfect tool for adding bills, converting measurements in recipes or other projects, and is a great tool for education to help solve complex math, algebra, or geometry problems.
HiEdu Calculator Pro Features
	Advanced Math Functions: The Pro version may offer...
</description></item><item><title>Download QRbot: QR &amp;amp; barcode reader 3.3.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:06:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-qrbot-qr-barcode-reader-8737.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-qrbot-qr-barcode-reader-8737.html
</guid><description>
Scan all types of QR codes and barcodes with QRBot's QR code reader. Quickly access your scanning-related functions: For example, add contact data to your address book or connect to a WiFi hotspot with just one click. Easily share arbitrary data such as website links by displaying them on your screen as QR codes and scanning them with another device.
Supported QR codes 
	Website links (URLs)
	Contact data (Mecard, Vcard, VCF)
	Calendar events
	WiFi hotspot access...
</description></item><item><title>Download Calculator Plus with History 8.0.6</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:06:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-calculator-plus-with-history-10531.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-calculator-plus-with-history-10531.html
</guid><description>
Plus Calculator with History is the perfect calculator for Android. It remembers everything you calculate and allows you to review it at any time, which is perfect for me when shopping, doing homework, balancing my checkbook, or even helping with taxes. And if you need to quit your job and go do something else, I'll have it all ready for you when you get back. You'll never need to re-enter the same calculation twice.
Features of Calculator Plus with History
	Show your calculations in...
</description></item><item><title>Download Silent Camera [High Quality] 8.16.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:06:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-silent-camera-10536.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-silent-camera-10536.html
</guid><description>
Introducing the best silent camera! Without the shutter sound, photos can be taken in complete silence! It also ranks number 1 among many silent cameras thanks to its high image quality! Take high-quality photos with the silent camera! You won't disturb anyone around you because the shutter sound can't be heard. You can take high-quality photos of any situation, such as your baby's cute sleeping face, your pet's natural behaviors, and words written on a blackboard!
Silent Camera...
</description></item><item><title>Download Duolingo: language lessons 6.47.6</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:05:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-duolingo-language-lessons-8265.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-duolingo-language-lessons-8265.html
</guid><description>
Duolingo is a popular language learning app that offers interactive lessons to help users learn new languages. This application offers many languages for you to choose from, including Spanish, French, German, Italian, Portuguese, Chinese, Japanese and many more.
This app offers an gamified learning experience with interactive lessons, exercises, and quizzes designed to help users learn new words, phrases, and grammar rules. This app is designed to be easy to use and suitable for people...
</description></item><item><title>Download Video Editor VideoShow Pro 10.2.4.2pro</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:05:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-video-editor-videoshow-pro-13946.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-video-editor-videoshow-pro-13946.html
</guid><description>
VideoShow Pro is a professional video editing application available on multiple platforms such as Android, iOS and Windows. The app offers a comprehensive feature set designed for both beginners and experienced users who want to create and edit videos with ease and flexibility.
Key features of VideoShow Pro:
	The Pro version is free of watermarks and ads, ensuring a smooth editing experience.
	Supports high-resolution video export, including 1080p and 4K quality without any loss of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Shazam: Find Music &amp;amp; Concerts 16.9.0-250904</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:05:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-shazam-music-discovery-10763.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-shazam-music-discovery-10763.html
</guid><description>
Shazam will identify any song in seconds. Discover, artists, lyrics, videos &amp;amp; playlists, all for free. Over 1 billion installs and counting. Use Pop-up Shazam to identify music in any app - Instagram, YouTube, TikTok... No connection? No problem! Shazam while offline.
Features of Shazam: Music Discovery
	Find the name of any song in seconds.
	Listen and add to Apple Music playlists.
	Follow along with time-synced lyrics.
	Watch music videos from Apple Music or YouTube.
	Enable...
</description></item><item><title>Download IPTV Pro 9.1.6</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:05:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-iptv-pro-9093.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-iptv-pro-9093.html
</guid><description>
IPTV Pro is an Android application that allows you to watch live TV channels and movies on your Android device. It provides access to many channels from around the world, including sports, news, movies, and entertainment channels. IPTV Pro supports both M3U and XSPF playlists, and allows you to add your own playlists.
IPTV Pro Features
	Supports M3U and XSPF playlists
	Playlist history
	Play a multicast stream using a UDP proxy (the proxy needs to be installed in your LAN)
	Grid, list...
</description></item><item><title>Download Calculator - Floating Widget 2.5.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:04:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-calculator-floating-widget-8355.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-calculator-floating-widget-8355.html
</guid><description>
A simple and stylish computer. Supports percentage calculations, constant calculations, iterative calculations, and exponential and interest rate calculations. Has a memory function as well as the ability to display and save formulas.
Calculator features
	All calculation results are saved and previous formulas can be viewed at any time.
	Everything typed is saved when the app quits, so it picks up where you left off.
	This widget can be used to perform application functions on the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wallpaper 4K HD – Wallcraft 3.58.00</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:04:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wallcraft-cool-4k-wallpaper-4d-12029.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wallcraft-cool-4k-wallpaper-4d-12029.html
</guid><description>
Wallcraft - free wallpaper app that helps you find the best ultra 4K wallpapers and cool backgrounds in 4K HD quality. In Wallcraft live 6K wallpapers you can choose cool 4K wallpapers for every taste. From any wallpaper application only here you can download cool new 3D wallpapers (live 4D wallpapers, parallax and only 3D graphics), for those with aesthetic taste, we There are so many cool abstract wallpapers, try our special couple photos. We have a large amount of free wallpapers with...
</description></item><item><title>Download ID Photo &amp;amp; Passport Portrait 1.2.0.5</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:03:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-id-photo-passport-portrait-10922.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-id-photo-passport-portrait-10922.html
</guid><description>
Photo ID supports all formats for various uses such as ID cards, passports for all countries, visas, driver's licenses, resumes, certificates, Social platforms and more! Photo ID automatically detects your portrait, eliminating the need for boring collages and searching for exact specifications. And you can use the Nuts ID Photo app to create photos by taking a photo of yourself, taking a portrait over and over again until you like it. If you need to use an ID card photo and feel it is...
</description></item><item><title>Download JPEG Image Compressor &amp;amp; Resize 3.0.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:03:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-jpeg-image-compressor-resize-13175.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-jpeg-image-compressor-resize-13175.html
</guid><description>
Want to quickly and batch resize your photos, but also want to change the aspect ratio with a photo resizer? Download now to reduce photo size in seconds without losing quality. Do you have hundreds of photos? Don't worry, our batch photo resizer supports batch photo resizing. Moreover, our free photo resizer app also has an advanced jpg, png, heic converter that will save you a lot of time needed to convert photo formats online. Whether you are a photographer, social media content...
</description></item><item><title>Download OneCalc+ All-in-one Calculator 2.3.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:03:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-onecalc-all-in-one-calculator-12061.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-onecalc-all-in-one-calculator-12061.html
</guid><description>
OneCalc+ All-in-one Calculator is a comprehensive calculator application that combines many functions and mathematical tools into a single application. It is designed to provide users with a convenient and efficient way to perform various calculations and solve complex equations on their mobile devices.
Main features:
	Calculate credit and savings
	Unit conversion
	Currency conversion
	Construction calculator
	Date and Time Calculator
Overall, OneCalc+ is a versatile and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Fasting - Intermittent Fasting 2.3.3</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:02:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-fasting-intermittent-fasting-13045.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-fasting-intermittent-fasting-13045.html
</guid><description>
Fasting Tracker will guide you to a new lifestyle with healthy habits. You will lose weight effectively and feel more active! With many different fasting plans, Fasting Tracker is suitable for beginners and experienced people, both men and women. It guides you to implement your plan. No need to change your diet, you can easily follow it.
Features of fasting tracker
	Many interrupted fasting plans
	For both beginners and experienced people
	One touch to start/end
	Customize the fasting...
</description></item><item><title>Download QR &amp;amp; Barcode Reader (Pro) 3.3.2-P</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:02:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-qr-barcode-reader-pro-11205.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-qr-barcode-reader-pro-11205.html
</guid><description>
QR &amp;amp; Barcode Reader is a modern QR code scanner and barcode scanner with all the features you need. Scan any QR code or barcode to get more information including results from popular online services: Amazon, eBay and Google!
Main features:
	Scan all popular barcode formats: QR, Data Matrix, Aztec, UPC, EAN, Code 39 and many more.
	Open URLs, connect to WiFi hotspots, add calendar events, read VCards, find product and price information, and more
	Protect yourself from malicious...
</description></item><item><title>Download MDScan + OCR 3.9.85</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:02:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-mobile-doc-scanner-mdscan-ocr-8307.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-mobile-doc-scanner-mdscan-ocr-8307.html
</guid><description>
Mobile Doc Scanner (MDS) is an application that allows users to scan, edit and save documents using the Android device's camera. It's designed to work as a portable scanner so you can easily digitize documents, receipts, business cards, and more.
All image processing is done on your device only! No material will be posted online without your wishes! Take photos with your camera, edit them with many advanced features, save to your favorite format and share on social networks, email,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Rain Alarm 6.0.5</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:01:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-rain-alarm-8639.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-rain-alarm-8639.html
</guid><description>
This weather app alerts you when rain is approaching. Alerts are a reliable short-term forecast based on near real-time data. This app is more accurate and reliable than a traditional forecast. It is useful for all outdoor activities - including cycling, motorcycling, hiking, gardening, BBQs, picnics, dog walking and DIY.
Features of Rain Alarm for Android
	Alerts for all types of precipitation, whether rain, snow or hail
	Alerts as a notification with vibration and/or sound
	Simple...
</description></item><item><title>Download Smart Launcher 6 ‧ Home Screen 6.5 build 044</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:01:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-smart-launcher-8412.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-smart-launcher-8412.html
</guid><description>
Smart Launcher is a mobile app that provides users with a customized home screen and app launcher on their Android devices. It includes features like minimalist interface, automatic app sorting, and gesture controls. The app also includes many customizable settings, such as the ability to change the theme, icon size, and screen layout, as well as the ability to create custom categories for the app.
Smart Launcher Features
	Ambient theme: Smart launcher automatically changes theme...
</description></item><item><title>Download Scientific Calculator Plus 8.1.3 build 92</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:01:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-scientific-calculator-plus-12199.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-scientific-calculator-plus-12199.html
</guid><description>
CalcTastic Plus is a feature-rich calculator with years of innovation and exceptional user ratings. Choose from 12 different themes, configurable screens and your choice of math, Algebra or RPN.
CalcTastic Plus includes two completely independent modes
	Highly accurate scientific calculator with Fractions, Complex Numbers, Physical Constants, Unit Converter, Advanced Statistics, History &amp;amp; Memory Registers and Full Online Help .
	Full-featured programmer's calculator with dedicated...
</description></item><item><title>Download Multi Timer StopWatch 2.13.22 build 494</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:00:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-multi-timer-stopwatch-8914.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-multi-timer-stopwatch-8914.html
</guid><description>
Multi Timer is a beautifully designed time management app. Multiple timers can be set, started and run independently at the same time. Stopwatch results can be stored. Use Multi Timer for cooking, sports, machine washing, studying, working, gaming - whatever you like.
Features of Multi Timer StopWatch
	Multiple timers at once: Store the timers you often use for cooking, sports, studying, working, gaming, whatever you want. Start them with just one tap, anytime you need.
	Timer in...
</description></item><item><title>Download Conversations (Jabber / XMPP) 2.19.5 build 4215904</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:00:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-conversations-jabber-xmpp-11493.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-conversations-jabber-xmpp-11493.html
</guid><description>
Free and open source Jabber/XMPP client for Android. Easy to use, reliable, battery friendly. With built-in support for images, group chats and e2e encryption.
Main features
	End-to-end encryption with OMEMO or OpenPGP
	Encrypted audio and video calls (DLTS-SRTP)
	Send and receive images
	Intuitive user interface follows Android Design guidelines
	Image / Avatar for your Contacts
	Sync with desktop client
	Conference (with bookmark support)
	Address book integration
	Multiple accounts...
</description></item><item><title>Download Money Manager: Expense Tracker 11.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Sep 2025 23:59:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-money-manager-expense-tracker-8782.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-money-manager-expense-tracker-8782.html
</guid><description>
Money Manager is a simple money management app to manage money and track your daily spending. Find out where you spend the most money with the help of our budgeting system that can help you control your spending and save more money. This free expense tracker app is not only an expense tracker that helps you easily record daily expenses and income, but also has additional features that make it easy to track and manage all types of content. financial content to help make the accounting...
</description></item></channel></rss>