<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 16:05:49 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 16:05:49 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download MemoryCleaner 1.9.4</title><pubDate> Mon, 02 Feb 2026 17:11:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-memorycleaner-12469.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-memorycleaner-12469.html
</guid><description>
MemoryCleaner is a tool to free up memory on your computer. This is a free app with a simple user interface that makes it easy for users of all skill levels to use. MemoryCleaner uses many functions built into Windows to free up memory without affecting your system. You can also access Memory Cleaner's functions right from the system tray without having to open the program. The cleaning processes are silent and the only time you see a warning is to briefly display the amount of RAM...
</description></item><item><title>Download Executor 2.2.3.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 02 Feb 2026 17:10:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-executor-271.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-executor-271.html
</guid><description>
Executor for windows is a software alternative premium customization features for the Windows "Run" and "Search Programs". When you press WIN + Z and provides the search results instant, as-you-type for any keywords you enter. By default, Executor will index all the Desktop and Start Menu and you can easily expand the search range by adding the folder location additional.
Executor for windows
The program comes with a list of commands built in which you can use to quickly access many...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDFgear 2.1.15</title><pubDate> Mon, 02 Feb 2026 17:09:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdfgear-9049.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdfgear-9049.html
</guid><description>
PDFgear is a PDF reader and editor that combines PDF editing functionality with an AI (artificial intelligence) assistant powered by ChatGPT. The user-friendly product PDFgear offers options that you cannot find in Adobe Acrobat. It's great that you can change the color of your comments with simple clicks.
PDFgear is a full-featured PDF editor that basically helps me do everything I need: edit, convert, form, signature, etc. The interface is intuitive and familiar, and all the features...
</description></item><item><title>Download XYplorer 28.20.0100</title><pubDate> Mon, 02 Feb 2026 17:07:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-533.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-533.html
</guid><description>
XYplorer - File Manager for Windows is software that supports users to manage files on the Window quickly and to arrange the folder tidy. XYplorer features tabbed browsing, search, files, powerful, preview, flexible, highly customizable interface, dual frame options and a variety of unique ways to automate effective tasks often repeat. It's fast, lightweight, and portable.
Features XYplorer
	XYplorer is a file manager mobile. It does not require any settings, store all configuration...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ratiborus KMS Tools Lite 01.02.2026</title><pubDate> Mon, 02 Feb 2026 17:06:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ratiborus-kms-tools-lite-11160.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ratiborus-kms-tools-lite-11160.html
</guid><description>
Ratiborus KMS Tools Lite is a collection of activators from Ratiborus for Windows XP, Vista, 7, 8, 8.1, 10, 11, Windows Server, Office 2010/2013/2016/2019 /2021/2024. It includes several utilities, each with its own set of features, mainly aimed at activating Microsoft Windows and Office products. The program is used to activate Microsoft products such as Windows and Office using Key Management Service (KMS). With a simple, easy-to-use interface that allows users to activate the product...
</description></item><item><title>Download Yamicsoft Windows 11/10 Manager 2.3.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 02 Feb 2026 17:06:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yamicsoft-windows-11-manager-6779.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yamicsoft-windows-11-manager-6779.html
</guid><description>
Windows 11 Manager is an all-in-one utility for Microsoft Windows 11 specially, it includes over forty different utilities to optimize, tweak, clean up, speed up and repair your Windows 11, helps make your system perform faster, eliminate system fault, increase stability and security, personalize your copy of Windows 11, and meet all of your expectations.
Features of Windows 11 Manager:
Information:
	Creates the system restore point manually;
	Gets detailed information about your...
</description></item><item><title>Download Recovery Toolbox for PDF 2.12.37.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 02 Feb 2026 17:05:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-recovery-toolbox-for-pdf-5206.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-recovery-toolbox-for-pdf-5206.html
</guid><description>
Recovery Toolbox for PDF is a compact tool that helps you repair damaged PDF files. Recover corrupted Adobe PDF documents with full support of recovering PDF files of all versions and sizes.
Features of Recovery Toolbox for PDF
	Recover corrupted Adobe PDF documents
	Full support of recovering PDF files of all versions and sizes
	A smart proprietary core that leverages the power of advanced document analysis and fixed methods
	Ability to fix some logical errors caused by errors in...
</description></item><item><title>Download DVDFab 13.0.5.6</title><pubDate> Mon, 02 Feb 2026 17:05:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dvdfab-67.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dvdfab-67.html
</guid><description>
DVDFab All-In-One is a multi-purpose combo of nearly all powerful DVDFab products-DVD replication, Ripper DVD, Blu-ray Ripper, Blu-ray Ripper, Copy UHD, Blu-ray to DVD, DVD to Blu-ray Transaction, DVD Creator, Blu-ray Creator, video conversion, Cinavia DVD removal, Windows DVD removal, DRM elimination for Apple, Screen Recorder and Editor for iOS, Hi-Fi Sound and File Transfer. It provides a complete solution to all of your DVD/Blu-ray/video problems and the perfect execution.
DvDFab -...
</description></item><item><title>Download Bitvise SSH Client 9.57</title><pubDate> Mon, 02 Feb 2026 17:04:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bitvise-ssh-client-2845.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bitvise-ssh-client-2845.html
</guid><description>
Bitvise SSH Client is a SSH terminal, tunneling and file transfer application SFTP for free with the command line interface and graphics. It supports all versions desktop and server of Windows! Bitvise SSH Client for free use! Bitvise SSH Client is an application multipurpose, fast and powerful in the transmission of the advanced file helps users control and manage the terminal remotely in a flexible manner. Bitvise SSH Client intensive support for establishing the secure connection...
</description></item><item><title>Download Monkeys Audio 12.10</title><pubDate> Mon, 02 Feb 2026 17:04:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-monkeys-audio-949.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-monkeys-audio-949.html
</guid><description>
Monkey\'s Audio is software that compresses digital music without loss of quality. Supports high quality WAV files and CD ripping. Monkeys Audio will compress .wav tracks into .ape files to reduce their size without loss of sound quality, decompress .ape, convert files, check file integrity and manage tags.
Unlike traditional methods like MP3 and OGG, which permanently remove quality to save space, Monkey\'s Audio only creates perfect copies with the same sound quality as the originals....
</description></item><item><title>Download ChrisPC YTD Downloader MP3 Converter Pro 6.26.0201</title><pubDate> Mon, 02 Feb 2026 17:04:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-ytd-downloader-mp3-converter-pro-2767.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-ytd-downloader-mp3-converter-pro-2767.html
</guid><description>
ChrisPC YTD Downloader MP3 Converter Pro is a Windows software dedicated to download and convert YouTube videos to audio file MP3 high quality. ChrisPC YTD Downloader MP3 Converter is one of the few program convert YouTube to MP3 (if not unique) available in the market to help you have quality best sound in the YouTube video you want to download and convert to MP3.
A in what format is most commonly used for recording in this decade is the MP3 format and thus we store on our utility...
</description></item><item><title>Download Recovery Toolbox for Excel 3.8.47.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 02 Feb 2026 17:03:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-recovery-toolbox-for-excel-8115.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-recovery-toolbox-for-excel-8115.html
</guid><description>
Recovery Toolbox for Excel is a tool developed to help you recover damaged Microsoft Excel files. It allows to open XLSX files of any version of Microsoft Excel (2007/2010/2013/2016/2019/2021 (Microsoft 365)) and preview the contents of XLSX documents and save the data to a safe location. other.
Also, Recovery Toolbox for Excel works completely independently of Microsoft Excel, you can also use Recovery Toolbox for Excel to view your Excel documents without installing Microsoft Excel or...
</description></item><item><title>Download Modbus Poll 12.2.0.2516</title><pubDate> Mon, 02 Feb 2026 17:03:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-modbus-poll-3852.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-modbus-poll-3852.html
</guid><description>
Modbus Poll is the simulator the Modbus is designed primarily to help developers device Modbus or others want to test and simulate the Modbus protocol. With the multiple document interface you can monitor a number of slave Modbus and / or the zone data at the same time. For each window you simply specify the ID slave, Modbus, function, address, size, and proportion of poll. You can read and write registers and coils from any window. If you want to change a register, just double-click the...
</description></item><item><title>Download OneCommander Pro 3.107.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 02 Feb 2026 17:02:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-one-commander-4232.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-one-commander-4232.html
</guid><description>
One Commander is a file manager for Microsoft Windows with function improved user interface and navigation experience, system file and manipulating the files. Utilities use the tree view to sort the folder, subfolders, and files your, make sure that the current location of you always clear. It supports multiple tabs, allowing you to easily switch between them and access the folder you need.
One Commander - a filemanager for Windows
Depending on the format of the files, some files can...
</description></item><item><title>Download EaseUS Partition Master Technican Edition 19.23.0 Build 202601261108</title><pubDate> Mon, 02 Feb 2026 17:01:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-partition-master-350.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-partition-master-350.html
</guid><description>
EaseUS Partition Master is software partition management all-in-one be used to redistribute capacity hard drive with high performance and keep all PC, laptop and server running perfect performance. Engineering software master partition deals with all the task partition in an effective way without loss of data. Just a few clicks to re-partition your hard drive, SSD, USB, flash drive, memory card, SD card, memory card and many other storage devices in Windows 10, 8.1, 8, 7, Vista, XP and...
</description></item><item><title>Download SQL Backup Master 8.1.1026 All Editions</title><pubDate> Mon, 02 Feb 2026 17:01:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sql-backup-master-6687.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sql-backup-master-6687.html
</guid><description>
SQL Backup Master backup your SQL Server database into any popular cloud hosting service such as Dropbox, OneDrive, Amazon S3, Microsoft Azure, Box and Google Drive. It can also backup the database to the FTP server-or a directory on your local machine, network server or storage device.
The backup of your SQL Server database to the cloud will not be complex or expensive. SQL Backup Master is born by providing an easy way to download copies of your database to one or more of the most...
</description></item><item><title>Download EASEUS Partition Master Unlimited Edition 19.23.0 Build 202601261108</title><pubDate> Mon, 02 Feb 2026 17:00:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-partition-master-unlimited-edition-3458.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-partition-master-unlimited-edition-3458.html
</guid><description>
EASEUS Partition Master Unlimited Edition is a partition solution all-in-one and tool kit, disk management PC &amp;amp; Server reliable, especially for large enterprise users. It allows unlimited usage within your company. Just a few clicks to re-partition your hard drive, SSD, USB, flash drive, memory card, SD card, memory card and many other storage devices in Windows 10, 8.1, 8, 7, Vista, XP and Windows Server 2016, 2012, 2008, 2003. EASEUS Partition Master Unlimited Edition extend...
</description></item><item><title>Download FreeCommander XE 2026 Build 941</title><pubDate> Mon, 02 Feb 2026 16:56:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-freecommander-xe-2746.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-freecommander-xe-2746.html
</guid><description>
FreeCommander XE is an alternative easy-to-use for manager file windows standard. The program helps you to do daily work in Windows. Here you can find all the necessary functions to manage the database of his. You can take FreeCommander anywhere - just copy the installation directory on a CD or USB-Stick - and you can work with this program on the computer foreign.
FreeCommander XE - a file Manager replacement for windows default
The features of FreeCommander
	Technology board dual -...
</description></item><item><title>Download Zero Install 2.28.3</title><pubDate> Mon, 02 Feb 2026 16:55:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zero-install-1632.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zero-install-1632.html
</guid><description>
Zero Install is a system, install the software distribution cross africa focus. Other features include full support for shared libraries (with the SAT for resolution dependent), share between users, and integration with the package manager original foundation. Zero Install supports both binary packages and source and works on Linux systems , OS X , Unix and Windows. It is completely open source.
Zero Install - System software installation
Zero Install also has a number of interesting...
</description></item><item><title>Download EASEUS Partition Master Server Edition 19.23.0 Build 202601261108</title><pubDate> Mon, 02 Feb 2026 16:54:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-partition-master-server-edition-3457.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-partition-master-server-edition-3457.html
</guid><description>
EASEUS Partition Master Server Edition is a powerful program that allows you to solution delete, create, merge, resize / move, split the partition to use better the full capacity of the hard drive. EasUS Partition Master Server Edition is the partition manager packed full of features and includes three main functions: The recovery guide partition manager partition and wizard restore partition.
These tools will enhance the management of your hard drive and will help you to use disk space...
</description></item><item><title>Download EASEUS Partition Master Professional Edition 19.23.0 Build 202601261108</title><pubDate> Mon, 02 Feb 2026 16:54:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-partition-master-professional-edition-3459.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-partition-master-professional-edition-3459.html
</guid><description>
EASEUS Partition Master Professional Edition is a utility software powerful and full will help you to better manage hard drives and partitions by yourself. This application includes three main functions, such as Program instructions for copying disk and partition, manager partition and wizard restore partition. Moreover, the program allows you to create CD or DVD that can boot, to help you recover the system in case of no boot.
EASEUS Partition Master Professional Edition is the most...
</description></item><item><title>Download Helium Music Manager Premium 17.4.566</title><pubDate> Mon, 02 Feb 2026 16:54:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-helium-music-manager-premium-164.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-helium-music-manager-premium-164.html
</guid><description>
Helium Music Manager is a music manager that can rip, tag, play, browse, search, rename, burn and synchronize your music with the mobile. You can control your music collection with Helium Music Manager. Stop using time looking for the file on your computer or looking through CDS, vinyl records and tapes - instead, simply enjoy and explore your music! Helium Music Manager can replace the ripper, the player, tag editor and related software to audio your other.
Helium Music Manager...
</description></item><item><title>Download Synchredible Professional 9.111</title><pubDate> Mon, 02 Feb 2026 16:53:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-synchredible-professional-1923.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-synchredible-professional-1923.html
</guid><description>
Synchredible Professional is the most advanced version help synchronize the folder and your drive quickly and easily. Whether it is a single file or an entire drive - Synchredible Professional will synchronize, copy and save them for you. The software guide will assist you to identify the work that is scheduled in advance or be done through the USB connection. This way, you can keep your files in sync - automatically.
In the past years, the advanced technology of the us in Synchredible...
</description></item><item><title>Download Duplicate File Finder Professional 2026 v410</title><pubDate> Mon, 02 Feb 2026 16:47:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-duplicate-file-finder-professional-4425.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-duplicate-file-finder-professional-4425.html
</guid><description>
Duplicate File Finder Professional is a compact application helps you quickly find and remove files duplicate on the computer. With Duplicate File Finder Professional you can choose any folder on the hard drive or use the folder standard user and our app will analyze the deep content of the selected folder to copy. It will take only a few seconds. The files will be compared by the hash algorithm MD5, which means they will be compared by content, not by name. Then, use our convenient...
</description></item><item><title>Download MassTube 2026 v21.3.3.185 Ultra</title><pubDate> Mon, 02 Feb 2026 16:46:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-masstube-plus-461.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-masstube-plus-461.html
</guid><description>
MassTube Plus is a small utility used to download the favorite videos of you on youtube on your computer. This is a software compact, has a simple design with few options to download videos fastest. The you complete peace of mind because the software is easy to use, built exclusively for a single goal: to retrieve the video file from YouTube, so it doesn't pack the other useful features such as search engine integrated and a download audio file.
MassTube can work with multiple output...
</description></item></channel></rss>