<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:42:36 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:42:36 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download FastKeys Pro 6.04</title><pubDate> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 17:11:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fastkeys-219.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fastkeys-219.html
</guid><description>
FastKeys is a compact tool used to create the shortcut, assign a shortcut key to specify the string stands for the text often use and manage mouse gestures. Users can specify the mouse manipulation to increase the performance of the work or simply replace a string or use an acronym.
FastKeys trigger to allow for expansion of abbreviations for texts used frequently in any application and save time typing. Enter a few letters and automates the task of repeating in a professional manner....
</description></item><item><title>Download ChrisPC YTD Downloader MP3 Converter Pro 6.25.1026</title><pubDate> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 17:10:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-ytd-downloader-mp3-converter-pro-2767.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-ytd-downloader-mp3-converter-pro-2767.html
</guid><description>
ChrisPC YTD Downloader MP3 Converter Pro is a Windows software dedicated to download and convert YouTube videos to audio file MP3 high quality. ChrisPC YTD Downloader MP3 Converter is one of the few program convert YouTube to MP3 (if not unique) available in the market to help you have quality best sound in the YouTube video you want to download and convert to MP3.
A in what format is most commonly used for recording in this decade is the MP3 format and thus we store on our utility...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tiny11 25H2 Build 26200.6899 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 17:10:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tiny11-8649.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tiny11-8649.html
</guid><description>
Tiny11 is a compact Windows operating system based on Windows 11 Pro 22H2, Tiny11 has everything you need for a comfortable, hassle-free computing experience. cumbersome and messy like a standard Windows installation. The operating system requires only 8GB of disk space and 2GB of RAM, and requires no TPM (Trusted Platform Module) and Secure Boot support.
The main goal of Tiny11 is to extend the reach of systems that can access Windows 11. The custom edition can run on any system...
</description></item><item><title>Download Red Gate SmartAssembly Professional 8.3.9.6618</title><pubDate> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 17:05:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-red-gate-smartassembly-1593.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-red-gate-smartassembly-1593.html
</guid><description>
Red Gate SmartAssembly is a tool that helps protect your application against reverse engineering or modifications prevent side Tuesday access to source code. This comprehensive solution protects the data card of you and more likely to report errors. This program makes files difficult can disassemble and injection code does not use, to help engineer can reverse and understand the core structure of the code. With your smartphone, you will have many features to tamper with the code as the...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Downloader 9.17.16</title><pubDate> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 17:04:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html
</guid><description>
YTD Youtube Downloader is an application that reliable and intuitive, allowing you to quickly download YouTube videos and save them to your computer. You can also convert the media files to the format desired video or extract audio streams and save separately. YTD Youtube Downloader lets you save your favorite clips of yourself from Youtube, Facebook, Vimeo and Dailymotion to your desktop. The software supports URLS from many web site hosting, multimedia and allows you to download desired...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wipe Pro 2025.13</title><pubDate> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 17:04:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wipe-pro-710.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wipe-pro-710.html
</guid><description>
Wipe Pro is software that helps clean up litter, increase in hard drive space besides also protect your privacy on the Internet, it removes records about personal activity on the computer. You will be able to delete browser history and the cache, the file index.dat, registry, files, cookies, internet history, auto complete, temporary internet files and many other items. This program also delete all activities other individuals that you made when using the PC and regardless of which...
</description></item><item><title>Download FX Science Tools MultiDocs 25.10.26</title><pubDate> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 17:03:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fx-science-tools-3744.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fx-science-tools-3744.html
</guid><description>
FX Science Tools provided to teachers of chemistry and physics the effective means to create equations and chemical structures. Just type and create. FX Chem FX Chem makes writing chemical equations become simple. You just type and FX Chem know enough about chemistry to put all the components of the equation at the right point. FX Chem can even create the chemical equations for nuclear - a very difficult thing in the Word. FX ChemSturation FX ChemSturation made the organic structure, what...
</description></item><item><title>Download ReShade 6.6.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 17:03:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-450-3227.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-450-3227.html
</guid><description>
ReShade is an open Source tool help improve the look of the old games on modern video cards as well as allow additional display technology / new video over on the old game doesn't support the technology that.
ReShade, technically, is a tool processing general for the games and video software. Imagine you see your favorite game yourself with the obscure-around, effects market the true depth or color correction. Function ReShade by showing in an automatic way and general access to...
</description></item><item><title>Download NonCompressibleFiles 4.91</title><pubDate> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 17:03:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-noncompressiblefiles-1688.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-noncompressiblefiles-1688.html
</guid><description>
NonCompressibleFiles is software compressed file size, the ability to create the file is not compressed or is compressed a maximum ability to transfer files. NonCompressibleFiles has the big advantage that is the ability to create one or thousands of files under 2 mode no compression or maximum compression. This is a strong possibility of the program that is not software would also have to be aimed to help increase work performance and reduce the time as well as effort of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ahnenblatt 4.36.0.5</title><pubDate> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 17:02:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ahnenblatt-3844.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ahnenblatt-3844.html
</guid><description>
Ahnenblatt is a genealogy software full-featured, easy to use suitable for beginners and even pedigree has the experience to organize genealogy research by you. Use plausibility checks to find out the inaccuracies in your family and create the chart impressive with just a few mouse clicks.
Ahnenblatt - Create family tree,
Recently, there has been strong increase of the general interest of the public for genealogical tree. Users who desire to track their heritage have many tools at...
</description></item><item><title>Download TubeMate Downloader 5.23.7</title><pubDate> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 17:01:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubemate-downloader-4250.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubemate-downloader-4250.html
</guid><description>
TubeMate Downloader is a smart application that lets you download any clip you want from the website hosting the main video and convert them in when download at or then. If you need a simple and effective tool to download videos, you can give it a try. With TubeMate Downloader, you can directly drag and drop video link from your browser into the drop-down box or application window to start downloading. You don't even need to copy and paste the video URL.
TubeMate Downloader - Support...
</description></item><item><title>Download FX Math Tools Manifest 25.10.26</title><pubDate> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 17:01:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fx-draw-tools-multidocs-8814.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fx-draw-tools-multidocs-8814.html
</guid><description>
MultiDocs is a new way to create self-modifying Word documents. MultiDocs' amazing new document reproduction features allow you to create reproducible tests and quizzes in minutes. Get new numbers, new diagrams and even brand new solutions! MultiDocs combines the power of Word with two leading products: FX Draw and FX Equation in a new and exciting way.
Features of FX Draw Tools MultiDocs
	Create multiple documents: The software allows users to create multiple math and evaluation...
</description></item><item><title>Download Syncovery Premium 11.10.0.120</title><pubDate> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 16:57:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncovery-pro-enterprise-232.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncovery-pro-enterprise-232.html
</guid><description>
Syncovery Pro Enterprise is a great application used to back up data and to synchronize personal computers, servers, laptops, notepads and storage online. The software comes with support for FTP and secure FTP servers, SSH, WebDAV, Amazon S3, http, update the part file, ZIP compression, data encryption, and schedule automatic backups.
Syncovery Pro Enterprise have the ability to freely select files and folders across the whole folder hierarchy in tree view and supports email...
</description></item><item><title>Download Fujidenolo Solutions SonicDICOM PACS 3.18</title><pubDate> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 16:57:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fujidenolo-solutions-sonicdicom-pacs-11865.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fujidenolo-solutions-sonicdicom-pacs-11865.html
</guid><description>
SonicDICOM is PACS software that combines the capabilities of a DICOM Server with a web browser-based DICOM Viewer. It is built with the latest technology and streamlined processes, can be easily deployed with minimal IT knowledge with flexible hardware, flexible according to the actual needs of the number of images and user activities. use.
DICOM Server Features
	DICOM / SCP Storage
	Find, move DICOM / SCP
	DICOM / SCP Verification
	In DICOM / SCU*
	DICOM / SCU Storage
	DICOM file...
</description></item><item><title>Download tinyMediaManager 5.2.3</title><pubDate> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 16:56:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tinymediamanager-1819.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tinymediamanager-1819.html
</guid><description>
tinyMediaManager is a media manager full-featured to arrange and cleanup your media library your. Just choose (s) the folder containing your movies and the program can automatically get all meta data required for movies and program your TV from TheMovieDB.org, Imdb.com, OFDb.de and other online sources. tinyMediaManager download at artwork, film, cast, plot and details of other communication. Each film or program is presented with a unique art background, category, and appropriate...
</description></item><item><title>Download FlowHeater 4.5.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 16:56:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-flowheater-7776.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-flowheater-7776.html
</guid><description>
FlowHeater is software that converts MS Access, MS Excel, MS SQL Server, MySQL, SQLite, PostgreSQL, Oracle, OleDB and ODBC data sources as well as formats text format (CSV​, TXT, ASC, ASCII, Flat File...) in a simple way. In addition, the software also supports unlimited data exchange streams.
Features of FlowHeater
	Text file for reading and writing text files (CSV, TXT, ASCII, FlatFile, etc.).
	MS Access is used to import and export data directly into and out of Microsoft Access...
</description></item><item><title>Download Database Tour Pro 11.5.8.1332</title><pubDate> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 16:51:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-database-tour-pro-5321.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-database-tour-pro-5321.html
</guid><description>
Database Tour Pro application is a comprehensive software that allows you to organize all the database is connected his. It provides support for Borland Database Engine (BDE) and Microsoft ActiveX Data Objects (ADO), SQL scripts, reports, along with conversion and data export, among others.
It contains a browser object for the function, package, triggers, folders, users, roles, profiles, sequences, work, style, Java, exception, link, database, general properties, table, schema, and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Explzh 9.89</title><pubDate> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 16:50:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-explzh-2278.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-explzh-2278.html
</guid><description>
Explzh is software that originated from Japan. This program works with most formats, can extract the file directly to FTP server, split large files into multiple smaller size. I would like to note that the storage supports encryption of files compressed using AES algorithm, has a system of tabs in the main window, you can search for the information you need in the repository and work with files, batch mode is done.
Explzh - Compress and decompress file
The file is support work with the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Psiphon 186.20251025</title><pubDate> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 16:49:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-psiphon-7347.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-psiphon-7347.html
</guid><description>
Psiphon is a firewall bypass tool by Psiphon Inc. Uses VPN, SSH and HTTP Proxy technology to give you uncensored access to Internet content. Your Psiphon app automatically learns about new hotspots to maximize your chances of bypassing censorship.
The way the software works is that Psiphon constantly changes the proxy, so the user's IP address is also constantly changing, the server will not detect the user's real address, so you can feel free. roof. access to websites and software...
</description></item><item><title>Download Full Convert Pro 25.10.1690</title><pubDate> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 14:08:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-full-convert-pro-14254.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-full-convert-pro-14254.html
</guid><description>
Full Convert Pro is a powerful database conversion and synchronization software tool developed by Spectral Core. The software supports a wide range of databases, including Microsoft Access, dBase, FoxPro, Excel, Firebird, Interbase, MySQL, Oracle, SQL Azure, and many others. The tool is designed to handle large databases, with file sizes over 500 GB, and provides fast data migration speeds, which can reach hundreds of records per second. The software has a comprehensive wizard that...
</description></item><item><title>Download PARS-BIM: ARCHITECTURE TOOLS 1.0.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 13:55:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pars-bim-architecture-tools-14253.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pars-bim-architecture-tools-14253.html
</guid><description>
PARS-BIM: Architecture Tools is a powerful plugin for Autodesk Revit, designed to automate and simplify the process of converting AutoCAD drawings to Revit models. The plugin automatically detects and models walls, doors, and windows based on recognized layers in the CAD file, making it an effective tool for streamlining BIM workflows in architectural design. This plugin enhances productivity by automating routine tasks involved in transferring CAD data to a BIM environment, thereby...
</description></item><item><title>Download Media Player Classic Black Edition 1.8.8</title><pubDate> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 01:54:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-media-player-classic-black-edition-3351.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-media-player-classic-black-edition-3351.html
</guid><description>
Media Player Classic Black Edition is abbreviated as MPC-BE is a free program that can interface black support users to watch movies, listen to music on the computer with the new interface. Media Player Classic - BE is based on the project "Media Player Classic" original (Gabest) and the project "Media Player Classic Home Cinema" (Casimir666), contains additional features and bug fixes.
Both programs are quite similar, because they are based on Media Player Classic original. In fact, MPC...
</description></item><item><title>Download PMAS - PowerShell Multi Activation System 7.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 01:52:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-powershell-tsf-activation-13584.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-powershell-tsf-activation-13584.html
</guid><description>
This advanced PowerShell script is a flexible and modular solution designed for licensing Windows and Office products. It runs a custom .NET library called LibTSforge.dll directly from memory to license Office. It can work in GUI mode or silent mode.
Features
	License management for both Windows and Office products
	Generate product keys with the help of LibTSforge.dll
	User-friendly graphical options with Out-GridView
	Compatible with KMS, MAK, RETAIL, OEM, AVMA license types
	In...
</description></item><item><title>Download R-Wipe &amp;amp; Clean 20.0 Build 2532</title><pubDate> Sun, 26 Oct 2025 17:41:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-wipe-clean-891.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-wipe-clean-891.html
</guid><description>
R-Wipe &amp;amp; Clean is software to delete junk files, unnecessary files from your computer to release the storage space and speed up your computer. In addition, R-Wipe &amp;amp; Clean also unleash the capacity of your drive and delete information invasion of privacy on different operations online and offline including your internet history and cookies, the list of downloaded files and documents were open, buffer different data, temporary files and many other items, created by the operating...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare UniConverter 17.0.0.418</title><pubDate> Sun, 26 Oct 2025 17:41:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-uniconverter-4808.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-uniconverter-4808.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare UniConverter ( old name is Wondershare Video Converter Ultimate) which allows you to convert the video format. You can cut, splice, move, or add effects, subtitles a easy way. When using software you easily cut, splice, move, as well as add the effects, the subtitles to the video.... Or can switch the clods SD, HD video to any format popular for use with iPod (Classic, Nano and Touch), iPhone, Apple TV, Zune, PSP, Pocket PC...
Wondershare UniConverter helps convert formats...
</description></item></channel></rss>