<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 16:00:13 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 16:00:13 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download RepairKit 1.3.7</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:43:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-repairkit-11968.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-repairkit-11968.html
</guid><description>
RepairKit is an all-in-one Java-based Windows repair and maintenance toolkit. RepairKit aims to provide a package that provides users with a dedicated system repair tool as well as quick access to some operating system features and some other PC maintenance software that comes with it. it.
If you want to keep your PC running smoothly and want to do it conveniently, RepairKit offers a simple and effective solution for that, with an automatic repair/cleanup module , as well as access to...
</description></item><item><title>Download GiliSoft Video Editor 19.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:38:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-giliSoft-video-editor-37.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-giliSoft-video-editor-37.html
</guid><description>
Software GiliSoft Video Editor supports editing video files in many formats such as AVI, MPEG, H. 264, SWF, MOV, WMV,... to run on popular devices like iPod, iPhone, PSP, PS3,....
Besides it also provides for users a lot of effects to help you edit brightness, contrast as well as saturation for his videos. Lots of different filters to help you get the perfect video the most. In particular, GiliSoft Video Editor also feature support insert watermark for your video. With this feature you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Perfectly Clear WorkBench 5.0.1.3069</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:37:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfectly-clear-workbench-6892.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfectly-clear-workbench-6892.html
</guid><description>
Perfectly Clear Workbench is an application that uses image editing libraries Perfectly Clear by Athentech and is provided to demonstrate the capabilities of the Perfectly Clear processing libraries, which recognize faces and allow quick export of processing settings for use.
One of the key features in Workbench is the ability to "export to API" when saving a Preset. This allows you to make image edits in Workbench and adjust the settings to suit your editing style and needs. You can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Blank And Secure 8.31</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:37:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blank-and-secure-2934.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blank-and-secure-2934.html
</guid><description>
Blank And Secure is a application lightweight and portable allows you to completely erase your sensitive data without possibility to restore. This add-on accomplish this by overwriting your files with zeros (0) before you delete them. This method is also called "zeroing data / drives". You should know that once completed, the complete data can't be recovered, so you should only use this tool if you want to permanently delete your files.
Blank And Secure - Delete data permanently
Blank...
</description></item><item><title>Download By Click Downloader 2.4.30</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:37:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-by-click-premium-193.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-by-click-premium-193.html
</guid><description>
YouTube By Click Premium is a high quality powerful video downloader including YouTube downloader, YouTube Converter, YouTube Chrome Downloader, Facebook Video Downloader, Downloader Vimeo, Dailymotion Downloader and supports many other video sites.
YouTube By Click
YouTube By Click Features
	YouTube by Click can download and convert files to MP3, MP4, FLV, AVI, WMV, 3GP, WAV and WEBM formats.
	Download all supported qualities, including HD.
	YouTube By Click downloads entire YouTube...
</description></item><item><title>Download Coolmuster JPG to PDF Converter 2.7.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:36:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-jpg-to-pdf-converter-9640.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-jpg-to-pdf-converter-9640.html
</guid><description>
Coolmuster JPG to PDF Converter is a software application developed by Coolmuster Studio. As the name suggests, it is designed to convert JPG (JPEG) image files into PDF files. The software provides a simple and convenient way to convert individual or multiple JPG files into a single PDF document.
Whether you have JPEG, PNG, TIFF or BMP files, the software's advanced algorithms maintain image quality, color accuracy, and resolution when converting them to PDF. Users can rely on the...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaInfo 26.01</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:36:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediainfo-1456.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediainfo-1456.html
</guid><description>
MediaInfo is a software that provides access to view the information of media files, such as technical information and tags of the video file and bad sound. Software displays detailed information including: format, profile, commercial name of the format, duration, bit rate overall, writing application and library, title, author, director, album, track number, updates.
MediaInfo - View file info media
The features and functions of MediaInfo
	Container: format, profile, commercial name...
</description></item><item><title>Download Fast Video Downloader 4.0.0.79</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:35:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fast-video-downloader-2619.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fast-video-downloader-2619.html
</guid><description>
Fast Video Downloader is a support program download quick video of genuine FastPcTools. ast Video Downloader is an easy to use program that allows you to download desired videos from a number of sites online storage. I think that I will not reveal secret if they write that most of the sites have video archives do not contain the ability to download videos and sometimes that's very necessary. This is when the same program is rescue, this allows you to save videos from the archive page as...
</description></item><item><title>Download EASEUS Partition Master WinPE Edition 19.23.0 Build 202601261108</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:35:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-partition-master-winpe-edition-3460.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-partition-master-winpe-edition-3460.html
</guid><description>
EASEUS Partition Master WinPE Edition is a version plugins help you to create a disk partition on WinPE for you to easily recover hard drive partition computer if not may broken or error. Boot disk EasUS Partition Master WinPE, format software mobile, you can:
	Works well in Windows, such as extend system partition or settling low disk space and managing disk space, recovery partition deleted , rebuild MBR, restore partition GPT, etc.
	You are allowed to resize the primary drive to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Coolmuster PDF to JPG Converter 2.5.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:34:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-pdf-to-jpg-converter-9593.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-pdf-to-jpg-converter-9593.html
</guid><description>
Convert PDF to high quality JPG, PNG, TIF, BMP and GIF images easily with Coolmuster PDF to JPG Converter. Coolmuster PDF to JPG Converter easily converts your PDF files into stunning images with just a few clicks, making it easy to work with your PDF content in a visually appealing way. It allows you to convert from PDF to JPG/JPEG, PDF to PNG, PDF to TIF, PDF to GIF, PDF to BMP.
You can select specific pages or range of pages without limitation and convert multiple PDF files to image...
</description></item><item><title>Download AntiPlagiarism.NET 4.154</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:34:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-antiplagiarismnet-2457.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-antiplagiarismnet-2457.html
</guid><description>
AntiPlagiarism NET is software to check the originality of some given text, most people find a section of text on the Internet, often the search engines quickly put out the answer to this question. Sometimes the results can be wrong, because not all results are accurate, a hundred percent. Fortunately, there are other solutions to the problem, for example, AntiPlagiarism.NET it can help you determine the originality of some given text. Application to operate correctly, you need to install...
</description></item><item><title>Download NetSpeedTray 1.2.4 + Portable</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:33:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-netspeedtray-14068.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-netspeedtray-14068.html
</guid><description>
NetSpeedTray is a lightweight, open source network monitor for Windows that displays upload/download speeds directly on the Taskbar with a native look and feel.
Designed to blend seamlessly with Windows 10/11 user interface. Includes intelligent detection of light and dark themes on the taskbar to ensure text is always visible. Sits quietly in the system tray without hogging resources. Features "Dynamic Update Rate" that automatically reduces update frequency when the network is idle to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Power-user Premium 1.7.73.270</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:33:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-power-user-premium-3149.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-power-user-premium-3149.html
</guid><description>
Power-user is a plugin for software, Microsoft Excel, PowerPoint and Word help you to provide more visual content so you can create the spreadsheet attractive. It contains templates, icons, tables, drawings and charts, modern, professional, allows you to build professional looking documents. You can add custom content to your project just by a click of the mouse and surprise clients and colleagues with your skills on Excel, PowerPoint and Word.
Power-user Premium - Plugin Excel,...
</description></item><item><title>Download JPEG Saver 5.45</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:32:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jpeg-saver-4333.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jpeg-saver-4333.html
</guid><description>
JPEG Saver is a display image screen saver allows you to display photos of his favorite form saver Windows screen with the transition effect different. Program JPEG Saver provides many configuration options allow you to customize how to display his image and in what order they are displayed. You can select multiple folder location as the source for pictures, screensavers, and more control images are displayed by setting custom filters based on file name, date and other criteria.
JPEG...
</description></item><item><title>Download F-Secure Uninstallation Tool 19.2.89</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:32:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-f-secure-uninstallation-tool-2250.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-f-secure-uninstallation-tool-2250.html
</guid><description>
F-Secure Uninstallation Tool is a simple program that allows you to completely delete the product from F-Secure from your computer. You can delete products from the system without leaving traces such as service platform, F-Secure 5.x, 6.x, 7.x, 8.x, security service F-Secure for consumers 6.x, 7.x, 8.x , 9.x, security service F-Secure for business 3.x, 4.x, F-Secure Anti-Virus / Internet Security 2005, 2006, 2007, 2008, 2009, 2010, 2011, 2012, 2013,..
F-Secure Uninstallation Tool to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Coolmuster PDF Image Extractor 2.3.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:31:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-pdf-image-extractor-4846.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-pdf-image-extractor-4846.html
</guid><description>
Coolmuster PDF Image Extractor is an effective tool to support users to extract images from PDF files very easily and quickly. After extract, you can add these images into PowerPoint slideshows, photo collage or use them for other purposes without any restrictions.
You feel tired when to extract photos from multiple PDF files different? Try function extract batch this to get images from all PDF documents in just one single operation.
	Provide 3 different ways to download all PDF file...
</description></item><item><title>Download Power-user for PowerPoint and Excel 1.7.73.270</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:31:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-power-user-for-powerpoint-and-excel-522.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-power-user-for-powerpoint-and-excel-522.html
</guid><description>
Power-user for PowerPoint and Excel is a utility providing you with a library of templates, icons, charts, maps and diagrams for spreadsheet and presentation. With Power-user for PowerPoint and Excel, you will attract the attention of your audience with stunning graphics will certainly impress.
Power-user comes with a collection of 2,000 icons to illustrate your slides. The icons are vector shapes so you can resize them without distortion and color back as you with. With Power-user, you...
</description></item><item><title>Download EaseUS Data Recovery Wizard Professional WinPE 20.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:30:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-data-recovery-wizard-winpe-4379.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-data-recovery-wizard-winpe-4379.html
</guid><description>
EaseUS Data Recovery Wizard WinPE - recovery software best data to restore data deleted, formatted or lost from PC, laptop or mobile device easily and quickly. Help get back the lost files or deleted photos, music, sounds, emails, etc. from hard drive, memory card, USB, digital cameras, mobile devices, and other storage media. Program recover data this recover files lost or deleted 100% safe from losing cases different data on different devices without overwriting original data.
EaseUS...
</description></item><item><title>Download Room Arranger 10.3.4.743</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:30:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-room-arranger-3779.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-room-arranger-3779.html
</guid><description>
Room Arranger is a 3D application lets you easily plan for the room, office or his apartment just a few mouse clicks. The application comes with a simple interface will significantly simplify your work. You can draw many kinds of objects and items to create furniture of your own. This app also includes a library of object rich.
Software Room Arranger enables you to view your project in 3D form. You can also upload the 3D scene interact on your blog or your website. The application uses...
</description></item><item><title>Download Coolmuster Word to PDF Converter 2.7.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:29:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-word-to-pdf-converter-4839.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-word-to-pdf-converter-4839.html
</guid><description>
Coolmuster Word to PDF Converter is a reliable app and simple and help users to quickly convert Word documents to PDF for easy management and share. After conversion Word documents to PDF format, you will easily transfer files between your computer with other apps without encountering problems connecting, how.
Now when using this software, you will be very surprised to see conversion results. PDF file is still retaining all contents, text, images, layout and original formatting in the...
</description></item><item><title>Download MyLanViewer Enterprise 6.7.5</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:29:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mylanviewer-enterprise-1274.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mylanviewer-enterprise-1274.html
</guid><description>
MyLanViewer is a program for scanning IP address, Netbios and LAN / Network powerful for Windows tool whois and traceroute, remote shutdown and process management Wake On LAN (WOL), scan and monitor wireless networks. This app will help you find all IP addresses, MAC addresses and shared folders of computers on the network wired or wireless (Wi-Fi).
MyLanViewer Enterprise - Scan IP address LAN/Network
The program scans network and displays the computer network in your window, friends...
</description></item><item><title>Download Coolmuster PDF Password Remover 2.3.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:28:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-pdf-password-remover-4203.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-pdf-password-remover-4203.html
</guid><description>
Coolmuster PDF Password Remover is software password unlock PDF files protected Click people like to use password to protect copyright PDF of their work out of copying, printing, editing or stealing by others. So, sometimes you need to delete password from PDF to edit, copy, or share. Under this situation, Coolmuster PDF Password Remover can be an ideal assistant to you can remove password as you like.
Coolmuster PDF Password Remover - Remove password protected PDF
Forget the PDF...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinShift Forge 0.7.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:27:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winshift-forge-14401.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winshift-forge-14401.html
</guid><description>
What is WinShift Forge?
WinShift Forge is a lightweight utility built to enhance the performance of Windows 11. WinShift Forge allows you to easily remove them, free up space, and speed up your system. WinShift Forge lets you instantly refresh your computer screen by customizing the most important icons. No more fumbling through complex system settings—easily take direct control of the core Windows visuals and make your PC truly your own.
Key Features:
Personalize Your PC
	Replace...
</description></item><item><title>Download Coolmuster PDF Locker 2.6.4</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:27:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-pdf-locker-9592.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-pdf-locker-9592.html
</guid><description>
Coolmuster PDF Locker is a software program designed to secure and protect PDF documents by adding password encryption and various access restrictions. It provides features that help you control and manage the security of your PDF files. Discover the importance of password protecting your PDF files to keep your valuable data safe and secure. Protect your documents and keep sensitive information private as you please with this PDF encryption software now.
Discover three levels of strong...
</description></item><item><title>Download Coolmuster PDF to Word Converter 2.3.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:26:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-pdf-to-word-converter-4838.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-pdf-to-word-converter-4838.html
</guid><description>
Coolmuster PDF to Word Converter is simple tool to help you convert PDF files to Word. Microsoft Word is a file format ideal, allows users to edit, change and share with your friends without encountering any restrictions. So, if you want to edit PDF files on Mac, then try converting it to Word format to edit better. Coolmuster PDF to Word Converter will help all Mac users to quickly export Adobe to Word docx.
Now, with Coolmuster PDF to Word Converter, users can perfectly peace of mind...
</description></item></channel></rss>