<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 17:42:05 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 17:42:05 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download System Info 19.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Dec 2025 16:45:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-system-info-11391.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-system-info-11391.html
</guid><description>
System Info is a simple piece of software that displays various information about your system, including its hardware, operating system, and more. Having everything presented in a single interface, where you can copy and share that data elsewhere, can finally become convenient for regular users. That's what System Information does: it gives you various data about your system, including hardware specifications, operating system, network, and more. without installation.
This application...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mozilla Firefox 146.0.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Dec 2025 16:45:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-firefox-quantum-501.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-firefox-quantum-501.html
</guid><description>
Firefox Quantum is a web browser independently provide the tabbed browsing combined with numerous handy features like pop-up blocker, Bookmarks, direct (integrated RSS), password manager, and more. Functionality can be extended with dozens of plugins available for free (extensions).
Firefox Quantum are interface completely new, beautiful, neat, minimalistic and delicate, eats less RAM to 30% compared with the old version and solve the condition consuming capacity
Firefox can import all...
</description></item><item><title>Download X-Sec Malware Scanner 3.2.4.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Dec 2025 16:44:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-x-sec-malware-scanner-9668.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-x-sec-malware-scanner-9668.html
</guid><description>
X-Sec Malware Scanner (formerly X-Sec Antivirus) is an efficient and user-friendly virus scanner designed to work smoothly with other anti-virus programs. To perform a scan, you need to access the Scan Task Manager by navigating to the Scan button. You can then choose between three different scanning options: Quick Scan, Full Scan, or Custom Scan.
Features of X-Sec Malware Scanner
	Completely compatible with other anti-virus software
	Simple User Interface
	Multi-language
	X-Sec...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDF-XChange Editor Plus 10.8.0.405</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Dec 2025 16:43:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-xchange-editor-plus-645.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-xchange-editor-plus-645.html
</guid><description>
PDF-XChange Editor Plus is the editor, PDF viewer, compact, fast with many features, add-ons, professional. When using the PDF-XChange Editor Plus, easy for users to create, view, edit, annotate, OCR and digital signing PDF files, plus much more.
PDF-XChange Editor is a PDF editing full-featured. With the help of it, you can edit, fix, add, or delete text easily. Graphics can also be moved, resized or removed.
Features PDF-XChange Editor Plus
Edit documents
	Use a variety of editing...
</description></item><item><title>Download CyberLink PowerDirector Ultimate 2026 v24.0.1216.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Dec 2025 16:43:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-powerdirector-ultimate-425.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-powerdirector-ultimate-425.html
</guid><description>
CyberLink PowerDirector Ultimate is software editor, edit video and make movies on the computer from a variety of templates are made available, complete with effects, transitions, animations, and music. CyberLink PowerDirector 17 is a combination of video editing software with advanced video editing features powerful. Cblowing need to add your clips into the time line and click on 'Production'!
The tool design video in CyberLink PowerDirector have the ability to customize helps you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Camera Raw 18.1.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Dec 2025 16:42:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-camera-raw-02en-785.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-camera-raw-02en-785.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Camera Raw is Plugin edit photo on photoshop with the ability to handle the raw photos after the shoot to create beautiful photos and quality than the input image initially, this program helps support the photographers in editing and photography, make the photo beautiful.
Adobe Camera Raw - edit Raw images Photoshop
Adobe Camera Raw is a plugin which is integrated accompanied by a number of software photo editing such as Photoshop, Photoshop Elements, After Effects and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Bluetooth MAC Address Changer 1.14.0.203b</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Dec 2025 16:42:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bluetooth-mac-address-changer-12592.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bluetooth-mac-address-changer-12592.html
</guid><description>
Bluetooth MAC Address Changer for Windows is a handy tool that allows you to change the Bluetooth MAC address (also known as "Bluetooth Address", "BD_ADDR", "Bluetooth Hardware ID", etc.) connection device (or integrated card). You can rely on Bluetooth MAC Address Changer if you want to change the MAC address of your Bluetooth adapter in an easy and convenient way. You can do this by manually entering your desired address in the dedicated field or by pressing the Random button....
</description></item><item><title>Download PDF-XChange Pro 10.8.0.405</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Dec 2025 16:41:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-xchange-editor-pro-3422.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-xchange-editor-pro-3422.html
</guid><description>
PDF-XChange Editor Pro is an application to manipulate and create PDF versatile, offering a wide range of useful features and powerful will help you to easily work with PDF files. This application is very flexible and allows you to easily create and modify PDF files. PDF-XChange Editor Pro provides a powerful set of tools and flexibility to work with PDF files, such as editor PDF-XChange new, utilities series, OFFice2PDF and the Addin tool Bar allows you to easily convert multiple file...
</description></item><item><title>Download Filezo 6.0.12</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Dec 2025 16:40:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-filezo-14317.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-filezo-14317.html
</guid><description>
Filezo instantly finds any file, folder or application on your Windows PC at lightning speed. Just type a few keys and launch! That's it! Filezo's smart search feature ensures meaningful and clean results. It makes your computing life more enjoyable by eliminating boring clicks. Saves a lot of time and effort!
	Quickly access any document, folder or program on Windows in less than 5 seconds! Whether it's on your local hard drive, cloud drive or network drive.
	Tag files and folders to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Win10 All Settings 2.0.4.36</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Dec 2025 16:40:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-win10-all-settings-5335.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-win10-all-settings-5335.html
</guid><description>
Win10 All Settings is to help users customize Windows 10 in any case with alternate configuration interfaces and it can also do some hidden settings. The software grants access to the Windows Master Control Panel (God Mode) and categorizes the built-in Windows 10.
settings
The settings set by Win10 All Settings operate based on information published on Microsoft websites. Operations are often complex, involve many steps, and require system-level knowledge that can be easily done by...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe DNG Converter 18.1.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Dec 2025 16:40:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-dng-converter-2452.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-dng-converter-2452.html
</guid><description>
Adobe DNG Converter, a free utility that converts files from more than 350 cameras to DNG, enables you to easily convert the files raw exclusively for camera file raw DNG more universal. A program strong enough which allows you to convert the source files RAW to DNG format popular and more convenient with a few clicks of the mouse.
DNG allows photographers to archive files, raw images of them in a single format for easy cataloging and access in the future. With specification formats are...
</description></item><item><title>Download Windows Key Viewer 1.3.0.20</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Dec 2025 16:39:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-key-viewer-8851.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-key-viewer-8851.html
</guid><description>
Using Windows Key Viewer, the current computer product key can be easily determined. In some cases, it is very important to know the product key, such as when resetting the computer.
In general, you can find the product key on your Windows installer or on a label on your computer. This label is often damaged and illegible, and when using multiple computers, installation packages can get confused. That's where Windows Key Viewer comes in handy, as the product key can easily be displayed...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mozilla Thunderbird 146.0.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Dec 2025 16:39:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thunderbird-1788.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thunderbird-1788.html
</guid><description>
Thunderbird is an email program full featured with controls spam integration, mail filter, address book, news groups and more. It provides a clean interface and easy to use (customizable). Thunderbird also provides the security features such as S / MIME, digital signing, message encryption, support for certificates and security devices.
Before using this feature, you should review the settings IMAP, SMTP, and SSL/TLS his. Now, what all you need to do is provide your name, email address,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Dr. Hardware 2026 v26.0.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Dec 2025 16:38:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dr-hardware-12023.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dr-hardware-12023.html
</guid><description>
Dr Hardware is a computer hardware diagnostic and information tool designed to provide detailed information about the hardware components of a computer system. This is a software program that helps users analyze and troubleshoot computer hardware for you, identify potential problems, and gather comprehensive information about system configuration.
Dr Hardware can detect and identify various hardware components installed in a computer, including processor, memory, hard drive, graphics...
</description></item><item><title>Download Universal Radio Hacker 2.10.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Dec 2025 16:32:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-universal-radio-hacker-8491.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-universal-radio-hacker-8491.html
</guid><description>
Universal Radio Hacker (URH) is a complete suite for wireless protocol investigation with native support for multiple spectrum software defined Radios. variable. URH allows for easy signal demodulation combined with automatic detection of modulation parameters making it easy to identify bits and bytes flying through the air. Since data is often encrypted before transmission, URH offers customizable decryptors to crack even complex encryptions like CC1101 data whiten.
When it comes to...
</description></item><item><title>Download QontrolPanel (QuickSoundSwitcher) 1.10.4</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Dec 2025 16:32:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quicksoundswitcher-14033.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quicksoundswitcher-14033.html
</guid><description>
QuickSoundSwitcher is a lightweight, open-source Windows utility designed to quickly and easily manage audio input and output devices. It allows users to switch between multiple audio devices (e.g. speakers, headphones, microphones) and control the volume directly from the system tray without navigating to complex Windows settings.
The program also provides an application volume mixer, allowing for volume adjustment and muting for individual programs. This tool is especially useful for...
</description></item><item><title>Download Robin YouTube Video Downloader Pro 7.0.6</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Dec 2025 16:31:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-video-downloader-pro-2828.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-video-downloader-pro-2828.html
</guid><description>
YouTube Video Downloader Pro is a Windows application professional to download and convert videos from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion and thousands of video sharing sites, other. It accelerates your download up to 5 times. YouTube Video Downloader Pro allows you to download multiple videos at the same time. It also allows you to pause, resume and cancel a download at any time.
YouTube Video Downloader Pro - Download online videos on social networks
Features of YouTube Video Downloader...
</description></item><item><title>Download Zoner Studio 19.2509.2.666</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Dec 2025 16:31:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zoner-photo-studio-x-95.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zoner-photo-studio-x-95.html
</guid><description>
Zoner Photo Studio X Pro helps you to control your photos. Zoner Photo Studio is a complete toolbox for managing and processing digital photos. Get photos from your camera, organize your archive, and edit and share your photos - never been easier! Zoner Photo Studio is useful for beginners, advanced users and photographers with experience, who can choose one of four different variations. Zoner Photo Studio is made for every user of digital cameras, scanners, and mobile devices. It contains...
</description></item><item><title>Download Viber for PC 26.8.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Dec 2025 16:28:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-viber-2406.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-viber-2406.html
</guid><description>
Viber is a software of instant messaging, based on VoIP protocols, multi-platform due to the Viber Media development for smart phones used to send sms and make calls over the internet. Along with text messaging, users can exchange images, video and audio.
Viber - software news message, chat online
This is a program that is quite popular is mainly designed for mobile phones, but now we are talking about the version for Windows, so immediately. It will allow you to send messages to other...
</description></item><item><title>Download Process Explorer 17.09</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Dec 2025 16:27:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-process-explorer-370.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-process-explorer-370.html
</guid><description>
Process Explorer is a software to track and manage the active processes on your computer, at the same time, timely detection and debugging.  Process Explorer shows you information about the processing and the process DLL already open or download. Screen Process Explorer consists of two window. The top part always displays the list of processes that are currently active, including the name of the account owner of them
Process Explorer helps you get the look more depth, more details about...
</description></item><item><title>Download PC Timer 18.48</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Dec 2025 16:27:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pc-timer-7519.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pc-timer-7519.html
</guid><description>
PC Timer is a simple tool to automatically shut down, log out, restart or lock your PC based on your scheduled time. A handy feature of the app is its ability to prevent unauthorized cancellation of a scheduled task. To do so, PC Timer .NET allows you to set a password that the user must provide to cancel the operation.
The advantage of the application is its simplicity, small footprint on the system and the fact that it does not require installation. Thanks to the ability to set tasks...
</description></item><item><title>Download Directory Opus Pro 13.20.2 Beta</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Dec 2025 16:26:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-opus-pro-779.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-opus-pro-779.html
</guid><description>
Directory Opus Pro is a software replacement for Explorer with traditional strength and function more than any manager other files. Directory Opus Pro full support for high DPI screen (for example 4K and 5K) with the rename dialog is redesigned, with new features. Besides being a recording macro only allows you to perform mass renaming complex that don't need regular expressions. In addition, Directory Opus Pro also enhances the ability to script.Better handling of renaming recursive and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Social Media Downloader 8.0.6</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Dec 2025 16:21:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-socialmediaapps-facebook-video-downloader-3742.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-socialmediaapps-facebook-video-downloader-3742.html
</guid><description>
SocialVideo Downloader (formerly SocialMediaApps Facebook Video Downloader) is a Windows application to download and convert your favorite videos from Facebook and hundreds of other video sharing sites. It increases your loading speed by up to 500%, or even more! The application has a simple and intuitive user interface, its main functions and features are quite obvious to anyone. , regardless of prior experience with similar purpose tools.
&amp;nbsp;
SocialVideo Downloader
The main...
</description></item><item><title>Download QuickTextPaste 9.35</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Dec 2025 16:21:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quicktextpaste-2905.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quicktextpaste-2905.html
</guid><description>
QuickTextPaste is a mobile application that allows you to add (paste) the text to be predetermined quickly in any Microsoft Windows program through keyboard shortcuts. You can copy the software on any USB flash drive or other portable device and carry it with you whenever you have to automate the task, paste text messages quickly and easily without having to redo the installation steps.
QuickTextPaste - Create shortcut paste text
Although this app seems geared to users who have more...
</description></item><item><title>Download Win10 BrightnessSlider 1.8.28</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Dec 2025 16:20:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-win10-brightnessslider-3116.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-win10-brightnessslider-3116.html
</guid><description>
Win10 BrightnessSlider is an open source application, simple and light, will put a brightness control small screen on the Tray of your task bar. Utilities give you the ability to adjust the brightness of the screen just by a click of the mouse. Moreover, you will be able to adjust brightness for multiple screens using this program.
Win10 BrightnessSlider suitable mainly for laptops, allows you to adjust the brightness of the screen depending on the ambient light to have good visibility...
</description></item></channel></rss>