<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 17:38:46 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 17:38:46 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Disk Pulse Ultimate 17.4.28 + Enterprise + Pro</title><pubDate> Thu, 06 Nov 2025 20:37:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-disk-pulse-ultimate-1465.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-disk-pulse-ultimate-1465.html
</guid><description>
Disk Pulse Ultimate is a monitoring solution change disk real-time allows one to monitor one or more disks or directories, save reports and statistics monitoring disk changes, the change is detected to the SQL database focus, execute custom commands and send E-Mail notifications when unauthorized changes are detected in the file system important.
Disk Pulse Ultimate - Monitor disc change
DiskPulse provides the ability for users to start / stop the monitoring operation disc change,...
</description></item><item><title>Download AI Image Object Replacer Pro 1.0.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 06 Nov 2025 18:22:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ai-image-object-replacer-pro-14249.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ai-image-object-replacer-pro-14249.html
</guid><description>
Are you tired of unwanted objects, people, or text cluttering up your perfect photos? Do you wish you could magically replace a dull sky or fix a buggy background without having to learn complicated software?
AI Image Object Replacer Pro brings the power of advanced image-rendering AI right to your desktop. Easily remove, replace, or add anything you can imagine to your photos with just a few clicks and a simple text prompt. Our intuitive tools and powerful AI models make professional...
</description></item><item><title>Download Advanced Renamer Commercial 4.19</title><pubDate> Thu, 06 Nov 2025 18:22:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-renamer-2647.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-renamer-2647.html
</guid><description>
Advanced Renamer is a program to rename multiple files and folders at the same time. By configuring the method name change, the name can be manipulated in many different ways. It's easy to set up a batch job using multiple methods on a large number of files. 14 different modes allow you to change the name, attributes and timestamp of the file in once. The file can also be copied or moved to new location based on information in the file.
The program can rename files in many different ways,...
</description></item><item><title>Download AnyMP4 Blu-ray Ripper 8.1.68</title><pubDate> Thu, 06 Nov 2025 18:21:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anymp4-blu-ray-ripper-3150.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anymp4-blu-ray-ripper-3150.html
</guid><description>
AnyMP4 Blu-ray Ripper is an advanced application and comprehensive allowing you to easily and quickly extract the Blu-Ray to your hard drive. You can rip discs to a variety of formats audio and video file downloads. This app also includes a set of functions powerful editing allows you to trim video length. change video effect, crop video frame, add watermark to your video, and more.
AnyMP4 Blu-ray Ripper - ripping Blu-Ray
The app will allow you to extract Blu-Ray formats various...
</description></item><item><title>Download Xfer Records Serum 2.0.23</title><pubDate> Thu, 06 Nov 2025 18:21:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-serum-serum-fx-3557.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-serum-serum-fx-3557.html
</guid><description>
Serum &amp;amp; Serum FX has an editor Wavetable built right in - you can create the wavetables of his own in many different ways. Import audio directly from audio files - Serum &amp;amp; Serum FX there are many methods and options for analyzing audio to separate audio into the waveform individually. Of course, you can import the wavetables of a cycle, as well as many at the same time (with the option to arrange to be built or re-order craft). Morphology between the wavetables different using...
</description></item><item><title>Download OneCommander Pro 3.103.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 06 Nov 2025 18:20:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-one-commander-4232.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-one-commander-4232.html
</guid><description>
One Commander is a file manager for Microsoft Windows with function improved user interface and navigation experience, system file and manipulating the files. Utilities use the tree view to sort the folder, subfolders, and files your, make sure that the current location of you always clear. It supports multiple tabs, allowing you to easily switch between them and access the folder you need.
One Commander - a filemanager for Windows
Depending on the format of the files, some files can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Renee PassNow Pro 2025.11.04.153</title><pubDate> Thu, 06 Nov 2025 18:20:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-renee-passnow-pro-3975.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-renee-passnow-pro-3975.html
</guid><description>
Renee PassNow Pro is the application used to reset BIOS passwords, a feature quite useful when users need to make changes there but can't access the BIOS because the login information is forgotten. Users can take advantage of Renee PassNow to discover the faults of Windows and fix them, as long as they can not boot into the operating system anymore.
Renee PassNow Pro - password Recovery system
This tool can create direct means to recover data with just a few mouse clicks, as it can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Atlantis Word Processor 5.0.0.8</title><pubDate> Thu, 06 Nov 2025 18:19:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-atlantis-word-processor-585.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-atlantis-word-processor-585.html
</guid><description>
Atlantis Word Processor is a word processor app with features format, standard text, autocorrect, and spell check.  Atlantis is a word processor in accordance with most of the tasks handled daily text. The interface is very easy to use and offers the toolbars, hotkeys and sound effects thanh can customize (can turn off). It includes a clip library for quick access to the text or images used regular preview, font format and many other features aimed at improving the process of your...
</description></item><item><title>Download Directory Opus Pro 13.19.4 Beta</title><pubDate> Thu, 06 Nov 2025 18:19:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-opus-pro-779.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-opus-pro-779.html
</guid><description>
Directory Opus Pro is a software replacement for Explorer with traditional strength and function more than any manager other files. Directory Opus Pro full support for high DPI screen (for example 4K and 5K) with the rename dialog is redesigned, with new features. Besides being a recording macro only allows you to perform mass renaming complex that don't need regular expressions. In addition, Directory Opus Pro also enhances the ability to script.Better handling of renaming recursive and...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Downloader 9.18</title><pubDate> Thu, 06 Nov 2025 18:18:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html
</guid><description>
YTD Youtube Downloader is an application that reliable and intuitive, allowing you to quickly download YouTube videos and save them to your computer. You can also convert the media files to the format desired video or extract audio streams and save separately. YTD Youtube Downloader lets you save your favorite clips of yourself from Youtube, Facebook, Vimeo and Dailymotion to your desktop. The software supports URLS from many web site hosting, multimedia and allows you to download desired...
</description></item><item><title>Download SoftPerfect Switch Port Mapper 25.11</title><pubDate> Thu, 06 Nov 2025 18:12:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-softperfect-switch-port-mapper-976.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-softperfect-switch-port-mapper-976.html
</guid><description>
SoftPerfect Switch Port Mapper is a software that manages and reports network connection. Listed MAC address, IP address and host name of the computer is linked. In addition, software SoftPerfect Switch Port Mapper can display supplier network card of each customer, speed ports and timer the frame is defective and discarded for each port. This can be a good support when troubleshooting network connectivity.
SoftPerfect Switch Port Mapper - Manage and report network connection
The main...
</description></item><item><title>Download Minimal Firewall 2.5.4</title><pubDate> Thu, 06 Nov 2025 18:02:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minimal-firewall-13877.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minimal-firewall-13877.html
</guid><description>
Minimal Firewall works in conjunction with Windows Firewall to block all unknown connections by default, prompting you to create application-based rules to mitigate malware, telemetry, and data leaks. Completely eliminate applications that call home without your knowledge. Minimal Firewall provides a more secure and integrated approach by interacting directly with the native Windows Firewall, eliminating the need for risky system modifications.
Core Features
	Lockdown Mode: The core...
</description></item><item><title>Download 4KSoftware 4K Downloader 5.19</title><pubDate> Thu, 06 Nov 2025 18:02:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-downloader-3858.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-downloader-3858.html
</guid><description>
4K Downloader is a Windows application small but powerful to download and convert video in 4K and 8K Ultra HD from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion and thousands of other video-based websites. It speeds up your download by up to 5 times. Consider that most smart phones, TVS, computers, and tablets all support the high definition format, don't be surprised when many users want to enjoy quality content on their device. 4K Downloader is a lightweight software designed to help you grab videos...
</description></item><item><title>Download EMDB 5.40</title><pubDate> Thu, 06 Nov 2025 18:02:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-emdb-64.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-emdb-64.html
</guid><description>
EMDB (Eric's Movie Database) allows you to sort and catalog collection DVD of you.All you have to do is enter the title (or part of it) and the program will enter the detail information and movie cover image from a selection database online.You can then add personal ratings, customize the details, replace cover photo and also set the path local file (if you have a digital copy on your disk).
EMDB - sort and catalog collection DVD of you
Other features include an option to track movies...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Video Downloader 11.29</title><pubDate> Thu, 06 Nov 2025 18:01:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-video-downloader-9636.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-video-downloader-9636.html
</guid><description>
YT Video Downloader is software used to easily and quickly download any video or audio content from any website in HD quality using video downloader online. Save videos from almost any website supported by a video downloader on your local hard drive. Media search is a convenient way to do this.
Features of YT Video Downloader
	Download videos from hundreds of video sites.
	Really increase your download speed by up to 500% or even more!
	Download 8K, 5K, 4K Ultra HD, 2K Quad HD, 1080p...
</description></item><item><title>Download Vov Music Player 11.8</title><pubDate> Thu, 06 Nov 2025 18:01:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vov-music-player-2512.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vov-music-player-2512.html
</guid><description>
Vov Music Player is a program very easy to use, can play all your favourite music from the desired folder directly from the taskbar. Listening to music is an enjoyable activity, we often do it when sitting in front of computer just to dilute the situation, that is, this is not the main purpose of the in PC. Usually listen to music to as a complement for those moments when you are busy, for example, doing something more interesting, work or play. With this in mind, program Vov Music Player...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cash Register Pro 4.0.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 06 Nov 2025 18:00:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cash-register-pro-3853.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cash-register-pro-3853.html
</guid><description>
Cash Register Pro a software cash register full of features and creative for a Windows computer, it will help you to better handle all the activities of the computer money. The application comes with the user interface logical and user friendly allows you to work quickly and do not commit the common error. The program can be used on a number of computers and offers a wide range of authorization secure and reliable. Cash Register Pro will help you track products and goods remain...
</description></item><item><title>Download PACETEQ OneTiming 1.10.231</title><pubDate> Thu, 06 Nov 2025 18:00:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-paceteq-onetiming-12731.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-paceteq-onetiming-12731.html
</guid><description>
OneTiming integrates all important data sources, including all major timing protocols, GPS feeds, Race Control Messages, weather data and video feeds. The optimal balance of performance and durability is designed to be the benchmark for dynamic and complex racing environments.
Key Features of OneTiming
	Data Integration: OneTiming seamlessly combines information from multiple channels, including timekeeping, telemetry, weather data, and audio/video feeds. This integration supports all...
</description></item><item><title>Download Free Video Cutter Joiner 2025.5</title><pubDate> Thu, 06 Nov 2025 17:59:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-video-cutter-joiner-6770.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-video-cutter-joiner-6770.html
</guid><description>
Free Video Cutter Joiner is the easiest video cutter joiner software can cut large video file and remove unwanted parts like commercials, outtakes and trailers. Free Video Cutter Joiner works well with many file formats like AVI, MPEG, MP4, WMV, 3GP, FLV,etc.
Features of Free Video Cutter Joiner
	Supporting any audio and video formats including AVI, MP4, FLV, WMV, MOV, VOB, 3GP etc
	Free Video Cutter Joiner also can join serval video files into MP4,AVI,FLV, WMV, MOV, VOB, MPG format...
</description></item><item><title>Download Kaspersky Virus Removal Tool 20.0.14.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 06 Nov 2025 17:59:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kaspersky-virus-removal-tool-4513.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kaspersky-virus-removal-tool-4513.html
</guid><description>
In most cases, when the virus had on the PC purpose, one can not do much because the malware typically does not allow users to install or update any software anti-virus any. Kaspersky Virus Removal Tool gives you the tool to search and remove virus on computer quickly. Tool of Kaspersky has taken some protective measures: it can be installed on infected computers, even in safe Mode and it can automatically remove viruses, Trojans, rootkits, adware or spyware.
Kaspersky Virus Removal...
</description></item><item><title>Download Social Media Downloader 7.9</title><pubDate> Thu, 06 Nov 2025 17:58:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-socialmediaapps-facebook-video-downloader-3742.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-socialmediaapps-facebook-video-downloader-3742.html
</guid><description>
SocialVideo Downloader (formerly SocialMediaApps Facebook Video Downloader) is a Windows application to download and convert your favorite videos from Facebook and hundreds of other video sharing sites. It increases your loading speed by up to 500%, or even more! The application has a simple and intuitive user interface, its main functions and features are quite obvious to anyone. , regardless of prior experience with similar purpose tools.
&amp;nbsp;
SocialVideo Downloader
The main...
</description></item><item><title>Download Flyby11 1.51.644</title><pubDate> Thu, 06 Nov 2025 17:57:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-flyby11-12467.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-flyby11-12467.html
</guid><description>
Flyby11 is a simple patcher that removes annoying restrictions that prevent you from installing Windows 11 (24H2) on unsupported hardware. Do you have an old PC? No TPM, Secure Boot or your processor is not supported? Flyby11 allows you to install Windows 11 24H2. There are no complicated steps. Just run the tool and you'll be running Windows 11 on your outdated machine in no time.
Technical overview
Flyby11 takes advantage of a feature of the Windows 11 setup process that uses the...
</description></item><item><title>Download IK Multimedia ARC X 1.0.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 06 Nov 2025 17:57:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ik-multimedia-arc-system-11503.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ik-multimedia-arc-system-11503.html
</guid><description>
ARC 4 combines ultra-precise measurement microphones, analysis software, and calibration plugins to improve the accuracy of your monitoring in any room. Work faster and more freely, confident that you're hearing your own music and that your music will sound great anywhere. With a faster, easier calibration process, new more natural algorithms, and configuration management on ARC Studio hardware, everything about ARC Studio is designed to help you focus on your music and creating tones....
</description></item><item><title>Download Flyoobe 1.51.644</title><pubDate> Thu, 06 Nov 2025 17:56:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oobelux-13956.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oobelux-13956.html
</guid><description>
Flyoobe was born out of the frustration many users felt with the Windows 11 setup experience. Whether it was the mandatory online account, the endless "Next, next, next..." screens, or the incomplete configuration options when you finally reached the desktop, the current setup lacked focus on what users really wanted.
Why choose Flyoobe?
	Simplifies the Windows 11 setup process right out of the box.
	Allows easy local account creation without need to hunt for hidden options.
	Includes...
</description></item><item><title>Download dbForge Studio for MySQL Enterprise 2025.2.109</title><pubDate> Thu, 06 Nov 2025 17:55:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbforge-studio-for-mysql-enterprise-edition-7743.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbforge-studio-for-mysql-enterprise-edition-7743.html
</guid><description>
dbForge Studio for MySQL is a popular GUI tool for developing, managing, and administering MySQL and MariaDB databases. The IDE allows you to create and execute queries, develop and debug stored procedures, automate database object management, and analyze table data through an intuitive interface. The MySQL client provides data and schema comparison and synchronization tools, database reporting tools, backup options with scheduling, and much more.
Features of dbForge Studio for...
</description></item></channel></rss>