<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 14:33:27 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 14:33:27 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Text Editor Pro 35.4.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 16 Feb 2026 17:23:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-text-editor-pro-800.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-text-editor-pro-800.html
</guid><description>
Text Editor Pro is software to handle text, HTML, Perl, Ruby, or Fortran with features syntax highlighting, professional. Text Editor provides syntax highlighting for over 50 scripts and has a simple interface and easy access. In addition, the Text Editor Pro also supports more than 50 programming languages like C ++, COBOL, graph DOT, DSP, DWScript, Fortran, Foxpro, Java, Perl, Python, Ruby, SQL and many other languages.
Text Editor Pro - text Processing professional
The software can...
</description></item><item><title>Download DesktopOK 12.29</title><pubDate> Mon, 16 Feb 2026 17:23:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopok-1635.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopok-1635.html
</guid><description>
DesktopOK is software save and restore the positions of icons. DesktopOK also offers a solution small but effective for the user to change the screen resolution often. DesktopOK is not installed and can be executed easily from the desktop, and can be carried on a small USB or memory device to another. Start of the program. The first time you use the program, the program will show you screen license. Free program and license info is only displayed the first time (on each PC).
DesktopOK -...
</description></item><item><title>Download EFI Boot Editor 1.5.6</title><pubDate> Mon, 16 Feb 2026 17:22:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-efi-boot-editor-7475.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-efi-boot-editor-7475.html
</guid><description>
EFI Boot Editor is a program that provides you with a graphical interface to check your current boot settings and make modifications to the EFI Boot Manager. With Windows Boot Manager you can check Description, path, category, general settings like timeout and whether properties are active or hidden. Optionally, the application can provide the same information in other formats, namel HEX, BASE64, UTF-8 or UTF-16.
Features of EFI Boot Editor
	Edit startup items.
	Add, remove, and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Certificate Manager 19.3</title><pubDate> Mon, 16 Feb 2026 17:21:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-certificate-manager-13958.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-certificate-manager-13958.html
</guid><description>
Certificate Manager provides an in-depth overview of your current certificates, allowing you to easily access detailed information. It also provides functions for both exporting existing certificates and importing new certificates, enhancing your certificate management capabilities.
Application certificates are often overlooked by most users until problems arise during application installation. For the average end user, there is little reason to focus on application certificates....
</description></item><item><title>Download ReShade 6.7.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 16 Feb 2026 17:20:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-450-3227.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-450-3227.html
</guid><description>
ReShade is an open Source tool help improve the look of the old games on modern video cards as well as allow additional display technology / new video over on the old game doesn't support the technology that.
ReShade, technically, is a tool processing general for the games and video software. Imagine you see your favorite game yourself with the obscure-around, effects market the true depth or color correction. Function ReShade by showing in an automatic way and general access to...
</description></item><item><title>Download CoolUtils Total Doc Converter 5.1.0.374/146</title><pubDate> Mon, 16 Feb 2026 17:18:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-total-doc-converter-84.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-total-doc-converter-84.html
</guid><description>
CoolUtils Total Doc Converter Program that will allow you to document conversion DOC to others, the list can be viewed on the official website or you can watch carefully the screenshot, I think the question would no longer can download CoolUtils Total Doc Converter below. There is batch processing,in general, everything is convenient, I hope you like it.
Total Doc Converter is conversion tools text comprehensive and multi-featured, very necessary when storing or printing the text. It also...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinScript 1.4.8</title><pubDate> Mon, 16 Feb 2026 17:17:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winscript-12800.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winscript-12800.html
</guid><description>
WinScript is an open source tool built to help you build custom scripts for Windows 10 and 11. It includes scripts for debugging, privacy, performance, and more, along with the ability to install all your favorite apps with just one click.
Features
	Debloat: Remove Windows bloatware, CoPilot, Edge, OneDrive, and other pre-installed features preset.
	Privacy: Disable Windows and 3rd party data collection, tracking, app access, and telemetry.
	Performance: Set background services to...
</description></item><item><title>Download PortableApps.com Installer 3.9.9</title><pubDate> Mon, 16 Feb 2026 17:16:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-portableappscom-installer-7673.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-portableappscom-installer-7673.html
</guid><description>
PortableApps.com Installer is an easy-to-use multilingual installer that allows you to package your portable applications without writing code. PortableApps.com Installer can be run from a cloud folder, an external drive or a local folder without installing to Windows. It's even better with the PortableApps.com Platform for easy installation and automatic updates.
Features of PortableApps.com Installer
	Proven NSIS Installer Core
	Excellent compression for distribution
	Easy...
</description></item><item><title>Download NIUBI Partition Editor Technician WinPE 10.3.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 16 Feb 2026 17:14:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-niubi-partition-editor-enterprise-edition-3461.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-niubi-partition-editor-enterprise-edition-3461.html
</guid><description>
NIUBI Partition Editor Enterprise Edition is designed for organizations medium and large. It supports Windows Server 2019/2016/2012/2008/2003, small business server 2011/2008/2003 and Windows 10/8/7 / Vista / XP (32 &amp;amp; 64 bit). Hard drive local / mobile, VMware, Hyper-V and all kinds of RAID array hardware are supported.
The enterprise version can be registered on the PC and unlimited servers belong to your organization, regardless of location. Partition manager enterprise helps you to...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube Downloader 3.9.18 (1502)</title><pubDate> Mon, 16 Feb 2026 17:13:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube Downloader  is a dedicated software that helps users  downloading youtube videos  Favorites on PC for offline viewing. With MediaHuman YouTube  Downloader  you can download videos from youtube website to your computer with  fast speed , with special software development technology that automatically receives videos from Websites, in addition to the ability to download videos from software websites, can convert downloaded video formats to various formats for the purpose...
</description></item><item><title>Download Snappy Driver Installer 1.26.1 (R2601)</title><pubDate> Mon, 16 Feb 2026 17:12:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-snappy-driver-installer-9472.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-snappy-driver-installer-9472.html
</guid><description>
Snappy Driver Installer is a free and open source software tool designed to help users install and update device drivers on Windows operating systems. Device drivers are software programs that allow the operating system to communicate with and control hardware devices such as graphics cards, sound cards, network adapters, etc.
It's important to note that while Snappy Driver Installer can be a useful tool for managing drivers on Windows systems, we always recommend caution when...
</description></item><item><title>Download MetaProducts Portable Offline Browser 8.8.0.5012</title><pubDate> Mon, 16 Feb 2026 17:11:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-metaproducts-portable-offline-browser-4701.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-metaproducts-portable-offline-browser-4701.html
</guid><description>
MetaProducts Portable Offline Browser is the leading app in the industry to store and download at website, MetaProducts Portable Offline Browser provides technology download at high level and strong features. Hosting your website automatically on a regular basis. Copy the website downloaded directly to your hard drive or to external media to another, such as a Flash drive or DVD. Storing downloaded content in any format: ZIP, CHM, EXE.
It's easy to download the website large amount or...
</description></item><item><title>Download Psiphon 186.20260215</title><pubDate> Mon, 16 Feb 2026 17:10:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-psiphon-7347.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-psiphon-7347.html
</guid><description>
Psiphon is a firewall bypass tool by Psiphon Inc. Uses VPN, SSH and HTTP Proxy technology to give you uncensored access to Internet content. Your Psiphon app automatically learns about new hotspots to maximize your chances of bypassing censorship.
The way the software works is that Psiphon constantly changes the proxy, so the user's IP address is also constantly changing, the server will not detect the user's real address, so you can feel free. roof. access to websites and software...
</description></item><item><title>Download MyLanViewer Enterprise 6.7.6</title><pubDate> Mon, 16 Feb 2026 17:09:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mylanviewer-enterprise-1274.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mylanviewer-enterprise-1274.html
</guid><description>
MyLanViewer is a program for scanning IP address, Netbios and LAN / Network powerful for Windows tool whois and traceroute, remote shutdown and process management Wake On LAN (WOL), scan and monitor wireless networks. This app will help you find all IP addresses, MAC addresses and shared folders of computers on the network wired or wireless (Wi-Fi).
MyLanViewer Enterprise - Scan IP address LAN/Network
The program scans network and displays the computer network in your window, friends...
</description></item><item><title>Download Executor 2.2.4.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 16 Feb 2026 17:09:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-executor-271.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-executor-271.html
</guid><description>
Executor for windows is a software alternative premium customization features for the Windows "Run" and "Search Programs". When you press WIN + Z and provides the search results instant, as-you-type for any keywords you enter. By default, Executor will index all the Desktop and Start Menu and you can easily expand the search range by adding the folder location additional.
Executor for windows
The program comes with a list of commands built in which you can use to quickly access many...
</description></item><item><title>Download Revive Faces 2.0.13</title><pubDate> Mon, 16 Feb 2026 17:08:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-revive-faces-13762.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-revive-faces-13762.html
</guid><description>
Have you ever looked at an old photo or video and wished you could see those faces clearly again? Time, blurriness, and pixels shouldn't steal the smiles, glances, or stories of the people you love. With Revive Faces, our breakthrough AI-powered restoration software, blurry, smudged, and pixelated faces can now shine with stunning clarity—as if they were taken yesterday.
Why Restore Faces?
	See the unseen again – Our advanced AI not only sharpens images, but also recreates lost...
</description></item><item><title>Download IM-Magic Partition Resizer 7.9.0 All Editions</title><pubDate> Mon, 16 Feb 2026 17:07:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-im-magic-partition-resizer-4544.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-im-magic-partition-resizer-4544.html
</guid><description>
IM-Magic Partition Resizer is tool magic partition for free to help shrink, expand, move, and merge the partitions without damaging data. It only needs a few mouse clicks from you to command software move the fence to perform on the disk partition and keep your files intact.
IM-Magic Partition Resizer - Restore hard drive partition
IM-Magic Partition Resizer helps to improve the volume boot to keep your system is not format the disk, reinstall the operating system or moving information...
</description></item><item><title>Download Howard Email Notifier 2.16</title><pubDate> Mon, 16 Feb 2026 17:06:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-howard-email-notifier-2231.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-howard-email-notifier-2231.html
</guid><description>
A simple program that on the taskbar next to the clock will inform you about the letters and new messages on the social network. As can be seen from the screenshot, it can operate with the account, Outlook, Gmail, Yahoo, Facebook, Twitter, Zoho, Mail.ru, Notes, and Virgilio.
Howard Email Notifier - email notification and social networking
Get notified about new emails in live.com, hotmail.com, mail.google.com, mail.yahoo.com, facebook.com, twitter.com, e.mail.ru IBM / Lotus Notes,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Coolutils Total Excel Converter 7.1.0.109</title><pubDate> Mon, 16 Feb 2026 17:06:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-total-excel-converter-849.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-total-excel-converter-849.html
</guid><description>
Coolutils Total Excel Converter is software that converts Excel documents to other formats like ODS, XML, SQL, WK2, WKS WAB, DBF, TEX and DIF for you to use. In addition, the software also supports converting Excel files into file DOC, DOCX, PDF, HTML, Access, TXT, ODT, ODS, XML, SQL, CSV, Lotus, DBF, TEX, DIFF, SYLK and LaTeX.
Coolutils Total Excel Converter - batch convert Excel
Total Excel Converter has a perfect layout and tight. When the conversion is finished you will get an...
</description></item><item><title>Download ET Optimizer 6.09.15</title><pubDate> Mon, 16 Feb 2026 17:05:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-et-optimizer-9574.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-et-optimizer-9574.html
</guid><description>
ET-Optimizer is a free, open source script to improve your computer's overall performance and optimize it for your workflow through optimized scripting. With this optimization, setup takes little effort. The script is developed from many sources found on the Internet, tested and updated for different versions of the system. The whole script is contained in 1 file, it uses: command prompt, powershell, power plan configuration, startup configuration, registry changes, network interface...
</description></item><item><title>Download MetaProducts Offline Explorer Enterprise 8.8.0.5012</title><pubDate> Mon, 16 Feb 2026 17:04:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-metaproducts-offline-explorer-enterprise-2653.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-metaproducts-offline-explorer-enterprise-2653.html
</guid><description>
MetaProducts Offline Explorer Enterprise is one of the most powerful programs to download both individual files and whole website. It works with HTTP, FTP and HTTPS. After download website to your hard drive, you can see it without need to connect to the Internet, and the download page will be much faster, because the Internet can sometimes work is slow, simply can different error.
MetaProducts Offline Explorer Enterprise is the leading application in the industry about storage and ing...
</description></item><item><title>Download Unicodia 3.1.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 16 Feb 2026 17:04:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-unicodia-8521.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-unicodia-8521.html
</guid><description>
Unicodia is free, open source software that can be used as an alternative character map for your Windows machine. The interface contains everything you need, allowing you to easily cycle through all the available ASCII symbols and copy them to the clipboard. Uncicodia is a great alternative to your standard Unicode characters and is filled with symbols/characters that make it useful for a number of different uses.
Features of Unicodia
	In Windows 10/11 — all characters of Unicode 15...
</description></item><item><title>Download MassTube 2026 v21.5.0.190 Ultra</title><pubDate> Mon, 16 Feb 2026 17:03:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-masstube-plus-461.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-masstube-plus-461.html
</guid><description>
MassTube Plus is a small utility used to download the favorite videos of you on youtube on your computer. This is a software compact, has a simple design with few options to download videos fastest. The you complete peace of mind because the software is easy to use, built exclusively for a single goal: to retrieve the video file from YouTube, so it doesn't pack the other useful features such as search engine integrated and a download audio file.
MassTube can work with multiple output...
</description></item><item><title>Download GPU-Z Portable 2.69.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 16 Feb 2026 17:02:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gpu-z-portable-11862.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gpu-z-portable-11862.html
</guid><description>
GPU-Z is a lightweight and portable software utility that provides users with detailed information about their graphics processing unit (GPU) and video card. This app is useful for monitoring your GPU's performance, verifying its specifications, and troubleshooting any problems that may arise.
GPU-Z Portable Features
	One of the main advantages of GPU-Z Portable is its portability. You can run the application directly from a USB flash drive or any other portable device without...
</description></item><item><title>Download Xmanager Power Suite 8.0.0017</title><pubDate> Mon, 16 Feb 2026 17:00:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xmanager-power-suite-4036.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xmanager-power-suite-4036.html
</guid><description>
Xmanager Power Suite is the network connection complete. The products include: Xmanager (server, PC X high performance); Xshell (SSH client, strong); Xftp (client-SFTP / FTP); Xlpd (a print management tools work). Xmanager Power Suite is a solution all-in-one includes Xmanager, Xshell, Xftp and Xlpd in a single set. Xmanager run the app window X and Xshell manage servers Unix / Linux remotely with a terminal safety. Xftp transfers files between systems securely, and Xlpd runs in locally...
</description></item></channel></rss>