<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 13:43:19 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 13:43:19 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Viber for PC 26.1.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Sep 2025 16:42:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-viber-2406.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-viber-2406.html
</guid><description>
Viber is a software of instant messaging, based on VoIP protocols, multi-platform due to the Viber Media development for smart phones used to send sms and make calls over the internet. Along with text messaging, users can exchange images, video and audio.
Viber - software news message, chat online
This is a program that is quite popular is mainly designed for mobile phones, but now we are talking about the version for Windows, so immediately. It will allow you to send messages to other...
</description></item><item><title>Download ZebraDesigner Professional 3.3.0.89</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Sep 2025 16:41:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zebradesigner-pro-7203.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zebradesigner-pro-7203.html
</guid><description>
ZebraDesigner Pro is an easy-to-use disc label design software that helps users create high-quality barcode labels quickly. With ZebraDesigner Pro software, you can easily create a variety of labels, whether simple or complex. Thanks to its user-friendly, Windows-based interface, no training or technical know-how is required. Another benefit is that design and editing is done in one window.
ZebraDesigner Pro provides users with the most used disc label design features, and includes a...
</description></item><item><title>Download Auslogics Duplicate File Finder Professional 11.1.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Sep 2025 16:41:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-auslogics-duplicate-file-finder-professional-12706.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-auslogics-duplicate-file-finder-professional-12706.html
</guid><description>
Auslogics Duplicate File Finder Professional is a software tool designed to help users identify and remove duplicate files from their systems effectively. When disk space starts to run out, you need a tool that allows you to clear memory in addition to regular trash cleaning. A duplicate finder is one of the best options that can often delete gigabytes on any computer.
Features of Auslogics Duplicate File Finder Professional
	Scan most types of drives for duplicates: With Duplicate...
</description></item><item><title>Download Directory Opus Pro 13.18.2 Beta</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Sep 2025 16:40:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-opus-pro-779.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-opus-pro-779.html
</guid><description>
Directory Opus Pro is a software replacement for Explorer with traditional strength and function more than any manager other files. Directory Opus Pro full support for high DPI screen (for example 4K and 5K) with the rename dialog is redesigned, with new features. Besides being a recording macro only allows you to perform mass renaming complex that don't need regular expressions. In addition, Directory Opus Pro also enhances the ability to script.Better handling of renaming recursive and...
</description></item><item><title>Download WizFlow Flowcharter Professional 7.45.2215</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Sep 2025 16:40:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wizflow-flowcharter-professional-3604.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wizflow-flowcharter-professional-3604.html
</guid><description>
WizFlow Flowcharter Professional is a tool for drawing diagrams and diagram easy-to-use, feature-rich, abundant for Windows. WizFlow lets you define "styles" shape using more than a hundred shapes and arrow heads to be determined first. Save your styles in the template to set the method of mapping your own. WizFlow comes with the template complete diagram to help you get started. WizFlow can create flowcharts and diagrams similar with minimal effort. When you draw a diagram of WizFlow...
</description></item><item><title>Download FileLocator Pro 2022 Build 3530</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Sep 2025 16:39:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-filelocator-pro-1056.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-filelocator-pro-1056.html
</guid><description>
FileLocator Pro is software manage files and search function the file quickly the software and data. FileLocator Pro helps you find things quickly. The unique feature of it allows the extraction of information in all file formats the most obscure.
FileLocator Pro - file Manager
The features of FileLocator Pro
	Search algorithm based on the C ++ multi-threading for ultra-fast
	Search for network drive by mapped drive or UNC paths
	Support regular expressions for file name and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Auslogics Duplicate File Finder 11.1.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Sep 2025 16:39:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-auslogics-duplicate-file-finder-1248.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-auslogics-duplicate-file-finder-1248.html
</guid><description>
Auslogics Duplicate File Finder is an application completely free on taiwebs.com user support, Windows search and delete the duplicate files due to the process of copying and storage for long days on your computer. The first thing the user sees is the software interface is very simple and easy to use. After process launch, Auslogics Duplicate File Finder will find and delete duplicate files from it will liberate space on the hard drive of your computer by finding and eliminate the...
</description></item><item><title>Download QuadSpinner Gaea 2.2.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Sep 2025 16:38:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quadspinner-gaea-3870.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quadspinner-gaea-3870.html
</guid><description>
QuadSpinner Gaea is design software terrain, sophisticated and modern for results the top in moments. The top tools of QuadSpinner Gaea makes realism became the basis. Workflows are streamlined, allowing you to easily gain visibility and work in parallel with your team. Interface is extremely modern and our multitude of gadgets stimulate creativity, not limit it. Working at Gaea very interesting and can help you set a performance standard new.
QuadSpinner Gaea - design software...
</description></item><item><title>Download EDGE Diagrammer 7.45.2215</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Sep 2025 16:38:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-edge-diagrammer-9462.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-edge-diagrammer-9462.html
</guid><description>
EDGE Diagrammer is a software application used to create graphical diagrams, especially in the field of systems engineering. The term "EDGE" stands for "Enhanced Diagram Graphics Environment". It provides a user-friendly interface and a set of tools for designing and documenting complex systems, processes, and workflows.
EDGE Diagrammer is all you need for block diagrams, flowcharts, organization charts, family trees, data flow diagrams and more. Free extension packs are available to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Geekbench Pro 6.5</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Sep 2025 15:46:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-geekbench-pro-606.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-geekbench-pro-606.html
</guid><description>
Geekbench Pro 4 gauge power your system and let you know whether your computer is ready to roar up. Mobile device or computer to your desk how strong? Each workload CPU model a task or application in the real world, to ensure meaningful results. The trial is very complex, avoid the incidents with simple patterns, memory access, simple and push the limits of your system.
Features Geekbench Pro
Calculate the benchmark
	Measuring the calculation performance of your GPU with benchmark...
</description></item><item><title>Download IK Multimedia Tonex Max 1.10.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Sep 2025 15:45:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ik-multimedia-tonex-max-7877.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ik-multimedia-tonex-max-7877.html
</guid><description>
TONEX software uses groundbreaking AI Machine Modeling technology to let you model the sound of any amp, cabinet, or combo and turn it into a plug-in, all with precision sounds are almost indistinguishable from reality. You can instantly play up to the more than 1,000 already available Melody Models along with browsing, performing, and downloading more and more Melody Models available on TONEX in ToneNET.
Features of IK Multimedia Tonex Max
	Modeled tone generator, player,...
</description></item><item><title>Download MusConv 4.10.414 Lifetime</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Sep 2025 15:45:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html
</guid><description>
MusConv transfers playlists, albums, followed artists and liked songs across a variety of services – Spotify, Apple Music, Amazon Music, YouTube, YouTube Music, iTunes, Deezer, Tidal, SoundCloud, Pandora and more 125 music services!
Features of MusConv Ultimate
	Transfer playlists, albums, followed artists and liked tracks between over 125 music servicesManage playlists (Delete, Merge, Split, Copy...)
	More than 125 music services supported
	Access DAILY updated music charts on...
</description></item><item><title>Download Calibre 8.10.0 + Portable</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Sep 2025 15:44:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-calibre-1669.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-calibre-1669.html
</guid><description>
Calibre  is an eBook library management application that allows you to manage your eBook collection, convert eBooks between different formats, Sync with popular e-reading devices and read your e-books with included viewer. You can sort books by author, title, date and other details, download meta information and book covers, add personalized tags and comments, and view your images in the cover display.
Collection of essential tools for adding metadata editing books or managing your...
</description></item><item><title>Download VovSoft AI Requester 4.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Sep 2025 15:43:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-ai-requester-8997.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-ai-requester-8997.html
</guid><description>
Vovsoft AI Requester is a program that can connect to OpenAI API easily. The software provides users with a reliable and easy-to-use interface that seamlessly integrates with the latest AI technologies, including GPT-3.5 and GPT-4.
Just like ChatGPT, you can connect to the OpenAI platform and start chatting with powerful AI bots capable of giving intelligent responses to a variety of queries and questions. The software is designed to be user-friendly and intuitive, allowing even...
</description></item><item><title>Download AutoHideMouseCursor 5.85</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Sep 2025 15:43:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-autohidemousecursor-4104.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-autohidemousecursor-4104.html
</guid><description>
AutoHideMouseCursor is a Microsoft Windows application mobile mini allows you to hide the cursor, if the mouse is not active for a period of time. With AutoHideMouseCursor you can automatically hide the mouse cursor with the timer can be customized this is utility desktop perfect when the cursor is too annoying to them, such as when used with the application handling the text because often when you add pointers, text and cover text.
AutoHideMouseCursor - Hide mouse cursor
User...
</description></item><item><title>Download Brave Browser 1.82.161</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Sep 2025 15:42:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-brave-browser-2874.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-brave-browser-2874.html
</guid><description>
Brave Browser is a browser based on Chromium, the basic principle is that operation fast and privacy of users. The program can block pop-up windows and other ads, plus it blocked the mechanism for monitoring the online activities of your. Therefore, you can purchase and safely browse the website you are interested in without having to worry about the fact that your activity will be monitored and then you will be shown the necessary advertising or service provider of parties...
</description></item><item><title>Download priPrinter Professional 7.0.0.2608</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Sep 2025 15:42:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-priprinter-professional-633.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-priprinter-professional-633.html
</guid><description>
priPrinter Professional is the printer driver allows you to manipulate the output of the printer before being printed. PriPrinter is installed and select the same as the printer driver other. After printing it automatically displays the preview in where you can preview his print, change the layout, page position back, cut them, and much more. Then, you print it to printer or save your document for later use. With PriPrinter you will always be sure his prints will look like. You can measure...
</description></item><item><title>Download ChessBase 18.15</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Sep 2025 15:41:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chessbase-13889.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chessbase-13889.html
</guid><description>
ChessBase is the personal, independent chess database that has become the world standard. Everyone uses ChessBase, from World Champions to the amateur player next door. It is the program of choice for anyone who loves the game and wants to learn more about it. Start your personal success story with ChessBase and enjoy the game even more.
Whether it's preparing for an individual opponent or tournament, managing and analyzing your own games, developing training materials for self-study or...
</description></item><item><title>Download Picture Window Pro 8.0.527</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Sep 2025 15:41:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-picture-window-pro-7452.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-picture-window-pro-7452.html
</guid><description>
Picture Window Pro is a powerful image editing tool designed for serious photographers with strict creative and quality standards. Its comprehensive set of photo editing and editing tools let you control and shape every aspect of your images.
Picture Window Pro 8 is a complete rewrite of Picture Window Pro 7. It features non-destructive image editing through a novel interface based on an image tree. It also fully supports large, high-resolution displays and can be used in dual monitor...
</description></item><item><title>Download App Builder 2025.31</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Sep 2025 15:40:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-app-builder-241.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-app-builder-241.html
</guid><description>
App Builder is a software application developer to help create and design apps, HTML5, web app, web app PWA on both platforms mobile and desktop. App Builder is professional software supports users to create the program HTML5 without writing code. It is very easy to use, suitable with all users who lack of professional knowledge in the field of programming and application design.
App Builder brings to 22 different themes that users can use to design for your app. You can choose 1 or a...
</description></item><item><title>Download Diffraction Limited MaxIm DL 7.2.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Sep 2025 15:40:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-diffraction-limited-maxim-dl-12651.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-diffraction-limited-maxim-dl-12651.html
</guid><description>
Diffraction Limited MaxIm DL is a specialized software designed for low-light and astrophotography applications, primarily using scientific-grade CCD cameras. Here's an overview of features, versions, and user feedback. Once your images are collected, MaxIm DL can automatically assemble your calibration images into groups, select the correct group for each individual image, calibrate and stack your images. You can process hundreds of images from different targets with just a few...
</description></item><item><title>Download priPrinter Server 7.0.0.2608</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Sep 2025 15:40:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-priprinter-server-9402.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-priprinter-server-9402.html
</guid><description>
priPrinter Server is a software solution that provides advanced printability and manageability for networked environments. It is designed to enhance the printing process, providing features that improve efficiency, reduce costs, and allow centralized control of print jobs. Finally, you can print your work to a real printer in one-sided or two-sided mode, saving it as a PDF or image file. Print history is readily available and easy to use, allowing you to check or reprint previously...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinScript 1.4.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Sep 2025 15:39:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winscript-12800.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winscript-12800.html
</guid><description>
WinScript is an open source tool built to help you build custom scripts for Windows 10 and 11. It includes scripts for debugging, privacy, performance, and more, along with the ability to install all your favorite apps with just one click.
Features
	Debloat: Remove Windows bloatware, CoPilot, Edge, OneDrive, and other pre-installed features preset.
	Privacy: Disable Windows and 3rd party data collection, tracking, app access, and telemetry.
	Performance: Set background services to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Softwarenetz Invoice Rechnung 11.23</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Sep 2025 15:39:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-softwarenetz-invoice-5588.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-softwarenetz-invoice-5588.html
</guid><description>
Softwarenetz Invoice is a useful program for self-employed, freelancers and small companies who are in need of a simple and user-friendly program for invoicing. The invoice program contains the complete address / customer database. You can see at a glance all invoices, payments and reminders for a particular customer. The memo field gives you the opportunity to enter customer specific information. Importing existing client from csv file is also included.
You can print your invoice on your...
</description></item><item><title>Download Telegram for Desktop 6.1.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Sep 2025 15:38:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-telegram-3376.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-telegram-3376.html
</guid><description>
Telegram is an instant messaging service and voice over IP services on the cloud platform. Client application Telegram is available for Android, iOS, Windows Phone, Windows NT, macOS, and Linux. Users can send messages and exchange photos, videos, stickers, audio and files of any kind.
Telegram - Messaging and free phone calls
Telegram seamless sync across all your devices and can be used on desktop, tablet and phone. You can send unlimited amount of messages, photos, videos and files...
</description></item></channel></rss>