<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 13:45:12 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 13:45:12 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Radiant Photo 2.1.1.790 + Addon Pack</title><pubDate> Fri, 10 Oct 2025 15:01:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-radiant-photo-8319.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-radiant-photo-8319.html
</guid><description>
Radiant Photo is a photo editing software that allows users to edit, enhance and organize their digital photos. It provides many tools to adjust color, brightness, contrast, saturation, and other image properties, as well as features to crop, rotate, and resize images.
Radiant Photo also includes many filters and effects that can be applied to photos to change their appearance. Additionally, it also allows users to organize their photos by creating albums, tagging photos, and searching...
</description></item><item><title>Download FastCopy Pro 5.11.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 10 Oct 2025 15:01:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fastcopy-pro-9404.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fastcopy-pro-9404.html
</guid><description>
FastCopy Pro is file copying and synchronization software designed to provide faster and more efficient file transfer operations than native file copying tools in operating system. It provides various features and optimizations to enhance the speed and reliability of file copying.
It can copy/delete unicode and more than MAX_PATH(260byte) pathname files. Automatically, after copy source and copy destination are HDD under the same physical HDD or evaluated, it will work as follows. Diff...
</description></item><item><title>Download 7 Caps 11.0 + Portable</title><pubDate> Fri, 10 Oct 2025 15:00:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-7-caps-3194.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-7-caps-3194.html
</guid><description>
7 Caps is a very small application that aims to notify you in real time whether the status of the keyboard Num Lock or Caps Lock change in real time. 7 Caps will be a money saver when the indicator light on the keyboard or laptop your current activities help you save or repair, or if you just want to verify functional status. This mode will be useful when entering a passage from a web page on a local documents, for example. But that's not all; you get some custom lightweight allows you to...
</description></item><item><title>Download WSCC Windows System Control Center 10.0.1.1 Commercial</title><pubDate> Fri, 10 Oct 2025 14:59:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wscc-windows-system-control-center-1599.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wscc-windows-system-control-center-1599.html
</guid><description>
WSCC Windows System Control Center can automatically install and update the add-ons are supported. Alternatively, WSCC can use the http protocol to download and run the program. WSCC is portable device, no installation required. Extract content of zip archive downloaded into any folder on your computer.
The interface is very simple and intuitive, thus allowing any type of user how to find his way, regardless of the experience of their previous with the IT world. Besides, it includes a...
</description></item><item><title>Download Quick Access Popup 12.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 10 Oct 2025 14:58:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quick-access-popup-984.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quick-access-popup-984.html
</guid><description>
Quick Access Popup  ( QAP ) is a software that provides quick access to files, files, windows applications and is  shortcut manager , mouse and keyboard.  Quick Access Popup  helps you quickly move between FILE, DOCUMENT, APPS in Windows Explorer or file dialog to quickly launch applications, documents or web pages at once 
To launch the pop-up menu, click the  QAP  icon in the Notifications area, press the Middle mouse button, or press Windows + W (these triggers can be changed under...
</description></item><item><title>Download Trillian 6.6 Build 6</title><pubDate> Fri, 10 Oct 2025 14:58:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-trillian-2638.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-trillian-2638.html
</guid><description>
Trillian is the chat help you sign in to more the registered name of a certain service or you can log on at the same time many services in a working window. It integrates multiple services such as Yahoo! MSN, IRC, AIM and ICQ. In addition, you can manage Email accounts, Facebook and Twitter friends - all in just one application.
Login is easy; just click on the network or the appropriate website and log in as normal. Trillian requires access your data (accepted) and post to friends...
</description></item><item><title>Download 4K Tokkit Pro 25.4.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 10 Oct 2025 14:57:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-tokkit-pro-6753.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-tokkit-pro-6753.html
</guid><description>
4K Tokkit Pro is an application created to bulk download TikTok content., save TikTok videos, captions, entire accounts, hashtags and single videos in high quality. . Watch TikToks offline, browse your TikTok feed without ads, repost clips to other social networks.
Features of 4K Tokkit Pro
	Download videos in bulk from your TikTok account. Save all videos from profile and get TikTok user's profile picture.
	Automatically get updates from your favorite TikTok creators and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Roxio Easy VHS to DVD Plus 4.0.13</title><pubDate> Fri, 10 Oct 2025 14:57:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-roxio-easy-vhs-to-dvd-plus-6772.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-roxio-easy-vhs-to-dvd-plus-6772.html
</guid><description>
Roxio Easy VHS to DVD Plus is premium software that helps you convert your VHS tapes to DVD or digital to enhance and preserve the your home movie. Capture analog video directly from your camcorder or VCR and burn to DVD or convert to popular digital formats for free sharing across devices
Roxio Easy VHS to DVD Plus also offers video trimming, quick editing, color enhancement, adding transitions, noise reduction and stabilizing old footage to Breathe new life into your old videos....
</description></item><item><title>Download Lyric Video Studio 1.3.34</title><pubDate> Fri, 10 Oct 2025 14:56:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lyric-video-studio-13581.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lyric-video-studio-13581.html
</guid><description>
Lyric Video Studio is a powerful, feature-rich video editor specifically designed to create lyric videos, music videos, and visualizers with ease. It integrates simple and effective text tools along with generative AI capabilities to streamline the video creation process. Whether you're a musician launching a killer new track, a content creator, or just love playing with visuals, this app lets you sync your lyrics to your music in just a few clicks. Enter lyrics, drag to sync and you're...
</description></item><item><title>Download Android Studio 2025.1.4.8</title><pubDate> Fri, 10 Oct 2025 14:56:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-android-studio-3890.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-android-studio-3890.html
</guid><description>
Android Studio is an Android development environment, completely new, provides many improvements and new features compared to Eclipse ADT. This software solution will is IDE the official Android when is finishing. This tool provides many tools and features such as editing, layout, rich set of tools to capture usability, compatibility version, performance and other issues, create a lot APK, build system based on Gradle flexibility, extended support for Google Services, integrated support...
</description></item><item><title>Download Basilisk Browser 2025.10.10</title><pubDate> Fri, 10 Oct 2025 14:55:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-basilisk-browser-3923.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-basilisk-browser-3923.html
</guid><description>
Basilisk Browser is a browser based on the XUL free and has many features, provides the interface is well designed and simple manipulation. The program is built based on the tool output and layout of the Goanna and based on the platform XUL merge, similar to Mozilla Firefox. Basilisk Browser was created as a reference program for the development of the platform XUL. You can use this app in replacement for Mozilla Firefox. This utility includes support many types of features needed for...
</description></item><item><title>Download Waterfox 6.6.4 / 2022.11</title><pubDate> Fri, 10 Oct 2025 14:54:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-waterfox-114.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-waterfox-114.html
</guid><description>
Waterfox is a 64-bit version of the foundation Firefox was built and the compiler Intel is optimized for speed and performance on Windows systems.Waterfox does not add any additional features or bling, in fact, it will automatically import all the gadgets and install is have of you, so you will feel like at home when you run it the first time.All the add-on your Firefox will work with Waterfox, however, only support the plug-in more 64-bit, is includes Adobe Flash, Oracle Java and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Stardock Start11 2.5.6 Beta</title><pubDate> Fri, 10 Oct 2025 14:53:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stardock-start11-7029.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stardock-start11-7029.html
</guid><description>
Start11 is an application capable of customizing the Start Menu and Taskbar on Windows 11 and Windows 10. This is an application that allows users to customize Windows 11 to suit their preferences. his personal. Start11 will help you bring the new Start Menu of Windows 11 to Windows 10. And vice versa, Start11 also helps you to bring the Start Menu of Windows 10 to Windows 11.
Start11 also helps users bring some functions of Windows 10 to Windows 11 through customizing the Taskbar such...
</description></item><item><title>Download Minimal Firewall 2.4.4</title><pubDate> Fri, 10 Oct 2025 14:48:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minimal-firewall-13877.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minimal-firewall-13877.html
</guid><description>
Minimal Firewall works in conjunction with Windows Firewall to block all unknown connections by default, prompting you to create application-based rules to mitigate malware, telemetry, and data leaks. Completely eliminate applications that call home without your knowledge. Minimal Firewall provides a more secure and integrated approach by interacting directly with the native Windows Firewall, eliminating the need for risky system modifications.
Core Features
	Lockdown Mode: The core...
</description></item><item><title>Download Opera One 122.0.5643.142</title><pubDate> Fri, 10 Oct 2025 14:47:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-972.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-972.html
</guid><description>
Opera is a fast, safe, configurable and compliant intranet web browser, which includes both the reader and the application. The Opera browser supports web browsing, listening to music, watching high speed movies, you can open many tabs on the Opera without affecting your browsing speed. Opera now supports almost all devices and operating systems such as windows, IOS, Android, linux, MacOS ...
Opera is a beautiful interface and many interesting features, operating on both PCs and mobile,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Remote Desktop Manager Enterprise 2025.3.16</title><pubDate> Fri, 10 Oct 2025 14:47:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-remote-desktop-manager-enterprise-242.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-remote-desktop-manager-enterprise-242.html
</guid><description>
Remote Desktop Manager Enterprise software is the complete management of remote connections and virtual machines from a single location, at the same time access support data online and cloud storage. Remote Desktop Manager supports multiple types of connections, not only connections for the protocol connect remote computer Remote Desktop Protocol (RDP).
Remote Desktop Manager easily add, edit, delete, share, organize and find your remote connection of you quickly. Compatible with...
</description></item><item><title>Download VCap Downloader Pro 0.1.37.6739</title><pubDate> Fri, 10 Oct 2025 14:46:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vcap-downloader-pro-8474.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vcap-downloader-pro-8474.html
</guid><description>
VCap Downloader Pro (VCapDL) is a popular piece of software that allows you to record video and audio from websites on the internet. The interface of the software is similar to a normal browser, making it easy for users to get used to and work with this software. User just need to copy video url from favorite browser and convert it to VCap Downloader Pro. It will capture the video and make the quality available for download. You can also extract the audio track from any video and convert...
</description></item><item><title>Download AllMapSoft Universal Maps Downloader 10.226</title><pubDate> Fri, 10 Oct 2025 14:46:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-universal-maps-downloader-736.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-universal-maps-downloader-736.html
</guid><description>
AllMapSoft Universal Maps Downloader is software download map images on the computer for offline viewing support many types such as Google Maps, Yahoo maps, Bing maps, OpenStreet Maps, Yandex Maps, Ovi Maps, MapQuest Maps. All the downloaded photos will be saved on disk. You can view downloaded maps by Maps Viewer Or you can combine them into one big bmp, or jpg file tif by Maps Combiner, and also you can export all the tiles into a database format MBTiles.
AllMapSoft Universal Maps...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDQ Inventory 19.5.0.0 Enterprise</title><pubDate> Fri, 10 Oct 2025 14:45:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdq-inventory-1468.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdq-inventory-1468.html
</guid><description>
PDQ Inventory is a software application to manage your system. This software will be able to manage your system by scanning the Windows operating system of you to provide information hardware, software, and configuration for the Windows operating system in your your tools. The tools available in this software helps you can scan the computer correctly.
In addition, the software PDQ Inventory can give you very detailed information. This software application is one of the management...
</description></item><item><title>Download Print.Test.Page.OK 3.44</title><pubDate> Fri, 10 Oct 2025 14:45:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-printtestpageok-4501.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-printtestpageok-4501.html
</guid><description>
Print.Test.Page.OK is a tool to print a test page allows you to check your printer to find errors and effective. Print.Test.Page.OK is equipped with two test pages, and slope color, allowing you to check the color printer at any time, regardless of whether it is color laser printer or modern inkjet printers. You can quickly start the print test page via the Print button. One thing essential is the color and the way it is displayed for your printer. Steaks, teen, color,...
</description></item><item><title>Download IntraWEB Ultimate 16.1.7</title><pubDate> Fri, 10 Oct 2025 14:44:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intraweb-ultimate-2007.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intraweb-ultimate-2007.html
</guid><description>
IntraWEB Ultimate is a tool to build the website. With this tool, the developer can create the page using the same method used to build the Windows program. Because the HTML page directly from the concept design to the user's computer does not download a bit more complicated and in fact is required from web server. So, the template IntraWeb on the server and download server and displays them to the user. Things technology direction of the IntraWEB Ultimate provides part flexibility and...
</description></item><item><title>Download FanControl v243</title><pubDate> Fri, 10 Oct 2025 14:44:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fancontrol-5749.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fancontrol-5749.html
</guid><description>
FanControl is a highly customizable fan control software for Windows. Stay in control of every aspect of your PC's GPU and CPU fan with the help of this highly customizable fan control app.
Features of FanControl
	Save, edit and load multiple configurations
	Multiple temperature sources (CPU, GPU, motherboard, hard drive, ".sensor" files)
	Custom fan curve
	Fine tune fan control response with steps,% start,% stop, response time and delay
	Mix different curves and sensors...
</description></item><item><title>Download All About PDF 3.2035</title><pubDate> Fri, 10 Oct 2025 14:44:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-all-about-pdf-3617.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-all-about-pdf-3617.html
</guid><description>
All About PDF is an application that edit, merge, split PDF file effective for the office work. Besides, All About PDF also lets you convert them to other formats using the versatile app, intuitive and flexible this.
All-About-PDF is a Windows application, fast and powerful built to take advantage of multiple processor cores of the computer to handle PDF quickly. With the licensing of permanent, simple, as well as the option of volume licensing to deploy across the organization,...
</description></item><item><title>Download RyTuneX 1.5.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 10 Oct 2025 14:43:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rytunex-11852.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rytunex-11852.html
</guid><description>
RyTuneX is an advanced optimizer built on the WinUI 3 framework, designed to enhance the performance of Windows devices. Designed for Windows 10 and 11, RyTuneX empowers users to easily remove stubborn pre-installed apps and optimize system resources.
RyTuneX Features
	Selectively remove apps: Easily uninstall unwanted pre-installed apps.
	Background services management: Streamline your system by disabling unnecessary services.
	Privacy enhancements: Strengthen your privacy by...
</description></item><item><title>Download Psiphon 186.20251009</title><pubDate> Fri, 10 Oct 2025 14:42:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-psiphon-7347.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-psiphon-7347.html
</guid><description>
Psiphon is a firewall bypass tool by Psiphon Inc. Uses VPN, SSH and HTTP Proxy technology to give you uncensored access to Internet content. Your Psiphon app automatically learns about new hotspots to maximize your chances of bypassing censorship.
The way the software works is that Psiphon constantly changes the proxy, so the user's IP address is also constantly changing, the server will not detect the user's real address, so you can feel free. roof. access to websites and software...
</description></item></channel></rss>