<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 21:35:23 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 21:35:23 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download XILS-lab PolyM 1.5.4</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 00:35:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xils-lab-polym-9258.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xils-lab-polym-9258.html
</guid><description>
XILS-lab PolyM is a software synthesizer plugin designed to simulate the sound of a classic Polymoog analog synthesizer. The polymoog was a groundbreaking instrument widely used in the 1970s and known for its rich and warm sound. PolyM offers a powerful and versatile audio engine that includes two oscillators, multi-mode filters, and a wide range of modulation sources. It also includes a built-in chorus and delay effects, which can be used to enhance the sound and create space and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Pulsar Audio IPA 25 1.0.11</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 00:34:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pulsar-audio-ipa-25-14071.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pulsar-audio-ipa-25-14071.html
</guid><description>
Pulsar Audio's IPA 25 is a classic VCA compressor emulation plugin, specifically inspired by the API 2500, providing a flexible multi-VCA dynamics system with modern control options for the engineer.
Key Features
	Faithful VCA modeling delivers classic tone with advanced control beyond the hardware limits.
	Modular signal flow and intuitive controls, allowing allows users to switch between different VCA circuits for more diverse sounds.
	Multi-circuit design: Provides both native...
</description></item><item><title>Download Nomad Factory 80s Spaces 2.5.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 00:34:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nomad-factory-80s-spaces-9464.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nomad-factory-80s-spaces-9464.html
</guid><description>
Nomad Factory 80s Spaces is a digital reverb plugin developed by Nomad Factory, a company known for creating audio processing software and plugins for professional audio production. . The 80s Spaces plugin aims to recreate the reverberation and atmosphere characteristics of the 1980s, giving users a nostalgic sound reminiscent of that era.
It's worth noting that Nomad Factory 80s Spaces is a software plugin designed for use in digital audio workstations (DAWs) or audio editing software....
</description></item><item><title>Download Pulsar Audio Pulsar 8200 1.2.7</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 00:34:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pulsar-audio-pulsar-8200-9385.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pulsar-audio-pulsar-8200-9385.html
</guid><description>
Pulsar Audio has announced the release of Pulsar 8200, a faithful emulation of the legendary GML 8200 designed by George Massenburg, inventor of parametric EQ. Besides emulating the sound of the original device, Pulsar Audio has incorporated all the features you would expect from a modern EQ plugin, such as filtering, tilt, sub and air band, editing visual curves, eliminators, auto-increment, etc. .
Like the original machine, the plugin offers tight and powerful bass, vibrant highs, and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Pulsar Audio Pulsar Massive 1.4.7</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 00:33:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pulsar-audio-pulsar-massive-9164.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pulsar-audio-pulsar-massive-9164.html
</guid><description>
Pulsar Massive is an emulation of the Manley Massive Passive* EQ found in most editing studios around the world. This machine is designed as a synthesis of the best passive equalizers of the past 70 years and some distinctive features in the design give it a completely unique sound.
First of all, the EQ's fully parallel topology provides a completely different response pattern than a digital equalizer with the same settings. The parallel equalizer's tonal corrections are not cumulative...
</description></item><item><title>Download IK Multimedia ARC X 1.0.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 00:33:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ik-multimedia-arc-system-11503.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ik-multimedia-arc-system-11503.html
</guid><description>
ARC 4 combines ultra-precise measurement microphones, analysis software, and calibration plugins to improve the accuracy of your monitoring in any room. Work faster and more freely, confident that you're hearing your own music and that your music will sound great anywhere. With a faster, easier calibration process, new more natural algorithms, and configuration management on ARC Studio hardware, everything about ARC Studio is designed to help you focus on your music and creating tones....
</description></item><item><title>Download Pulsar Audio Vocal Studio 1.0.17</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 00:32:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pulsar-audio-vocal-studio-13849.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pulsar-audio-vocal-studio-13849.html
</guid><description>
Pulsar Audio Vocal Studio is an all-in-one vocal processing plugin designed to deliver professional vocal mixes quickly and intuitively by combining many essential vocal production tools into a single interface. It offers a comprehensive channel array with preamp, compression, EQ, gating, de-essing, reverb, delay, saturation and a suite of creative effects.
Key Features:
	Tri-Mode Preamp: Choose between Solid State, Tube and Germanium saturation models with adjustable drive for warmth...
</description></item><item><title>Download XILS-lab XILS 201 Vocoder 1.1.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 00:32:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xils-201-vocoder-9240.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xils-201-vocoder-9240.html
</guid><description>
XILS 201 Vocoder is a virtual analog synthesizer plugin designed for use in digital audio (DAW) workstations. The XILS 201's string sections let you create rich, vibrant string sounds, with controls for vibrato, tremolo, and ensemble effects. The polyphonic synthesizer offers a wide range of sounds, from warm accompaniment to strong lead, with a variety of filter, envelope, and modulation source options.
X201 Vocoder is modeled after an extremely rare, extremely expensive (even at the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Nomad Factory Retro EQs Bundle 2.3.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 00:32:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nomad-factory-retro-eqs-bundle-10600.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nomad-factory-retro-eqs-bundle-10600.html
</guid><description>
Nomad Factory Retro EQs Bundle is a faithful emulation of the Pultec &amp;amp; Legendary Altec from the 50s. The hardware has been heard on countless records and is still in use today. With v2, it adds adjustable analog circuit modules (in both Pulse-Tec &amp;amp; ALL-Tec plug-ins), simulating the complex operation of the original tubes and transformers. head. They create pleasantly similar saturation effects to any sound you feed them. V2 features a completely rewritten DSP, an all-new...
</description></item><item><title>Download Pulsar Audio Pulsar Primavera 1.2.7</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 00:31:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pulsar-audio-pulsar-primavera-11662.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pulsar-audio-pulsar-primavera-11662.html
</guid><description>
Pulsar Primavera is a 6-in-1 reverb plugin that includes equipment heard on countless hits throughout the ages. Known for their unique, warm, characterful and natural tone, these reverbs created a sonic identity that lasted from the 50s to the 70s and is back in vogue today.
It is a complete reverb chain plugin with built-in saturation, filter, presence and fade controls. Get that signature “twang” sound within seconds and test out next-generation features built into the...
</description></item><item><title>Download ToneBoosters Plugin Bundle 2.0.8</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 00:30:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-toneboosters-plugin-bundle-3675.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-toneboosters-plugin-bundle-3675.html
</guid><description>
ToneBoosters Plugin Bundle is a package tool sound is to combine the digital signal processing advanced and deployed multi-platform is optimized with the easy to use interface to optimize workflow of you. We combine the digital signal processing advanced and highly optimized deployment platform interface with simple-to-use to optimize your work.
ToneBoosters Plugin Bundle - audio tools
ToneBoosters Plugin Bundle includes:
	Barricade: True-peak mastering limiter.
	BitJuggler: The...
</description></item><item><title>Download Pulsar Audio Pulsar Smasher 1.5.7</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 00:29:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pulsar-audio-smasher-3823.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pulsar-audio-smasher-3823.html
</guid><description>
Pulsar Audio Smasher is a custom modification not seen of the circuit the classic compressor Urei 1176, a single recipe that we stumbled across while tweaking the other algorithms. Hardware compressor 1176 original offers a choice of four rates, but the studio engineer was soon discovered that the press all of them at the same time lead to sound distortion, explosion and very high compression. This is the mode "all buttons in mode," or "You" that Pulsar Audio Smasher is designed...
</description></item><item><title>Download Pulsar Audio Pulsar 1178 1.5.7</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 00:29:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pulsar-audio-pulsar-1178-9167.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pulsar-audio-pulsar-1178-9167.html
</guid><description>
Pulsar Audio Pulsar 1178 is an audio plug-in (VST/VST3/AU/AAX) that meticulously reproduces the original 1178 hardware compressor in color and compression characteristics of the original 1178 hardware compressor. it, while adding some extra features, making it a very flexible compressor for tracking and mixing. It has added all the features you'd expect from a modern, versatile plug-in, including full sidechain EQ for additional control, optional saturation stages for warmth and...
</description></item><item><title>Download XILS-lab XILS 4 1.6.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 00:29:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xils-lab-xils-4-9257.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xils-lab-xils-4-9257.html
</guid><description>
XILS-lab XILS 4 is a software synthesis plugin designed to emulate the iconic EMS VCS4 analog synthesizer. It provides a powerful and flexible audio engine that can be used to create a wide variety of sounds and effects.
Plugin consists of three main modules: Compositor, Sequencer, and Effects Processor. The Synthesizer module offers a variety of oscillators, including classical waveforms, noise generators, and more. It also includes a variety of filters, envelopes, and modulation...
</description></item><item><title>Download XILS-lab XILS 5000 Vocoder 1.1.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 00:28:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xils-5000-vocoder-9241.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xils-5000-vocoder-9241.html
</guid><description>
Inspired by the EMS Flagship Vocoder, XILS-lab used its knowledge gained during simulation of both the VCS3 synthesizer and the VP300 VocoderPlus to develop the XILS 5000 Vocoder. An audio encoder is a synthesizer that accepts an external sound source, an instrument, or a pre-recorded signal that you can process, with or without a keyboard, into a variety of sounds. The human voice, the most diverse sound of all, can be fed into the Voice Encoder, so that you can change the Pitch, Tone,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Pulsar Audio Pulsar Mu 1.6.7</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 00:28:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pulsar-audio-pulsar-mu-9182.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pulsar-audio-pulsar-mu-9182.html
</guid><description>
Pulsar Audio Pulsar Mu is a software plugin designed for audio compression and dynamic range control in music production and audio post-production. It is based on the classic Fairchild 670 compressor, which is known for its warm, smooth and clear sound.
Pulsar Mu has a series of controls to adjust the compression ratio, attack and release time, and other parameters of the audio signal. It also includes a sidechain filter, which can be used to shape the compression effect based on the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Pulsar Audio Pulsar Echorec 1.7.7</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 00:27:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pulsar-audio-pulsar-echorec-9183.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pulsar-audio-pulsar-echorec-9183.html
</guid><description>
Pulsar Audio Pulsar Echorec is a software emulation of the iconic echo/delay device of the same name produced by the Italian brand Binson in the 1960s. The sound of This platter delay was different from the tape delay used at the time and largely contributed to the sonic signatures of many '70s bands: Pink Floyd, The Shadows, Jimmy Page, etc.
Features of Pulsar Audio Pulsar Echorec
	Best software emulation of Binson Echorec 2
	Vintage Echorec devices are known for their saturation,...
</description></item><item><title>Download XILS-lab StiX 1.6.5</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 00:27:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xils-lab-stix-9256.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xils-lab-stix-9256.html
</guid><description>
XILS-lab StiX is a virtual analog and multi synthesizer drum machine plugin designed for music producers and sound designers. It offers a wide range of sounds and features that can be used to create unique and complex drum patterns.
StiX includes a powerful synthesis engine that provides various types of synthesis, including FM, subtraction, and sample-based synthesis. It also features a step sequencer with up to 16 steps, allowing users to program complex drum patterns with ease.
The...
</description></item><item><title>Download RegCool 2.037</title><pubDate> Mon, 22 Sep 2025 20:04:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-regcool-42.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-regcool-42.html
</guid><description>
RegCool is a powerful and user-friendly registry editor for Windows operating systems. The registry is an important part of the Windows operating system, containing important settings and configurations that determine how your computer functions. With RegCool, users can easily navigate, edit, and manage registry keys and values, making it a valuable tool for advanced users and IT professionals.
RegCool's main features:
	User-friendly interface: RegCool has a clear and intuitive user...
</description></item><item><title>Download QOwnNotes 25.9.5</title><pubDate> Mon, 22 Sep 2025 20:04:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qownnotes-3178.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qownnotes-3178.html
</guid><description>
QOwnNotes is notes bookmark file simple text (GPL) open source application for GNU / Linux , Mac OS X and Windows of Patrizio Bekerle ( pbek on GitHub and IRC) (optional) activity along with the notes application of ownCloud or Nextcloud. QOwnNote store your notes as plain text files and can be synchronized with synchronization function file of ownCloud / Nextcloud. You can also use other apps like Syncthing or Dropbox . Just write out your thoughts as they appear, and edit them if...
</description></item><item><title>Download Flow Launcher 2.0.1 + Portable</title><pubDate> Mon, 22 Sep 2025 20:03:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-flow-launcher-7073.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-flow-launcher-7073.html
</guid><description>
Flow Launcher is a program for quick file search and application launcher for Windows with community-created plugins. You can efficiently search everything from apps, files, bookmarks, YouTube, Twitter and more. In addition, it also supports Command Prompt and Powershell Commands, making it a comprehensive search engine for any option.
Features of Flow Launcher
	Search file contents
	Support searching using environment variable paths
	Run batch commands and PowerShell as Administrator...
</description></item><item><title>Download Topaz Photo Pro 1.0.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 23:42:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-photo-ai-8105.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-photo-ai-8105.html
</guid><description>
What is Topaz Photo AI?
Topaz Photo AI is a professional software that automatically adjusts for your image quality needs. Simply import images into Topaz Photo AI and it will use specially trained AI models to first detect unique details, clarity, and resolution issues before applying the intelligently adjusts to maximize your image quality.
For users experienced with Topaz Labs image quality applications, it combines the functionality of DeNoise AI, Sharpen AI and Gigapixel AI into...
</description></item><item><title>Download Topaz Video 1.0.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 23:39:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-video-enhance-ai-3733.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-video-enhance-ai-3733.html
</guid><description>
Topaz Video Enhance AI is a tool to increase video quality with this great technology ONE. Topaz Video Enhance WHO wide open your video to resolutions up to 8K with the details and consistency of motion. Until the present, there is no way to re-create a perfect high resolution video from the footage is low resolution. From the family film to SD low quality to DVD quality and more than that, Video Enhance WHO will convert your video into the footage is upgrade clear with resolutions up to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Topaz Gigapixel Pro 1.0.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 23:37:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-ai-gigapixel-1318.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-ai-gigapixel-1318.html
</guid><description>
Topaz ONE Gigapixel is the first app and only use the power of artificial intelligence to enhance your photos, add natural details, for great results. Use technology to learn deep, AIGigapixel ™ can zoom in and fill in the details that the products change in size other are not included. The traditional method this created blurred image, a non-realistic and do not have the detail present in the image have high resolution.
Topaz A.I. Gigapixel - enhance image quality
The content of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tiny11 24H2 Build 26100.6584</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 23:36:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tiny11-8649.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tiny11-8649.html
</guid><description>
Tiny11 is a compact Windows operating system based on Windows 11 Pro 22H2, Tiny11 has everything you need for a comfortable, hassle-free computing experience. cumbersome and messy like a standard Windows installation. The operating system requires only 8GB of disk space and 2GB of RAM, and requires no TPM (Trusted Platform Module) and Secure Boot support.
The main goal of Tiny11 is to extend the reach of systems that can access Windows 11. The custom edition can run on any system...
</description></item></channel></rss>