<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 15:33:44 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 15:33:44 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download MAME 0.280</title><pubDate> Sun, 31 Aug 2025 18:15:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mame-3320.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mame-3320.html
</guid><description>
MAME is an emulator of open source and free are designed to recreate the hardware of the game system arcade in software on the personal computer modern and other platforms. The goal is to preserve gaming history by preventing classic games from being lost or being forgotten.
MAME - emulator classic game
MAME (Multiple Arcade Machine Emulator) is a software that has the ability to simulate an arcade machine, allowing you to play the classic arcade game on his computer. This tool can...
</description></item><item><title>Download CrystalDiskInfo 9.7.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 31 Aug 2025 18:13:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-crystaldiskinfo-1683.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-crystaldiskinfo-1683.html
</guid><description>
CrystalDiskInfo is a software to monitor and evaluate status of hard drive a way the most accurate, simple, fast and compact. CrystalDiskInfo will help you complete peace of mind when always know hard drive of his computer are in any situation. The software let you know the status of the hard drive, how when operating, to avoid the risks that can be foreseen, most discs contain important data.
CrystalDiskInfo - See information hard drive
Some function information of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Perfectly Clear WorkBench 4.8.0.2847</title><pubDate> Sun, 31 Aug 2025 18:13:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfectly-clear-workbench-6892.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfectly-clear-workbench-6892.html
</guid><description>
Perfectly Clear Workbench is an application that uses image editing libraries Perfectly Clear by Athentech and is provided to demonstrate the capabilities of the Perfectly Clear processing libraries, which recognize faces and allow quick export of processing settings for use.
One of the key features in Workbench is the ability to "export to API" when saving a Preset. This allows you to make image edits in Workbench and adjust the settings to suit your editing style and needs. You can...
</description></item><item><title>Download DISMTools 0.7</title><pubDate> Sun, 31 Aug 2025 18:13:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dismtools-12200.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dismtools-12200.html
</guid><description>
Inspired by Visual Studio, DISMTools is a user interface for DISM that allows you to manage Windows Imaging (WIM) files and much more. You can use it to uninstall apps, add driver or tool packages, etc.
DISM: This is a tool used to maintain and repair Windows images. This includes Windows Recovery Environment, Windows Setup, and Windows PE (WinPE). You can also use DISM to repair Windows images locally on your computer.
DISMTools: This is a user-friendly interface that allows you to...
</description></item><item><title>Download dBpoweramp Image Converter Premier R2025-08-29</title><pubDate> Sun, 31 Aug 2025 18:12:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbpoweramp-image-converter-7007.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbpoweramp-image-converter-7007.html
</guid><description>
dBpoweramp Image Converter is a simple visual transformation application that aims to make the transition as simple as possible. dBpoweramp Image Converter will switch between all popular formats, Bitmap, PNG, JPEG, TIFF and many other formats. It also has the ability to make mass transformation for multiple files and folders with only one click and filter on the png or other types of files.
dBpoweramp Image Converter is capable of switching high speed by using simultaneously all CPU...
</description></item><item><title>Download DeskSoft EarthView 7.13.8</title><pubDate> Sun, 31 Aug 2025 18:11:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desksoft-earthview-184.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desksoft-earthview-184.html
</guid><description>
With software DeskSoft EarthView you can easily create wallpapers to your computer or select screen saver of your favorite. the program can change day and night, the clouds will also change according to weather conditions current on one or another part of the earth, you can see the lights of the city.
Features of DeskSoft EarthView can be interesting, because of DeskSoft EarthView support for day and night, you can view atmospheric phenomena, light city can see, the cloud is displayed,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Hallmark Card Studio Deluxe 23.0.1.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 31 Aug 2025 18:11:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hallmark-card-studio-delux-9807.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hallmark-card-studio-delux-9807.html
</guid><description>
Hallmark Card Studio Deluxe is a software application developed by Hallmark to help users create personalized greeting cards, invitations and other printable cards. It offers a wide range of templates, design tools, and features to assist in creating custom tags for different occasions.
Features of Hallmark Card Studio Deluxe
	Over 20,400 Customizable imprints and projects for every occasion
	Over 21,000 Breathtaking Graphics including Exclusive Hallmark Art
	Featured library of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Chaos Enscape 4.10.0.464</title><pubDate> Sun, 31 Aug 2025 18:10:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-enscape-3d-4125.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-enscape-3d-4125.html
</guid><description>
Enscape 3D is the tool support simulation 3D for the software Revit, SketchUp, Rhino, ArchiCAD. With real-time technology of Enscape 3D your project is displayed in the form of walk-3D is fully displayed, can be navigated and explored from every angle, at every moment of the day. With direct link between Enscape 3D and CAD programs, you can track all updates for his plan immediately. More Enscape to your work to give yourself more time to create and innovate. Enscape 3D offers many options...
</description></item><item><title>Download Avid Media Composer 25.6 Dongle BackUp</title><pubDate> Sun, 31 Aug 2025 18:09:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avid-media-composer-5432.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avid-media-composer-5432.html
</guid><description>
Avid Media Composer is the industry's most proven video editing software, trusted by professional editors in every segment of filmmaking, television, broadcast and online streaming. Designed for handling large volumes of various file-based media, Media Composer provides accelerated HD and high-resolution workflow, real-time collaboration, and powerful media management, Eliminate time-consuming tasks so you can concentrate on telling a great story.
Media Composer 2020 is packed with a lot...
</description></item><item><title>Download HTML Compiler 2025.18</title><pubDate> Sun, 31 Aug 2025 18:09:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-html-compiler-2548.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-html-compiler-2548.html
</guid><description>
HTML Compiler is a program for Microsoft Windows (tm) allows you to put an entire HTML application (including HTML, CSS, JavaScript, images, etc.) into a Windows application independent can be executed like any other application window the application. HTML Compiler allows you to customize file real exam results by changing the icon of them and set some other options. For example, you can allow or not allow the ability to print the HTML pages, allow or disallow the text selection and many,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Picture Window Pro 8.0.525</title><pubDate> Sun, 31 Aug 2025 18:08:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-picture-window-pro-7452.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-picture-window-pro-7452.html
</guid><description>
Picture Window Pro is a powerful image editing tool designed for serious photographers with strict creative and quality standards. Its comprehensive set of photo editing and editing tools let you control and shape every aspect of your images.
Picture Window Pro 8 is a complete rewrite of Picture Window Pro 7. It features non-destructive image editing through a novel interface based on an image tree. It also fully supports large, high-resolution displays and can be used in dual monitor...
</description></item><item><title>Download tinyMediaManager 5.2.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 31 Aug 2025 18:08:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tinymediamanager-1819.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tinymediamanager-1819.html
</guid><description>
tinyMediaManager is a media manager full-featured to arrange and cleanup your media library your. Just choose (s) the folder containing your movies and the program can automatically get all meta data required for movies and program your TV from TheMovieDB.org, Imdb.com, OFDb.de and other online sources. tinyMediaManager download at artwork, film, cast, plot and details of other communication. Each film or program is presented with a unique art background, category, and appropriate...
</description></item><item><title>Download AllMapSoft Google Maps Downloader 8.878</title><pubDate> Sun, 31 Aug 2025 18:08:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-google-maps-downloader-2796.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-google-maps-downloader-2796.html
</guid><description>
AllMapSoft Google Maps Downloader is a reliable application aimed at downloading maps from Google at high speed. The result is a set of small images can be combined in a larger map. This can serve in a large variety of projects, from creating a tile map to presentations and tutorials.
Google Maps Downloader successfully fulfills both of those conditions, providing simple means to quickly grab maps at the resolution satisfactory. In addition, it is extremely easy to use and integrated a...
</description></item><item><title>Download Photo Supreme 2025.3.3.8073</title><pubDate> Sun, 31 Aug 2025 18:07:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photo-supreme-430.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photo-supreme-430.html
</guid><description>
Photo Supreme is a software product management professional pictures of idimager. With Photo Supreme you can arrange, manage back stock photo archive of yourself and share them with you here and relatives easily via Email or Facebook. Photo Supreme provides users method to sort images effective, logical, as well as edit and share your photos with friends and relatives in the family. Especially the Photo Supreme allows to work with multiple image formats and support mounting support,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Nicky Romero Kickstart 2 2.0.8</title><pubDate> Sun, 31 Aug 2025 18:07:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nicky-romero-kickstart-11050.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nicky-romero-kickstart-11050.html
</guid><description>
Kickstart 2 immediately solves the problem of bumps, clutter and bass. Forget fiddling with compressors – Nicky Romero and Cableguys put everything you need to create professional side chains into one quick, easy plugin. Simply drop Kickstart into any track to instantly lower the volume with each drum hit, making room for your bass.
Main features:
	Every DAW, every genre
	Instant setup
	16 handcrafted curves
	Large mixing knob
	Follow any rhythm
	Multi-band side chain
	Visual view
</description></item><item><title>Download CrystalDiskInfo Portable 9.7.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 31 Aug 2025 18:06:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-crystaldiskinfo-portable-11173.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-crystaldiskinfo-portable-11173.html
</guid><description>
CrystalDiskInfo Portable (portable version) is utility software designed to monitor the health and performance of hard disk drives (HDD) and solid state drives (SSD). This tool is often used to check the status of drives in a computer to ensure they are operating normally and predict possible drive errors.
It provides detailed information about the drive, such as temperature, drive status, total operating hours, etc. Software to read S.M.A.R.T. (Self-Monitoring, Analysis and Reporting...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaMonkey Gold 2024.2.0.3166 Beta</title><pubDate> Sun, 31 Aug 2025 18:06:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediamonkey-gold-231.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediamonkey-gold-231.html
</guid><description>
MediaMonkey Gold is music manager and music player multimedia for the music collection and iPod users. MediaMonkey lists the audio file of you as CD, OGG, WMA, MPC, FLAC, APE, WAV and MP3 and includes the edit smart card and an automatic file and folder to arrange your music library.
MediaMonkey Gold also has CD ripper, CD / DVD Burner, and audio converter for saving music, and manual or editor list automatically to create mixed music.
Features MediaMonkey Gold
	Automatically find...
</description></item><item><title>Download Awesome Miner Ultimate 11.2.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 31 Aug 2025 18:05:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-awesome-miner-9041.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-awesome-miner-9041.html
</guid><description>
Awesome Miner is a software application designed to manage and monitor cryptocurrency mining operations. It supports a wide variety of mining hardware, including ASICs and GPUs, and can be used to manage mining for a variety of cryptocurrencies, including Bitcoin, Ethereum, and Litecoin.
Powerful tool to manage and monitor cryptocurrency mining activities. With support for a wide variety of mining hardware and cryptocurrencies, mobile apps, and customizable alerting and performance...
</description></item><item><title>Download EarthTime 6.30.8</title><pubDate> Sun, 31 Aug 2025 18:05:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-earthtime-185.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-earthtime-185.html
</guid><description>
EarthTime is software that displays the time and date local time of any place in the world. This application has database integration good for 3000 city, users can manually add, download at EarthTime if you want to. EarthTime allows you to install for the time zone and current local time.EarthTime displays the Earth according to the view night and day, you can view the map in full screen mode.
EarthTime
The feature on EarthTime
	EarthTime allows users to interact with visualization...
</description></item><item><title>Download AllMapSoft Universal Maps Downloader 10.218</title><pubDate> Sun, 31 Aug 2025 18:04:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-universal-maps-downloader-736.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-universal-maps-downloader-736.html
</guid><description>
AllMapSoft Universal Maps Downloader is software download map images on the computer for offline viewing support many types such as Google Maps, Yahoo maps, Bing maps, OpenStreet Maps, Yandex Maps, Ovi Maps, MapQuest Maps. All the downloaded photos will be saved on disk. You can view downloaded maps by Maps Viewer Or you can combine them into one big bmp, or jpg file tif by Maps Combiner, and also you can export all the tiles into a database format MBTiles.
AllMapSoft Universal Maps...
</description></item><item><title>Download App Builder 2025.24</title><pubDate> Sun, 31 Aug 2025 18:04:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-app-builder-241.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-app-builder-241.html
</guid><description>
App Builder is a software application developer to help create and design apps, HTML5, web app, web app PWA on both platforms mobile and desktop. App Builder is professional software supports users to create the program HTML5 without writing code. It is very easy to use, suitable with all users who lack of professional knowledge in the field of programming and application design.
App Builder brings to 22 different themes that users can use to design for your app. You can choose 1 or a...
</description></item><item><title>Download Top Process Monitor 11.3</title><pubDate> Sun, 31 Aug 2025 18:03:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-top-process-monitor-2753.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-top-process-monitor-2753.html
</guid><description>
Top Process Monitor is a small utility that allows you to view the processes are using most CPU, memory and other important components in your system. It can be easily installed and configured, even by inexperienced users. The interface of the application is based on a small frame that you can move to any location on the screen. So, you can check the current CPU, along with the application and the total stream is included.
Top Process Monitor - View operation, the CPU, computer...
</description></item><item><title>Download Free Music and Video Downloader 3.07</title><pubDate> Sun, 31 Aug 2025 18:02:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-music-and-video-downloader-123.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-music-and-video-downloader-123.html
</guid><description>
Free Music &amp;amp; Video Downloader (formerly the Free Music Downloader) allows you to download his favorite music at the form of MP3 files from many different online sources, including Last.FM, Grooveshark, Sogou, VKontakte, SoundCloud, and many other things.Just enter name of artist or song you are looking for and click the Search button to see a list of results and download the songs you want.You can customize the services that applications will use to search, put the download folder...
</description></item><item><title>Download KS DB Merge Tools for MySQL 1.23.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 31 Aug 2025 17:59:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ks-db-merge-tools-for-mysql-12756.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ks-db-merge-tools-for-mysql-12756.html
</guid><description>
KS DB Merge Tools for MySQL is a distinct and incorporated search engine that is easy to use for the MySQL and MariaDB database.
Main features
	Comparison of both schema and data
	Quick filter to display all/new/changed
	Unity of changes in both directions
	Light GUI for Windows, command line for Windows and Linux
	Free version with basic features, available for commercial use. No credit cards, no registration, no advertisements, no hidden telemetry.
The supported DBMS, MySQL...
</description></item><item><title>Download AllMapSoft Offline Map Maker 8.348</title><pubDate> Sun, 31 Aug 2025 17:58:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-offline-map-maker-656.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-offline-map-maker-656.html
</guid><description>
AllMapSoft Offline Map Maker is software create, organize, offline map from Google Maps, Yahoo maps, Bing maps and Openstreetmap. You can view offline maps downloaded with map viewer offline. And you can zoom out or zoom in the offline map or export map under the file format .BMP with file world xxx.bpw, and can output files xxx.map for OziExplorer. If you want to make a offline map of your city by yourself, it is very useful for you.
Features AllMapSoft Offline Map Maker
	You can...
</description></item></channel></rss>