<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:50:59 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:50:59 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download IDM 6.4x by Ali.Dbg v20.5</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:46:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-64x-by-alidbg-13003.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-64x-by-alidbg-13003.html
</guid><description>
IDM 6.4x by Ali.Dbg is a compact program (only 0.1 MB) used to activate Internet Download Manager, Windows 7, 8, 10, 11 operating systems and Office suite from 2016 - 2024.
Previously, it was simply a patch for the regular IDM (Internet Download Manager) software. But with recent updates, the author Ali.Dbg has added tools for WinRAR/Windows/Office (inspired by MAS:Massgravel).
In addition, with the addition of the new WinToolBox toolkit (from ChrisTitusTech) users can use it to...
</description></item><item><title>Download K-Lite Codec Pack Full 19.4.5</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:44:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-115.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-115.html
</guid><description>
K Lite Codec Pack Full brings pc users an optimal solution for watching movies, listening to music, support most popular format today by using collection codec rich. This software also allows you to refine the quality of videos and music to enjoy, create a list of music and video to comfortable enjoy.
Prompt to software, listen to music, watch movies, currently, part, user will prompt to programs like VLC or KMP ... With VLC, it was too familiar with users, not just watch videos, listen...
</description></item><item><title>Download K-Lite Codec Pack Mega 19.4.5</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:43:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-mega-3202.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-mega-3202.html
</guid><description>
K-Lite Mega Codec Pack is a collection of components needed for audio playback and the video in the player DirectShow like Windows Media Player, Media Center, and Media Player Classic. This is the latest beta version, Pack Codec K-Lite latest stable. The Mega variant is the biggest of the four variants of the codec pack. It provides everything you need to play all audio and video files. In addition, it also contains some codecs ACM / VFW can be used by the application coding / video...
</description></item><item><title>Download CyberLink PowerDirector Ultimate 2026 v24.1.1326.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:42:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-powerdirector-ultimate-425.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-powerdirector-ultimate-425.html
</guid><description>
CyberLink PowerDirector Ultimate is software editor, edit video and make movies on the computer from a variety of templates are made available, complete with effects, transitions, animations, and music. CyberLink PowerDirector 17 is a combination of video editing software with advanced video editing features powerful. Cblowing need to add your clips into the time line and click on 'Production'!
The tool design video in CyberLink PowerDirector have the ability to customize helps you...
</description></item><item><title>Download AnyBurn Pro 6.7</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:42:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anyburn-pro-8828.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anyburn-pro-8828.html
</guid><description>
AnyBurn Pro is disc burning software that allows users to create, burn and copy a variety of discs, including CDs, DVDs and Blu-ray discs. It also provides additional features such as creating, converting and mounting disk images. Exclusive features of AnyBurn Pro version:
	Convert Audio File Format
	Install Windows onto a USB drive
Features of AnyBurn Pro
	Burn Disc: AnyBurn Pro allows users to burn a variety of discs, including data, audio and video CDs, DVDs and Blu-ray discs....
</description></item><item><title>Download ShareX 19.0.2 + Portable</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:41:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sharex-946.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sharex-946.html
</guid><description>
ShareX is a screen capture tool lets you capture an area on your desktop and automatically save to clipboard, your hard drive or download now up more than 25 file storage service different, including Imgur, Flickr , ImageShack, TinyPic, Dropbox and others.
With the "After Capture" allows you to choose whether you want to download snapshots of yourself up hosting service or keep it locally and support more action even adding watermarks to mark copyright photos.
ShareX - Capture screen...
</description></item><item><title>Download Photoscape X Pro 4.2.9</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:40:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photoscape-x-pro-4417.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photoscape-x-pro-4417.html
</guid><description>
Photoscape X Pro is an all-in-one photo editing software offers image features related to Photo Viewer, Editor, Cut Out, batch, collage, Combine, Create GIF, Color Picker, Screen Capture, RAW images and more. Photoscape X Pro - an impressive application that allows you to take screenshots and edit photos. It allows you to create mosaic as well as animated GIF. It is a process installation is very simple and easy and after the installation process is complete, you are greeted with user...
</description></item><item><title>Download AnyBurn 6.7</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:40:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anyburn-1165.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anyburn-1165.html
</guid><description>
AnyBurn is software to burn CD, DVD and Blu-ray helps you easily create disk images and software synthesis of multimedia or USB drive can boot. As far as installation, you can make the tool verify written data, eject the disc after recording, as well as finalize the disc (an option required by media player). The application supports many image files, such as ISO, DAA, BIN, MDF, MDS, NRG, CDI, IMG, UIF and WIM.
AnyBurn - Create disc DVD, Blu-ray
In addition, you can create audio CD from...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cubase Pro 15.0.10</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:40:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-steinberg-cubase-pro-3528.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-steinberg-cubase-pro-3528.html
</guid><description>
Steinberg Cubase Pro - The highest and most professional from the publisher Steinberg. Current program Steinberg Cubase Pro is priced near$ 600. But we will provide versions completely free for you. Can you might also like more simple versions, you can download version Cubase Elements at our website.
Steinberg Cubase Pro - music Production professional
Steinberg Cubase Pro is one of the pack music creation software, the most powerful in the world. With a variety of tools, unparalleled...
</description></item><item><title>Download Perfectly Clear WorkBench 5.0.1.3059</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:39:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfectly-clear-workbench-6892.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfectly-clear-workbench-6892.html
</guid><description>
Perfectly Clear Workbench is an application that uses image editing libraries Perfectly Clear by Athentech and is provided to demonstrate the capabilities of the Perfectly Clear processing libraries, which recognize faces and allow quick export of processing settings for use.
One of the key features in Workbench is the ability to "export to API" when saving a Preset. This allows you to make image edits in Workbench and adjust the settings to suit your editing style and needs. You can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Quick Clipboard Editor 3.3.0.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:39:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quick-clipboard-editor-9421.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quick-clipboard-editor-9421.html
</guid><description>
Quick Clipboard Editor is free software that provides direct access to the text stored in your clipboard, allowing you to quickly modify it to meet your needs. meet your needs before pasting the text into the app you want. It allows you to quickly retrieve previous clips from your clipboard history, find and replace specific words or phrases, insert new content into each line, trim unwanted pieces of text, keep or remove lines or characters based on different criteria, arrange text using...
</description></item><item><title>Download ExifTool 13.47</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:38:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-exiftool-1685.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-exiftool-1685.html
</guid><description>
ExifTool is a library of Perl platform-independent plus a command line application for reading, writing, and editing meta information in various file types. ExifTool supports many metadata formats including EXIF , GPS , IPTC , XMP , JFIF , GeoTIFF , ICC Profile , Photoshop IRB , FlashPix , AFCP and ID3 , as well as notes of the manufacturer of many digital cameras by Canon , Casio , DJI , FLIR , FujiFilm , GE , GoPro , HP , JVC / Victor , Kodak , Leaf , Minolta / Konica-Minolta , Motorola...
</description></item><item><title>Download O&amp;amp;O Defrag Pro 30.5.1214</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:38:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-o-o-defrag-pro-149.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-o-o-defrag-pro-149.html
</guid><description>
O&amp;amp;O Defrag Pro is the professional software has the ability to defragment the hard disk and can work with the file system different from FAT / 32 to NTFS / 5, and support for the different arrays Volume / Stripe Sets. You can also set the schedule which O &amp;amp; O Defrag will be booted and perform a number of manipulation certain. Regular defragmentation of the disk partition optimized performance of your computer. The user interface is very easy to use. It has a ribbon bar displays all...
</description></item><item><title>Download O&amp;amp;O Defrag Server 30.5.1214</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:38:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-defrag-server-2521.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-defrag-server-2521.html
</guid><description>
O&amp;amp;O Defrag Server professional software has the ability to defragment the hard disk and can work with the file system different from FAT / 32 to NTFS / 5, and support for the different arrays Volume / Stripe Sets. You can also set the schedule which O &amp;amp; O Defrag will be booted and perform a number of manipulation certain. Regular defragmentation of the disk partition optimized performance of your computer. The user interface is very easy to use. It has a ribbon bar displays all the...
</description></item><item><title>Download EndNote 2025.3 Build 19899</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:37:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-endnote-4237.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-endnote-4237.html
</guid><description>
EndNote X9 as a researcher, you constantly carry the different roles, addressing the competing demands on your time and coordinate not only the activities of the own in study published that all your collaborators on the whole and on the whole world. EndNote X9 is software management reference not only frees you from the tedious work in collecting and managing research material and format folder manually but also help you easy and more controlled in coordination with colleagues.
EndNote...
</description></item><item><title>Download Directory Opus Pro 13.21</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:37:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-opus-pro-779.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-opus-pro-779.html
</guid><description>
Directory Opus Pro is a software replacement for Explorer with traditional strength and function more than any manager other files. Directory Opus Pro full support for high DPI screen (for example 4K and 5K) with the rename dialog is redesigned, with new features. Besides being a recording macro only allows you to perform mass renaming complex that don't need regular expressions. In addition, Directory Opus Pro also enhances the ability to script.Better handling of renaming recursive and...
</description></item><item><title>Download LibreWolf 147.0.2-1</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:36:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-librewolf-11967.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-librewolf-11967.html
</guid><description>
LibreWolf is a customized and independent version of Firefox, with the main goals being user privacy, security and freedom. LibreWolf is designed to provide increased protection against tracking and fingerprinting techniques and includes a number of security enhancements. This is achieved through our security and privacy oriented settings and patches. LibreWolf also aims to remove all telemetry, data collection and annoyances, as well as disable anti-free features like DRM.
LibreWolf...
</description></item><item><title>Download AutoHideMouseCursor 6.11</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:35:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-autohidemousecursor-4104.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-autohidemousecursor-4104.html
</guid><description>
AutoHideMouseCursor is a Microsoft Windows application mobile mini allows you to hide the cursor, if the mouse is not active for a period of time. With AutoHideMouseCursor you can automatically hide the mouse cursor with the timer can be customized this is utility desktop perfect when the cursor is too annoying to them, such as when used with the application handling the text because often when you add pointers, text and cover text.
AutoHideMouseCursor - Hide mouse cursor
User...
</description></item><item><title>Download Bitsum Process Lasso Pro 17.0.2.20</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:34:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bitsum-process-lasso-pro-289.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bitsum-process-lasso-pro-289.html
</guid><description>
Bitsum Process Lasso Pro is software compact statistics and troubleshoot computer systems, such as crashes by control CPU. Technological process Lassos ProBalance (process balance) adjust the smart priority of running programs so that the process works poorly or too active will not affect the ability to use your computer!
Software Process Lasso to help manage the program or application will be managed and controlled to not have the ability to monopolize the CPU. Process Lasso also...
</description></item><item><title>Download R-Studio 9.5 Build 191686 Network / Technician</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:34:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-studio-1415.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-studio-1415.html
</guid><description>
R-Studio is a group of software data recovery and data recovery powerful and effective. -STUDIO is the solution to recover most comprehensive data for the file restored from the variants NTFS, NTFS5, ReFS, FAT12 / 16/32, exFAT, HFS / HFS + (Macintosh), Little and Big Endian of UFS1 / UFS2 (FreeBSD / OpenBSD / NetBSD / Solaris) and Ext2 / Ext3 / Ext4 partition FS (Linux).
R-Studio is also used to recover file raw (scan known file types) for the file system is damaged or not determined. It...
</description></item><item><title>Download Transmission 4.1.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:33:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-transmission-8668.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-transmission-8668.html
</guid><description>
Transmission is a free, open-source, cross-platform BitTorrent client widely used to download large files over the internet. With Transmission, you can download torrent files, manage your downloads, and control upload and download speeds. It is a popular choice among people who want a fast, simple and efficient torrent client. To download Transmission, you can visit the official website and choose the appropriate version for your operating system.
Features of Transmission
	Easy to...
</description></item><item><title>Download CPUID HWMonitor Pro 1.57</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:32:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cpuid-hwmonitor-pro-712.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cpuid-hwmonitor-pro-712.html
</guid><description>
CPUID HWMonitor Pro is the powerful solution to hardware monitoring, display of parameters such as system temperature, voltage, fan speed and many factors and variables, other important of your computer. HWMonitor Pro has the read view "tree" so that you can easily monitor each parameter as view and track temperature, CPU core, and analyze other details like temperature assembly of the primary hard drive.
CPUID HWMonitor Pro - hardware Monitoring
HWMonitor Pro can easily connect to a...
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 7.9.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:32:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-11-7760.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-11-7760.html
</guid><description>
TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 is a program that allows users to discover hidden settings in Windows 11. This application is specially designed for Windows 11, groups many registry settings and distribute them from the easy and secure user interface. With TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 you can move the Windows taskbar to the top and resize the taskbar by editing the registry value. With any application that modifies the registry, we recommend that you have a backup copy...
</description></item><item><title>Download Registry Finder 2.61.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:32:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-registry-finder-1016.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-registry-finder-1016.html
</guid><description>
Registry Finder is management software Registry help you check the Registry and see the results returned are displayed in the list. Registry Finder is a reliable software capable of finding a particular keyword in the register of Windows and displays all the matching items.
Registry Finder - Check the Registry
Registry Finder allows you to perform thorough search through the register Windows, to determine the desired string. The Windows registry is a file base system acts as a database...
</description></item><item><title>Download Garden Planner 3.8.82</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:31:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-garden-planner-186.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-garden-planner-186.html
</guid><description>
Garden Planner : If you want to create a garden plan, create a landscape by activity or simply be curious, then you can download Garden Planner .   Garden Planner is a program that helps the user to design a dream garden through the layout and arrangement of plants, plants, buildings and objects, creating living spaces. style is consistent with the user's criteria and standards.
Garden Planner application is very simple, just select bushes, other plants, trees, pond and drag them into...
</description></item></channel></rss>