<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 15:47:15 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 15:47:15 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download StartAllBack 3.9.13.5293</title><pubDate> Tue, 05 Aug 2025 18:12:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-startallback-6857.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-startallback-6857.html
</guid><description>
With the official release of Windows 11, chances are that most of you want to try it out. As the name suggests, StartAllBack is a small, lightweight tool that can help you enjoy the power of the new operating system while keeping the look and feel, especially because main work area, desktop of Windows 7, Windows 10 as taskbars and start menu styles.
StartAllBack is specially designed for Windows 11 and will not work on any older operating systems. If you want to get the start menu back...
</description></item><item><title>Download MAGIX Photostory Deluxe 2025 v24.0.1.233</title><pubDate> Tue, 05 Aug 2025 18:11:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-magix-photostory-deluxe-717.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-magix-photostory-deluxe-717.html
</guid><description>
MAGIX Photostory Deluxe version 2019 provides the movement of camera, zoom and music in a slideshow of photos incredible. Our templates help you to create the slideshow entertainment absolutely does take time. Includes: new photos and 1,500 effects and music. Add to that, get more effects, more in Store Photostory!
MAGIX Photostory Deluxe - professional photo editing and add effects on the photos
Unlimited slideshows. Explore the design possibilities endless: With the stunning effects...
</description></item><item><title>Download UniFab 3.0.2.4</title><pubDate> Tue, 05 Aug 2025 18:10:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-unifab-10377.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-unifab-10377.html
</guid><description>
UniFab is software to efficiently convert, compress and edit more than 1000 video formats for playback on any device without losing quality. Enlarge video/audio to 1080p/DTS 7.1 and upgrade video to HDR10 or Dolby Vision with AI Enhancer. UniFab Pro provides the best AI-powered zoom tool that allows you to enlarge videos from low resolutions, such as 360p, 480p and 720p, to 1080p without losing any quality. Clearer and sharper image details will bring you an exceptional viewing...
</description></item><item><title>Download Prepros 7.27</title><pubDate> Tue, 05 Aug 2025 18:10:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-prepros-4471.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-prepros-4471.html
</guid><description>
Prepros is a tool simple to use display interface is minimalistic and allows users to load, view and preprocess images, CSS and JS. Prepros available in a bright and dark themes, the user interface has a sleek style and is optimized to show all the highlights the potential that you encountered in the process of compiling highlights. You can start by adding the project you are implementing, an action you can complete in a convenient way by dragging and dropping.
Prepros - Learn to write...
</description></item><item><title>Download ChrisPC Win Experience Index 7.25.0804</title><pubDate> Tue, 05 Aug 2025 18:09:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-win-experience-index-2338.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-win-experience-index-2338.html
</guid><description>
ChrisPC Win Experience Index helps to check performance of RAM, processor CPU to know that his machine still works fine with the program ChrisPC Win Experience Index brings back the Windows Experience Index are installed on windows 8.1 of you to take out only the number of hardware, after checking the software, return the original interface of your operating system.
ChrisPC Win Experience Index - performance test computer
ChrisPC Win Experience Index installed quickly, after launch,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Zortam Mp3 Media Studio Pro 33.10</title><pubDate> Tue, 05 Aug 2025 18:09:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zortam-mp3-media-studio-pro-135.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zortam-mp3-media-studio-pro-135.html
</guid><description>
Zortam Mp3 Media Studio Pro brings you rich processing tools music includes extract and convert music from CD to Mp3 format, edit, music cards, music download....You can also create discs CD high-quality music, with Zortam Mp3 Media Studio search music files duplicated to remove them from the system, rename music files, switch back and forth between formats.
Zortam Mp3 Media Studio Pro is rated as perfect software in the processing of the MP3 files on the computer. First of all, you can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Gilisoft DRM Protection 8.5</title><pubDate> Tue, 05 Aug 2025 18:08:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-video-drm-protection-5260.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-video-drm-protection-5260.html
</guid><description>
Gilisoft Video DRM Protection is software that helps you can protect your videos and the E-Learning content to another by secure, encrypted the files, your content and distribute them to the target audience authorized of you. Very easy to make video / sound / pictures of you can't see are for anyone except those you allow. Gilisoft Video DRM Protection can encrypt and pack video &amp;amp; codec &amp;amp; player into exe.
Gilisoft Video DRM Protection can easily encode almost any kind of Video...
</description></item><item><title>Download Trellix Stinger (McAfee Stinger) 13.0.0.426</title><pubDate> Tue, 05 Aug 2025 18:07:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mcafee-stinger-202.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mcafee-stinger-202.html
</guid><description>
McAfee Stinger is a free utility that functions to scan, check and remove the hazards and obstacles as virus or malware for Windows, whether they are hiding deep into the system.
In addition, due to the ability to search for the correct folder, or the data at risk contains viruses to scan instead you have to remove a long time waiting for antivirus software to scan all system on your computer. Thus speed of work of the McAfee Stinger faster and somewhat more accurate.
Themselves McAfee...
</description></item><item><title>Download ExtraDisks Home 25.8.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 05 Aug 2025 18:07:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-extradisks-home-7758.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-extradisks-home-7758.html
</guid><description>
ExtraDisks is a set of tools for creating virtual disks on your computer physical drives that do not change and are not divided into additional partitions. The program contains tools for creating encrypted disks, file-based virtual disks and directory-based virtual disks. The current version includes the following tools: Encrypted Disks, Virtual Disks, Folder Disks, Startup Manager, System Tweaker.
Features of ExtraDisks
ExtraDisks: Encrypted Disk
This tool is used to create encrypted...
</description></item><item><title>Download Extra Subst Home 10.8</title><pubDate> Tue, 05 Aug 2025 18:07:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-extra-subst-2605.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-extra-subst-2605.html
</guid><description>
Extra Subst is program designed to help access to the folder is regular use of your computer easier. It is also used to create, edit and remove virtual drives of your computer. Extra Subst creates virtual drives on the basis of the selected folder. Physical drives remain unchanged and are not divided into additional partitions.
Create a new virtual disk is very simple, because you only need to specify the folder which will be connected to, then select the letters and go to it. New virtual...
</description></item><item><title>Download Fast File Encryptor 13.8</title><pubDate> Tue, 05 Aug 2025 18:06:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fast-file-encryptor-2606.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fast-file-encryptor-2606.html
</guid><description>
Fast File Encryptor is the encoder files fast designed for fast processing of the file very big. It can encrypt or decrypt files, contents of folders and contains a lot of additional tools. In addition, there is a tool responsible to completely remove files from the hard drive, you need it if you don't want to leave traces 100 percent in the system. You need to specify the password or key, then select the encryption method, remember remember everything, otherwise it will not work, then...
</description></item><item><title>Download EncryptOnClick 2.4.16</title><pubDate> Tue, 05 Aug 2025 18:06:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-encryptonclick-4935.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-encryptonclick-4935.html
</guid><description>
EncryptOnClick is a tool to encrypt / decrypt simple encrypted using AES 256 bit military grade, fully compatible with WinZip 9. It encrypts the file or folder is selected, and compresses them at the same time. The file is encrypted can be decrypted by EncryptOnClick and anyone who uses WinZip 9x and have the matching password.
EncryptOnClick is designed with simple interface and easy to use for all user objects. To encrypt data on the application window you browse to the file and...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinScript 1.4.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 05 Aug 2025 18:05:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winscript-12800.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winscript-12800.html
</guid><description>
WinScript is an open source tool built to help you build custom scripts for Windows 10 and 11. It includes scripts for debugging, privacy, performance, and more, along with the ability to install all your favorite apps with just one click.
Features
	Debloat: Remove Windows bloatware, CoPilot, Edge, OneDrive, and other pre-installed features preset.
	Privacy: Disable Windows and 3rd party data collection, tracking, app access, and telemetry.
	Performance: Set background services to...
</description></item><item><title>Download EJ Technologies Install4j 11.0.5</title><pubDate> Tue, 05 Aug 2025 18:05:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ej-technologies-install4j-1405.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ej-technologies-install4j-1405.html
</guid><description>
Install4j is a software quite or manufacturer's EJ Technologies, software helps users to build installer Java multi-platform powerful creation of the original installation and the program launch JAVA application. install4j very easy to use, support large platform and system screen and powerful action of it.
EJ Technologies Install4j - build installer Java Multi-platform
The features of Install4j
Easy to use special
	A number of construction installation requirements, you must first...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tier1App yCrash 3.0.9.4</title><pubDate> Tue, 05 Aug 2025 18:01:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tier1app-ycrash-13868.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tier1app-ycrash-13868.html
</guid><description>
yCrash is a root cause analysis tool developed by Tier1App that helps identify the source of complex manufacturing issues. The tool is designed to quickly determine why issues like CPU spikes, memory degradation, or increased response times occur, rather than simply identifying what the problem is.
Key features and functionality of yCrash include:
	Automatic data collection and analysis The tool collects and analyzes over 18 different artifacts, including GC logs, stream backups, and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Software Ideas Modeler Ultimate 15.01</title><pubDate> Tue, 05 Aug 2025 18:01:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-software-ideas-modeler-ultimate-10388.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-software-ideas-modeler-ultimate-10388.html
</guid><description>
Software Ideas Modeler Ultimate is a feature-rich CASE tool that can help you design software using various modeling tools and schematic notations. It will help you create a UML model, ERD designer, diagram generator, wireframing tool or BPMN editor.
Features of Software Ideas Modeler Ultimate
	Tools for UML diagrams, class diagrams, block diagrams, data flow diagrams, and other tools help you design your software or its key parts accurately.
	Handle user requests...
</description></item><item><title>Download CrushFTP 11.3.5.33</title><pubDate> Tue, 05 Aug 2025 18:00:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-crushftp-13882.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-crushftp-13882.html
</guid><description>
CrushFTP is an extremely powerful, easy-to-use solution that runs on almost any operating system: macOS 10.9+/11/12+, Win2012+, Linux, Solaris, BSD, Unix, etc! Any operating system that can run Java 8 at a minimum can run CrushFTP. It supports multiple protocols including FTP, FTPS, SFTP, HTTP, HTTPS, WebDAV, and WebDAV SSL, making it flexible for secure file transfers across a variety of environments.
Key features of CrushFTP include:
	Cross-platform compatibility: Runs on macOS,...
</description></item><item><title>Download NWinfo 1.4.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 05 Aug 2025 17:54:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nwinfo-12590.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nwinfo-12590.html
</guid><description>
NWinfo is a Win32 program that allows you to obtain system and hardware information. It displays essential information about CPU, memory, disk, network, and even system operating details. Because it's portable, you can carry NWinfo on a USB stick and use it on any Windows machine, making it a useful tool for both tech enthusiasts and troubleshooters.
Features of NWinfo
	Get detailed information about SMBIOS, CPUID, S.M.A.R.T., PCI, EDID, etc.
	Supports export in JSON, YAML and LUA...
</description></item><item><title>Download Qalculate! 5.7.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 05 Aug 2025 17:54:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qalculate-7213.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qalculate-7213.html
</guid><description>
Qalculate! is a versatile cross-platform desktop calculator. It's simple to use but offers the power and flexibility typically reserved for complex math packages, as well as useful tools for everyday needs (such as currency converters and fractional calculations). hundred). Features include a large library of customizable functions, unit calculations and conversions, physical constants, symbol calculations (including integrals and equations), arbitrary precision, uncertainty transfer,...
</description></item><item><title>Download EverNote 10.149.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 05 Aug 2025 17:53:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-evernote-3261.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-evernote-3261.html
</guid><description>
EverNote is the all in one tool allows you to track notes, todo items, memos, outlines, excerpts, websites, ideas and other things and automatically synchronize them between multiple computers and mobile devices (iPhone, Android, etc.). You can choose to sort their notes into categories, password protect them, export them to XML and more. EverNote supports a number of pattern notes allow you to add to-do list, spreadsheet like Excel to calculate costs (automatic sum), notes, phone, contact...
</description></item><item><title>Download Raqsoft ReportLite 20250523</title><pubDate> Tue, 05 Aug 2025 15:04:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-raqsoft-reportlite-14006.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-raqsoft-reportlite-14006.html
</guid><description>
ReportLite is a desktop reporting tool that uses the same operating methods as Excel, supports multiple data files as data sources, and generates reports in various formats. Simple operation and flexible settings greatly improve the efficiency of report generation. The tool works similarly to Excel, making it easy for users familiar with spreadsheet tools to use.
Features of ReportLite
	Wizard-based report creation to simplify and quickly set up reports.
	Supports multiple data files...
</description></item><item><title>Download Raqsoft YModel 1.3.8</title><pubDate> Tue, 05 Aug 2025 14:59:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-raqsoft-ymodel-14005.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-raqsoft-ymodel-14005.html
</guid><description>
Raqsoft YModel is an automated data mining tool designed to enable one-click model building, making it accessible to both beginners and programmers unfamiliar with data mining or statistics. YModel enables rapid and automated predictive model creation without requiring deep expertise. YModel supports a comprehensive workflow including data import, target variable configuration, variable selection, model setup, evaluation, and prediction. Models are saved in dedicated files (mcf and pcf...
</description></item><item><title>Download Flameshot 13.0.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 23:26:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-flameshot-11451.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-flameshot-11451.html
</guid><description>
Flameshot is a powerful and user-friendly screenshot tool for Windows that makes it easy to take, edit, and share screenshots. It offers a wide range of features and customization options, making it suitable for both casual and expert users.
It has an interactive GUI (graphical user interface) with controls to select the desired capture area, move and resize the capture window, perform editing with popular drawing tools ( pencil, line, rectangle, circle, blur, undo/redo) and select the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Advanced SystemCare Ultimate 17.5.0.133</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 23:23:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-systemcare-ultimate-132.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-systemcare-ultimate-132.html
</guid><description>
Advanced SystemCare Ultimate 17: Antivirus software that also helps protect, repair, clean and optimize your PC. Based on BitDefender antivirus technology and IObit anti-malware engine, it is part of IObit antivirus project devoted to providing better and value-added services to our users.
With real-time protection against viruses, spyware and phishing attacks, powerful tuning and cleaning functions, Advanced SystemCare Ultimate provides always-on protection, Automatic and all-in-one...
</description></item><item><title>Download ProfiCAD 13.1.5</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 23:23:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-proficad-1546.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-proficad-1546.html
</guid><description>
ProfiCAD is a software Program to draw diagram and circuit diagram of the electrical circuit and electronics with many features to support users. ProfiCAD will search the control circuit is different then help, you can design a variety of diagram techniques, such as diagrams, pneumatic and hydraulic. One of the obvious features of this product is the simplicity of it. Simple in the tool bar and the icons represent the parts. Simply arrange the menu, just put the items on the screen and...
</description></item></channel></rss>