<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 13:44:47 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 13:44:47 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Total Commander - file manager 3.60d Final</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 16:44:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-total-commander-file-manager-8328.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-total-commander-file-manager-8328.html
</guid><description>
Total Commander - file manager is a file manager application available for Android devices as an APK file. It allows users to easily manage and organize their files and folders, including the ability to copy, move, rename, and delete files. The application also includes a built-in text editor, image viewer and media player, allowing users to open and view different types of files directly within the application.
Features of Total Commander - File Manager
	Dual-pane file browsing for...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDF Viewer Pro 2025.5.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 16:43:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pdf-viewer-pro-9527.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pdf-viewer-pro-9527.html
</guid><description>
Whether you're working alone or collaborating with a team, PDF Viewer Pro maximizes productivity, allowing you to view, search, and annotate PDF documents easily on your phone or tablet. your Android tablet or Chromebook.
Features of PDF Viewer Pro
View documents on the go
	Easily open PDF files from your favorite cloud provider, email, or directly from the website you're browsing.
	Search for the exact text you are looking for in the document.
	Double-tap the screen to Smart Zoom...
</description></item><item><title>Download Photo Editor 12.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 16:43:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-iudesk-photo-editor-8321.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-iudesk-photo-editor-8321.html
</guid><description>
Photo Editor is a small but powerful photo editing application. If you have some knowledge about photography, you can do a lot with Photo Editor. Now use Photo Editor to edit photos on your mobile phone just like on your PC.
Photo Editor Features
	Color: exposure, brightness, contrast, saturation, temperature, tone, and hue
	Curves &amp;amp; levels: color fine-tuning
	Effects: gamma correction, auto contrast, auto tone, vibrance, blur, sharpen, oil painting, sketch, high contrast black...
</description></item><item><title>Download Solid Explorer File Manager 3.2.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 16:42:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-solid-explorer-file-manager-8924.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-solid-explorer-file-manager-8924.html
</guid><description>
Solid Explorer is a file management application inspired by old file management applications. Solid Explorer is a popular file management app for Android devices that allows users to manage and organize their files and folders in an intuitive and user-friendly interface. It offers many features that make it stand out from other file management apps.
Solid Explorer allows you to navigate to files stored on your device and automatically organize them into collections. You can view,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Podcast Republic - Podcast app 25.11.26R</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 16:42:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-podcast-republic-podcast-app-8131.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-podcast-republic-podcast-app-8131.html
</guid><description>
Podcast Republic is a podcast app that allows users to discover, download and listen to podcasts on their mobile devices. Podcast Republic is a top quality Podcast App on Android with 4+ million downloads, 76k+ authentic reviews, 600k+ podcasts, and 40+ million episodes worldwide. It offers features like automatic downloading, variable playback speed, and the ability to create and manage playlists. Podcast Republic also supports Android Auto and Chromecast, so you can listen to podcasts...
</description></item><item><title>Download AI Video Editor - VideoShow AI 11.0.2.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 16:42:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-video-editor-maker-videoshow-8149.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-video-editor-maker-videoshow-8149.html
</guid><description>
Video Editor &amp;amp; Maker VideoShow is a video editing and movie making app that allows you to create and edit videos on your mobile device. With this movie maker, creating memes, creating videos or slideshows with photos, images, music, stickers and sound effects is easy and fun. Providing the latest Halloween materials! Young filmmakers can even beautify videos with text, FX, effects, GIFs, trendy filters, transitions or live dubbing in a creative and personalized way.
All-in-one...
</description></item><item><title>Download Weather &amp;amp; Radar USA - Pro 2025.24.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 16:41:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-weather-radar-usa-pro-8391.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-weather-radar-usa-pro-8391.html
</guid><description>
Weather &amp;amp; Radar USA is a mobile application that provides users with real-time weather information and forecasts for locations in the United States. The app includes many features such as current weather conditions, hourly and daily forecasts, radar and satellite images, and severe weather alerts. It also includes many customizable settings, such as the ability to set up multiple locations and receive notifications about specific weather conditions.
Features of Weather &amp;amp; Radar...
</description></item><item><title>Download IPTV Pro 9.1.13</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 16:41:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-iptv-pro-9093.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-iptv-pro-9093.html
</guid><description>
IPTV Pro is an Android application that allows you to watch live TV channels and movies on your Android device. It provides access to many channels from around the world, including sports, news, movies, and entertainment channels. IPTV Pro supports both M3U and XSPF playlists, and allows you to add your own playlists.
IPTV Pro Features
	Supports M3U and XSPF playlists
	Playlist history
	Play a multicast stream using a UDP proxy (the proxy needs to be installed in your LAN)
	Grid, list...
</description></item><item><title>Download AccuWeather: Weather Radar 21.1.4-4-rc</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 16:41:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-accuweather-weather-radar-8893.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-accuweather-weather-radar-8893.html
</guid><description>
Weather warnings from AccuWeather are exceptionally accurate. Whether it's windy, sunny or rainy, you can stay one step ahead with AccuWeather weather radar. Be prepared for daily forecasts or sudden changes in weather with live alerts and accurate weather forecasts. Daily weather snapshots provide storm warnings, weather updates and RealFeel Temperature®, helping to predict today's weather.
With AccuWeather's superior accuracy™ for local forecasts, you'll never miss a memorable...
</description></item><item><title>Download Calculator Plus with History 8.1.6</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 16:40:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-calculator-plus-with-history-10531.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-calculator-plus-with-history-10531.html
</guid><description>
Plus Calculator with History is the perfect calculator for Android. It remembers everything you calculate and allows you to review it at any time, which is perfect for me when shopping, doing homework, balancing my checkbook, or even helping with taxes. And if you need to quit your job and go do something else, I'll have it all ready for you when you get back. You'll never need to re-enter the same calculation twice.
Features of Calculator Plus with History
	Show your calculations in...
</description></item><item><title>Download Email Aqua Mail - Fast, Secure 1.56.0 build 105600588</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 16:40:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-email-aqua-mail-fast-secure-8329.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-email-aqua-mail-fast-secure-8329.html
</guid><description>
Aqua Mail is the right app for all your email needs! Whether it's a work or personal email, a company exchange server, or even a rarely used secondary account, Aqua Mail lets you easily access all your emails from one complete app. edit.
No complicated setup required, just enter your email and password and you're done. With flexibility and diverse customization options, Aqua Mail's goal is to reflect the needs of modern users and provide a platform that anyone can tailor to their needs...
</description></item><item><title>Download ASICS Runkeeper - Run Tracker 16.17</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 16:40:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-asics-runkeeper-run-tracker-8334.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-asics-runkeeper-run-tracker-8334.html
</guid><description>
Join a community that helps people escape difficulties and stick with running forever! Track your workouts, set goals, sweat, and see your progress. Whether you're trying to track a 5K goal or train for a marathon, use the GPS app trusted by 50 million users and counting.
ASICS Runkeeper - Run Tracker is a mobile application that allows users to track running and fitness activities on their Android devices. The app uses GPS to track the user's distance, pace, and running time as well as...
</description></item><item><title>Download JPEG Optimizer PRO 1.1.20</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 16:39:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-jpeg-optimizer-pro-with-pdf-support-10818.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-jpeg-optimizer-pro-with-pdf-support-10818.html
</guid><description>
Can't send images due to email attachment size limits? No room to save them on your SD card? JPEG Optimizer is the best solution for you. This app will allow you to compress large photos into smaller ones with little or no loss of quality. Furthermore, the unique ISO Noise Optimization algorithm allows you to reduce image file size to improve quality.
Features of JPEG Optimizer PRO
	Compress, resize photos
	Compress or resize multiple photos at once
	Allows you to adjust the quality...
</description></item><item><title>Download Listen Audiobook Player 5.3.6 build 1100</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 16:38:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-listen-audiobook-player-8511.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-listen-audiobook-player-8511.html
</guid><description>
Listen Audiobook Player is a mobile app for playing audiobooks on your phone or tablet. It lets you play, pause, rewind, and fast-forward audiobooks with ease, while also providing a convenient way to track your listening progress.
Some key features of Listen Audiobook Player include:
	Library Management: Allows you to store and organize your audiobooks in a virtual library for easy access.
	Bookmark: Automatically saves your listening position so you can pick up where you left...
</description></item><item><title>Download All-In-One Calculator 3.2.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 16:38:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-all-in-one-calculator-9092.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-all-in-one-calculator-9092.html
</guid><description>
All-In-One Calculator is a simple, clean and easy-to-use calculator with a full set of tools for everyday life, such as a unit converter, currency converter, percentage calculator and more. From simple or complex calculations, to unit and currency conversions, percentages, ratios, area, volume, etc. it does it all. And it does it!
Features of All-In-One Calculator
Main Calculator
	Simple or Scientific Layout
	40 Light or Dark (AMOLED) Themes
	Editable Input &amp;amp; Cursor
	Copy &amp;amp;...
</description></item><item><title>Download DAVx⁵ – CalDAV CardDAV WebDAV 4.5.6.1-gplay</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 16:37:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-davx-caldav-carddav-webdav-8633.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-davx-caldav-carddav-webdav-8633.html
</guid><description>
DAVx is the only all-in-one app for everything CalDAV, CardDAV and WebDAV! This is a full-featured synchronization solution for your contacts (CardDAV), calendar (CalDAV), and tasks (based on VTODO). The app is easy to install and integrates seamlessly with your favorite calendar/contacts apps (including default apps). It can also be used separately if you have CalDAV, CardDAV or just Tasks. DAVx can also be used to access your remote WebDAV files.
Features of DAVx for Android
	Sync...
</description></item><item><title>Download Librera PRO - Book reader 9.1.12</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 16:37:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-librera-pro-all-my-books-9008.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-librera-pro-all-my-books-9008.html
</guid><description>
PRO Librera Reader is an easy-to-use and highly configurable reading application that supports most popular document formats, including: PDF, EPUB, EPUB3, MOBI, DjVu, FB2, FB2.zip, TXT, RTF, AZW, AZW3, CBR, CBZ, HTML, XPS, MHT and more. With a simple yet powerful interface, Librera Reader makes reading documents a real pleasure. Librera even has a unique hands-free, auto-scrolling music mode.
Some key features of Librera reader include:
Easily explore documents with optional and...
</description></item><item><title>Download TechCalc+ Calculator 5.2.5 build 369</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 16:37:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-techcalc-calculator-8396.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-techcalc-calculator-8396.html
</guid><description>
TechCalc+ Calculator is a mobile application that provides users with advanced scientific and engineering calculations on their Android devices. It includes many functions and features, such as trigonometry, logarithms, complex numbers, and unit conversions, making it suitable for students, engineers, and scientists. The app also includes many customizable settings, such as the ability to choose between different modes, such as RPN, algebra, and engineering, and customize the layout and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Web Video Cast | Browser to TV 5.12.8 build 5610</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 16:36:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-web-video-cast-browser-to-tv-8372.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-web-video-cast-browser-to-tv-8372.html
</guid><description>
Web Video Cast allows you to watch TV videos from your favorite websites including movies, TV shows, live news, sports and IPTV. It also allows you to stream local videos stored on your phone. Image and audio files are also supported. Subtitles are detected on the website, you can also use your own subtitles or you can use the built-in search feature of OpenSubtitles.org.
Web Video Caster supports the most popular streaming devices, allowing your TV to stream video directly from the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Shazam: Find Music &amp;amp; Concerts 16.20.0-251120</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 16:36:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-shazam-music-discovery-10763.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-shazam-music-discovery-10763.html
</guid><description>
Shazam will identify any song in seconds. Discover, artists, lyrics, videos &amp;amp; playlists, all for free. Over 1 billion installs and counting. Use Pop-up Shazam to identify music in any app - Instagram, YouTube, TikTok... No connection? No problem! Shazam while offline.
Features of Shazam: Music Discovery
	Find the name of any song in seconds.
	Listen and add to Apple Music playlists.
	Follow along with time-synced lyrics.
	Watch music videos from Apple Music or YouTube.
	Enable...
</description></item><item><title>Download Password Safe and Manager 9.0.0 build 900001</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 16:35:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-password-safe-and-manager-8210.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-password-safe-and-manager-8210.html
</guid><description>
Password Safe and Manager is a password management application for Android devices. The app also includes features like login autofill, a password generator, and a built-in browser to access your account directly from the app. It's a great way to securely store and manage your login information and other sensitive information.
Summary of essential functions
	securely store passwords, access data, etc.
	classify your entries in Password Security
	access via a single master...
</description></item><item><title>Download Passwords &amp;amp; Passkeys－Safe 26.7.13</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 16:35:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-password-manager-safeincloud-pro-10227.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-password-manager-safeincloud-pro-10227.html
</guid><description>
Protect your data with a unique and secure password! Forget the headache of remembering PINs and passwords! START USING PASSWORD MANAGER TODAY! SafeInCloud is a complete password management solution: Free desktop app + Mobile app for phones and tablets.
Features of Password Manager SafeInCloud Pro
	Material Design
	Dark theme
	Strong encryption (AES)
	Cloud synchronization (Google Drive, Dropbox, OneDrive)
	Finger Scan and Multi-Window (Samsung devices)
	Analyze password...
</description></item><item><title>Download Easy Notes - Note Taking Apps 1.3.32.1126</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 16:35:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-easy-notes-notebook-notepad-8388.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-easy-notes-notebook-notepad-8388.html
</guid><description>
Easy Notes - Great note taking app, Notepad, Notebook, Free Notes is a free easy to use note taking app for notes app. With this easy notebook and notepad app, take quick notes with colorful backgrounds and checklists to organize notes and tasks easily. Use this aesthetic note taker and note taker to add photos or audio to your notes. Easy Notes is a useful notebook and note-taking app for taking notes and organizing work.
Features of Easy Notes - Notebook, Notepad
	Free Notepad and...
</description></item><item><title>Download PeakFinder 4.8.62</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 16:34:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-peakfinder-10050.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-peakfinder-10050.html
</guid><description>
Explore more mountains than any other climber! PeakFinder AR makes it possible… and shows the names of all the mountains and peaks with a 360° panoramic display. This functionality is completely offline - and worldwide! PeakFinder knows more than 650,000 mountain peaks - from Mount Everest to that little hill on the corner.
PeakFinder Features
	Works offline and worldwide
	Includes more than 650,000 peak names
	Install the camera image using a panoramic drawing *
	Display real-time...
</description></item><item><title>Download 9GAG: Funny GIF, Meme &amp;amp; Video 8.17.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 16:34:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-9gag-funny-gif-meme-video-11500.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-9gag-funny-gif-meme-video-11500.html
</guid><description>
9GAG has the best funny, cute, weird, wacky, cosplay photos, GIFs, videos, memes, photos on the web. We are your greatest and happiest source. With millions of visitors every day, 9GAG is an application that helps you play LOL, kill time and make new friends around the world.
9GAG features
	The 9GAG app loads quickly and allows for easy scrolling. Don't waste time picking me up or just having a good laugh.
	Carry unlimited fun in your pocket. Enjoy 9GAG anytime, anywhere and...
</description></item></channel></rss>