<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 01:42:50 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 01:42:50 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download NetSpeedTray 1.1.6 + Portable</title><pubDate> Fri, 29 Aug 2025 00:03:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-netspeedtray-14068.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-netspeedtray-14068.html
</guid><description>
NetSpeedTray is a lightweight, open source network monitor for Windows that displays upload/download speeds directly on the Taskbar with a native look and feel.
Designed to blend seamlessly with Windows 10/11 user interface. Includes intelligent detection of light and dark themes on the taskbar to ensure text is always visible. Sits quietly in the system tray without hogging resources. Features "Dynamic Update Rate" that automatically reduces update frequency when the network is idle to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Radiant Photo 2.1.0.756 + Addon Pack</title><pubDate> Thu, 28 Aug 2025 23:56:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-radiant-photo-8319.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-radiant-photo-8319.html
</guid><description>
Radiant Photo is a photo editing software that allows users to edit, enhance and organize their digital photos. It provides many tools to adjust color, brightness, contrast, saturation, and other image properties, as well as features to crop, rotate, and resize images.
Radiant Photo also includes many filters and effects that can be applied to photos to change their appearance. Additionally, it also allows users to organize their photos by creating albums, tagging photos, and searching...
</description></item><item><title>Download JoyToKey 7.3.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 28 Aug 2025 23:55:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-joytokey-1983.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-joytokey-1983.html
</guid><description>
JoyToKey (or Joy2Key) enables game controller PC simulation input keyboard and mouse for Windows applications and web games can be controlled by the joystick of your favorite! Whenever the buttons and sticks are pressed on the controller, JoyToKey will convert them into keyboard strokes and / or mouse movement to the destination application will act as able to use the keyboard and mouse real. JoyToKey lets create some configuration file, which supports up to 16 joysticks, compatible with...
</description></item><item><title>Download SoftMaker Office Professional 2024 Rev S1226.0817</title><pubDate> Thu, 28 Aug 2025 23:55:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-softmaker-office-professional-819.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-softmaker-office-professional-819.html
</guid><description>
SoftMaker Office Professional version, professional office support in terms of writing, calculation, presentation, E-mail, tasks,.. When using SoftMaker Office documents, calculations and presentations are handled as fast as e-mail or appointment and task planning. From the simple work daily to these documents, the most demanding, SoftMaker Office 2018 is the indispensable help of you.
SoftMaker Office is compatible with all the Microsoft Office. It edit Microsoft Office documents true to...
</description></item><item><title>Download R-Wipe &amp;amp; Clean 20.0 Build 2523</title><pubDate> Thu, 28 Aug 2025 23:53:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-wipe-clean-891.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-wipe-clean-891.html
</guid><description>
R-Wipe &amp;amp; Clean is software to delete junk files, unnecessary files from your computer to release the storage space and speed up your computer. In addition, R-Wipe &amp;amp; Clean also unleash the capacity of your drive and delete information invasion of privacy on different operations online and offline including your internet history and cookies, the list of downloaded files and documents were open, buffer different data, temporary files and many other items, created by the operating...
</description></item><item><title>Download Iperius Backup Full 8.6.3</title><pubDate> Thu, 28 Aug 2025 23:53:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iperius-backup-621.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iperius-backup-621.html
</guid><description>
Iperius Backup software supports backup and restore of data can be stored on a cloud service, and AES 256-bit. This is the perfect software to get the advantages of the many services that cloud storage is provided by the famous supplier like Google or Microsoft. With a single application, you will can easily save your files externally on Google Drive, Dropbox or Microsoft SkyDrive.
Iperius Backup uses the technology images Windows drive most advanced, allows to copy entire operating...
</description></item><item><title>Download InternetTest Pro 9.0.1.2508</title><pubDate> Thu, 28 Aug 2025 23:52:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-internettest-6718.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-internettest-6718.html
</guid><description>
InternetTest is a small multipurpose tool to check internet connection status and more, you can easily verify if a particular website is down or not. no and navigate to it via the Down Detector function. You can also check the IP location in the app via OpenStreetMap, Bing Maps or Google Maps. It will also give you the connection history displayed on the right side of the simple interface.
Features of InternetTest
	Check your Internet connection
	IP Localization
	Down Detector
	Dark...
</description></item><item><title>Download Battery Monitor 10.5</title><pubDate> Thu, 28 Aug 2025 23:51:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-battery-monitor-1049.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-battery-monitor-1049.html
</guid><description>
Battery Monitor is a small utility that display on the computer screen the details current battery of laptop your as its name. The interface is based on a small frame can be moved to any location on the screen, with the help of the mouse cursor.
Battery Monitor is not popular and you can quickly get overview of the battery details while working in other apps. The main frame displays the clock and percent level, battery status, remaining time, charging speed and charging current. Battery...
</description></item><item><title>Download EmEditor Pro 25.3.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 28 Aug 2025 23:49:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-emeditor-pro-69.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-emeditor-pro-69.html
</guid><description>
EmEditor Pro - the professional version of editor text powerful for programmers, web developers and ordinary users with illumination of syntax and Unicode support. The features of the editor such as search and replace in files using regular expressions, automatic code detect, bookmark link and address email, block selection mode, configure the button bar, menu, font and elements color. With each language you can set separate configuration.
EmEditor Pro - text Editor professional
The...
</description></item><item><title>Download pdfMachine Ultimate 20.48</title><pubDate> Thu, 28 Aug 2025 23:48:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdfmachine-ultimate-959.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdfmachine-ultimate-959.html
</guid><description>
pdfMachine Ultimate  is a PDF reader and editor. Additionally, pdfMachine converts a print stream from an application directly into PDF. Just open your document you want to convert, then click "print", choose "Broadgun pdfMachine printer" and the conversion is complete.
pdfMachine Ultimate - Read and edit PDF files 
Broadgun pdfMachine Ultimate  will make it easy to read  PDF  files for PDFs or other portable document formats that make extensive use of the original file formats...
</description></item><item><title>Download Photo Supreme 2025.3.3.8062</title><pubDate> Thu, 28 Aug 2025 23:48:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photo-supreme-430.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photo-supreme-430.html
</guid><description>
Photo Supreme is a software product management professional pictures of idimager. With Photo Supreme you can arrange, manage back stock photo archive of yourself and share them with you here and relatives easily via Email or Facebook. Photo Supreme provides users method to sort images effective, logical, as well as edit and share your photos with friends and relatives in the family. Especially the Photo Supreme allows to work with multiple image formats and support mounting support,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Opera One 121.0.5600.38</title><pubDate> Thu, 28 Aug 2025 23:47:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-972.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-972.html
</guid><description>
Opera is a fast, safe, configurable and compliant intranet web browser, which includes both the reader and the application. The Opera browser supports web browsing, listening to music, watching high speed movies, you can open many tabs on the Opera without affecting your browsing speed. Opera now supports almost all devices and operating systems such as windows, IOS, Android, linux, MacOS ...
Opera is a beautiful interface and many interesting features, operating on both PCs and mobile,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tenorshare 4DDiG File Repair 4.2.0.9</title><pubDate> Thu, 28 Aug 2025 23:46:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tenorshare-4ddig-file-repair-5630.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tenorshare-4ddig-file-repair-5630.html
</guid><description>
Tenorshare 4DDiG File Repair is AI-powered software to repair damaged or damaged videos, photos, files and audios, improve their quality and add color to black media white. 4DDiG photo editing solves all photo problems like blurry photos, overexposed photos, etc. Powered by AI, it can dramatically improve image resolution and colorize black and white photos in seconds, not hours.
Features of Tenorshare 4DDiG File Repair
	Easily repair any blurry, overexposed and damaged videos, photos...
</description></item><item><title>Download 3DP Chip 25.8</title><pubDate> Thu, 28 Aug 2025 23:46:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-3dp-chip-2282.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-3dp-chip-2282.html
</guid><description>
3DP Chip is software commonly used in the update of the version latest driver for your computer. The advantage of this software is completely free, compact and easy to use. 3DP Chip will help the hardware always works in the best state, with the 3DP Chip, you can know the driver has been outdated, then let the software automatically searches for the latest version and installed for your system.
3DP Chip - Download and update driver
With the 3DP Chip you can learn everything about the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Secret Disk Pro 2025 v312</title><pubDate> Thu, 28 Aug 2025 23:46:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secret-disk-pro-933.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secret-disk-pro-933.html
</guid><description>
Secret Disk Pro 4 is a software to create a virtual disk can be hidden and password protected to keep your data private and safe. You can store any file and folder on the disk. Disc secret works like a hard disk typically, and is compatible with any any other program that you have installed. You can have more than one disk secret, and you can also choose disk letter.
Secret Disk Pro 4 - Create and secure drive
Secret Disk does not encrypt any files, it just limits access to your files...
</description></item><item><title>Download DesktopOK 11.97</title><pubDate> Thu, 28 Aug 2025 23:45:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopok-1635.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopok-1635.html
</guid><description>
DesktopOK is software save and restore the positions of icons. DesktopOK also offers a solution small but effective for the user to change the screen resolution often. DesktopOK is not installed and can be executed easily from the desktop, and can be carried on a small USB or memory device to another. Start of the program. The first time you use the program, the program will show you screen license. Free program and license info is only displayed the first time (on each PC).
DesktopOK -...
</description></item><item><title>Download IntraWEB Ultimate 16.1.3</title><pubDate> Thu, 28 Aug 2025 23:44:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intraweb-ultimate-2007.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intraweb-ultimate-2007.html
</guid><description>
IntraWEB Ultimate is a tool to build the website. With this tool, the developer can create the page using the same method used to build the Windows program. Because the HTML page directly from the concept design to the user's computer does not download a bit more complicated and in fact is required from web server. So, the template IntraWeb on the server and download server and displays them to the user. Things technology direction of the IntraWEB Ultimate provides part flexibility and...
</description></item><item><title>Download EssentialPIM Pro Business 12.5.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 28 Aug 2025 23:44:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-essentialpim-pro-561.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-essentialpim-pro-561.html
</guid><description>
EssentialPIM Pro is software for managing personal information allows you to create tasks, notes, appointments, contacts and to-do list, browse mail email Outlook and synchronize the data with the background spectrum biếnduyệt email Outlook email and synchronize data with the popular platform.
With EssentialPIM Pro, you can navigate and create appointments and new task list by specifying as much information as possible, such as subject, location, status, duration, start and finish,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Opera GX (Gaming Browser) 121.0.5600.41</title><pubDate> Thu, 28 Aug 2025 23:43:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-gx-3170.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-gx-3170.html
</guid><description>
Opera GX is a special version of the Opera browser is built to complement gamers avid. Browser this game comes with the unique features to help users make maximum use of both the game and their browser. Opera GX is built specifically to support the game. This browser includes the unique features to help users have the best experience when gaming and surfing the web.
Opera GX - special browser for gamers
GX Control allows you to set a limit on the level of use RAM, CPU and network where...
</description></item><item><title>Download Vivaldi Browser 7.5.3735.66</title><pubDate> Thu, 28 Aug 2025 23:43:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vivaldi-159.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vivaldi-159.html
</guid><description>
Vivaldi is a browser designed for users who have power and offer the option to customize high. You can choose the location of the tabs and the address bar, put the hotkeys for the common tasks and many other features. Also, Vivaldi also provides a number of improvements such as Tab Stacks to group multiple open tabs into a tab, leads to interface less cluttered. Can notes and added a screenshot of a web page while browsing, storing an attachment, and add the URL to easily sort and locate...
</description></item><item><title>Download Geometric Glovius Pro 6.6.40.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 28 Aug 2025 23:42:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-geometric-glovius-pro-754.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-geometric-glovius-pro-754.html
</guid><description>
Geometric Glovius Pro is viewer CAD 3D modern for files CATIA, NX, STEP, IGES, Pro/ENGINEER and Creo, SolidWorks, Inventor and Solid Edge. The work of Geometric Glovius Pro is made exact measurements, cut dynamic sections, compare differences between models and export to 3D PDF, STL and Glovius Mobile.
Geometric Glovius Pro - manager, and view CAD 3D
The features of Geometric Glovius Pro
	Modern interface, simple, easy to use
	Mobile app for free for iOS &amp;amp; Android powerful...
</description></item><item><title>Download App Builder 2025.24</title><pubDate> Thu, 28 Aug 2025 23:42:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-app-builder-241.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-app-builder-241.html
</guid><description>
App Builder is a software application developer to help create and design apps, HTML5, web app, web app PWA on both platforms mobile and desktop. App Builder is professional software supports users to create the program HTML5 without writing code. It is very easy to use, suitable with all users who lack of professional knowledge in the field of programming and application design.
App Builder brings to 22 different themes that users can use to design for your app. You can choose 1 or a...
</description></item><item><title>Download ButterScroll 1.3.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 28 Aug 2025 23:41:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-butterscroll-13824.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-butterscroll-13824.html
</guid><description>
Smooth scrolling on Windows just got better. Smooth scrolling for Windows is what ButterScroll is all about. It improves the way your mouse scrolls using customizable speed and ease settings.
Smooth scrolling for all types of mice.
ButterScroll improves your everyday scrolling experience with smooth scrolling precision, customizable controls, and a satisfying feel across all your Windows apps — from browsers to spreadsheets.
ButterScroll Features
	Easy to set up and use
	Smooth,...
</description></item><item><title>Download DBF Converter 7.61</title><pubDate> Thu, 28 Aug 2025 23:41:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbf-converter-6362.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbf-converter-6362.html
</guid><description>
DBF Converter is a common solution for all your DBF format conversion needs. Whenever you need to extract data from the DBF file to CSV, XLS, XLSX, SQL or pure text, the software will provide a simple way to do this with minimal effort.
Features of DBF Converter
	Work with DBF Converter is easy. You specify a DBF file or a directory with DBF files that you want to convert, select the fields and filter out the records you need. Then, just a click to DBF Converter to turn the source...
</description></item><item><title>Download DBF Viewer 2000 v8.80.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 28 Aug 2025 23:40:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbf-viewer-2000-7869.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbf-viewer-2000-7869.html
</guid><description>
DBF Viewer 2000 is a fast, efficient solution for viewing and editing all types of DBF files. It can handle files from dBase, Visual dBase, Foxpro, Visual FoxPro and Clipper, just to name a few, with performance that easily rivals expensive professional database utilities. DBF Viewer 2000 is extremely fast, does any task, just one simple query and cleanup copy to export data at lightning speed.
With DBF Editor's simple, dynamically generated visual dialogs, you can easily view the...
</description></item></channel></rss>