<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:39:41 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:39:41 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Q-Dir 12.42</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 02:25:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-q-dir-348.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-q-dir-348.html
</guid><description>
Q-Dir is software to manage the entire file and folder on the computer, allowing to see file in same time 4 different positions (viewport quadro) while still maintaining all the standard features of the Explorer.
It also provides a variety of management features, additional files included the filter file color-coding, layouts and columns can be customized, quick access to file and folder favorites and more.
Other features of Q-Dir , including directory listings (.txt, .doc .html .csv),...
</description></item><item><title>Download FanControl v250</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 02:24:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fancontrol-5749.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fancontrol-5749.html
</guid><description>
FanControl is a highly customizable fan control software for Windows. Stay in control of every aspect of your PC's GPU and CPU fan with the help of this highly customizable fan control app.
Features of FanControl
	Save, edit and load multiple configurations
	Multiple temperature sources (CPU, GPU, motherboard, hard drive, ".sensor" files)
	Custom fan curve
	Fine tune fan control response with steps,% start,% stop, response time and delay
	Mix different curves and sensors...
</description></item><item><title>Download doPDF 11.9.512</title><pubDate> Wed, 26 Nov 2025 23:53:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dopdf-923.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dopdf-923.html
</guid><description>
doPDF is software that converts any printable document how to PDF format. doPDF acts as a virtual printer for PDF documents. The program installs as a printer driver virtual and can be accessed from any application which supports printing.
doPDF which allows users to create PDF documents by choosing "Print" from any application and with only a single operation, you can convert your document such as Microsoft Excel, Word, PowerPoint or the email and the address of your favorite websites to...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinToHDD Professional + Technician 6.8.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 26 Nov 2025 23:51:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wintohdd-professional-technician-4406.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wintohdd-professional-technician-4406.html
</guid><description>
WinToHDD is software Windows handy and useful allows you to install or re-install Windows without using CD / DVD drive or USB. With this software installed All-In-One Windows, you can easily re-install Windows, install Windows on another drive than the one where Windows operating system you installed, or is installing Windows operating system (Windows vista or later) to another disk.
WinToHDD Professional + Technician - Support install Windows
In addition to creating a USB drive that...
</description></item><item><title>Download Radiant Photo 2.2.0.814 + Addon Pack</title><pubDate> Wed, 26 Nov 2025 23:51:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-radiant-photo-8319.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-radiant-photo-8319.html
</guid><description>
Radiant Photo is a photo editing software that allows users to edit, enhance and organize their digital photos. It provides many tools to adjust color, brightness, contrast, saturation, and other image properties, as well as features to crop, rotate, and resize images.
Radiant Photo also includes many filters and effects that can be applied to photos to change their appearance. Additionally, it also allows users to organize their photos by creating albums, tagging photos, and searching...
</description></item><item><title>Download AI Voice Changer 5.5.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 26 Nov 2025 23:50:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ai-voice-changer-14258.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ai-voice-changer-14258.html
</guid><description>
AI Voice Changer is a real-time voice changer powered by artificial intelligence technology. It allows users to easily change their voice style, tone, and intonation to create a unique voice experience. Whether it's gaming, live entertainment, voice chat, or content creation, AI Voice Changer delivers natural, smooth, intelligent, and accurate voice changing effects.
Features of AI Voice Changer
	Dual Recording Mode
	Recording Mode: Record first, then apply effects and...
</description></item><item><title>Download 3DCoat 2025.13</title><pubDate> Wed, 26 Nov 2025 23:50:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-3d-coat-1269.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-3d-coat-1269.html
</guid><description>
3D Coat is a computer program that trade for modeling objects of different organic and 3D models low-poly. The app provides a variety of tools allow users to create sculptures, adding topology, create UV maps, texture surface interactions of the model, showing the static and animated round of the pattern.
3D Coat - 3D modeling
The content in the software 3D Coat:
Texture simple and PBR:
	Support drawing drawings top en model, draw the pixel and Ptex
	Rendered physics-based (PBR)...
</description></item><item><title>Download Directory Opus Pro 13.19.7 Beta</title><pubDate> Wed, 26 Nov 2025 23:49:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-opus-pro-779.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-opus-pro-779.html
</guid><description>
Directory Opus Pro is a software replacement for Explorer with traditional strength and function more than any manager other files. Directory Opus Pro full support for high DPI screen (for example 4K and 5K) with the rename dialog is redesigned, with new features. Besides being a recording macro only allows you to perform mass renaming complex that don't need regular expressions. In addition, Directory Opus Pro also enhances the ability to script.Better handling of renaming recursive and...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinToHDD Enterprise 6.8</title><pubDate> Wed, 26 Nov 2025 23:48:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wintohdd-enterprise-388.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wintohdd-enterprise-388.html
</guid><description>
WinToHDD Enterprise is useful software that allows you to install or reinstall Windows without using a CD/DVD or USB drive. This is the software that can set up all the settings of the windows in one. With WinToHDD Enterprise it is easy to reinstall Windows, install Windows on other disks with your Windows operating system settings or copy existing Windows OS settings.
In addition to creating a USB drive that contains all the setup files of the OS, you can use an app like WinToHDD. Its...
</description></item><item><title>Download Luminar Neo 1.25.1 (15981)</title><pubDate> Wed, 26 Nov 2025 23:47:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-luminar-neoo-7194.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-luminar-neoo-7194.html
</guid><description>
Luminar Neo is an innovative image editor powered by futuristic AI technologies that simplifies complex editing workflows and allows creators to turn their boldest ideas into reality. Luminar Neo calculates image depth and generates 3D maps, allowing you to naturally scatter light in 3D across a 2D image. This opens the door to unleash your creativity to bring your artistic vision to life.
MaskAI automates the masking process by identifying objects in the image and creating the correct...
</description></item><item><title>Download Print Artist Gold 25.0.3.4</title><pubDate> Wed, 26 Nov 2025 23:47:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-print-artist-gold-12667.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-print-artist-gold-12667.html
</guid><description>
Print Artist Gold allows users to create impressive designs for home, school or business purposes, making it a versatile tool for both personal and professional use. It offers 16,700+ professionally designed templates, 277,000+ stunning graphics, 700+ premium fonts, and more! With powerful yet easy-to-use design, text, and drawing customization tools, an advanced photo editor, a library of special text effects, and more, you'll create stunning print projects. professional, eye-catching...
</description></item><item><title>Download VectorStyler 1.3.001</title><pubDate> Wed, 26 Nov 2025 23:46:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vectorstyler-7917.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vectorstyler-7917.html
</guid><description>
VectorStyler provides a complete set of drawing, design and illustration tools needed for modern design. Create illustrations, logos, icons, drawings, typography, vector art for screen, print and web. With many new features, VectorStyler redefines and extends the tools available to illustrators and designers, improving the creation of complex illustrations and designs.
Shape effects can be used to adjust the shape of objects, create different distortions, or add detail to shapes. Shape...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tecplot Focus 2025 R1 v2025.1.0.72401</title><pubDate> Wed, 26 Nov 2025 23:46:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tecplot-focus-6031.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tecplot-focus-6031.html
</guid><description>
Tecplot Focus allows you to quickly draw up your sugar and surface techniques as well as check the exact data in the way you want. You can analyze and explore complex data sets, organize lots of XY, 2D and 3D cells, and communicate your results to your colleagues with high quality output.
This application is very easy to use and is the perfect solution for all the needs of your image from the simple XY tiles to the complex dynamic images of the contaminant beam. This is a comprehensive...
</description></item><item><title>Download FanCtrl 1.7.8</title><pubDate> Wed, 26 Nov 2025 23:45:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fanctrl-5779.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fanctrl-5779.html
</guid><description>
FanCtrl is software that allows you to automatically control the fan speed on your PC. FanCtrl is easy to use, although the app is best for high-end users. You can cause damage to your computer due to overheating or conflict with other processors or other monitoring software. As an independent developed application, not all motherboards are or may be supported.
The application is well positioned and is located in the system tray with the name of the motherboard, every fan and control...
</description></item><item><title>Download File Viewer Plus 6.2.0.80</title><pubDate> Wed, 26 Nov 2025 23:44:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-file-viewer-plus-6043.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-file-viewer-plus-6043.html
</guid><description>
File Viewer Plus 4 opens more than 400 file formats. See dozens of common types of files, such as Office documents, PDF and photo files, all with a program. Play hundreds of audio and video file formats with a built-in multimedia browser. Compress the archive file with the file compression solution. You can also open file formats that are less popular with File Viewer Plus. See the Microsoft Project and Visio documentation. Open source code files that mark the syntax. Open the email...
</description></item><item><title>Download Rainbow Analyst add-in Professional 25.11.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 26 Nov 2025 23:43:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rainbow-analyst-add-in-professional-11122.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rainbow-analyst-add-in-professional-11122.html
</guid><description>
Rainbow Analyst add-in Professional is a powerful tool designed to enhance data analysis in Microsoft Excel. This add-on provides many advanced features and visualizations to help users gain valuable insights from their data.
One of the key features of Rainbow Analyst is the ability to create color-coded reports and charts. Users can assign specific colors to different data values, making it easier to identify patterns, trends, and outliers. This visual representation of data enhances...
</description></item><item><title>Download VovSoft Picture Downloader 3.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 26 Nov 2025 23:42:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-picture-downloader-5253.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-picture-downloader-5253.html
</guid><description>
VovSoft Picture Downloader is the download at images to find and download millions of image files from web easily. VovSoft Picture Downloader has a simple interface consists of two separate tabs, one to search images by search engine and another to perform a search on a specific website. Method download at first allows you to select tools to use and perform a search online using the keyword as a primary filter, while method Monday requires you to enter a starting URL and search for...
</description></item><item><title>Download 5KPlayer 6.11</title><pubDate> Wed, 26 Nov 2025 23:42:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-5kplayer-1085.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-5kplayer-1085.html
</guid><description>
5KPlayer is software play music and watch movies on the computer with many different formats are supported. 5KPlayer, composite the HD video (MKV) free, the music player, the media player supports DLNA &amp;amp; AirPlay, and the download at online. 5KPlayer has the ability to play a video format 4K, 5K, the video is 1080p HD, DVD, listen the you music MP3, AAC, APE, FLAC sound quality, best picture. In addition, you can view video formats MKV, M2TS, MP4, AVI, WMV, FLV, 4K, 5K Ultra HD is...
</description></item><item><title>Download VovSoft Collect URL 3.6</title><pubDate> Wed, 26 Nov 2025 23:41:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-collect-url-7395.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-collect-url-7395.html
</guid><description>
VovSoft Collect URL is an internet scanner like a search engine bot. Starting from the URL the user entered, it lists all the links on the URL. Then it recursively scans all the links in the list. Users can limit URL Crawl to only one domain name. The file extension ignore list can be edited. Connection and response timeout values ​​are editable. Additionally, the user can change the user agent value for HTTP and HTTPS connections.
Features of VovSoft Collect URL
	Scan the...
</description></item><item><title>Download KS DB Merge Tools for PostgreSQL Pro 1.16</title><pubDate> Wed, 26 Nov 2025 23:41:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ks-db-merge-tools-for-postgresql-pro-10408.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ks-db-merge-tools-for-postgresql-pro-10408.html
</guid><description>
KS DB Merge Tools for PostgreSQL Pro is software specifically designed for PostgreSQL databases, allowing you to synchronize and compare both schema and data. In essence, it can compare schema and data in two different PostgreSQL databases. It can compare both schemas and programming objects, such as tables, views, procedures, functions, and sequences.
Features of KS DB Merge Tools for PostgreSQL Pro
	Compare two PostgreSQL databases side by side
	Compare schemas and data in...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft PowerToys for Windows 10/11 0.96.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 26 Nov 2025 23:40:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-powertoys-for-windows-6014.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-powertoys-for-windows-6014.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft PowerToys is a user-proficiency set to adjust and streamline their Windows experience for higher productivity. Inspired by Windows 95's PowerToys project, this reboot provides users with proficiency in ways to exploit the more efficient Windows 10 and customisable processes it provides for each work process.
Utility of Microsoft PowerToys
	FancyZones is a window manager that allows you to easily create complex windows layout and quickly locate windows in those layout.
	Image...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tecplot RS 2024 R1 M1 v2024.1.0.67830</title><pubDate> Wed, 26 Nov 2025 20:44:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tecplot-rs-5019.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tecplot-rs-5019.html
</guid><description>
Tecplot RS helps you manage and analyze large amounts of data, simulation reservoir, discover the knowledge about the behavior pattern of reservoir and convey your results to colleagues and management by image and animation professional. Tools analysis and visualization is very important in process simulation to help you fully understand his model. Work closely with the reservoir engineers in the past 15 years, our team has researched the process simulation reservoir typical.
The main...
</description></item><item><title>Download Internet Download Manager (IDM) 6.42 Build 56</title><pubDate> Wed, 26 Nov 2025 16:03:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-inetnet-download-manager-161.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-inetnet-download-manager-161.html
</guid><description>
Internet Download Manager is the download acceleration software, the best download support now, it can help you speed up the download up to five times, continue and schedule downloads. The latest version of IDM adds the compatibility of Windows 10 and Windows 11, it has supported all current popular browsers such as Internet Explorer, Mozilla Firefox, Opera, Google Chrome, ..
Download IDM with the latest version on taiwebs.com making it easy to download and manage your downloaded files...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ant Download Manager Pro 2.16.3 Build 92038</title><pubDate> Wed, 26 Nov 2025 16:02:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ant-download-manager-pro-137.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ant-download-manager-pro-137.html
</guid><description>
Ant Download Manager Pro is software support download has the same features as IDM, even it has many prominent features, more user friendly more and have speed download data incredible. Ant Download Manager is a Internet content downloader quickly with support download at video! Function: fully Integrated with the web browsers most popular: Internet Explorer 8+, Mozilla Firefox 32 +, Google Chrome 31+ and the copies of them (Pale Moon, Opera, Vivaldi, Slimjet, ComodoDragon, etc.). you...
</description></item><item><title>Download IDM Retail 6.42 Build 56</title><pubDate> Wed, 26 Nov 2025 16:02:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-internet-download-manager-retail-3609.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-internet-download-manager-retail-3609.html
</guid><description>
IDM - Internet Download Manager Retail is a reliable utility and high efficiency will help you to increase your download speed and manage download at better. The program allows you to easily schedule, pause and resume downloads with a single click. Moreover, the application provides error resilience robust and can restart the download at the interrupted or broken. You can restore the download is interrupted due to network problems, lost connections, unexpected power outages, computer...
</description></item></channel></rss>