<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 20:01:34 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 20:01:34 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Zero Cleaner: clear cache 4.1.6</title><pubDate> Wed, 15 Oct 2025 22:11:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-zero-cleaner-clear-cache-10667.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-zero-cleaner-clear-cache-10667.html
</guid><description>
Zero Cleaner is a mobile application that specializes in removing cache files from your device. Cache files are temporary data stored by applications and websites to improve their performance and load times. Over time, cache files can accumulate and take up valuable storage space on your device.
Some key features of Zero Cleaner include:
	Cache Cleaner: The app will scan your device for cache files created by apps and web browsers, allowing you to clear them with just a tap. This...
</description></item><item><title>Download Another Note Widget 3.8.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 15 Oct 2025 22:11:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-another-note-widget-11282.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-another-note-widget-11282.html
</guid><description>
Another Note Widget is a simple note-taking widget for your Home screen, perfect for short daily notes.
Main features:
	Choose from a variety of designs: Personalize your notes with 6 different designs: Sticky, Plain, Notebook, Chalkboard, and more
	40+ themes: Different pins and 40+ themes (Christmas, Halloween, Valentine's Day, holidays, food, animals, sports, etc.) to decorate your notes.
	Text and Drawings: Your notes can contain simple text enriched with emojis or hand-drawn...
</description></item><item><title>Download Phone Dialer &amp;amp;amp; Contacts: drupe 3.19.17.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 15 Oct 2025 22:11:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-phone-dialer-contacts-drupe-11477.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-phone-dialer-contacts-drupe-11477.html
</guid><description>
Want to see caller ID, spam indicator and block spammers, directly from your call screen? drupe is your application. Trusted by over 20 million users worldwide. drupe replaces your boring call screen with a fresh interface, built and configured precisely for you! Forget about traditional Phone Book applications!
Main features:
	Smart Dialer - Dialing across multiple apps is quick and easy
	Smart caller ID tracker and blocker to find unknown numbers - drupe ID identifier will help you...
</description></item><item><title>Download AnExplorer Pro File Transfer 5.8.9</title><pubDate> Wed, 15 Oct 2025 22:10:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-file-manager-pro-tv-usb-otg-8358.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-file-manager-pro-tv-usb-otg-8358.html
</guid><description>
AnExplorer File Explorer is a unique file manager for TV and Watch file management tool. It is simple, small, fast and efficient File Explorer. Only file managers support RTL and display the size of folders on storage. It is designed for all devices including Phones, Phablets, Tablets, Watches and TVs. It is completely designed using Material Design.
Pro TV USBOTG File Manager Features
	Full-featured It provides all file management features including cut, copy, delete, rename,...
</description></item><item><title>Download AdGuard Ad Blocker 4.12.77 Final</title><pubDate> Wed, 15 Oct 2025 22:10:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-adguard-block-ads-without-root-8215.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-adguard-block-ads-without-root-8215.html
</guid><description>
AdGuard for Android is the only root-free ad blocker for Android that removes ads in apps and browsers, protects your privacy, and helps you manage your apps. Adguard is designed to block unwanted ads, pop-ups and banners while you browse the web on your device. It uses a combination of local VPN technology and a custom DNS server to block ads, meaning it can block ads in apps as well as in web browsers.
In addition, Adguard also blocks tracking scripts from collecting information about...
</description></item><item><title>Download AppKiller: close apps 4.1.5</title><pubDate> Wed, 15 Oct 2025 22:10:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-appkiller-close-apps-11977.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-appkiller-close-apps-11977.html
</guid><description>
AppKiller: close apps allows users to quickly and effectively kill background applications that are consuming system resources, such as RAM and CPU, which can help improve overall speed and performance. device responsiveness. By freeing up system resources, users can also see increased battery life because their devices are no longer consuming power on unnecessary background processes. This can be especially beneficial for users who use their devices throughout the day and need to...
</description></item><item><title>Download NetGuard - no-root firewall 2.334</title><pubDate> Wed, 15 Oct 2025 22:09:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-netguard-no-root-firewall-9603.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-netguard-no-root-firewall-9603.html
</guid><description>
NetGuard provides simple and advanced ways to block Internet access - no root required. Individual apps and sites can allow or deny access to your Wi-Fi and/or cellular connection.
Features of NetGuard for Android
	Simple to use
	No root required
	100% open source
	Don't call home
	No tracking or analytics
	No ads
	Actively developed and supported
	Supports Android 5.1 and above
	Supports IPv4/IPv6 TCP/UDP
	Supports connection sharing
	Option to enable when screen is on
	Roaming...
</description></item><item><title>Download Web Video Cast | Browser to TV 5.12.7 build 5606</title><pubDate> Wed, 15 Oct 2025 22:09:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-web-video-cast-browser-to-tv-8372.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-web-video-cast-browser-to-tv-8372.html
</guid><description>
Web Video Cast allows you to watch TV videos from your favorite websites including movies, TV shows, live news, sports and IPTV. It also allows you to stream local videos stored on your phone. Image and audio files are also supported. Subtitles are detected on the website, you can also use your own subtitles or you can use the built-in search feature of OpenSubtitles.org.
Web Video Caster supports the most popular streaming devices, allowing your TV to stream video directly from the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Rotation | Orientation Manager 29.0.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 15 Oct 2025 22:09:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-rotation-orientation-manager-8332.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-rotation-orientation-manager-8332.html
</guid><description>
Rotate | Orientation Manager is a mobile application for Android devices that allows users to control screen rotation settings on their devices. This app allows users to set custom rotation settings for different apps, and also provides a quick toggle to enable or disable rotation globally.
Rotation feature | Orientation Manager
	Control screen rotation on a per-app basis
	Option to set custom rotation settings for different applications
	Quick toggle switch to enable or disable...
</description></item><item><title>Download AdGuard for Android TV 4.12.77</title><pubDate> Wed, 15 Oct 2025 22:09:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-adguard-for-android-tv-12118.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-adguard-for-android-tv-12118.html
</guid><description>
To provide full compatibility with Android TV, we've created a streamlined version of AdGuard for Android. This version incorporates key features designed to enhance your TV browsing experience. AdGuard for Android TV is the only app that blocks ads, protects your privacy and acts as a firewall for your Smart TV. Relax and watch your favorite shows with top security and no ads!
Main features:
Block ads on TV
	AdGuard blocks banners, pop-ups, and ads on the home screen. Watch your...
</description></item><item><title>Download WiFi Direct + 10.0.17</title><pubDate> Wed, 15 Oct 2025 22:08:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wifi-direct-10153.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wifi-direct-10153.html
</guid><description>
Wi-Fi Direct is a Wi-Fi standard for peer-to-peer wireless connections that allows two devices to establish a direct Wi-Fi connection without the need for an intermediate wireless access point, router, or Internet connection.
Features of WiFi Direct +
	Fast
	Completely free, no intrusive ads.
	Supports all file transfers.
	Supports multiple file transfers.
	Supports folder transfer.
	Supports file transfer to and from external sdcard.
	Tested on many devices.
	Advanced file chooser.
</description></item><item><title>Download Fing - Network Tools 12.11.1 build 121101002</title><pubDate> Wed, 15 Oct 2025 22:08:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-fing-network-tools-8540.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-fing-network-tools-8540.html
</guid><description>
Fing is a popular network scanning application that allows users to discover devices connected to the local network, view their IP and MAC addresses, and perform various network tests. Fing is the #1 Network Scanner: detects all devices connected to your WiFi and identifies them with our patented technology that is also used by router manufacturers and companies antivirus used worldwide.
Features of Fing for Android
	Network Scan: Quickly find all devices connected to your Wi-Fi...
</description></item><item><title>Download Business Calendar 2 Pro 2.53.4 build 253401</title><pubDate> Wed, 15 Oct 2025 22:08:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-business-calendar-8433.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-business-calendar-8433.html
</guid><description>
Business Calendar 2 Pro is the premium version of our popular calendar app. It provides a great overview of your appointments, is easy to use, and gives you powerful tools to plan and schedule your events and tasks.
Features of Business Calendar
Your personal organizer
	calendar, planner and tasks in one app
	6 clearly designed main views: month, week, day, agenda, year and tasks
	popup with live event details in month view
	flexible daily and weekly planning that can be adjusted...
</description></item><item><title>Download Subtitle Downloader Pro 16.0.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 15 Oct 2025 22:07:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-subtitle-downloader-pro-9643.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-subtitle-downloader-pro-9643.html
</guid><description>
Download subtitles for your TV shows and movies from the most popular subtitle providers to your PC or tablet/phone. This powerful app allows you to download your video's subtitles directly to your device's SD card or even a network share/drive (supports Samba/SMB and SFTP/SSH). This capability extends to multiple files, giving users the freedom to select and download up to ten files at a time. A notable feature of Subtitle Downloader Pro is that it provides quality/release matching....
</description></item><item><title>Download My Budget Book 9.10</title><pubDate> Wed, 15 Oct 2025 22:07:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-my-budget-book-8935.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-my-budget-book-8935.html
</guid><description>
My budget book helps you manage your money more effectively by recording your income and expenses easily. Using individual or recurring transaction features, you can track and forecast your balance. You can also visualize your records with dynamic charts and graphs.
Budget mode allows you to set limits or goals for custom time periods. Buying too many clothes? Set a monthly limit. Spending too much on take away coffee? Set weekly limits. Saving for a dream vacation? Set a savings goal...
</description></item><item><title>Download Background Eraser 35.0.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 15 Oct 2025 22:07:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-background-eraser-11158.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-background-eraser-11158.html
</guid><description>
This is an application for cutting photos and making the background of photos transparent. The resulting photos can be used as stickers with other applications to create collages, collages.
Features of Background Eraser
	"Magic" mode: Detects photo edges for easy erasing &amp;amp; precisely.
	"Auto" or "Color" mode: Automatically remove similar pixels.
It is very important to make the background of the photo transparent correctly
if you want to overlap photos and create beautiful...
</description></item><item><title>Download Math Tricks Workout 2.7.3.3</title><pubDate> Wed, 15 Oct 2025 22:06:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-math-tricks-workout-8232.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-math-tricks-workout-8232.html
</guid><description>
Math Tricks Exercises can be an Android app designed to help users improve their math skills and speed through the use of various tricks and techniques. Math Tricks Exercises is one of the best math tricks app that brings you the most interesting exercises and practice to test and improve your math skills. Inspired by Vedic Maths, This is the most fun and free math learning app ever!
Features of Math Tricks Workout
	Various math problems, including addition, subtraction,...
</description></item><item><title>Download ImageMagick 7.1.2-7</title><pubDate> Wed, 15 Oct 2025 16:18:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-imagemagick-1319.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-imagemagick-1319.html
</guid><description>
ImageMagick is software image processing command line to create, edit, compose, or convert bitmap images. ImageMagick is completely free for users and you easily download it on taiwebs.com. Typical functions most of software is able to read and write images in many formats (over 100) including DPX, EXR, GIF, JPEG, JPEG-2000, PDF, PhotoCD, PNG, Postcript, SVG, and TIFF.
ImageMagick - image Processing
The Windows version of ImageMagick is installed. Just click on the appropriate version...
</description></item><item><title>Download HWiNFO 8.32 Build 5840</title><pubDate> Wed, 15 Oct 2025 16:14:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hwinfo-1828.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hwinfo-1828.html
</guid><description>
HWiNFO (HWiNFO32) is a diagnostic tool and hardware information, recognizes and displays detailed information about all the hardware components of you. HWiNFO will hold the component in the tree view and provide the report easy to read for each category.
HWiNFO - Hardware Diagnostics
HWiNFO is especially useful so you don't have to install it on each computer and completely for free. Just run the direct program and you will have full information of the computer that you need. The...
</description></item><item><title>Download Bulk Image Downloader 6.60</title><pubDate> Wed, 15 Oct 2025 16:14:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bulk-image-downloader-121.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bulk-image-downloader-121.html
</guid><description>
Bulk Image Downloader is an application specially developed to help you download the images in full size from the Bulk Image Downloader most of the web gallery or web forum.
Bulk Image Downloader what?
Support image storage - BID works with almost every archive page popular images, such as flickr, imagevenue, imagefap, imagebam, etc.
Social networking sites - BID supports downloading from sites such as facebook, myspace, and twitter as tweetphoto.com, twitpic.com, yfrog.com
Images are...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mozilla Thunderbird 144.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 15 Oct 2025 16:14:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thunderbird-1788.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thunderbird-1788.html
</guid><description>
Thunderbird is an email program full featured with controls spam integration, mail filter, address book, news groups and more. It provides a clean interface and easy to use (customizable). Thunderbird also provides the security features such as S / MIME, digital signing, message encryption, support for certificates and security devices.
Before using this feature, you should review the settings IMAP, SMTP, and SSL/TLS his. Now, what all you need to do is provide your name, email address,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft Office Pro Plus - Online Installer 3.3.7</title><pubDate> Wed, 15 Oct 2025 16:12:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-office-professional-plus-x86-x64-online-installer-7661.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-office-professional-plus-x86-x64-online-installer-7661.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft Office 2021 Professional Plus x86-x64 - Online Installer is a small script that helps users to download and install Microsoft Office 2021 Professional Plus including all updates directly from Microsoft CDN Server.
The version of Office 2021 downloaded and installed on your computer will include the following programs: Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Outlook, OneNote, Publisher, Access, Visio, Project, ProofingTools, OneDrive Desktop.
Usage:
Unzip the downloaded ZIP Archive...
</description></item><item><title>Download Claris FileMaker Pro 22.0.3.300</title><pubDate> Wed, 15 Oct 2025 16:11:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-filemaker-pro-advanced-487.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-filemaker-pro-advanced-487.html
</guid><description>
FileMaker Pro Advanced is software via internet easy manager database, contacts, projects and inventory data, and generate reports. FileMaker Pro will help users to build database customize and design them to fit with the activities and profile of their business. More than a million people around the world use platform FileMaker every day to complete the work faster and more efficient in work.
Features on FileMaker Pro Advanced
Anywhere access
	Use one unified platform to create the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Free YouTube Download 4.4.41.1014 Premium</title><pubDate> Wed, 15 Oct 2025 16:10:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-download-1177.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-download-1177.html
</guid><description>
Free YouTube Download Premium is the most popular application to download videos from YouTube. The program was released in 2006 and regularly updated since then. Use the program to download and convert YouTube videos to view offline anytime.
Free YouTube Download - added Support to download youtube
Download more videos! Save whole playlists and YouTube channels, videos from a playlist individually (history, video be favorite, favourites, Watch later), videos from many different...
</description></item><item><title>Download Google Chrome 141.0.7390.108</title><pubDate> Wed, 15 Oct 2025 16:10:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-chrome-1012.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-chrome-1012.html
</guid><description>
Google Chrome web browser is the most used today. Support surf the web, listen to music, watch movies, play web game effective no jerky lag with the internet connection stable. When you are surfing the web or performing an important task, whether it is operation big or small, work or entertainment, then Chrome has the smart features and the speed you need to make, create and explore on the net.
The latest version of Google Chrome is the third 114. But we are providing for users Google...
</description></item></channel></rss>