<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 03:38:02 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 03:38:02 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download MPV-EASY Player 0.41.0.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Dec 2025 00:19:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mpv-easy-player-3110.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mpv-easy-player-3110.html
</guid><description>
MPV-EASY Player is movies player based on mpv. It comes with easy to use interface, you can quickly adjust many parameters, the default settings are carefully adjusted will be able to stimulate all the performance of the mpv, so use mpv player simple than before a lot.
Basically, MPV-EASY Player is the assembly and combination of MPV, configuring mpv files, the command lua (including all scripts to be shared by other people on github), and the command js with the to read and fully...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinShift Forge 0.5.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Dec 2025 00:18:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winshift-forge-14401.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winshift-forge-14401.html
</guid><description>
What is WinShift Forge?
WinShift Forge is a lightweight utility built to enhance the performance of Windows 11. WinShift Forge allows you to easily remove them, free up space, and speed up your system. WinShift Forge lets you instantly refresh your computer screen by customizing the most important icons. No more fumbling through complex system settings—easily take direct control of the core Windows visuals and make your PC truly your own.
Key Features:
Personalize Your PC
	Replace...
</description></item><item><title>Download Glary Utilities Pro 6.36.0.40</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 20:29:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-utilities-pro-76.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-utilities-pro-76.html
</guid><description>
Glary Utilities Pro is a collection of tools and system utilities to fix, speed up, maintain and protect your computer. Glary Utilities Pro allows you to clean junk files, system downloads, as well as the subscriptions are not valid and Internet traces (that support the plug-in more for the 45+ program outside). You can also manage and delete add-ons of the browser, analyze the use of disk and find the file duplicate.
Glary Utilities Pro - optimized system
Key features Glary Utilities...
</description></item><item><title>Download AITextTune 1.6.0.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 20:28:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aitexttune-12973.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aitexttune-12973.html
</guid><description>
AITextTune is an AI-powered tool designed to enhance and refine text content. It offers features such as improving clarity and coherence, generating summaries, and translating text into multiple languages. Users can easily adjust their writing style from formal to creative. This tool is very flexible and can be used on many different software and platforms.
AITextTune Features
	WRITE PERFECTLY: Improve the clarity and coherence of your writing! Create summaries and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wise Disk Cleaner 11.3.1.851</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 20:27:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wise-disk-cleaner-392.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wise-disk-cleaner-392.html
</guid><description>
Wise Disk Cleaner software to clean hard drive by finding and deleting junk files downloads accumulate over time. Wise Disk Cleaner is pre-configured with about 50 types of extension files can usually be considered disposable, and you can extend the range by adding the file types of their own.
Wise Disk Cleaner to use the advanced algorithm with the ability to quick scan and comprehensive scan of hard drive space. Users can delete browsing history as well as the personal data important...
</description></item><item><title>Download reaConverter Pro 8.0.174</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 20:27:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html
</guid><description>
reaConverter Pro is software image processing feature with batch conversion and image editing periodically becomes simple. eaConverter also provide command line utilities allow you to process images automatically, thus helping you shorten the time for other work.
reaConverter Pro integrated powerful tool of Uber with many great features. It provides advanced solutions to process and adjust images. Management of the conversion process the base image with the latest version of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tenorshare 4DDiG File Repair 4.3.6.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 20:26:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tenorshare-4ddig-file-repair-5630.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tenorshare-4ddig-file-repair-5630.html
</guid><description>
Tenorshare 4DDiG File Repair is AI-powered software to repair damaged or damaged videos, photos, files and audios, improve their quality and add color to black media white. 4DDiG photo editing solves all photo problems like blurry photos, overexposed photos, etc. Powered by AI, it can dramatically improve image resolution and colorize black and white photos in seconds, not hours.
Features of Tenorshare 4DDiG File Repair
	Easily repair any blurry, overexposed and damaged videos, photos...
</description></item><item><title>Download Vector 35 Binary Ninja 5.2.8722 Personal</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 20:26:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vector-35-binary-ninja-8951.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vector-35-binary-ninja-8951.html
</guid><description>
Vector 35 Binary Ninja is a reverse engineering platform designed to help security researchers, developers and binary code analysts. It is a software tool that allows users to disassemble, decompile, and debug binaries, making it easier to understand how the program works and to identify potential vulnerabilities.
This tool provides a user-friendly interface that makes it easy to navigate and analyze binary files. It includes a wide range of features for code separation, including...
</description></item><item><title>Download UPDF 2.1.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 20:25:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-updf-14160.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-updf-14160.html
</guid><description>
UPDF for Windows is easy-to-use PDF software for Windows! Enjoy powerful editing tools for text, images, links, and more in your PDFs. Customize backgrounds, watermarks, and page sizes as easily as in Word. AI-powered PDF editor and manager that offers a wide range of features including editing, annotating, converting, OCR (Optical Character Recognition), organizing, protecting, sharing, printing, summarizing, translating, and interpreting PDF files.
Features of UPDF
Analyze PDFs with...
</description></item><item><title>Download Glarysoft Malware Hunter Pro 1.210.0.841</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 20:25:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glarysoft-malware-hunter-pro-235.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glarysoft-malware-hunter-pro-235.html
</guid><description>
Glarysoft Malware Hunter capabilities, comprehensive protection against threats, data protection and privacy, ensure the computer is no longer virus. It allows you against many types of viruses, trojans with the ability to super fast scanning to detect and remove the malware quickly. Glarysoft Malware Hunter has a simple design of the interface, but the pace of new work is the most important problem of this software.
Features Glarysoft Malware Hunter Pro
	Automatically search, detect,...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube Downloader 3.9.18 (2612)</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 20:25:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube Downloader  is a dedicated software that helps users  downloading youtube videos  Favorites on PC for offline viewing. With MediaHuman YouTube  Downloader  you can download videos from youtube website to your computer with  fast speed , with special software development technology that automatically receives videos from Websites, in addition to the ability to download videos from software websites, can convert downloaded video formats to various formats for the purpose...
</description></item><item><title>Download Glary Malware Hunter PRO 1.210.0.841</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 20:24:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-malware-hunter-pro-77.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-malware-hunter-pro-77.html
</guid><description>
Glary Malware Hunter PRO - detection of file malware on your computer and delete dangerous content, allowing you to run on-demand scan of the area, important system or specific files. As suggested by its name, Malware Hunter is designed to find and remove the files and components potential danger on your computer, keep it out of the virus and the type of threat other.
Glary Malware Hunter PRO - perfect protection of your equipment
Features Glary Malware Hunter PRO
- Scan ultrasound...
</description></item><item><title>Download Glary Quick Startup 6.0.1.18</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 20:24:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-startup-manager-1340.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-startup-manager-1340.html
</guid><description>
Quick StartUp is software that helps you track and control programs and automated services that run when the computer system starts. StartUp Manager brings a simple solution to removing programs that do not need to run with your system and your system resources.
Startup Delayer is also software that allows you to monitor and control startup processes with windows, from which optimizing and reducing the launch time of the PC. When you use this software, users easily shut down the...
</description></item><item><title>Download ToDoList 9.1.7.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 20:23:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-todolist-1637.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-todolist-1637.html
</guid><description>
ToDoList is an application note and task management with multiple options, set up help you to easily split and track the progress of the work. Todolist helps millions of people feel in control of their lives more and be the leader in a number of organizations inspired the world to believe. Todolist keep all to-dos of I in one place and perfectly integrated with the other tools that I use. It helps me turn everything faster.
ToDoList - management software job
Every day you have to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Glary Tracks Eraser 6.0.1.32</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 18:08:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-tracks-eraser-1342.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-tracks-eraser-1342.html
</guid><description>
Glary Tracks Eraser is security software privacy when browsing the web, allows you to delete all traces of network access and trace number, including browser cache, cookies, the website is already open, the URL has been entered, the document new mines, temporary files,... Glary Tracks Eraser that helps you free up space in hard disk drives, scan entire junk files in the drive with the speed of processing is extremely fast. Data deleted by Glary Tracks Eraser will not be able to restore,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Glary Disk Cleaner 6.0.1.39</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 18:08:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-disk-cleaner-1341.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-disk-cleaner-1341.html
</guid><description>
Glary Disk Cleaner is the software helps to erase the file system temporarily, cleanup your browser cache, or release the folder. Glary Disk Cleaner show scan results in detail, help you pick exactly each file to delete. The list file is much more wide open, with temporary files, user-generated, or the file system, cache, bug report, log files, data in recycle bin, the shortcut expires.
Glary Disk Cleaner - garbage system
Glary Disk Cleaner is designed to be simple as possible in use....
</description></item><item><title>Download VueScan Pro 9.8.50</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 18:03:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vuescan-pro-75.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vuescan-pro-75.html
</guid><description>
VueScan Pro l  is one of the software  Scan quality pictures  First and appeared quite soon,  VueScan Pro  always asserted its No. 1 position on the technology pages, awards as well as user reviews. Through many versions, VueScan Pro 9 is greatly improved in terms of interface and features. Supporting most popular image formats today, this software will help you scan images quickly, easy to use and high quality output. With the color balance mode, you won't have to worry about blurring the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Nero Burning ROM 27.0.1.4</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 18:02:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nero-burning-rom-2019-155.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nero-burning-rom-2019-155.html
</guid><description>
Nero Burning ROM 2021  efficient data backup and CD burning software burns them to your favorite disc type. Want to keep your data safe and secure? Want to create discs with maximum reliability? No problem with the latest version of Nero Burning ROM, which uses SecurDisc 4.0 and more to ensure the best results.
With Nero, the disc is written fairly quickly and error-free, with many tools integrated into one simple interface. Nero also features mp3 file mixing, video editing, slideshow...
</description></item><item><title>Download IObit Malware Fighter Pro 13.1.0.1617</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 18:02:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iobit-malware-fighter-pro-257.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iobit-malware-fighter-pro-257.html
</guid><description>
IObit Malware Fighter Pro is security software, remove malicious program with many advanced features that help protect safety for your system. IObit Malware Fighter Pro integration inside is the power of technology Dual-Core help quick scan and deep scan the entire system to detect and eliminate concerns about the virus.
IObit Malware Fighter Pro a lot of attention by the ability to detect and remove programs spyware from the system with fast speed and the most accurate. More special is...
</description></item><item><title>Download Yamicsoft Windows 11/10 Manager 2.3</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 17:55:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yamicsoft-windows-11-manager-6779.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yamicsoft-windows-11-manager-6779.html
</guid><description>
Windows 11 Manager is an all-in-one utility for Microsoft Windows 11 specially, it includes over forty different utilities to optimize, tweak, clean up, speed up and repair your Windows 11, helps make your system perform faster, eliminate system fault, increase stability and security, personalize your copy of Windows 11, and meet all of your expectations.
Features of Windows 11 Manager:
Information:
	Creates the system restore point manually;
	Gets detailed information about your...
</description></item><item><title>Download RedNotebook 2.42</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 17:54:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rednotebook-2884.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rednotebook-2884.html
</guid><description>
RedNotebook is a note-taking app for free. It allows you to format, tag and search your entries. You can also add images, links and templates can customize, check the spelling of your notes and export into plain text, HTML or LaTeX. RedNotebook is free software under the GPL.
RedNotebook - Write notes, edit text
Features of RedNotebook
	Use #hashtags
	Format your text bold , italic or underline
	Insert images, files and links to the website
	Links and email addresses are recognized...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tenorshare 4DDiG Email Repair 1.0.1.4</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 17:49:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tenorshare-4ddig-email-repair-11818.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tenorshare-4ddig-email-repair-11818.html
</guid><description>
Tenorshare 4DDiG Email Repair is a powerful software application designed to help Windows users repair damaged or unusable email files. Whether your Outlook, Windows Mail or other email client files are inaccessible or display error messages, this program will provide an effective solution to recover your emails and attachments.
Tenorshare 4DDiG Email Repair is a reliable and effective tool to repair damaged email files on Windows. Whether you're dealing with file corruption, error...
</description></item><item><title>Download O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro 22.1.229 / Server</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 17:40:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-diskimage-pro-218.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-diskimage-pro-218.html
</guid><description>
O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro is software backup data comprehensive and effective is provided to protect the data of the computer system, it creates images for individual drives or the entire system that still does not affect your system.
O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro allows the user to backup the entire computer or drive, the and files whenever you want even while the computer is being used. Or can use O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro to create a copy chinh sac of computer disk drives, can be used instead of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download O&amp;amp;O BlueCon Tech Edition 23.0.14008</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 17:39:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-bluecon-tech-edition-4038.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-bluecon-tech-edition-4038.html
</guid><description>
O&amp;amp;O BlueCon Tech Edition provides a set of powerful tools for users, administrators and service technicians so that the system is broken can be operated back without install ago. The user interface is based on Windows help the use of O&amp;amp;O BlueCon Tech Edition easy to the level required less time for training. It is in the side of administrators in the process of daily as well as whenever disaster happens.
O&amp;amp;O BlueCon Tech Edition - to fix Windows system
BlueCon boot all the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Boris FX CrumplePop Pro 2025.5.3</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 17:38:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-boris-fx-crumplepop-complete-9687.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-boris-fx-crumplepop-complete-9687.html
</guid><description>
Boris FX CrumplePop Complete is a complete set of audio plugin tools to make your sound the best with advanced AI technology. Never before has dealing with common audio problems like background noise, echoes, traffic, wind, and more. as well as enhancing the sound quality to achieve professional results has never been easier. The CrumplePop audio tools are easy to use if you're a beginner, and powerful enough to meet the daily needs of audio professionals.
Features of Boris FX...
</description></item></channel></rss>