<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 09:04:58 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 09:04:58 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download CyberLink YouCam 10.1.4728.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 22 Nov 2025 02:42:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-youcam-deluxe-978.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-youcam-deluxe-978.html
</guid><description>
CyberLink YouCam Deluxe is software video, chat online and chat with friends along with a multitude of effects, unique video editing. YouCam fully integrated into the video chat application like Skype, as well as the service broadcast live on Facebook and YouTube.
CyberLink YouCam Deluxe - Dial and edit video directly
CyberLink YouCam Deluxe provides the functionality to edit videos directly on the network with over 200 fun effects for video chats and recording. In addition, the...
</description></item><item><title>Download AITextTune 1.4.2.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 22 Nov 2025 02:42:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aitexttune-12973.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aitexttune-12973.html
</guid><description>
AITextTune is an AI-powered tool designed to enhance and refine text content. It offers features such as improving clarity and coherence, generating summaries, and translating text into multiple languages. Users can easily adjust their writing style from formal to creative. This tool is very flexible and can be used on many different software and platforms.
AITextTune Features
	WRITE PERFECTLY: Improve the clarity and coherence of your writing! Create summaries and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Monkeys Audio 11.87</title><pubDate> Sat, 22 Nov 2025 02:41:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-monkeys-audio-949.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-monkeys-audio-949.html
</guid><description>
Monkey\'s Audio is software that compresses digital music without loss of quality. Supports high quality WAV files and CD ripping. Monkeys Audio will compress .wav tracks into .ape files to reduce their size without loss of sound quality, decompress .ape, convert files, check file integrity and manage tags.
Unlike traditional methods like MP3 and OGG, which permanently remove quality to save space, Monkey\'s Audio only creates perfect copies with the same sound quality as the originals....
</description></item><item><title>Download CyberLink PerfectCam Premium 2.3.7821.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 22 Nov 2025 02:41:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-perfectcam-premium-375.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-perfectcam-premium-375.html
</guid><description>
CyberLink PerfectCam Premium is software that supports the work of makeup face on, webcam, from the makeup artist professional.  PerfectCam will help you looks perfect on her webcam enjoy brightness, contrast and exposure, video ideal for online meetings and even applied to smooth the skin.
PerfectCam use technology face recognition is patented, the library installed virtual makeover instant of PerfectCam brings you looks professional and prepared whenever you need.
Features CyberLink...
</description></item><item><title>Download BitTorrent PRO 7.11.0.47229</title><pubDate> Sat, 22 Nov 2025 02:40:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bittorrent-pro-190.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bittorrent-pro-190.html
</guid><description>
BitTorrent PRO supports users to share files via p2p peer-to-peer network protocol, and allows you to download torrent data quickly and safely, without requiring What other software must you use? Using this tool, users can download many different types of data, manage bandwidth effectively, and can download many files at the same time, even large files.
In addition, the feature of this network is a very high jump speed, which can be achieved by the initial method of releasing files from...
</description></item><item><title>Download VideoPad Video Editor Pro 17.54 Beta</title><pubDate> Sat, 22 Nov 2025 02:40:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-videopad-video-editor-pro-268.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-videopad-video-editor-pro-268.html
</guid><description>
VideoPad Video Editor Pro is software edit video from any camcorder, DV camcorder, VHS player or webcam for best quality. The interface of this utility is divided into several parts (for example: list of multi-media, Effects, transitions, Files, Clips, video track, audio track, overlay), which makes everything seem difficult to operate. You can capture videos from camcorder or other devices like webcam or capture card TV and after you have added files and sequence clips to the queue, you...
</description></item><item><title>Download uTorrent Pro 3.6.0 Build 47224</title><pubDate> Sat, 22 Nov 2025 02:39:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-utorrent-pro-79.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-utorrent-pro-79.html
</guid><description>
uTorrent - Download the torrent file
uTorrent Pro is an application BitTorrent efficient for Windows. Most of the features in the BitTorrent client and others have in uTorrent, including priority bandwidth, scheduling, automatic download at RSS and Mainline DHT. Additionally, uTorrent supports specification joint protocol encryption and peer exchange of goods. Unlike many torrent clients, it does not hog system resources have value - typically using less than 6MB of memory, allowing you...
</description></item><item><title>Download LibreWolf 145.0.1-2</title><pubDate> Sat, 22 Nov 2025 02:38:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-librewolf-11967.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-librewolf-11967.html
</guid><description>
LibreWolf is a customized and independent version of Firefox, with the main goals being user privacy, security and freedom. LibreWolf is designed to provide increased protection against tracking and fingerprinting techniques and includes a number of security enhancements. This is achieved through our security and privacy oriented settings and patches. LibreWolf also aims to remove all telemetry, data collection and annoyances, as well as disable anti-free features like DRM.
LibreWolf...
</description></item><item><title>Download DipTrace 5.2.0.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 22 Nov 2025 02:38:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-diptrace-4611.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-diptrace-4611.html
</guid><description>
DipTrace is EDA software / CAD to create schematics and printed circuit boards. The developer provides the interface and multi-language instructions (available in English and 22 other languages). DipTrace has 4 modules: The edit capture schematic editor layout PCB with features automatically based on shape and integrated preview &amp;amp; casting, 3D editing, composition and The edit template. DipTrace is a powerful software and intuitive aimed at the expert want to create the layout PCB,...
</description></item><item><title>Download KILHO AutoClick 1.4.6</title><pubDate> Sat, 22 Nov 2025 02:37:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kilho-autoclick-12515.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kilho-autoclick-12515.html
</guid><description>
AutoClick is a software or script designed to automate mouse clicking tasks, especially useful for repetitive actions in a variety of applications, including gaming and data entry. It allows users to define specific click points and automatically click at those locations. This tool is user-friendly and supports recording click sequences for repeated use.
AutoClick allows users to set precise time intervals and geographic coordinates for various click patterns. Additionally, AutoClick...
</description></item><item><title>Download ExpanDrive 2025.11.12</title><pubDate> Sat, 22 Nov 2025 02:36:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-expandrive-609.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-expandrive-609.html
</guid><description>
ExpanDrive is software sync cloud storage strong support BackBlaze B2, Google Team Drive, SMB / CIFS and new interface and easy user search file version, share links and much more.  ExpanDrive mapped network drives for macOS and Micosoft Windows connect with all the provide major cloud storage such as Dropbox, Google Drive, Google Team Drive, Amazon Drive, Box, OneDrive, OneDrive for Business, Sharepoint, Openstack Swift , BackBlaze B2, Amazon S3 or SFTP servers, FTP or WebDAV on your own...
</description></item><item><title>Download Rainlendar Pro 2.23.0 Build 183</title><pubDate> Sat, 22 Nov 2025 02:36:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rainlendar-pro-3123.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rainlendar-pro-3123.html
</guid><description>
Rainlendar is a calendar that is personal and powerful and will help you to easily manage and view all your tasks and important events of you. The program allows you to keep the mission and events of yourself in the separate list, allowing you to keep your own life organized better. This app will also inform you about the mission and upcoming events.
Rainlendar will store your information in the format iCalWiki compatible with the majority of the calendar widget. This means you can easily...
</description></item><item><title>Download MP3Studio YouTube Downloader 2.0.29.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 22 Nov 2025 02:35:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mp3studio-youtube-downloader-6778.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mp3studio-youtube-downloader-6778.html
</guid><description>
MP3Studio YouTube Downloader is an efficient and user-friendly software developed to provide you with an easy means of getting all your favorite videos from the web and store them on your PC, in one of the available formats. With MP3Studio YouTube Downloader, you can download up to 99 songs at once in the background as you start your business.
Use this media editor to preload various songs via YouTube and other services. It will provide you with good quality music that you can listen to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Geometric Glovius Prime 6.7.0.95</title><pubDate> Sat, 22 Nov 2025 02:35:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-geometric-glovius-pro-754.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-geometric-glovius-pro-754.html
</guid><description>
Geometric Glovius Pro is viewer CAD 3D modern for files CATIA, NX, STEP, IGES, Pro/ENGINEER and Creo, SolidWorks, Inventor and Solid Edge. The work of Geometric Glovius Pro is made exact measurements, cut dynamic sections, compare differences between models and export to 3D PDF, STL and Glovius Mobile.
Geometric Glovius Pro - manager, and view CAD 3D
The features of Geometric Glovius Pro
	Modern interface, simple, easy to use
	Mobile app for free for iOS &amp;amp; Android powerful...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaMonkey Gold 2024.2.0.3178 RC3</title><pubDate> Sat, 22 Nov 2025 02:34:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediamonkey-gold-231.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediamonkey-gold-231.html
</guid><description>
MediaMonkey Gold is music manager and music player multimedia for the music collection and iPod users. MediaMonkey lists the audio file of you as CD, OGG, WMA, MPC, FLAC, APE, WAV and MP3 and includes the edit smart card and an automatic file and folder to arrange your music library.
MediaMonkey Gold also has CD ripper, CD / DVD Burner, and audio converter for saving music, and manual or editor list automatically to create mixed music.
Features MediaMonkey Gold
	Automatically find...
</description></item><item><title>Download Spybot Anti-Beacon 5.4</title><pubDate> Sat, 22 Nov 2025 02:34:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-spybot-anti-beacon-2274.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-spybot-anti-beacon-2274.html
</guid><description>
Spybot Anti-Beacon is a small utility to prevent and stop the method of tracking different (e.g., remote) in Windows 10. Developer writes that he just saw a series of such programs, but they are all unfinished or unfinished workers, plus have the program install the type of ads and other junk into the system.
Spybot Anti-Beacon - Block and stop the service in windows 10
Features disabled:
	This tool will disable as follows:
	Remote server
	Remote service
	The program improves the...
</description></item><item><title>Download SysTools SQL Server Recovery Manager 7.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 22 Nov 2025 02:33:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-systools-sql-server-recovery-manager-12420.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-systools-sql-server-recovery-manager-12420.html
</guid><description>
The software gives you the option to recover corrupted database files. You can open and restore both SQL Primary Database (MDF) files as well as Secondary Database (NDF) files. Additionally, the tool can restore deleted Tables, Stored Procedures, Functions, Triggers, etc.
Features
	Restore &amp;amp; Export SQL Database: Primary File (MDF), Secondary File (NDF) and Backup (BAK)
	Analyze SQL Server LOG database transactions
	Export MDF, LDF and BAK Files to SQL Server Located on the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cash Register Pro 4.0.4</title><pubDate> Sat, 22 Nov 2025 02:33:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cash-register-pro-3853.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cash-register-pro-3853.html
</guid><description>
Cash Register Pro a software cash register full of features and creative for a Windows computer, it will help you to better handle all the activities of the computer money. The application comes with the user interface logical and user friendly allows you to work quickly and do not commit the common error. The program can be used on a number of computers and offers a wide range of authorization secure and reliable. Cash Register Pro will help you track products and goods remain...
</description></item><item><title>Download ThinkAutomation Studio Professional 5.1.1096.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 22 Nov 2025 02:32:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thinkautomation-studio-professional-9635.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thinkautomation-studio-professional-9635.html
</guid><description>
ThinkAutomation Studio Professional is software that automates on-premises and cloud-based business processes to cut costs and save time. Automate incoming communication channels, monitor databases, react to incoming webhooks, web forms and chat bots. Handles documents, attachments, local files, and other message sources.
Parse and extract data from incoming messages and take actions in business processes, such as outbound communications, updating on-premises and cloud databases,...
</description></item><item><title>Download VovSoft Collect URL 3.5</title><pubDate> Sat, 22 Nov 2025 02:27:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-collect-url-7395.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-collect-url-7395.html
</guid><description>
VovSoft Collect URL is an internet scanner like a search engine bot. Starting from the URL the user entered, it lists all the links on the URL. Then it recursively scans all the links in the list. Users can limit URL Crawl to only one domain name. The file extension ignore list can be edited. Connection and response timeout values ​​are editable. Additionally, the user can change the user agent value for HTTP and HTTPS connections.
Features of VovSoft Collect URL
	Scan the...
</description></item><item><title>Download EKIO - Loudspeaker Management Application 1.0.8.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 23:30:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ekio-loudspeaker-management-application-14305.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ekio-loudspeaker-management-application-14305.html
</guid><description>
EKIO is a loudspeaker management application that allows you to customize the sound of your loudspeaker system for optimal performance. The application provides the ability to easily create crossovers for full-range speakers, integrate subwoofers, and equalize your sound system. Additionally, EKIO can import loudspeaker measurements to achieve the best settings and achieve the best audio performance.
EKIO is a Windows application that works with the ASIO audio interface. However, if...
</description></item><item><title>Download Inno Setup Compiler 6.6.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 20:22:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-inno-setup-compiler-2655.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-inno-setup-compiler-2655.html
</guid><description>
Inno Setup Compiler is a system installed based on free software created by Delphi by Jordan Russell. The first version was released in 1997. QuickStart of Inno Setup include main Inno Setup and also includes an option to install the script editor Inno Script Studio. The script editor is not official and is not mandatory for general use, but help Inno Setup easier to use.
Inno Setup Compiler - software create file setup.exe
The features of Inno Setup Compiler
	Support for every...
</description></item><item><title>Download PicPick Pro 7.4.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 20:20:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-picpick-pro-2003.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-picpick-pro-2003.html
</guid><description>
PicPick Pro is a premium version paid free of PicPick. PicPick Pro is a screen capturing tool included editing has taken with many built-in tools available as measurement tool on the screen, including a color picker, color palette, protractor pixel, protractor, cross and many more. The program allows you to capture the entire desktop, active window, selected area or window control just by the click of a button or via keyboard shortcut.
PicPick Pro - Take a screenshot
PicPick Pro has an...
</description></item><item><title>Download PicPick 7.4.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 20:19:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-picpick-1323.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-picpick-1323.html
</guid><description>
PicPick is an application that captures the screen including the editing the photo has been taken with many built-in tools available as measurement tool on the screen, including a color picker, color palette, protractor pixel, protractor, cross and many more. The program allows you to capture the entire desktop, active window, selected area or window control just by the click of a button or via keyboard shortcut.
PicPick - Take a screenshot
Can load the captured image into the image...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tiny11 25H2 Build 26200.7171 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 20:19:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tiny11-8649.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tiny11-8649.html
</guid><description>
Tiny11 is a compact Windows operating system based on Windows 11 Pro 22H2, Tiny11 has everything you need for a comfortable, hassle-free computing experience. cumbersome and messy like a standard Windows installation. The operating system requires only 8GB of disk space and 2GB of RAM, and requires no TPM (Trusted Platform Module) and Secure Boot support.
The main goal of Tiny11 is to extend the reach of systems that can access Windows 11. The custom edition can run on any system...
</description></item></channel></rss>