<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 13:51:33 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 13:51:33 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Print Conductor 11.0.2512.15130</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 16:50:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-print-conductor-1559.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-print-conductor-1559.html
</guid><description>
Print Conductor is the software supports automatic printing of documents, text in different formats at the same time, all without opening each one. Print Conductor supports more than 75 kinds of different material and works with all types of printers. With Print Conductor, the printing of large volume of files as easy as 1-2-3. You no longer need to manually open each file, select printer, make settings to print, click "Print" and repeat. Instead, just drag and drop your documents into the...
</description></item><item><title>Download AutoPowerOptionsOK 6.29</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 16:39:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-autopoweroptionsok-1820.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-autopoweroptionsok-1820.html
</guid><description>
AutoPowerOptionsOK is a small program that can automatically turn off your screen, put your computer in sleep mode or switch between the power options. Each action can be triggered based on the absence of events keyboard and / or mouse for a specified time interval. For example, you can automatically turn off the screen if the mouse or keyboard has not been used in 10 minutes.
AutoPowerOptionsOK - power Management automatically
AutoPowerOptionsOK is a compact tool designed to help you...
</description></item><item><title>Download SoundVolumeView 2.49</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 16:30:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-soundvolumeview-2695.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-soundvolumeview-2695.html
</guid><description>
SoundVolumeView is a simple tool for Windows Vista / 7/8/2008/10, displays general information and current volume levels for all components sound activity on your system and allows you to mute and unmute them instantly. SoundVolumeView also allows you to save audio configuration to a file, containing the current volume level status and mute / unmute of all audio components, as well as the audio devices to default, then upload the same file to restore exactly the same file volume levels and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Certificate Manager 18.47</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 16:29:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-certificate-manager-13958.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-certificate-manager-13958.html
</guid><description>
Certificate Manager provides an in-depth overview of your current certificates, allowing you to easily access detailed information. It also provides functions for both exporting existing certificates and importing new certificates, enhancing your certificate management capabilities.
Application certificates are often overlooked by most users until problems arise during application installation. For the average end user, there is little reason to focus on application certificates....
</description></item><item><title>Download BytesMorph OST PST Converter 2.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 13:47:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bytesmorph-ost-pst-converter-14345.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bytesmorph-ost-pst-converter-14345.html
</guid><description>
Convert your Outlook email archive (both PST and OST files) to a variety of industry-standard formats. Whether you need to migrate email data, create a searchable archive, comply with regulations, or simply preserve your Outlook mailbox, this tool provides enterprise-grade conversion capabilities.
Supports two file formats
	PST file support: Convert Outlook's personal archive files (.pst) with full attribute extraction capabilities
	OST file support: Convert Outlook's offline archive...
</description></item><item><title>Download BytesMorph Secure File Eraser 2.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 13:43:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bytesmorph-secure-file-eraser-14344.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bytesmorph-secure-file-eraser-14344.html
</guid><description>
BytesMorph Secure File Eraser is your trusted solution for permanently and securely deleting files. Protect your sensitive data with military-grade erasure algorithms, ensuring files can never be recovered.
Military-Grade Security
Choose from industry-standard secure erasure algorithms:
	DoD 5220.22-M - 3-Step Department of Defence Standard
	Gutmann Method - Maximum 35-Step Security
	Schneier Method - Professional 7-Step Standard Random number of steps - Custom multi-step...
</description></item><item><title>Download BytesMorph Universal XML Converter 2.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 13:37:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bytesmorph-universal-xml-converter-14343.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bytesmorph-universal-xml-converter-14343.html
</guid><description>
BytesMorph Universal XML Converter is the most comprehensive and professional tool designed to convert XML files to many popular formats with advanced features and robust error handling capabilities. Whether you're dealing with large datasets, corrupted XML files, or need batch processing across different formats, this application consistently delivers reliable results.
Superior Multi-Format Export
	Excel (.xlsx) - Professional Spreadsheet with Auto-Adjusting Columns and...
</description></item><item><title>Download BytesMorph Mbox Converter 2.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 13:33:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bytesmorph-mbox-converter-14342.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bytesmorph-mbox-converter-14342.html
</guid><description>
BytesMorph Mbox Converter is the ultimate solution for managing and converting Mbox email archive files. Whether you're switching from one email application to another, archiving important contacts, or analyzing email data, our comprehensive tool provides everything you need.
Key Features
	Load individual Mbox files or entire folders
	Export to PDF, CSV, EML, EMLX, JSON formats
	Navigate folders in a hierarchical structure
	Preview emails by time
	Advanced Export...
</description></item><item><title>Download BytesMorph Email Address Extractor 2.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 13:28:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bytesmorph-email-address-extractor-14341.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bytesmorph-email-address-extractor-14341.html
</guid><description>
Transform your email data into a useful contact list with BytesMorph Email Address Extractor - the most comprehensive email address extraction tool available. Whether you're switching between email systems, building contact databases, or analyzing communication patterns, this professional tool handles all major email file formats accurately and easily.
Supports popular file formats
	Outlook files: OST, PST, MSG
	Standard email: EML, EMLX (Apple Mail)
	Unix systems: MBOX
	Contact File:...
</description></item><item><title>Download Telegram for Desktop 6.3.7</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Dec 2025 23:01:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-telegram-3376.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-telegram-3376.html
</guid><description>
Telegram is an instant messaging service and voice over IP services on the cloud platform. Client application Telegram is available for Android, iOS, Windows Phone, Windows NT, macOS, and Linux. Users can send messages and exchange photos, videos, stickers, audio and files of any kind.
Telegram - Messaging and free phone calls
Telegram seamless sync across all your devices and can be used on desktop, tablet and phone. You can send unlimited amount of messages, photos, videos and files...
</description></item><item><title>Download KMPlayer (KMP) 2025.11.14.11 x64 / 4.2.3.30 x86</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Dec 2025 23:00:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kmplayer-kmp-902.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kmplayer-kmp-902.html
</guid><description>
KMPlayer (KMP) is software watch movies listen to music multi-function for video enthusiasts. KMPlayer development is many types of the format different. KMPlayer has improved on sound quality, images when listening to music and watching movies, the playback speed of video is faster, more codec player is added to the software video decoder is optimized.
KMPlayer also supports a variety of audio formats and video and offers a the interface can be customized with the preview coverflow and...
</description></item><item><title>Download FoneLab Data Retriever 3.0.32</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Dec 2025 22:59:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fonelab-data-retriever-593.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fonelab-data-retriever-593.html
</guid><description>
FoneLab Data Retriever is a tool safe and convenient to restore data deleted or lost (such as photos, documents, email, video, etc.) on windows / mac, hard drive, flash drive, memory card, digital camera and more. There are many different methods that you can try to restore lost data on computer hard drive and other devices due to deleting, partition formatted, hard drive RAW or other incidents, the collected data FoneLab will be the best choice for you because of the convenience and...
</description></item><item><title>Download reaConverter Pro 8.0.170</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Dec 2025 22:58:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html
</guid><description>
reaConverter Pro is software image processing feature with batch conversion and image editing periodically becomes simple. eaConverter also provide command line utilities allow you to process images automatically, thus helping you shorten the time for other work.
reaConverter Pro integrated powerful tool of Uber with many great features. It provides advanced solutions to process and adjust images. Management of the conversion process the base image with the latest version of...
</description></item><item><title>Download AnyMP4 Data Recovery 3.0.32</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Dec 2025 22:58:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anymp4-data-recovery-2499.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anymp4-data-recovery-2499.html
</guid><description>
AnyMP4 Data Recovery software is data recovery professional and safe. AnyMP4 Data Recovery can help you recover almost all files lost, such as photos, documents, email, audio, video and many other things from the computer disk, flash drive, memory card / memory card on mobile phone or camera. Whether you lost files to delete, format, etc., or your data are gone for the collapse of the system, virus attack, etc., you can also use the program data recovery this powerful to help...
</description></item><item><title>Download Red Gate SmartAssembly Professional 8.4.1.6697</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Dec 2025 22:57:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-red-gate-smartassembly-1593.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-red-gate-smartassembly-1593.html
</guid><description>
Red Gate SmartAssembly is a tool that helps protect your application against reverse engineering or modifications prevent side Tuesday access to source code. This comprehensive solution protects the data card of you and more likely to report errors. This program makes files difficult can disassemble and injection code does not use, to help engineer can reverse and understand the core structure of the code. With your smartphone, you will have many features to tamper with the code as the...
</description></item><item><title>Download AOMEI Backupper Pro / Technician / Server 8.1.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Dec 2025 22:57:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aomei-backupper-pro-98.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aomei-backupper-pro-98.html
</guid><description>
AOMEI Backupper pro is a software backup and recovery professional, easy to use. Fully protect your computer from data loss. It allows you to backup an entire PC and Server, provides one-click backup your system partition or your disk and execute it in a few minutes. This software also can explore the created image and restore it on hard drive if your data gets lost or corrupted. In addition, you can create the recovery disk the ability to boot to recover his data after a system crash and...
</description></item><item><title>Download CoolUtils Total Image Converter 8.2.0.286</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Dec 2025 22:56:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-total-image-converter-848.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-total-image-converter-848.html
</guid><description>
CoolUtils Total Image Converter is software to convert images to other formats, and can edit, cut, resize and rotate them. With Total Image Converter you easy convert TIFFs into JPEGS, make photos suitable for the web or recover old photos in the supported format.
&amp;nbsp;CoolUtils Total Image Converter - convert images to other formats
Features CoolUtils Total Image Converter
	Total Image Converter supports almost all image formats
	Support convert eagle picture series.
	Total Image...
</description></item><item><title>Download ProgeCAD Professional 26.0.10.10</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Dec 2025 22:56:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-progecad-professional-847.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-progecad-professional-847.html
</guid><description>
ProgeCAD Professional is a CAD application 2D / 3D compatibility AutoCAD works with the file DWG of AutoCAD. This is a best solution for AEC, MCAD and all usages CAD generic. ProgeCAD Professional works natively with DWG! Fully compatible with AutoCAD® without conversion.
ProgeCAD Professional - Cad application in 2D and 3D
The main features of ProgeCAD Professional from the developer
	ProgeCAD convert PDF to DWG
	22.000 blocks are ready to use
	Export STEP, IGES, PDF, DWF, 3DS, DAE...
</description></item><item><title>Download AOMEI Backupper WinPE 8.1 Technician</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Dec 2025 22:55:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aomei-backupper-sever-99.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aomei-backupper-sever-99.html
</guid><description>
AOMEI Backupper server is a software backup and recovery professional, easy to use. It allows you to backup, secure Server, providing one-click backup your system partition or your disk and execute it in a few minutes. This software also can explore the created image and restore it on hard drive if your data gets lost or corrupted.
AOMEI Backupper sever what ?
AOMEI Backupper sever - backup data recovery sever
√ AOMEI Backupper sever also allows you to copy partitions or disk. The...
</description></item><item><title>Download Syncovery Premium 11.11.8.138</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Dec 2025 22:54:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncovery-pro-enterprise-232.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncovery-pro-enterprise-232.html
</guid><description>
Syncovery Pro Enterprise is a great application used to back up data and to synchronize personal computers, servers, laptops, notepads and storage online. The software comes with support for FTP and secure FTP servers, SSH, WebDAV, Amazon S3, http, update the part file, ZIP compression, data encryption, and schedule automatic backups.
Syncovery Pro Enterprise have the ability to freely select files and folders across the whole folder hierarchy in tree view and supports email...
</description></item><item><title>Download Apeaksoft Data Recovery 3.0.32</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Dec 2025 22:54:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-apeaksoft-data-recovery-2546.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-apeaksoft-data-recovery-2546.html
</guid><description>
Apeaksoft Data Recovery offers professional solutions to handle the data loss problems different. It can help you to recover all kinds of data from your computer, recycle bin, hard drive / flash memory card, etc. whether you mistakenly deleted some key files or lost data due to hard drive formatted or system malfunction, loss of data will no longer be the biggest nightmare of you.
Apeaksoft Data Recovery - Restore lost data
The features of Apeaksoft Data Recovery
	Recover data from...
</description></item><item><title>Download VovSoft Tree Notes 2.6</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Dec 2025 22:53:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-tree-notes-11294.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-tree-notes-11294.html
</guid><description>
Vovsoft Tree Notes is a decentralized note-taking application designed to improve your organizational efficiency and streamline your information management process. This powerful software provides users with a user-friendly platform to create, organize and access their notes with ease.
Tree Notes for Windows is a flexible and powerful note-taking solution that meets the needs of individuals, students, professionals, and creative minds alike. Boost your productivity, stay organized, and...
</description></item><item><title>Download JWIZARD Cleaner 1.10.6</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Dec 2025 22:53:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jwizard-cleaner-12853.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jwizard-cleaner-12853.html
</guid><description>
Effective Windows cleaning software to remove unnecessary files from your PC. JWIZARD Cleaner for Windows quickly frees up disk space and keeps your system in an optimal state, ensuring your PC runs stably and efficiently. This application is designed to provide you with a comprehensive tool to analyze and optimize your PC by performing a comprehensive cleanup or a more detailed cleanup, targeting specific areas such as system, browser, mail, etc.
Features of JWIZARD Cleaner
	Clean...
</description></item><item><title>Download Muni Animation MotionMuse 1.1.8</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Dec 2025 22:52:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-muni-animation-motionmuse-12700.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-muni-animation-motionmuse-12700.html
</guid><description>
MotionMuse is a user-friendly toolkit designed for 3D character animation, intended to simplify the animation process and make it accessible to new artists without the need for deep knowledge. wide. Its intuitive interface allows users to create, edit and animate animations with ease.
Main features
	Easy-to-use toolset: MotionMuse is built to accommodate users who may not have a background in 3D animation, featuring a streamlined interface that reduces complexity.
	Character Rigging:...
</description></item><item><title>Download Allround Automations PL-SQL Developer 16.0.8.2176</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Dec 2025 22:52:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allround-automations-plsql-developer-4730.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allround-automations-plsql-developer-4730.html
</guid><description>
Allround Automations PL/SQL Developer is a development environment integration is specifically targeted at the development application units are stored for the Oracle database. Over time, we have seen the business logic more and move towards the Oracle server, make PL / SQL programming become an important part of the development process overall. This software focuses on ease of use, coding quality and the main advantage in the process of software development, Oracle.
The features of...
</description></item></channel></rss>