<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 01:40:10 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 01:40:10 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download WD Drive Utilities 2.1.5.482</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Sep 2025 19:00:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wd-drive-utilities-3316.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wd-drive-utilities-3316.html
</guid><description>
WD Drive Utility is a program is relatively small, after the launch will give you all the tools to manage and refine the function of the external hard drive from the manufacturer Western Digital, also it can diagnose and identify the potential issues that may arise in the future when future use.
WD Drive Utilities - Manage and refine external hard drive
WD Drive Utility and WD Security, are contained within the WD Drive Utility and the zip files WD Security and install software Western...
</description></item><item><title>Download Internet Download Manager (IDM) 6.42 Build 45</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Sep 2025 18:57:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-inetnet-download-manager-161.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-inetnet-download-manager-161.html
</guid><description>
Internet Download Manager is the download acceleration software, the best download support now, it can help you speed up the download up to five times, continue and schedule downloads. The latest version of IDM adds the compatibility of Windows 10 and Windows 11, it has supported all current popular browsers such as Internet Explorer, Mozilla Firefox, Opera, Google Chrome, ..
Download IDM with the latest version on taiwebs.com making it easy to download and manage your downloaded files...
</description></item><item><title>Download Bandicam 8.2.2.2531</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Sep 2025 18:57:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bandicam-243.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bandicam-243.html
</guid><description>
Bandicam is the software screen recording powerful, helps users to record all activities happening on the computer such as video games, presentations,..
Software Bandicam uses graphics technology DirectX / OpenGL will help you carry out a video record with high compression ratio, while keeping the video quality closer to the original work and provide superior performance compared with other programs providing the same functionality.
Bandicam can create video with quality high but...
</description></item><item><title>Download Photoscape X Pro 4.2.8</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Sep 2025 18:56:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photoscape-x-pro-4417.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photoscape-x-pro-4417.html
</guid><description>
Photoscape X Pro is an all-in-one photo editing software offers image features related to Photo Viewer, Editor, Cut Out, batch, collage, Combine, Create GIF, Color Picker, Screen Capture, RAW images and more. Photoscape X Pro - an impressive application that allows you to take screenshots and edit photos. It allows you to create mosaic as well as animated GIF. It is a process installation is very simple and easy and after the installation process is complete, you are greeted with user...
</description></item><item><title>Download IDM Retail 6.42 Build 45</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Sep 2025 18:55:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-internet-download-manager-retail-3609.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-internet-download-manager-retail-3609.html
</guid><description>
IDM - Internet Download Manager Retail is a reliable utility and high efficiency will help you to increase your download speed and manage download at better. The program allows you to easily schedule, pause and resume downloads with a single click. Moreover, the application provides error resilience robust and can restart the download at the interrupted or broken. You can restore the download is interrupted due to network problems, lost connections, unexpected power outages, computer...
</description></item><item><title>Download ACDSee Photo Studio Home 2026 v29.0.0.3255</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Sep 2025 18:55:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-acdsee-photo-studio-home-3444.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-acdsee-photo-studio-home-3444.html
</guid><description>
ACDSee Photo Studio Home 2020 - The management of digital assets the best on the market
Is an amateur,, reality, photo collection of you continue to expand and you need to continue his work. With tools that help manage digital assets, productivity, and edit and distribute photos, ACDSee Photo Studio Home 2020 packing a punch worth. Existing feature recognition and face recognition, many basket pictures to collect assets on your hard drive, manage your keywords, improve, convert files in...
</description></item><item><title>Download CyberLink AudioDirector Ultra 2026 v16.0.5703.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Sep 2025 18:54:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-audiodirector-ultra-288.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-audiodirector-ultra-288.html
</guid><description>
Sound is half the movie experience and improving the audio in the project video will greatly enhance the final result. AudioDirector contains advanced tools help edit and edit the audio quickly and simply. With the audio feature and seamless integration with PowerDirector.
We provide CyberLink AudioDirector Ultra editor software, mix, and adjust the soundtrack, effects, audio for video, and all the passages spoken in the video. CyberLink AudioDirector Ultra is the upgrade version of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wise Care 365 Pro 7.3.1.714</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Sep 2025 18:54:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wise-care-365-pro-106.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wise-care-365-pro-106.html
</guid><description>
Wise Care 365 pro is a package of utilities registry, disk, and other systems important for your PC. Easy to use and effective, Wise Care 365 is the best solution to improve the performance of your computer. Get Wise Care 365 and your computer will never run slow again!
Wise Care 365 pro is what?
Wise Care 365 Pro
	Check PC a clicks
	Pc cleaning &amp;amp; speed up
	Inventory hardware
	Protecting your privacy
	Protect real-time system
	Silent mode
	Boot speed faster
	Freeing up disk...
</description></item><item><title>Download VanDyke SecureCRT and SecureFX 9.6.4.3695</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Sep 2025 18:53:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vandyke-securecrt-and-securefx-815.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vandyke-securecrt-and-securefx-815.html
</guid><description>
VanDyke SecureCRT and SecureFX is a file transfer app safety, flexibility with an intuitive interface provides remote access, secure file transfer. VanDyke provides simulation terminal firmly to the expert computing, enhance productivity with management enhanced and a variety of ways to save time and streamline the task repeated. SecureCRT has the security firm of SSH, session management extension and advanced commands, SecureCRT will help enhance your productivity.
VanDyke SecureCRT...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cockos REAPER 7.46</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Sep 2025 18:52:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cockos-reaper-889.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cockos-reaper-889.html
</guid><description>
Cockos REAPER is a powerful software for for windows, chp lets you record, arrange, edit, and display the audio waveform multi-track. Cockos REAPER offers an extensive feature set includes many effects and a sample project. REAPER supports ASIO, Kernel Streaming, WaveOut, and DirectSound for playback and recording. It reads the files in WAV, OGG and MP3 files and records WAV files. You can arrange any number of items in any number of tracks and use plug-in sound processing (DirectX and...
</description></item><item><title>Download CyberLink ColorDirector Ultra 2026 v14.0.5712.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Sep 2025 18:52:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-colordirector-ultra-283.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-colordirector-ultra-283.html
</guid><description>
CyberLink ColorDirector Ultra is a necessary tool to create impressive, stories, and evoking responses from your video viewers. ColorDirector provides all the video creators of all skill levels the means to dramatically improve their projects through the use of tools to control color and light.
Features of CyberLink ColorDirector Ultra
HDR Video : Apply HDR to your videos to add more dynamic range than in your scenes, bring out the detail and highlight the best parts of your...
</description></item><item><title>Download Opera One 122.0.5643.51</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Sep 2025 18:51:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-972.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-972.html
</guid><description>
Opera is a fast, safe, configurable and compliant intranet web browser, which includes both the reader and the application. The Opera browser supports web browsing, listening to music, watching high speed movies, you can open many tabs on the Opera without affecting your browsing speed. Opera now supports almost all devices and operating systems such as windows, IOS, Android, linux, MacOS ...
Opera is a beautiful interface and many interesting features, operating on both PCs and mobile,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Remote Computer Manager 6.5.4</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Sep 2025 18:51:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-remote-computer-manager-1111.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-remote-computer-manager-1111.html
</guid><description>
Remote Computer Manager is a software management remote desktop allows network administrators centralized management of PC network and perform operations such as control computer remotely, remote shutdown, run the command (executed), launch applications and processes, Wake-on-LAN over IPv4, Wake on LAN over IPv6, lock workstation, log in , log out, sleep, hibernate, wake up, reboot, power on, power power off, lock and unlock input devices, merge registry, copying files, installation...
</description></item><item><title>Download CoolUtils PDF Combine Pro 7.5.0.61</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Sep 2025 18:50:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-pdf-combine-pro-580.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-pdf-combine-pro-580.html
</guid><description>
CoolUtils PDF Combine Pro  is software that helps you combine  PDF, DOC, TXT, DOCX, HTML, XLS, images  h (TIFF, JPEG, PNG) and  email  as a  PDF  file. With PDF Combine Pro it is easier than ever to combine documents into one PDF file. Now you don't have to use some programs and converters to get a PDF. Everything for PDF Combine Pro to do for you.
Office, fax, email files - get combined PDF in seconds for personal use, commercial needs, electronic discovery, or manufacturing.  PDF...
</description></item><item><title>Download Brave Browser 1.82.170</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Sep 2025 18:49:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-brave-browser-2874.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-brave-browser-2874.html
</guid><description>
Brave Browser is a browser based on Chromium, the basic principle is that operation fast and privacy of users. The program can block pop-up windows and other ads, plus it blocked the mechanism for monitoring the online activities of your. Therefore, you can purchase and safely browse the website you are interested in without having to worry about the fact that your activity will be monitored and then you will be shown the necessary advertising or service provider of parties...
</description></item><item><title>Download Aiseesoft Screen Recorder 3.1.36</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Sep 2025 18:48:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aiseesoft-screen-recorder-631.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aiseesoft-screen-recorder-631.html
</guid><description>
Aiseesoft Screen Recorder is the software supports recording, take a screenshot with any videos and save them back with high quality. Apps screen recording video strong this can help you get online movies and radio, game capture, make video tutorials, record videos, capture screenshot, etc. on Windows 10/8/7.
Screen capture software helps you record almost any video screen you want. You can use it to record online video, game, podcast, webinars, lectures, presentations, Skype calls,...
</description></item><item><title>Download MetaProducts Portable Offline Browser 8.8.0.5004</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Sep 2025 18:48:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-metaproducts-portable-offline-browser-4701.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-metaproducts-portable-offline-browser-4701.html
</guid><description>
MetaProducts Portable Offline Browser is the leading app in the industry to store and download at website, MetaProducts Portable Offline Browser provides technology download at high level and strong features. Hosting your website automatically on a regular basis. Copy the website downloaded directly to your hard drive or to external media to another, such as a Flash drive or DVD. Storing downloaded content in any format: ZIP, CHM, EXE.
It's easy to download the website large amount or...
</description></item><item><title>Download Duplicate &amp;amp; Same Files Searcher 10.7.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Sep 2025 18:48:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-duplicate-same-files-searcher-1758.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-duplicate-same-files-searcher-1758.html
</guid><description>
Duplicate &amp;amp; Same Files Searcher is the duplicate search allows you to search for files similar or identical on your computer and help you delete to free up disk space.The interface of the app Duplicate &amp;amp; Same Files Searcher user-friendly. So, you can immediately start the search by setting the destination drive.
Duplicate &amp;amp; Same Files Searcher - Find duplicate files
With software you can include and exclude file types, set file size, minimum and maximum, just find the link...
</description></item><item><title>Download Software Companions GerbView 11.22.0.620</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Sep 2025 18:47:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-software-companions-gerbview-1484.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-software-companions-gerbview-1484.html
</guid><description>
GerbView is a file, advanced, but easy to use, convert, print, and view files HPGL, HPGL / 2, Excellon and raster. It supports both RS274D and RS274X. You can use this software to convert the old format and RS274D standard to the new RS274X have default data. Gerbview is used to represent and illustrate the intricate design of you.
Software Companions GerbView - conversion, printing, and viewing HPGL, HPGL / 2, Excellon
You don't need to wait for rendered images to see the picture of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Valentina Studio Pro 16.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Sep 2025 18:47:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-valentina-studio-pro-2122.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-valentina-studio-pro-2122.html
</guid><description>
Valentina Studio Pro is the best way to transform your data into meaningful information; create, manage, query and explore MySQL, Postgre MariaDB, MS SQL Server and SQLite database.
Valentina Studio Pro
Features of Valentina Studio Pro
SCHEMA EDITING &amp;amp; MAPPING
	Manage multiple databases in tabs and views that can be attached is
	Create / Drop / alter / Browse Tables, fields, index, trigger, constraints, links, views, stored procedures, properties, Sequences, Types, ...
	Edit the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Advanced CSV Converter 7.81</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Sep 2025 18:46:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-csv-converter-4508.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-csv-converter-4508.html
</guid><description>
Advanced CSV Converter is a conversion tool CSV to DBF, Excel (XLS, XLSX), TXT, HTML, PRG, XML, SQL, RTF. To convert a file, the program provides an interface controlled by the wizard, guides you step by step conversion. Use the wizard, you select file input, select the format and destination folder. If necessary, you can set the filter switch according to the example and select columns you want to exclude from the process. When the conversion process is started, the program will extract...
</description></item><item><title>Download Vivaldi for macOS 7.6.3797.52</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Sep 2025 18:46:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/mac/download-vivaldi-for-macos-3443.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/mac/download-vivaldi-for-macos-3443.html
</guid><description>
The Vivaldi for MacOS browser does not track users and offers more features than any other modern browser. Managed by Jon von Tetzchner (co-founder of Opera browser), Vivaldi for MacOS is driven by the real needs of today's users and ensures that they have the best tools to browse and get work done.
Vivaldi for MacOS - Modern web browser
Users can adjust Vivaldi to suit their browsing needs them without limiting customization options. Vivaldi takes the browser to the next level with a...
</description></item><item><title>Download SysTools SQL Server Migrator 6.1.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Sep 2025 18:45:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-systools-sql-server-migrator-12348.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-systools-sql-server-migrator-12348.html
</guid><description>
SQL Server Data Migration Tool is a reliable software that helps users migrate records &amp;amp; schemas from all objects of SQL Server to another object.
Features
	Move a database from a live SQL Server to another live SQL Server
	Supports database migration from offline MDF File to live SQL Server
	Move a database from an online or offline SQL Server to a .sql log file
	Supports migrating databases from SQL Server to SQL Server in the network
	Move objects like Tables, Functions, Views,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Master Packager Pro 25.7.9392</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Sep 2025 18:44:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-master-packager-pro-7982.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-master-packager-pro-7982.html
</guid><description>
Master Packager Pro is an application packaging tool for creating and editing Microsoft Windows Installer (MSI) files and repackaging other installations to MSI format. Its job is to make application packaging easy, fast, accessible to everyone from freelancers, small companies, and application packaging businesses.
Features of Master Packager Pro
	Create MSI and MST files from scratch or modify the Vendor Microsoft Windows installer.
	Simple design made to be as user-friendly as...
</description></item><item><title>Download Valentina Server 16.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Sep 2025 18:44:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-valentina-server-10771.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-valentina-server-10771.html
</guid><description>
Valentina Server is software that provides reports from all major databases or with its own advanced object-relational database system. It will combine an enterprise reporting server and two database servers into a single solution. You get all the technical features of Valentina Server in terms of usage, more connections and live technical support.
Features of Valentina Server
	Enterprise report server turns data into highly formatted reports in the form of multimedia web pages, text,...
</description></item></channel></rss>