<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 17:43:00 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 17:43:00 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download XnViewMP 1.9.3</title><pubDate> Mon, 11 Aug 2025 19:18:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xnview-mp-1074.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xnview-mp-1074.html
</guid><description>
XnViewMP "XnView MP" is the enhanced version of XnView Classic. This is the view and convert images multi-platform powerful, compatible with more than 500 image formats, different today. XnView MP easily export images to about 70 file format is different. Similar to XnConvert, XnView MP also features integrated switch at the same time batch file to help you process photos faster. XnView is another version of the photo viewer but with the ability to support formats more limited.
XnView...
</description></item><item><title>Download Bandicam 8.2.0.2523</title><pubDate> Mon, 11 Aug 2025 19:17:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bandicam-243.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bandicam-243.html
</guid><description>
Bandicam is the software screen recording powerful, helps users to record all activities happening on the computer such as video games, presentations,..
Software Bandicam uses graphics technology DirectX / OpenGL will help you carry out a video record with high compression ratio, while keeping the video quality closer to the original work and provide superior performance compared with other programs providing the same functionality.
Bandicam can create video with quality high but...
</description></item><item><title>Download Thorium Reader 3.2.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 11 Aug 2025 19:16:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thorium-reader-11878.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thorium-reader-11878.html
</guid><description>
Thorium Reader is open source ebook reading software designed to deliver a seamless and feature-rich reading experience. It supports various e-book formats, including EPUB, PDF, and CBZ, allowing users to read their favorite books, magazines, and comics from a single app.
Thorium Reader is a user-friendly, versatile ebook reader software designed to meet the needs of bookworms and digital readers. With a customizable interface, extensive format compatibility, accessibility features, and...
</description></item><item><title>Download RAM Saver Professional 25.8.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 11 Aug 2025 19:16:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ram-saver-pro-565.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ram-saver-pro-565.html
</guid><description>
RAM Saver Pro is a professional software optimize RAM is for system stable operation with high performance. RAM Saver Pro aims to provide all the tools necessary to increase the amount of free memory, at any time, also monitor and check the RAM.
When using RAM Saver Pro, you will be allowed to access its main menu by right-clicking on the tray icon. Also, if you want to display the main panel of the program you just double-click the icon. In addition, from the main interface of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download GoodSync Enterprise 12.9.5.5</title><pubDate> Mon, 11 Aug 2025 19:15:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-goodsync-enterprise-163.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-goodsync-enterprise-163.html
</guid><description>
GoodSync Enterprise is a software that saves files and files easily and is reliable. It automatically analyts, synchronize and backup your email, family photos, contacts, MP3, financial documentation and other important files-between desktop computers, laptops, servers, external drives and Windows Mobile devices as well as remotely via FTP , SFTP, WebDAV and more. The GoodSync synchronized software combines bulletproof reliability with an extremely easy interface to compare, synchronize...
</description></item><item><title>Download yt-dlp 2025.08.11</title><pubDate> Mon, 11 Aug 2025 19:15:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-dlp-6802.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-dlp-6802.html
</guid><description>
yt-dlp is a youtube-dl branch based on youtube-dlc currently not working. The main focus of this project is the addition of new features and patches while still updating the original project.
</description></item><item><title>Download LibreWolf 141.0.3-1</title><pubDate> Mon, 11 Aug 2025 19:15:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-librewolf-11967.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-librewolf-11967.html
</guid><description>
LibreWolf is a customized and independent version of Firefox, with the main goals being user privacy, security and freedom. LibreWolf is designed to provide increased protection against tracking and fingerprinting techniques and includes a number of security enhancements. This is achieved through our security and privacy oriented settings and patches. LibreWolf also aims to remove all telemetry, data collection and annoyances, as well as disable anti-free features like DRM.
LibreWolf...
</description></item><item><title>Download IntraWEB Ultimate 16.1.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 11 Aug 2025 19:14:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intraweb-ultimate-2007.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intraweb-ultimate-2007.html
</guid><description>
IntraWEB Ultimate is a tool to build the website. With this tool, the developer can create the page using the same method used to build the Windows program. Because the HTML page directly from the concept design to the user's computer does not download a bit more complicated and in fact is required from web server. So, the template IntraWeb on the server and download server and displays them to the user. Things technology direction of the IntraWEB Ultimate provides part flexibility and...
</description></item><item><title>Download MP08 for Siemens Solid Edge 2025</title><pubDate> Mon, 11 Aug 2025 19:14:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mp5-for-siemens-solid-edge-7416.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mp5-for-siemens-solid-edge-7416.html
</guid><description>
Solid Edge is the most fully featured combined 2D/3D CAD system that uses synchronous technology to speed up the design and editing process, as well as enhanced support for reused geometry. import. The new version of Solid Edge provides enhanced functionality based on synchronous technology, which dramatically speeds up the product design process and simplifies the modification, import, and application of data generated in systems. Different CADs. The latest version includes improvements...
</description></item><item><title>Download Robin YouTube Video Downloader Pro 6.15.5</title><pubDate> Mon, 11 Aug 2025 19:13:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-video-downloader-pro-2828.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-video-downloader-pro-2828.html
</guid><description>
YouTube Video Downloader Pro is a Windows application professional to download and convert videos from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion and thousands of video sharing sites, other. It accelerates your download up to 5 times. YouTube Video Downloader Pro allows you to download multiple videos at the same time. It also allows you to pause, resume and cancel a download at any time.
YouTube Video Downloader Pro - Download online videos on social networks
Features of YouTube Video Downloader...
</description></item><item><title>Download Muziza YouTube Downloader Converter 8.11.3</title><pubDate> Mon, 11 Aug 2025 19:08:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-muziza-youtube-downloader-converter-3972.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-muziza-youtube-downloader-converter-3972.html
</guid><description>
Muziza YouTube Downloader Converter is a tool to create conditions for an attractive interface and many features to help you to download video clips from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion, Instagram and other sites. Muziza YouTube Downloader Converter can also download the video UHD 8K, 5K, 4K, QHD 2K, HD 1080p and 720p from YouTube. The app allows you download only audio stream from YouTube and save as MP3. You don't need to download the entire video file.
Muziza YouTube Downloader...
</description></item><item><title>Download Calsep PVTSIM Nova 7.0.16122</title><pubDate> Mon, 11 Aug 2025 19:08:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-calsep-pvtsim-10323.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-calsep-pvtsim-10323.html
</guid><description>
PVTsim is a simulation tool that works across many engineering fields. Whether you are looking for fluid properties deep in a reservoir, in a well, in a subsea pipeline, or at the surface, you can rely on predictions with PVTsim. It enables reservoir engineers, flow assurance specialists and process engineers to combine reliable fluid characterization procedures with powerful and efficient regression algorithms to match Fluid properties and experimental data. Fluid parameters can be...
</description></item><item><title>Download NETworkManager 2025.8.10.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 11 Aug 2025 19:07:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-networkmanager-3328.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-networkmanager-3328.html
</guid><description>
NETworkManager is an open-Source tool that allows you to manage the network and troubleshoot the network. NETworkManager focus a number of tools can support managing network connections. You are granted access to a large assortment of tools available from the main window of NETworkManuber to effective use. You can use this tool to view network interface along with many bit other essential information such as IP address, DNS server, etc.). The network Card is connected can be configured...
</description></item><item><title>Download DesktopDigitalClock 5.57</title><pubDate> Mon, 11 Aug 2025 19:07:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopdigitalclock-4114.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopdigitalclock-4114.html
</guid><description>
DesktopDigitalClock is a program that desktop clock digital simply and beautifully with the theme and different custom for all MS-OS was inspired from the lock screen! Be made according to numerous requests of users, with the idea of the clock lock screen appearance in Windows 10 / 8.1 after login, display the time and date when the log in the left corner, to the analog clock to appear on desktop Windows.
DesktopDigitalClock - the clock on the computer
The basic function: high...
</description></item><item><title>Download elysia alpha compressor 2.1.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 11 Aug 2025 19:06:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-elysia-alpha-compressor-13839.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-elysia-alpha-compressor-13839.html
</guid><description>
elysia alpha compressor is a highly regarded analog mastering compressor, renowned for its pristine sound quality, versatility, and professional dynamics handling. First released in 2008, it quickly became the standard in mastering thanks to its clean, transparent compression even at aggressive settings and rich feature set including built-in parallel compression, M/S matrix, signature EQ filters, and various modes such as Auto-Fast, Warm, Soft Clip, Feedforward, and Feedback. It delivers...
</description></item><item><title>Download StationPlaylist Studio Pro 6.1.1.13</title><pubDate> Mon, 11 Aug 2025 19:06:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stationplaylist-studio-pro-6342.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stationplaylist-studio-pro-6342.html
</guid><description>
StationPlaylist Studio Pro is our streaming software for the studio, providing useful features to support DJ during live performances and to automate without supervision. StationPlaylist Studio Pro performs a multi-player management job. The studio manages and controls many of the internal players for purposes such as automatic cross-and-song overlap. Plus an advanced smart band that means that all the music will be perfectly combined without human interference.
Features of...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT-DL 11.3.3</title><pubDate> Mon, 11 Aug 2025 19:06:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-dl-5876.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-dl-5876.html
</guid><description>
YT-DL is a small program to download videos from YouTube and other video sites. Our goal is to make the program as simple as its name.
The features of YT-DL
	Download the video from YouTube and other video sites
	Increase download speed up to 400%
	Download multiple videos at the same time
	Pause and continue to download at any time
	Preview video content while downloading
</description></item><item><title>Download Cash Register Pro 3.2.6</title><pubDate> Mon, 11 Aug 2025 19:06:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cash-register-pro-3853.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cash-register-pro-3853.html
</guid><description>
Cash Register Pro a software cash register full of features and creative for a Windows computer, it will help you to better handle all the activities of the computer money. The application comes with the user interface logical and user friendly allows you to work quickly and do not commit the common error. The program can be used on a number of computers and offers a wide range of authorization secure and reliable. Cash Register Pro will help you track products and goods remain...
</description></item><item><title>Download Exacoustics GHOST 1.1.7</title><pubDate> Mon, 11 Aug 2025 19:05:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-exacoustics-ghost-13879.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-exacoustics-ghost-13879.html
</guid><description>
Exacoustics GHOST is a powerful and innovative synthesis plugin that uniquely combines Wavetable synthesis and Frequency Modulation (FM) synthesis into one integrated instrument. Released in August 2024 by Brisbane-based developer Exacoustics, the plugin quickly gained attention for its fresh approach and deep sound design capabilities.
Key Features:
	Hybrid Synthesis Engine: Combines the flexibility of wavetable oscillators with the complexity and richness of FM synthesis.
	Six...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Geek YTDL Pro 11.3.3</title><pubDate> Mon, 11 Aug 2025 19:05:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-geek-ytdl-pro-9895.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-geek-ytdl-pro-9895.html
</guid><description>
YT Geek YTDL Pro is software that helps users easily download videos from YouTube and hundreds of other video sites. It is very easy to use, just paste the video URL and you can download the video while keeping the original quality. Not only videos on Youtube, users can download any video from social networking sites like Facebook, Vimeo, Myspace video,...
Features of YT Geek YTDL Pro
	Download videos from YouTube and other video sites.
	Increase download speed up to 400%.
	Download...
</description></item><item><title>Download Luci Studio 6.0.11</title><pubDate> Mon, 11 Aug 2025 16:12:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-luci-studio-14036.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-luci-studio-14036.html
</guid><description>
Luci Studio is professional live streaming software for the internet that turns Windows, Mac or Linux devices into powerful audio streaming sources or receivers. The software supports studio quality point-to-point audio, multi-channel streaming with up to 64 simultaneous stereo streams and offers features such as low latency RTP streaming with bi-directional communication, SIP support, multicast streaming and integration with multiple audio codecs including MP2, AAC, Opus and even the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft Activation Scripts 3.5</title><pubDate> Mon, 11 Aug 2025 15:52:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-activation-scripts-5390.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-activation-scripts-5390.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft Activation Scripts is an open source Windows and Office activation tool that features online HWID, Ohook, KMS38 and KMS activation methods, along with advanced troubleshooting functionality.
Activation methods
			Trigger type
			Supported products
			Activation time
			HWID
			Windows 10-11
			Permanent
			Ohook
			Office
			Permanent
			KMS38
			Windows 10-11, Server
			Until 2038
			Online KMS
			Windows / Office
			180 days (with...
</description></item><item><title>Download Unicodia 2.12.6</title><pubDate> Mon, 11 Aug 2025 15:51:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-unicodia-8521.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-unicodia-8521.html
</guid><description>
Unicodia is free, open source software that can be used as an alternative character map for your Windows machine. The interface contains everything you need, allowing you to easily cycle through all the available ASCII symbols and copy them to the clipboard. Uncicodia is a great alternative to your standard Unicode characters and is filled with symbols/characters that make it useful for a number of different uses.
Features of Unicodia
	In Windows 10/11 — all characters of Unicode 15...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Downloader 9.15.5</title><pubDate> Mon, 11 Aug 2025 15:51:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html
</guid><description>
YTD Youtube Downloader is an application that reliable and intuitive, allowing you to quickly download YouTube videos and save them to your computer. You can also convert the media files to the format desired video or extract audio streams and save separately. YTD Youtube Downloader lets you save your favorite clips of yourself from Youtube, Facebook, Vimeo and Dailymotion to your desktop. The software supports URLS from many web site hosting, multimedia and allows you to download desired...
</description></item><item><title>Download 4KSoftware 4K Downloader 5.16.3</title><pubDate> Mon, 11 Aug 2025 15:51:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-downloader-3858.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-downloader-3858.html
</guid><description>
4K Downloader is a Windows application small but powerful to download and convert video in 4K and 8K Ultra HD from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion and thousands of other video-based websites. It speeds up your download by up to 5 times. Consider that most smart phones, TVS, computers, and tablets all support the high definition format, don't be surprised when many users want to enjoy quality content on their device. 4K Downloader is a lightweight software designed to help you grab videos...
</description></item></channel></rss>