<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 19:55:58 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 19:55:58 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Ghostery for Firefox 10.5.9 + Chrome / Opera / Edge</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 22:55:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ghostery-for-firefox-320.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ghostery-for-firefox-320.html
</guid><description>
Ghostery for Firefox is a browser add-on for Firefox allows you to see what kind of technical track is used by the current website, including tags, error web, pixels and beacons. Ghostery also gives you the hints to learn about the objects that are "of interest" to you includes the privacy policy useful links other.
Ghostery for Firefox comes with the option to block any elements of this, including ads, cookies, tracking, analysis, social extensions and more. You can select the items to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Windows Movie Maker 2025 v10.0.0.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 22:54:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-movie-maker-4542.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-movie-maker-4542.html
</guid><description>
Windows Movie Maker is a video editing app that allows you to transform images, audio files and short clips into full movies. It accepts all types of media, including photos from digital cameras, flash cards, mobile phone and DVD. With this helpful program, it's easy to sort and select the photos and videos you want to use in the next film of his. You can also add text, transitions, effects, etc. change as much as you want or let Windows Movie Maker do it for you.
Windows Movie Maker -...
</description></item><item><title>Download Photo Supreme 2025.3.3.8094</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 22:54:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photo-supreme-430.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photo-supreme-430.html
</guid><description>
Photo Supreme is a software product management professional pictures of idimager. With Photo Supreme you can arrange, manage back stock photo archive of yourself and share them with you here and relatives easily via Email or Facebook. Photo Supreme provides users method to sort images effective, logical, as well as edit and share your photos with friends and relatives in the family. Especially the Photo Supreme allows to work with multiple image formats and support mounting support,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Kindle for PC 2.8.70980</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 22:54:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kindle-for-pc-6655.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kindle-for-pc-6655.html
</guid><description>
Kindle for PC is a handy and handy application that you can use to read a Kindle book with a computer without a Kindle device. To use it, you need to have an Amazon account registered, as the app will prompt you to log in as soon as the startup starts. Simple interface, which allows you to browse through your book library and manage your collections.
Features of Kindle for PC
	The navigation is so easy, because the entry can help you move to the desired chapter and you can use the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Red Gate SmartAssembly Professional 8.3.8.6565</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 22:53:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-red-gate-smartassembly-1593.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-red-gate-smartassembly-1593.html
</guid><description>
Red Gate SmartAssembly is a tool that helps protect your application against reverse engineering or modifications prevent side Tuesday access to source code. This comprehensive solution protects the data card of you and more likely to report errors. This program makes files difficult can disassemble and injection code does not use, to help engineer can reverse and understand the core structure of the code. With your smartphone, you will have many features to tamper with the code as the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Lesspain Kyno Premium 1.9.0.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 22:52:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lesspain-kyno-premium-3732.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lesspain-kyno-premium-3732.html
</guid><description>
Lesspain Kyno Premium is an app for managing multi-media smart allows you to manage, sift and transfer the code means for free adjustment according to the process of your work. Preview, check and arrange your photos from all your cameras quickly on set or in post, even in a group. Quickly find and organize the media files on the drive reduce load or stored your. Immediate use without training or studying the documentation.
Lesspain Kyno Premium - multimedia Manager
Browse videos...
</description></item><item><title>Download Windows Video Editor Pro 2025 v10.0.0.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 22:51:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-video-editor-6420.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-video-editor-6420.html
</guid><description>
Windows Video Editor is the 2021 editing tool collection that has everything you need to edit your video file. You can easily Cut, Crop, Rotate, Split, Trim or Join your videos. You can add Effects, Text, Animations, Watermarks, Subtitles, Music to your videos. You can adjust video speed, brightness, contrast, saturation or anything else of your videos. You can do almost everything to edit your videos! And You can edit videos in batch!
Features of Windows Video Editor
	With Windows...
</description></item><item><title>Download Waterfox 6.6.3 / 2022.11</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 22:51:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-waterfox-114.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-waterfox-114.html
</guid><description>
Waterfox is a 64-bit version of the foundation Firefox was built and the compiler Intel is optimized for speed and performance on Windows systems.Waterfox does not add any additional features or bling, in fact, it will automatically import all the gadgets and install is have of you, so you will feel like at home when you run it the first time.All the add-on your Firefox will work with Waterfox, however, only support the plug-in more 64-bit, is includes Adobe Flash, Oracle Java and...
</description></item><item><title>Download InstaBot Pro 7.1.9</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 22:50:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-instabot-pro-8820.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-instabot-pro-8820.html
</guid><description>
InstaBot Pro is a piece of software designed to automate your “likes”, finding new followers profiled by similar accounts and Get your followers really interested in your content. Everyone knows now that the success of an instagram account also depends on the interactions and activity level of that particular account in the community.
Features of InstaBot Pro
	GET FOLLOWERS: Export followers of other profiles and/or users based on specific Hashtags.
	AUTO FOLLOW: Automatically...
</description></item><item><title>Download VovSoft VCF Editor 2.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 22:50:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-vcf-editor-12583.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-vcf-editor-12583.html
</guid><description>
Vovsoft VCF Editor is a powerful, offline tool designed to manage and edit vCard (VCF) files on Windows. Running locally on the user's computer, the tool ensures privacy and security by processing all data offline without the need for an internet connection. This makes this tool ideal for users who prioritize keeping their communications private and secure.
Features of VovSoft VCF Editor
	This vCard editor software allows users to easily load, view and edit key contact fields such as...
</description></item><item><title>Download Windows Video Converter 2025 v10.0.0.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 22:50:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-video-converter-6371.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-video-converter-6371.html
</guid><description>
Windows Video Converter is a comprehensive software with many features such as Transaction, Download and Rapid Video Editing. Windows Video Converter supports video conversion to 1000 formats at a rate of 30 times faster without reducing the quality. Download and convert video online. Cut, Cut, Add Text, Effect, Appendix, And More.
Features of Windows Video Converter
	The conversion of video to over 1000 formats.
	The speed is 30 times faster.
	The quality is not reduced.
	Download...
</description></item><item><title>Download VirtualBox 7.2.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 22:49:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-virtualbox-285.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-virtualbox-285.html
</guid><description>
VirtualBox is a virtualization software open source allows you to run one or more operating system in a virtual machine while running Windows. It is used for purposes such as experience app or try to play the game new in a safe environment, do not affect the main operating system of you. With this software, users will better control multiple virtual machines at the same time.
VirtualBox - Create virtual drive allows running multiple operating systems at the same time
The program comes...
</description></item><item><title>Download Reportizer 6.5.10.395</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 22:48:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reportizer-5205.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reportizer-5205.html
</guid><description>
Reportizer is a tools report database. Easily create, modify, and print reports database. Allows to manage collection reports. Support database BDE or ADO. Tested on dBase (DBF), Paradox (DB), Text (TXT), the values are separated by commas (CSV), Oracle, Interbase, Microsoft Access, Microsoft Excel, SQL Server, Visual FoxPro, MySQL, PostgreQuery, HTML.
The design reports visually. Reports can be edited in the report design, intuitive and convenient with the toolbar and powerful tool. For...
</description></item><item><title>Download Any MP3 Converter 2025 v10.0.0.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 22:47:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-mp3-converter-11983.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-mp3-converter-11983.html
</guid><description>
Any MP3 Converter is a user-friendly tool that supports many audio formats, including MP3. It allows you to convert audio files quickly and easily. It supports more than 1000 Video/Audio Formats. 30 times faster speed and no quality loss. Optimized for high quality HD Video and large Video files. Download and convert online videos like YouTube, Vimeo, etc. Trim/Join/Crop/Rotate, Add Text, Effects, Subtitles and more...
Main features of Any MP3 Converter
	MP3 converter allows you to...
</description></item><item><title>Download AccdbMerge 1.35.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 22:47:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-accdbmerge-12716.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-accdbmerge-12716.html
</guid><description>
AccdbMerge is a reliable program that allows you to quickly combine information and structure from multiple Microsoft Access database files, in two projects. The application can perform advanced data segregation, to avoid duplicate entries. Furthermore, the program provides support for differential comparison of batch data.
AccdbMerge Features
	The software can open password-protected files and compare them in two parallel projects. You can save settings, in case you often work with...
</description></item><item><title>Download Brave Browser 1.82.166</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 22:46:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-brave-browser-2874.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-brave-browser-2874.html
</guid><description>
Brave Browser is a browser based on Chromium, the basic principle is that operation fast and privacy of users. The program can block pop-up windows and other ads, plus it blocked the mechanism for monitoring the online activities of your. Therefore, you can purchase and safely browse the website you are interested in without having to worry about the fact that your activity will be monitored and then you will be shown the necessary advertising or service provider of parties...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare PDFelement Pro 12.0.2.3719</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 17:44:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-pdfelement-pro-105.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-pdfelement-pro-105.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare PDFelement Pro support users to convert PDF to office documents for easier use, modify in every situation. Is one of the software conversion material is rated best today, integrated with many features. We recommend that you should use experience software many useful features this.
Wondershare PDFelement Pro - conversion Fie PDF more features, multi-language
Wondershare PDFelement Pro what?
Convert PDF into Word, Excel, PowerPoint...
• Convert PDF and protected PDF into...
</description></item><item><title>Download VueScan Pro 9.8.47</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 17:44:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vuescan-pro-75.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vuescan-pro-75.html
</guid><description>
VueScan Pro l  is one of the software  Scan quality pictures  First and appeared quite soon,  VueScan Pro  always asserted its No. 1 position on the technology pages, awards as well as user reviews. Through many versions, VueScan Pro 9 is greatly improved in terms of interface and features. Supporting most popular image formats today, this software will help you scan images quickly, easy to use and high quality output. With the color balance mode, you won't have to worry about blurring the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Active Partition Recovery Ultimate 25.1.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 17:43:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-active-partition-recovery-ultimate-611.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-active-partition-recovery-ultimate-611.html
</guid><description>
Active@ Partition Recovery Ultimate is a data recovery tool in the end. In addition to the Professional features, it also contains an ISO image that can boot (based on WinPE Active @ Boot Disk Lite) that you can burn to CD-ROM or write to a USB Flash drive and boot Windows from CD-ROM / USB to recover partitions (including the system) as well as to restore files and special folder from within the Windows environment familiar.
The final version includes Active@ LiveCD (recovery...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft Office 2021-2024 Professional Plus VL (64-bit) 2508 Build 19127.20222 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 17:43:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-office-2021-6670.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-office-2021-6670.html
</guid><description>
Since the end of February 2021, Microsoft has announced two new versions of Office 2021 including: Office 2021 and Office LTSC. Reportedly, Office 2021 is the next version of Office 2019, promising to bring users a better experience in the new Word, Excel or PowerPoint tools.
With each office user, the Microsoft Office toolkit is essential and indispensable software in the job. Microsoft Office has undergone numerous editions from Office 2010, 2013, 2016, 2019 to Microsoft 365 developed...
</description></item><item><title>Download AVS Video Editor 11.1.2.42</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 17:42:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs-video-editor-426.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs-video-editor-426.html
</guid><description>
AVS Video Editor is software professional video editing for windows with full features useful, easy-to-use.  When using AVS Video Editor you can record a video, to impose various effects, create and burn DVD, export movies to various video formats, convert video to iPod, PSP, mobile phones and the other portable device.
Features AVS Video Editor
Format support
	AVS Video Editor supports all major video formats. Edit and save the video file in the codec AVI, VOB, MP4, DVD, WMV, 3GP,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft Office 2024 Professional Plus LTSC v2408 Build 17932.20540 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 17:41:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-office-2024-professional-plus-64-bit-10679.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-office-2024-professional-plus-64-bit-10679.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft has officially announced the final version of the Office 2024 release for Windows and Mac users. After releasing a preview version in the first half of this year, the product has been finalized and is now available to users. Office 2024 includes updated versions of apps from the Word 2024, Excel 2024, PowerPoint 2024, Outlook 2024, Access 2024, and Publisher 2024 suites.
Office 2024 includes virtually every change that has been added to the suite of programs in Office 365 over...
</description></item><item><title>Download Advanced Installer Architect 23.0.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 17:40:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-installer-128.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-installer-128.html
</guid><description>
Advanced Installer is a Windows utility designed to help you build the package Windows Installer in a working environment clean and intuitive.
Although it has many parameters dedicated but the user interface is very simple and gives users the ability to create new projects by selecting the type, namely installer (for example: application Visual Studio or .NET, pack 32/64-bit mixture), Java , updates, support, mobile devices, and other things.
Advanced Installer - An environment for...
</description></item><item><title>Download vMix Pro 28.0.0.42</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 17:40:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vmix-pro-930.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vmix-pro-930.html
</guid><description>
vMix Pro is software production, recording and streaming live events. Create the products professional video in HD, SD and even 4K. vMix is a software Video Mixer and Switcher that utilizes the latest advances in computer hardware to provide live mix HD video, a task previously only possible on hardware mixers expensive dedicated.
vMix Pro - Production, create video
The features of vMix Pro
	Has the ability to create 4K videos, HD and SD.
	Support for webcam and capture card.
	NDITM...
</description></item><item><title>Download DaVinci Resolve Studio 20.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 17:39:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-davinci-resolve-studio-1072.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-davinci-resolve-studio-1072.html
</guid><description>
DaVinci Resolve Studio is professional video editing and color grading software developed by Blackmagic Design. This is an enhanced version of the free DaVinci Resolve software, providing additional features and capabilities for professional video editing, color correction, and post-production.
One of the outstanding features of DaVinci Resolve Studio is its powerful color correction capabilities. It provides a comprehensive set of tools and features for advanced color correction,...
</description></item></channel></rss>