<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 19:58:23 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 19:58:23 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Google Drive (Backup and Sync) 114.0.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Sep 2025 22:35:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-drive-6751.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-drive-6751.html
</guid><description>
Using Google Drive is a great way to store your files safely in secure data centers, where your files will not be lost. Even if your computer, phone or tablet is broken, the files you store in the Google Drive are safe. Download photos, videos, documents, and other files that are important to you up to Google Drive. Continue with the memory up to 15GB. Free. Google Drive helps you access your file faster by recognizing the objects in your image and text in the scanned documents.
Easy to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Java SE Development Kit 25.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Sep 2025 22:35:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-java-se-development-kit-6881.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-java-se-development-kit-6881.html
</guid><description>
Java allows you to play online games, chat with people around the world, and view images in 3D. These applications, written in the Java programming language and accessible from your browser, are called applets. Companies also use Java applications for intranet applications and other e-business solutions.
Java is used by companies in all major industries. Whether deployed on mobile phones, embedded devices, game consoles, laptops, or in data centers, Java provides rich user interfaces,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Media Player Classic Home Cinema 2.5.3</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Sep 2025 22:34:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-media-player-classic-home-cinema-2839.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-media-player-classic-home-cinema-2839.html
</guid><description>
Media Player Classic Home Cinema is a multimedia compact for Microsoft Windows 32 bit and 64 bit. MPC mimics the interface of Windows Media Player 6.4, but provides most options and features available in the modern means. Media Player Classic Home Cinema for free 100% no advertising, so you can directly access content and enjoy media playback without being distracted.
With Media Player Classic Home, you can now change the design a multimedia of the custom toolbar. There is a range to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Free Download Manager 6.30.0 Build 6459</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Sep 2025 22:34:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-download-manager-3105.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-download-manager-3105.html
</guid><description>
Free Download Manager is free application download manager, Free Download Manager will significantly increase downloads by splitting the files into several smaller parts and then downloads at the same time. Speed your download will be significantly increased. Manager download free can also continue to download at broken or not responding, so you don't need start downloading from the beginning after occasionally interrupted.
Free Download Manager - Manage and speed up downloads
You can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Windows 10 Pro Lite 22H2 Build 1904X.6332 Ghost Spectre</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Sep 2025 22:33:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-10-pro-lite-8714.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-10-pro-lite-8714.html
</guid><description>
Windows 10 Pro Lite is a version of the Windows 10 operating system that has been optimized for performance and reduced in size to be lighter and faster than the standard version of Windows 10 Pro. The Lite version of Windows 10 is designed to work well on older or lower-end hardware, making it a good choice for devices with limited resources.
Windows 10 Pro Lite has a smaller install size and uses less system resources than the standard version of Windows 10. This version also includes...
</description></item><item><title>Download Futuremark PCMark Pro 10 v2.2.2737</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Sep 2025 22:32:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-futuremark-pcmark-pro-1275.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-futuremark-pcmark-pro-1275.html
</guid><description>
Futuremark PCMark 10 Professional Edition is a suite of comprehensive test includes multiple tasks to be performed in the work environment modern. With the option of running quick, extended and customized in accordance with your needs, PCMark 10 is a standard PC complete for modern office and is the ideal choice for organizations that buy PC with big volume.
Futuremark PCMark Pro
PCMark 10 easy to install and run, no need for complex configuration. Running the benchmark itself and you...
</description></item><item><title>Download SolidWorks 2025 SP4.0 Full Premium</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Sep 2025 22:32:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-solidworks-01en-6421.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-solidworks-01en-6421.html
</guid><description>
SolidWorks  is 3D design software running on Windows operating system and available since 1997, created by Dassault Systèmes SolidWorks Corp. SolidWorks is a computer-aided design, analysis and preparation system for the manufacture of products of any complexity and purpose. CALS technology, including bidirectional data exchange with other Windows applications and interactive document creation Depending on the type of task to be solved.
SolidWorks's line of analysis and simulation...
</description></item><item><title>Download The Graphics Creator 8 1.4.15</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Sep 2025 22:30:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-the-graphics-creator-6419.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-the-graphics-creator-6419.html
</guid><description>
The Graphics Creator  is this program that allows you to create your own graphics in minutes without any design skills or big budget. Attract attention with stunning graphics. Search hundreds of thousands of high-quality photos and videos. And much more.
Features of The Graphics Creator
	Search hundreds of thousands of high-quality photos and videos
	Choose from 1000+ beautiful fonts from Google
	Erase the background of the image to make it transparent
	Increase Graphics Maker's...
</description></item><item><title>Download Embarcadero RAD Studio 13.0 Florence Architect Version 37.0.57242.3601</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Sep 2025 22:29:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-embarcadero-rad-studio-10661.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-embarcadero-rad-studio-10661.html
</guid><description>
RAD Studio is Embarcadero's integrated development environment (IDE) for software development. It supports application development for various platforms, including Windows, macOS, iOS, Android, and Linux. RAD Studio is known for its emphasis on rapid application development (RAD) and provides many tools and components to streamline the development process.
IDE includes Delphi and C++ Builder, which are programming languages used to build native applications. Delphi is a language based...
</description></item><item><title>Download nTopology 5.30.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Sep 2025 22:28:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ntopology-7887.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ntopology-7887.html
</guid><description>
nTopology is software that enables engineers and designers to create any geometry no matter how complex and meet the requirements of high performance products . Our software is used from research through production to create breakthrough products and processes for the aerospace, automotive, medical and consumer industries. Our customers depend on the general design capabilities of the nTopology to get the most out of new hardware, optimize components where performance is important,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Intel Ethernet Adapter Complete Driver Pack 30.4.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Sep 2025 22:27:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intel-ethernet-adapter-complete-driver-pack-7424.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intel-ethernet-adapter-complete-driver-pack-7424.html
</guid><description>
Intel Ethernet Adapter Complete Driver Pack contains all Intel® Ethernet networking software and drivers for Windows, Linux and FreeBSD versions currently supported for most Intel Ethernet Adapters. Not all Intel Ethernet Adapters and Intel Ethernet Controllers are supported in all versions of Windows, Linux, or FreeBSD.
What's new in this release:
In this point release, NVM Update Package 3.20 has been updated. If you currently have the 3.20 update package installed and are running...
</description></item><item><title>Download ChrisPC Free VPN Connection 4.25.0917</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Sep 2025 22:27:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-free-vpn-connection-2887.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-free-vpn-connection-2887.html
</guid><description>
ChrisPC Free VPN Connection software allows you to create VPN connection (virtual private network) to the server for free from the United States, Germany, Canada, France, Germany, Russia, Singapore, the Netherlands. This will help you to unblock your favorite sites to watch free TV and on-demand television when living abroad, travelling, on business or vacation. In addition, here is the solution to overcome the limited area for the popular websites: Google, YouTube, Facebook, Instagram,...
</description></item><item><title>Download EverNote 10.155.5.14508</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Sep 2025 22:26:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-evernote-3261.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-evernote-3261.html
</guid><description>
EverNote is the all in one tool allows you to track notes, todo items, memos, outlines, excerpts, websites, ideas and other things and automatically synchronize them between multiple computers and mobile devices (iPhone, Android, etc.). You can choose to sort their notes into categories, password protect them, export them to XML and more. EverNote supports a number of pattern notes allow you to add to-do list, spreadsheet like Excel to calculate costs (automatic sum), notes, phone, contact...
</description></item><item><title>Download Windows and Office Genuine ISO Verifier 12.26.50.25</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Sep 2025 22:25:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-and-office-genuine-iso-verifier-542.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-and-office-genuine-iso-verifier-542.html
</guid><description>
Windows and Office Genuine ISO Verifier is a small utility used to check for Microsoft Office and Windows ISO genuine or not by carrying out verification fast SHA-1 and MD5. The software has a friendly interface with the user and not cause you any real trouble whatsoever while navigating.
Users use tool requires to specify the file input and the application will automatically perform the rest of the work. Windows and Office Genuine ISO Verifier can compare the file SHA-1 with the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Imaginando VS 2.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Sep 2025 22:25:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-imaginando-vs-11117.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-imaginando-vs-11117.html
</guid><description>
Take your music to another dimension with a captivating visual world. VS - Visual Synthesizer makes it easy to represent your sounds optically in a highly customizable way. At the core of Imaginando VS is a set of graphics shaders called materials, which render procedurally generated geometry in real time, based on each material's unique set of parameters. VS comes equipped with 50 beautifully hypnotic materials for you to customize and combine to create mesmerizing performances.
Visual...
</description></item><item><title>Download The Foundry Nuke Studio 16.0v6</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Sep 2025 22:25:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-the-foundry-nuke-studio-733.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-the-foundry-nuke-studio-733.html
</guid><description>
Nuke®, NukeX® and Nuke Studio offer cutting-edge toolkits for node-based compositing, editorial and review. The Nuke family's unparalleled flexibility and collaborative workflows help you get the highest quality results-fast.
Power and performance
Built to meet the needs of modern production work, the Nuke family offers unparalleled levels of power and performance, whether you're a team with a deadline or tackling a solo project.
Collaborative workflow
Efficient, collaborative...
</description></item><item><title>Download Massive X 1.6.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Sep 2025 22:24:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-native-instruments-massive-x-2123.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-native-instruments-massive-x-2123.html
</guid><description>
Massive X is a synthesizer developed by Native Instruments, designed to create a wide variety of sounds and styles for electronic music production. It is the successor of the popular Massive synthesizer and offers many new features and improvements. Based on state-of-the-art architecture, it offers pristine sound and tremendous creative flexibility for artists and sound designers alike – allowing them to create, adjust, and experiment with sounds from a variety of sources. different...
</description></item><item><title>Download StruSoft FEM-Design Suite 24.00.004</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Sep 2025 22:24:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-strusoft-fem-design-suite-7996.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-strusoft-fem-design-suite-7996.html
</guid><description>
FEM-Design Suite is a software for designing concrete, steel and timber structures according to EU standards. It features a unique user-friendly working environment based on familiar CAD tools that make structural modeling and editing simple and intuitive. The fast and easy nature of FEM-Design makes it ideal for all types of construction tasks from single element design to global stable analysis of large structures and making it become the best practical tool for structural...
</description></item><item><title>Download Clementine Music Player 1.4.1-55</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Sep 2025 17:49:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-clementine-4762.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-clementine-4762.html
</guid><description>
Clementine is a tools multi-platform software which allows you to listen to music from hard drive, library, audio CDS or the Internet, as well as manage it, edit the card and see the lyrics. Clementine is inspired by Amarok 1.4, focusing on a easy to use interface for searching and playing your music.
Clementine also allows you can view track information such as length, bit rate, sample rate, size, file type, number of times played and your ranking, as well as complete the card...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tablacus Explorer 25.9.7</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Sep 2025 17:48:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tablacus-explorer-3674.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tablacus-explorer-3674.html
</guid><description>
Tablacus Explorer is a file manager open-source is designed to help you arrange the contents of your folders. Tablacus Explorer has a user interface very simple and you will be familiar with working with this program immediately. Folders and files can be sorted or grouped by name, type, size and date when they were last modified. App can automatically remember to set your tab if you close it and allows you to copy or move items to different positions and save the settings to format an XML...
</description></item><item><title>Download Perfectly Clear WorkBench 4.8.0.2852</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Sep 2025 17:46:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfectly-clear-workbench-6892.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfectly-clear-workbench-6892.html
</guid><description>
Perfectly Clear Workbench is an application that uses image editing libraries Perfectly Clear by Athentech and is provided to demonstrate the capabilities of the Perfectly Clear processing libraries, which recognize faces and allow quick export of processing settings for use.
One of the key features in Workbench is the ability to "export to API" when saving a Preset. This allows you to make image edits in Workbench and adjust the settings to suit your editing style and needs. You can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Internet Download Manager (IDM) 6.42 Build 43</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Sep 2025 17:46:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-inetnet-download-manager-161.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-inetnet-download-manager-161.html
</guid><description>
Internet Download Manager is the download acceleration software, the best download support now, it can help you speed up the download up to five times, continue and schedule downloads. The latest version of IDM adds the compatibility of Windows 10 and Windows 11, it has supported all current popular browsers such as Internet Explorer, Mozilla Firefox, Opera, Google Chrome, ..
Download IDM with the latest version on taiwebs.com making it easy to download and manage your downloaded files...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wise Care 365 Pro 7.3.1.713</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Sep 2025 17:45:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wise-care-365-pro-106.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wise-care-365-pro-106.html
</guid><description>
Wise Care 365 pro is a package of utilities registry, disk, and other systems important for your PC. Easy to use and effective, Wise Care 365 is the best solution to improve the performance of your computer. Get Wise Care 365 and your computer will never run slow again!
Wise Care 365 pro is what?
Wise Care 365 Pro
	Check PC a clicks
	Pc cleaning &amp;amp; speed up
	Inventory hardware
	Protecting your privacy
	Protect real-time system
	Silent mode
	Boot speed faster
	Freeing up disk...
</description></item><item><title>Download IDM Retail 6.42 Build 43</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Sep 2025 17:44:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-internet-download-manager-retail-3609.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-internet-download-manager-retail-3609.html
</guid><description>
IDM - Internet Download Manager Retail is a reliable utility and high efficiency will help you to increase your download speed and manage download at better. The program allows you to easily schedule, pause and resume downloads with a single click. Moreover, the application provides error resilience robust and can restart the download at the interrupted or broken. You can restore the download is interrupted due to network problems, lost connections, unexpected power outages, computer...
</description></item><item><title>Download ZoomIt 9.01</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Sep 2025 17:43:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zoomit-3162.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zoomit-3162.html
</guid><description>
ZoomIt is a tool zoom and annotate on desktop, allows you to zoom the screen by mouse roller or arrow keys up and down on the keyboard. It is activated by a keyboard shortcut can be customized and can also be used to draw on the computer to your desk (with or without zoom), using a customizable color and pen width.
ZoomIt - Zoom in and annotate the screen
ZoomIt helps you highlighted in red highlight the segment points, the text is important. Thanks to this, the other people easily...
</description></item></channel></rss>