<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 17:44:17 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 17:44:17 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download DiskMax 7.25</title><pubDate> Mon, 28 Jul 2025 20:40:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-diskmax-5940.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-diskmax-5940.html
</guid><description>
Using DiskMax to periodically make a robust drive cleaner and optimize performance to keep your PC healthy. After using DiskMax, you will notice that your system will work better, the apps will start faster, the files will open faster and the games will run better. Just run DiskMax over time to keep your system steady.
Even if you are an advanced user, DiskMax will be useful to you because it automate all the tasks needed to keep your system clean and quickly, helping you enjoy the...
</description></item><item><title>Download PPTube 10.5.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 28 Jul 2025 20:39:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pptube-12556.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pptube-12556.html
</guid><description>
PPTube Video Downloader allows you to download HD videos easily, from 720p, 1080p, 2K, 4K and 8K. You can save multiple videos at the same time. Just copy multiple video URLs from various websites and paste them into PPTube Downloader, then you can download multiple videos in seconds.
In addition, you can download HD videos from Instagram, TikTok, Facebook, Apple Music, Vimeo, adult websites, etc. and convert them to MP4, MP3, MOV, AAC and more than 20 other output formats. PPTube...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinCatalog 2024.14.1.728</title><pubDate> Mon, 28 Jul 2025 20:39:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wincatalog-615.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wincatalog-615.html
</guid><description>
WinCatalog 2018 is a software cataloguer multi-function for the disk, file, folder, and any objects not files. Not always easy to track the location of a number of files in your computer, especially if you have a huge collection of CD and DVD. If you are one of those users, then surely there will be appropriate tools to work with such a task. WinCatalog is a software utility designed to help you find documents and data from your computer by building an index that allows you immediate...
</description></item><item><title>Download Simple Sticky Notes 6.8</title><pubDate> Mon, 28 Jul 2025 20:39:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-simple-sticky-notes-2180.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-simple-sticky-notes-2180.html
</guid><description>
Simple Sticky Notes is software that creates sticky notes on screen Desktop computer help you easily remember the schedule of his. Simple Sticky Notes allow users to fashion digital sticky / post it notes and almost "sticky" notes on a desktop operation Windows. It is completely ideal for the kind of users who need to write everything down with pen and paper to avoid the discomfort of forget everything. This program of articles simple digital notes, it certainly will prove to be of great...
</description></item><item><title>Download RapidRAW 1.3.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 28 Jul 2025 20:38:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rapidraw-13957.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rapidraw-13957.html
</guid><description>
RapidRAW is a modern, high-performance, open-source RAW photo editor, designed to deliver a fast and clean editing experience with a lightweight footprint (under 30MB). Built with performance and usability in mind, the software is aimed at photographers who want a simple, efficient, and fun workflow without compromising performance.
Key Features
	GPU-accelerated processing: Uses a custom WGSL shader to process all image adjustments on the GPU, allowing for smooth, responsive editing...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ahnenblatt 4.32.0.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 28 Jul 2025 20:38:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ahnenblatt-3844.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ahnenblatt-3844.html
</guid><description>
Ahnenblatt is a genealogy software full-featured, easy to use suitable for beginners and even pedigree has the experience to organize genealogy research by you. Use plausibility checks to find out the inaccuracies in your family and create the chart impressive with just a few mouse clicks.
Ahnenblatt - Create family tree,
Recently, there has been strong increase of the general interest of the public for genealogical tree. Users who desire to track their heritage have many tools at...
</description></item><item><title>Download iDownerGo Pro 10.5.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 28 Jul 2025 20:37:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idownergo-12439.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idownergo-12439.html
</guid><description>
iDownerGo is the best tool that allows users to download videos, music and playlists from more than 10,000 streaming sites. It can easily convert videos to MP4, MOV, MKV, 3GP, AAC, WAV, FLAC and other formats on PC and Mac. With this amazing program, users can enjoy their favorite media content without restrictions.
iDownerGo Features
	Download any video up to 8K resolution
	Download 1080p videos online from over 10,000 popular streaming sites easily.
	Save any video in various...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Downloader 9.15.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 28 Jul 2025 20:37:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html
</guid><description>
YTD Youtube Downloader is an application that reliable and intuitive, allowing you to quickly download YouTube videos and save them to your computer. You can also convert the media files to the format desired video or extract audio streams and save separately. YTD Youtube Downloader lets you save your favorite clips of yourself from Youtube, Facebook, Vimeo and Dailymotion to your desktop. The software supports URLS from many web site hosting, multimedia and allows you to download desired...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Video Downloader 11.26</title><pubDate> Mon, 28 Jul 2025 20:36:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-video-downloader-9636.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-video-downloader-9636.html
</guid><description>
YT Video Downloader is software used to easily and quickly download any video or audio content from any website in HD quality using video downloader online. Save videos from almost any website supported by a video downloader on your local hard drive. Media search is a convenient way to do this.
Features of YT Video Downloader
	Download videos from hundreds of video sites.
	Really increase your download speed by up to 500% or even more!
	Download 8K, 5K, 4K Ultra HD, 2K Quad HD, 1080p...
</description></item><item><title>Download WindowTop Pro 5.28.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 28 Jul 2025 20:36:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windowtop-6955.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windowtop-6955.html
</guid><description>
WindowTop is a program that pins windows on Desktop, in other words it sets the window to float above all other program windows, creating transparency for the windows. that window via a dedicated slider, which supports adjusting transparency, changing the color of application windows or similar programs with the dark theme of the Windows 10 operating system, creating contrast and reducing tension straight, painful for the eyes.
Features of WindowTop
	Put window on top
	Set window to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Hybrid 2025.07.27.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 28 Jul 2025 20:35:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hybrid-2233.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hybrid-2233.html
</guid><description>
Hybrid is a multifunctional program that allows you to record videos on media Blu-ray or AVCHD, also you can convert data in formats x264, Xvid, VP8, ac3, ogg, mp3, aac and flac formats mp4, m2ts, mkv, webm. You can download Hybrid below. Please note that after conversion, you can write the result right into the media. That's not all, you also can use the edit program and the card, you can work with subtitles. You will get a large number of installation, a simple interface, in that it's...
</description></item><item><title>Download PC Assist Software PDF Assist 2.5.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 28 Jul 2025 20:35:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pc-assist-software-pdf-assist-12798.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pc-assist-software-pdf-assist-12798.html
</guid><description>
One of the most widely used file formats today is PDF, due to its many advantages. Not only because it is cross-platform, but also because it is compact, secure and ensures the integrity of graphics, displaying identical content regardless of the device it is viewed on. PDF Assist is a full-featured PDF processing tool that not only acts as a PDF viewer but also comes with options to annotate documents, sort pages, hide sensitive content or completely encrypt a file, convert, merge and...
</description></item><item><title>Download DroidKit 2.3.6.20250728</title><pubDate> Mon, 28 Jul 2025 20:35:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-droidkit-6578.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-droidkit-6578.html
</guid><description>
DroidKit is data recovery software for your mobile device, it will quickly scan your phone memory and save photos, WhatsApp chats and files, messages Messages, contacts and more essential data up to 13 categories, covering almost everything you need every day. All Android phones and tablets are supported. Without rooting your device. No tech skills required. No need to wait many days. You can get back what you've lost with just a few simple clicks, instantly.
Besides, DroidKit also has...
</description></item><item><title>Download EarthTime 6.30.6</title><pubDate> Mon, 28 Jul 2025 20:34:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-earthtime-185.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-earthtime-185.html
</guid><description>
EarthTime is software that displays the time and date local time of any place in the world. This application has database integration good for 3000 city, users can manually add, download at EarthTime if you want to. EarthTime allows you to install for the time zone and current local time.EarthTime displays the Earth according to the view night and day, you can view the map in full screen mode.
EarthTime
The feature on EarthTime
	EarthTime allows users to interact with visualization...
</description></item><item><title>Download MKVToolnix 94.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 28 Jul 2025 20:33:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mkvtoolnix-1129.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mkvtoolnix-1129.html
</guid><description>
MKVToolnix is software that supports video editing, such as cutting or splicing the videos together to create a complete video and unique. MKVToolnix to help you cut the interesting scenes in the video to create the short clips impress others. In addition, you can also stitch multiple videos together to create a single video quality, get big interest from viewers.
MKVToolnix - Cut and connect video
MKVToolnix allows you to customize and manage up the MKV file had to be cut or connect...
</description></item><item><title>Download Drastic MediaReactor WorkStation 7.0.974</title><pubDate> Mon, 28 Jul 2025 20:33:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-drastic-mediareactor-workstation-5756.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-drastic-mediareactor-workstation-5756.html
</guid><description>
Drastic MediaReactor WorkStation is a live plugin version of Drastic's MediaReactor file translation system. Instead of having to use a separate translation step, artists can work with footage that comes directly in their favorite creative software. Contemporary manufacturing processes can access a growing choice of equipment and formats acquisition, production, mezzanine and output. Unfortunately, the proprietary nature of these media tools often results in content translation taking time...
</description></item><item><title>Download Yellow Leads Extractor 9.2.8</title><pubDate> Mon, 28 Jul 2025 20:32:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yellow-leads-extractor-3729.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yellow-leads-extractor-3729.html
</guid><description>
Yellow Leads Extractor is the software that allows users to make 100% custom search in the browser. When you have this program then you don't need to do more work to retrieve information from the yellow pages. You just need to enter the category and location. After entering the information when you will click on the option data get then all the information will be extracted.
Yellow Leads Extractor - custom Search on the browser
The features of the Yellow Leads Extractor
	You can save...
</description></item><item><title>Download Remote Desktop Manager Enterprise 2025.2.22</title><pubDate> Mon, 28 Jul 2025 20:32:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-remote-desktop-manager-enterprise-242.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-remote-desktop-manager-enterprise-242.html
</guid><description>
Remote Desktop Manager Enterprise software is the complete management of remote connections and virtual machines from a single location, at the same time access support data online and cloud storage. Remote Desktop Manager supports multiple types of connections, not only connections for the protocol connect remote computer Remote Desktop Protocol (RDP).
Remote Desktop Manager easily add, edit, delete, share, organize and find your remote connection of you quickly. Compatible with...
</description></item><item><title>Download Pazu StreamGet All-In-One Video Downloader 2.7.6</title><pubDate> Mon, 28 Jul 2025 20:31:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pazu-streamget-all-in-one-video-downloader-12037.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pazu-streamget-all-in-one-video-downloader-12037.html
</guid><description>
StreamGet All-In-One Video Downloader is the ultimate downloading solution for you. It supports downloading any movies and shows from the most popular streaming sites including Netflix, Prime Video, Disney Plus, Max, Hulu, and Apple TV Plus. The downloader is continuously updated to support more platforms in the future.
Download movies and shows from various streaming platforms to MP4/MKV on your Windows device and enjoy them anywhere you want.
Features of Pazu StreamGet All-In-One...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cash Register Pro 3.2.5</title><pubDate> Mon, 28 Jul 2025 20:31:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cash-register-pro-3853.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cash-register-pro-3853.html
</guid><description>
Cash Register Pro a software cash register full of features and creative for a Windows computer, it will help you to better handle all the activities of the computer money. The application comes with the user interface logical and user friendly allows you to work quickly and do not commit the common error. The program can be used on a number of computers and offers a wide range of authorization secure and reliable. Cash Register Pro will help you track products and goods remain...
</description></item><item><title>Download Easy Window Invert 1.0.0.10</title><pubDate> Mon, 28 Jul 2025 20:30:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easy-window-invert-12671.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easy-window-invert-12671.html
</guid><description>
By using Easy Window Invert software, you can significantly increase user experience. It allows color blind as well as visually impaired users to use computers.
You can use Easy Window Invert to create a dark mode for software that doesn't have a dark mode. If there is an unpleasant contrast difference between the active window and the rest of the screen, it is possible to cover distracting parts of the screen with a hotkey-activated background panel.
In a multiple display system, you...
</description></item><item><title>Download TubeMate Downloader 5.21.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 28 Jul 2025 20:30:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubemate-downloader-4250.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubemate-downloader-4250.html
</guid><description>
TubeMate Downloader is a smart application that lets you download any clip you want from the website hosting the main video and convert them in when download at or then. If you need a simple and effective tool to download videos, you can give it a try. With TubeMate Downloader, you can directly drag and drop video link from your browser into the drop-down box or application window to start downloading. You don't even need to copy and paste the video URL.
TubeMate Downloader - Support...
</description></item><item><title>Download Directory Opus Pro 13.17.3 Beta</title><pubDate> Mon, 28 Jul 2025 20:30:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-opus-pro-779.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-opus-pro-779.html
</guid><description>
Directory Opus Pro is a software replacement for Explorer with traditional strength and function more than any manager other files. Directory Opus Pro full support for high DPI screen (for example 4K and 5K) with the rename dialog is redesigned, with new features. Besides being a recording macro only allows you to perform mass renaming complex that don't need regular expressions. In addition, Directory Opus Pro also enhances the ability to script.Better handling of renaming recursive and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Gilisoft AI Toolkit 10.5</title><pubDate> Mon, 28 Jul 2025 20:29:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-ai-toolkit-9520.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-ai-toolkit-9520.html
</guid><description>
Gilisoft AI Toolkit is a comprehensive software package that can be useful for businesses and individuals who want to integrate AI technology into their workflow. Gilisoft AI Toolkit is a software package that includes various tools for working with artificial intelligence, including chatbots, OCR (optical character recognition), TTS (text-to-speech) software, and ASR (automatic speech recognition). The chatbot tool allows users to create their own chatbots and customize them to their...
</description></item><item><title>Download App Builder 2025.16</title><pubDate> Mon, 28 Jul 2025 20:29:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-app-builder-241.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-app-builder-241.html
</guid><description>
App Builder is a software application developer to help create and design apps, HTML5, web app, web app PWA on both platforms mobile and desktop. App Builder is professional software supports users to create the program HTML5 without writing code. It is very easy to use, suitable with all users who lack of professional knowledge in the field of programming and application design.
App Builder brings to 22 different themes that users can use to design for your app. You can choose 1 or a...
</description></item></channel></rss>