<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:43:25 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:43:25 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download MiniTool Power Data Recovery Personal / Business 12.8 All Editions</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 18:58:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minitool-power-data-recovery-1168.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minitool-power-data-recovery-1168.html
</guid><description>
MiniTool Power Data Recovery is software data recovery from hard drives, SD, Smartmedia, compact Flash, memory Cards and other media. Power Data Recovery recovers files and data lost due to random erase, format, attack virus, breakdown when creating the partition or download, turn off the computer, format the storage media, or use FDISK, damage the boot sector MBR,...
MiniTool Power Data Recovery - data recovery
Features of MiniTool Power Data Recovery
	Recover data after accidental...
</description></item><item><title>Download reaConverter Pro 8.0.176</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 18:58:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html
</guid><description>
reaConverter Pro is software image processing feature with batch conversion and image editing periodically becomes simple. eaConverter also provide command line utilities allow you to process images automatically, thus helping you shorten the time for other work.
reaConverter Pro integrated powerful tool of Uber with many great features. It provides advanced solutions to process and adjust images. Management of the conversion process the base image with the latest version of...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDQ Inventory 19.6.29.0 Enterprise</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 18:57:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdq-inventory-1468.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdq-inventory-1468.html
</guid><description>
PDQ Inventory is a software application to manage your system. This software will be able to manage your system by scanning the Windows operating system of you to provide information hardware, software, and configuration for the Windows operating system in your your tools. The tools available in this software helps you can scan the computer correctly.
In addition, the software PDQ Inventory can give you very detailed information. This software application is one of the management...
</description></item><item><title>Download iTop Data Recovery Pro 6.0.0.924</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 18:57:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-itop-data-recovery-pro-7139.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-itop-data-recovery-pro-7139.html
</guid><description>
iTop Data Recovery Pro is a powerful data recovery tool that speeds up scanning and data recovery processes due to iTop's unique recovery algorithm. In just a few minutes, you can get your deleted files back perfectly as expected. Besides, Scan options are diverse for different needs. You can quickly find your lost data by Location and File Type.
iTop Data Recovery allows you to easily perform file recovery without limitations. More than 1000 file formats are supported. Meanwhile, this...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDQ Deploy 19.6.29.0 Enterprise</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 18:56:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdq-deploy-1469.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdq-deploy-1469.html
</guid><description>
PDQ Deploy Enterprise is an application to keep the Windows PC and the programs installed on it. Software PDQ Deploy helps you to connect multiple patch or a windows app (.exe, .msi) with multiple operating systems. The deployment software can be install, delete, run script, reboot, copy the file, sliding mode, send messages, etc.
PDQ Deploy Enterprise
Features of PDQ Deploy Enterprise
	Send notifications (alerts) via email
	Run the script as popular as .vbs, .reg .bat and .ps1
	Run...
</description></item><item><title>Download Chaos Corona 14.1 for 3ds Max 2018 - 2026</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 18:55:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chaos-corona-2986.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chaos-corona-2986.html
</guid><description>
Corona Renderer is the name of the plug-in technique and dedicated powerful, but have high functionality for Autodesk software 3ds Max. Plug before you is a standalone application known to the CLI. In addition, users can use this tool to promote their business on software Maxon Cinema 4D is also used. The manufacturers of this product believe that working with this tool is very simple and in fact you only need to press the activities rendered. With this tool easier than ever can do the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Chaos Corona 14.1 for Cinema 4D R17 - 2026</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 18:55:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-corona-renderer-for-cinema-4d-6499.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-corona-renderer-for-cinema-4d-6499.html
</guid><description>
Corona Renderer  is the name of a powerful, but highly functional engineering and dedicated plug-in for Autodesk 3ds Max software. Plug in before you are a known CLI standalone application. In addition, users can use this tool to advertise their business on Maxon Cinema 4D software which is also used. The manufacturers of this product firmly believe that working with this tool is very simple, and in fact you just need to hit render the rendering operations. With this tool it's easier...
</description></item><item><title>Download Help &amp;amp; Manual Professional 10.0.3 Build 7453</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 18:54:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-help-manual-professional-1451.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-help-manual-professional-1451.html
</guid><description>
Help &amp;amp; Manual Professional is software create files, instructions and help handle all the technical aspects, complexity of workflow. Help and Manual help you to simplify work instead of wasting endless amount of time to "programming", you can focus the entire effort in writing his material, so that all work time is your work time efficiently.
Help &amp;amp; Manual Professional - Create a file guide and help
The features and how the work of Help &amp;amp; Manual Professional
	Help &amp;amp;...
</description></item><item><title>Download Text Editor Pro 35.2.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:43:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-text-editor-pro-800.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-text-editor-pro-800.html
</guid><description>
Text Editor Pro is software to handle text, HTML, Perl, Ruby, or Fortran with features syntax highlighting, professional. Text Editor provides syntax highlighting for over 50 scripts and has a simple interface and easy access. In addition, the Text Editor Pro also supports more than 50 programming languages like C ++, COBOL, graph DOT, DSP, DWScript, Fortran, Foxpro, Java, Perl, Python, Ruby, SQL and many other languages.
Text Editor Pro - text Processing professional
The software can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Lyric Video Studio 1.4.12</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:40:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lyric-video-studio-13581.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lyric-video-studio-13581.html
</guid><description>
Lyric Video Studio is a powerful, feature-rich video editor specifically designed to create lyric videos, music videos, and visualizers with ease. It integrates simple and effective text tools along with generative AI capabilities to streamline the video creation process. Whether you're a musician launching a killer new track, a content creator, or just love playing with visuals, this app lets you sync your lyrics to your music in just a few clicks. Enter lyrics, drag to sync and you're...
</description></item><item><title>Download PC Assist Software PDF Assist 3.0.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:40:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pc-assist-software-pdf-assist-12798.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pc-assist-software-pdf-assist-12798.html
</guid><description>
One of the most widely used file formats today is PDF, due to its many advantages. Not only because it is cross-platform, but also because it is compact, secure and ensures the integrity of graphics, displaying identical content regardless of the device it is viewed on. PDF Assist is a full-featured PDF processing tool that not only acts as a PDF viewer but also comes with options to annotate documents, sort pages, hide sensitive content or completely encrypt a file, convert, merge and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Executor 2.2.2.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:39:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-executor-271.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-executor-271.html
</guid><description>
Executor for windows is a software alternative premium customization features for the Windows "Run" and "Search Programs". When you press WIN + Z and provides the search results instant, as-you-type for any keywords you enter. By default, Executor will index all the Desktop and Start Menu and you can easily expand the search range by adding the folder location additional.
Executor for windows
The program comes with a list of commands built in which you can use to quickly access many...
</description></item><item><title>Download Inno Setup Unpacker 2.1.4</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:39:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-inno-setup-unpacker-12546.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-inno-setup-unpacker-12546.html
</guid><description>
Inno Setup is a popular and reliable application that creates program installers by helping you create scripts. Extracting the installation files from their container, resulting from compiling code with Inno Setup, can only be done through self-extracting files. In other words, you need to create a self-extracting executable to shell the installation documents.
Inno Setup Unpacker can help you avoid such actions, which is especially useful because some system security protocols block...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter 3.9.18 (0401)</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:39:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-to-mp3-converter-1744.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-to-mp3-converter-1744.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter is the software support download youtube video and convert video to mp3 format fast and most simple. MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter allows you download and convert videos from YouTube and other websites to MP3 format by pasting the YouTube URL into the application. When you paste the URL, the program will display thumbnails for videos and you have the option to customize the title information, artist and album before you begin the process of...
</description></item><item><title>Download IObit Smart Defrag Pro 11.2.0.472</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:38:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iobit-smart-defrag-pro-319.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iobit-smart-defrag-pro-319.html
</guid><description>
IObit Smart Defrag Pro is software that defragment the disk to help speed up the whole system to prevent the technical errors not desired. Based on the technology of disk defragmentation latest of IObit, and technology “boot Time disk defrag” Smart Defrag 5 is created with the ability to defragment in the world. It not only provides defragmentation, but also smart sorting your files based on using frequency, thus increasing the disk speed and the whole system for highest...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mass Image Compressor 4.2.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:37:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mass-image-compressor-12571.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mass-image-compressor-12571.html
</guid><description>
Mass Image Compressor is easy to use - a point-and-shoot mass image compression and conversion tool for Web page optimization, photographers, HTML game creators, and regular Windows users.
MassImageCompressor reduces image size significantly (&amp;gt;90%) according to user-selected size and quality parameters. Reduce large numbers of images in a folder (and optional subfolders) with just one click. Batch compressing images for websites, emails or mobile storage has never been easier! Most...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinScript 1.4.4</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:37:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winscript-12800.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winscript-12800.html
</guid><description>
WinScript is an open source tool built to help you build custom scripts for Windows 10 and 11. It includes scripts for debugging, privacy, performance, and more, along with the ability to install all your favorite apps with just one click.
Features
	Debloat: Remove Windows bloatware, CoPilot, Edge, OneDrive, and other pre-installed features preset.
	Privacy: Disable Windows and 3rd party data collection, tracking, app access, and telemetry.
	Performance: Set background services to...
</description></item><item><title>Download VovSoft Search Text in Files 5.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:28:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-search-text-in-files-5417.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-search-text-in-files-5417.html
</guid><description>
VovSoft Search Text in Files is an application that searches through text files with simple queries, and the application will quickly find the file. Select the folder, enter the search text and filename filter, then click the Start button. All files including the search text will be listed. You can export the list to text or a CSV file. You can open, copy or delete files by right clicking. You can also display file sizes and file icons by using checkboxes.
VovSoft Features Search Text...
</description></item><item><title>Download PLEdit 7.4.0.742</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:23:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pledit-5224.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pledit-5224.html
</guid><description>
PLEdit is the application that allows to edit and compile the module code PL / SQL (the stored procedure.) It is optimized for fast and friendly resource. Thanks to the user interface according to the card of the program, you can open and edit multiple modules at the same time. In addition, you have the option to save the workspace current and complete his mission at a later date.
PLEdit supports marked syntax, help you write the code and detect errors more easily, also can turn on or...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wing FTP Server Corporate 8.1.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:23:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wing-ftp-server-corporate-2752.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wing-ftp-server-corporate-2752.html
</guid><description>
Wing FTP Server Corporate is a highly functional, easy and safe can be used in the operating system Windows, Linux, Mac and Solaris are used. The software supports a number of file transfer protocol such as FTP, HTTP, FTPS, HTTPS and SFTP. Wing FTP Server provides web-based interface to manage the server at any time. You can also get performance server and the online and even send email notifications about various events happening on the server.
Management server multi-function
Wing FTP...
</description></item><item><title>Download Malwarebytes Support Tool 1.9.17.1158</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:22:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-malwarebytes-support-tool-4901.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-malwarebytes-support-tool-4901.html
</guid><description>
Malwarebytes Support Tool is designed to help you fix the problem with Malwarebytes for Windows. Tool support Malwarebytes combines many utilities, such as utilities cleanup Malwarebytes and scan tool recover Farbar. Tool support Malwarebytes collect information from your computer and create a new support ticket or update a ticket out there with the information collected.
Tool support Malwarebytes can do?
	Provides the option of self-help to troubleshoot
	Create a support ticket...
</description></item><item><title>Download AndroidDrive 2.4.14</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:22:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-androiddrive-10400.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-androiddrive-10400.html
</guid><description>
AndroidDrive is a program that allows mounting Android smartphones/tablets as drives on Windows. When AndroidDrive is running and you connect an Android device, AndroidDrive automatically mounts the drive containing that device's internal storage (files, folders).
Once you have started AndroidDrive, the connected Android smartphone/tablet will be recognized as a new drive in Windows Explorer. This way, any files, photos, or other media can be moved back and forth between your Windows...
</description></item><item><title>Download Synchredible Professional 9.101</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:16:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-synchredible-professional-1923.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-synchredible-professional-1923.html
</guid><description>
Synchredible Professional is the most advanced version help synchronize the folder and your drive quickly and easily. Whether it is a single file or an entire drive - Synchredible Professional will synchronize, copy and save them for you. The software guide will assist you to identify the work that is scheduled in advance or be done through the USB connection. This way, you can keep your files in sync - automatically.
In the past years, the advanced technology of the us in Synchredible...
</description></item><item><title>Download Synchredible 9.101</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:16:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-synchredible-53.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-synchredible-53.html
</guid><description>
Synchredible is an easy to use tool to synchronize folders and files. It provides a wizard interface lets you set up the sync job, select files to exclude, schedule the job to execute automatically, and more.Additional features include support for network and external drives, check CRC32, and more.
Synchredible - synchronization of folders and files
Among other things, you can use the filter for the file type specific data synchronization according to the time or routine deletion of...
</description></item><item><title>Download NTFS Permissions Auditor Pro 26.1.4</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:15:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-albusbit-ntfs-permissions-auditor-pro-7539.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-albusbit-ntfs-permissions-auditor-pro-7539.html
</guid><description>
NTFS Permissions Auditor Pro is a software to quickly and easily audit directory permissions in your Windows system. It allows you to quickly analyze, verify and review any NTFS folder permissions and provides additional features like powerful, customizable filtering, exporting to different formats, etc.
Features of NTFS Permissions Auditor Pro
	Get up and running with just one install.
	Instant and accurate details about NTFS permissions for all target folders.
	Filters combine many...
</description></item></channel></rss>