<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 15:42:29 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 15:42:29 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Windows 11 Media Creation Tool 10.0.26100.7019</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 17:39:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-11-media-creation-tool-6838.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-11-media-creation-tool-6838.html
</guid><description>
Windows 11 Media Creation Tool (also known as Create Windows 11 Installation Media) is a free tool from Microsoft and is less than 10MB in size. Windows 11 Media Creation Tool allows users to easily download Windows 11 ISOs directly from Microsoft without a product key. You can use it to clean install or upgrade to Windows 11.
Windows 11 Media Creation Tool can also be used to upgrade your existing PC to Windows 11 or to create a USB or DVD and install Windows 11 on another PC. The tool...
</description></item><item><title>Download OBS Studio 32.0.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 17:38:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-open-broadcaster-software-2451.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-open-broadcaster-software-2451.html
</guid><description>
Open Broadcaster Software is abbreviated as OBS is a program to detect the type of multimedia content to the internet. It is worth noting that a simple interface and the presence of a good tool. You can adjust the quality of the audio and video before starting the broadcast, you can specify the URL, choose the resolution of the screen, etc. With strong desire, videos which you found can be saved to your hard drive.
Open Broadcaster Software - LiveStream on PC
The basic features of Open...
</description></item><item><title>Download XRECODE3 1.173 Final</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 17:35:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xrecode-iii-2915.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xrecode-iii-2915.html
</guid><description>
"Xrecode II" is the switch and grab the audio allows you to convert from mp2, mp3, ac3, aiff, wma, amr, ogg, ape, flac, cue, mpc, wv, tak, mid, cue, m4b, tta, wav, dts , wav (rf64), m4a, mp4, ra, shn, rm, avi, aac, mpg, vob, mka, mkv, flv, Mov, swf, ofr, divx, wmv, spx, mp3, m4v, 3gp, m2v, 3g2, m4v, m2ts, ts, adts, tak, xm, mod, it, s3m, alac, umx, mtm, mlp to m4a, ape, flac, mp4 (using NeroAAC), raw, ogg, wav, wav (rf64) , wma, mpc, WavPack, mp2, ofr, Speex, ac3, tak, aiff, snd, Shorten...
</description></item><item><title>Download Advanced Installer Architect 23.2.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 17:35:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-installer-128.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-installer-128.html
</guid><description>
Advanced Installer is a Windows utility designed to help you build the package Windows Installer in a working environment clean and intuitive.
Although it has many parameters dedicated but the user interface is very simple and gives users the ability to create new projects by selecting the type, namely installer (for example: application Visual Studio or .NET, pack 32/64-bit mixture), Java , updates, support, mobile devices, and other things.
Advanced Installer - An environment for...
</description></item><item><title>Download Intel Wireless Bluetooth Driver (Windows 10/11) 23.170.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 17:34:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intel-wireless-bluetooth-driver-5952.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intel-wireless-bluetooth-driver-5952.html
</guid><description>
Intel Wireless Bluetooth Driver is recommended for users, including family users and business customers with Intel Wireless Bluetooth technology.
Note: When you update the wireless application suite software package, it may not update the wireless controller controller if it includes the same driver as the previous release.
The internal products include:
	Intel 速 Dual Band Wireless-AC 3165
	Intel 速 Dual Band Wireless-AC 3168
	Intel 速 Dual Band Wireless-AC 7265
	Intel 速 Dual Band...
</description></item><item><title>Download Astute Graphics Plug-ins Elite Bundle 4.4.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 17:34:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-astute-graphics-plug-ins-elite-bundle-5523.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-astute-graphics-plug-ins-elite-bundle-5523.html
</guid><description>
Astute Graphics Plug-ins Elite Bundle is a set of graphics editing tools for Adobe Illustrator. It includes many unique tools like Phantasm, VectorScribe, WidthScribe and many others. Get the complete set of plug-ins and transform your workflow in Illustrator. Add speed, ease, and precision with all our plug-ins and become the Astute Graphics Plug-in Elite Package!
Astute Graphics Plug-ins Elite Bundle Features:
	Correct alignment + selection
	Sketching visual vector
	Instantly...
</description></item><item><title>Download mIRC 7.82</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 17:33:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mirc-756.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mirc-756.html
</guid><description>
mIRC is a client application used to communicate, share, play or work with others on IRC networks around the world. The software interface is practical, clean, highly configurable and supports features such as friends lists, file transfer, connect to multiple servers, IPv6, SSL encryption, proxy support, display UTF-8, UPnP, custom sound, spoken message, notification tray , logs messages, and more.
mIRC - Chat, chat online
mIRC also has a language powerful script can be used both to...
</description></item><item><title>Download OCCT 15.0.5.99</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 17:32:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-occt-perestroika-1680.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-occt-perestroika-1680.html
</guid><description>
OCCT is a free application designed to benchmark and overclock system components. Test tool OverClock includes 4 different tests to assess the stability of your computer. CPU and CPU: Linpack to test the processor, GPU: 3D to check stability of the graphics processor and power supply combination of CPU: Linpack and GPU: 3D to download power of you up to the maximum.
OCCT - Measuring system components
The features of OCCT
	Support is enabled for a maximum of 16 cores.
	All the tests...
</description></item><item><title>Download Hot Door CADtools 2026 v30.0.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 17:32:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hot-door-cadtools-5031.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hot-door-cadtools-5031.html
</guid><description>
Hot Door CADtools is a plug-in add features to Illustrator, the program will add 92 drawing tools, editing, labeling, sizing, conversion, create, and utilities are organized in 10 groups tool in the tool palette in Adobe Illustrator. New tools recently added include: Scale, Line, Repeat, Repeat Along the Path, Scaled Type, Grid, and Wave tools.
The main features of Hot Door CADtools
	Improved table and tools
	Preview label and size
	Compression table by hiding the parts you don't...
</description></item><item><title>Download EverNote 10.160.4.39297</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 17:31:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-evernote-3261.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-evernote-3261.html
</guid><description>
EverNote is the all in one tool allows you to track notes, todo items, memos, outlines, excerpts, websites, ideas and other things and automatically synchronize them between multiple computers and mobile devices (iPhone, Android, etc.). You can choose to sort their notes into categories, password protect them, export them to XML and more. EverNote supports a number of pattern notes allow you to add to-do list, spreadsheet like Excel to calculate costs (automatic sum), notes, phone, contact...
</description></item><item><title>Download IPSwitcher 4.5.0.35</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 17:31:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ipswitcher-9317.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ipswitcher-9317.html
</guid><description>
IPSwitcher is a free software that allows users to switch between different IP addresses or network configurations on the device of a PC. The purpose of IPSwitcher is to make it easy and simple to configure your IP settings for IPv4 and IPv6 with Internet Explorer proxy settings.
Features of IPSwitcher
	The IP adapter allows you to change your network settings to make them work properly.
	This free IP changer allows you to save different network profiles, so you can activate them...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tor Browser 15.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 17:30:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tor-browser-1833.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tor-browser-1833.html
</guid><description>
Tor Browser also has full name is Tor Browser Bundle is a web browser give you ability to access the internet safety and security your personal information as well as sensitive documents absolutely. By Tor Browser Bundle will automatically change the IP address on the machine to hide the identity when surfing the web. Tor Browser is free web browser full-featured basic and advanced allows you to leverage the Tor network anonymously without need to make any configuration changes or install...
</description></item><item><title>Download Secure Eraser Pro 7.006</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 17:29:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secure-eraser-1003.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secure-eraser-1003.html
</guid><description>
Secure Eraser is a software to delete data permanently on the folder of the hard drive to data can not be recovered by any software. Secure Eraser is software delete data completely best. The software has simple interface and very small capacity. In addition, the software Secure Eraser also helps to tidy and clean the system, prevent the fragmentation of the hard drive.
Secure Eraser - Tool To Delete Data Permanently
Secure Eraser supports 4 standard delete data (US DoD 5220,22-ME, US...
</description></item><item><title>Download Stardock Start11 2.5.6.3</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 17:29:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stardock-start11-7029.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stardock-start11-7029.html
</guid><description>
Start11 is an application capable of customizing the Start Menu and Taskbar on Windows 11 and Windows 10. This is an application that allows users to customize Windows 11 to suit their preferences. his personal. Start11 will help you bring the new Start Menu of Windows 11 to Windows 10. And vice versa, Start11 also helps you to bring the Start Menu of Windows 10 to Windows 11.
Start11 also helps users bring some functions of Windows 10 to Windows 11 through customizing the Taskbar such...
</description></item><item><title>Download Opera One 123.0.5669.23</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 17:28:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-972.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-972.html
</guid><description>
Opera is a fast, safe, configurable and compliant intranet web browser, which includes both the reader and the application. The Opera browser supports web browsing, listening to music, watching high speed movies, you can open many tabs on the Opera without affecting your browsing speed. Opera now supports almost all devices and operating systems such as windows, IOS, Android, linux, MacOS ...
Opera is a beautiful interface and many interesting features, operating on both PCs and mobile,...
</description></item><item><title>Download WSCC Windows System Control Center 10.0.1.2 Commercial</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 17:28:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wscc-windows-system-control-center-1599.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wscc-windows-system-control-center-1599.html
</guid><description>
WSCC Windows System Control Center can automatically install and update the add-ons are supported. Alternatively, WSCC can use the http protocol to download and run the program. WSCC is portable device, no installation required. Extract content of zip archive downloaded into any folder on your computer.
The interface is very simple and intuitive, thus allowing any type of user how to find his way, regardless of the experience of their previous with the IT world. Besides, it includes a...
</description></item><item><title>Download Monkeys Audio 11.70</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 17:27:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-monkeys-audio-949.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-monkeys-audio-949.html
</guid><description>
Monkey\'s Audio is software that compresses digital music without loss of quality. Supports high quality WAV files and CD ripping. Monkeys Audio will compress .wav tracks into .ape files to reduce their size without loss of sound quality, decompress .ape, convert files, check file integrity and manage tags.
Unlike traditional methods like MP3 and OGG, which permanently remove quality to save space, Monkey\'s Audio only creates perfect copies with the same sound quality as the originals....
</description></item><item><title>Download ManicTime Pro 2025.3.0.3</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 17:27:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-manictime-18.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-manictime-18.html
</guid><description>
ManicTime is a software automatically collect information about how to use your computer. It records the time of operation of the machine, see the change data in the machine, how much data you share, received on or moved away, what software you use, use at any time
ManicTime allows you to keep up the work of the staff, send progress reports accurately and manage your time better than ever. This type of software can help your business more efficient when it comes to the internal problems...
</description></item><item><title>Download Rename Master 4.00</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 17:26:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rename-master-4524.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rename-master-4524.html
</guid><description>
Rename Master is a powerful application and effectively allow you to easily and quickly rename multiple files just by a click of the mouse. The program can delete, add or replace parts of the filename and also supports renaming files using EXIF tags, and JPEG, MP3 tags, text files, video tag and attribute files.
Rename Master - rename files batch
Neat interface, smart arrangement
Rename Master includes a feature arranged smartly will help you keep your files in order. Unicode support...
</description></item><item><title>Download Arsenal Image Mounter Professional 3.12.331</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 17:25:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-arsenal-image-mounter-professional-4881.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-arsenal-image-mounter-professional-4881.html
</guid><description>
Arsenal Image Mounter Professional version is the most professional help to mount the contents of disk images as complete disc in Windows. As far as Windows are concerned, the contents of the disk image is mounted by it's SCSI disks a reality. The SCSI disks the allows users to benefit from features dedicated to disk as integrated with The disk management, launch the virtual machine (and then skip authentication Windows) management, the drive is protected by BitLocker, mounting the Copies,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Revo Registry Cleaner Free 2.0.2 + Portable</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 17:25:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-revo-registry-cleaner-free-12717.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-revo-registry-cleaner-free-12717.html
</guid><description>
Revo Registry Cleaner Free is a powerful tool designed to clean, tune and optimize the Windows Registry. Explore the powerful Registry Cleaner with over 15 scanning categories to find and remove invalid and unnecessary Registry entries. Customize your cleaning routine with custom key inclusions/exclusions and 4 different deep scan modes.
In addition, it also supports custom backups for user-specified keys as well as full Registry backups providing peace of mind as they ensure the safety...
</description></item><item><title>Download Subtitle Edit 4.0.14</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 17:24:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-subtitle-edit-2177.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-subtitle-edit-2177.html
</guid><description>
Subtitle Edit is software can both create new and edit captions already on your hard drive and added videos. The program will give the user a set of tools reliable and of high quality. If you believe that the author of the development and simply reviews on the Internet, then that is a large number of useful tools can distinguish this product with other similar substances, also provides the ability to overlay subtitles on the video. With Subtitle Edit you can easily configure caption,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Parallels Toolbox Business Edition 7.1.1.4366</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 17:24:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-parallels-toolbox-7787.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-parallels-toolbox-7787.html
</guid><description>
Parallels Toolbox is Parallels' all-in-one solution with over 40 tools for Windows. These applications are accessible on the same user interface, including tools for compressing and decompressing software packages, recording screen or audio content, taking screenshots, etc... Designed for creative individuals, students, small business owners, seasoned multi-taskers, IT managers and everyone in between. Parallels Toolbox allows anyone to get the most out of their Windows machine without...
</description></item><item><title>Download Playnite 10.42</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 17:23:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-playnite-6972.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-playnite-6972.html
</guid><description>
Playnite is an open-source video game library manager and manager with support for third-party libraries such as Steam, GOG, Origin, Battle.net and Uplay. Includes supporting the game, providing a unified interface for your game. With Playnite, you can comfortably enter the game from Steam, Battle.net, Origin, GOG and Uplay services, including uninstalled games.
You have three options to view when using Playnite. You also have the custom game option or add any game or program with...
</description></item><item><title>Download HeavyM Pro Plus 2.14.3</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 17:22:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-heavym-enterprise-6963.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-heavym-enterprise-6963.html
</guid><description>
HeavyM is a tool designed for projection mapping with its ease of use and simplicity. HeavyM will turn your bright ideas into outstanding visual experiences with the largest and most complete library of visual effects on the market. There are over 1000 potential combinations, leaving endless space to customize your projection mapping. All the tests and changes you make are live. No render time to break the creativity.
HeavyM has created all the creative tools you need to bring your maps...
</description></item></channel></rss>