<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:01:21 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:01:21 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download NanaZip 6.0.1632.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 20 Feb 2026 17:24:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nanazip-8074.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nanazip-8074.html
</guid><description>
NanaZip is an open source file archiver for the modern Windows experience, forked from the source code of the popular open source file archiver 7-Zip. NanaZip is considered an interesting alternative to WinRAR and WinZip. According to tests, NanaZip provides about 10% better compression ratio than WinRAR and WinZip.
Supported formats:
	Packing/unpacking: 7Z, ZIP, XZ, BZIP2, GZIP, TAR and WIM.
	Extract: RAR, AR, ARJ, CAB, CHM, CPIO, CramFS, DMG, EXT, FAT, GPT, HFS, IHEX, ISO, LZH,...
</description></item><item><title>Download DesktopImages3D 2.55</title><pubDate> Fri, 20 Feb 2026 17:23:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopimages3d-7387.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopimages3d-7387.html
</guid><description>
DesktopImages3D is a desktop 3D visualization tool for MS Windows that is great for displaying images in an interlaced and creative way! Basic functions: total transparency, size settings, fonts, as well as a selection of different 3D themes are available and can be customized.
Features of DesktopImages3D
	3D box's optional transparency
	Several themes to display images
	Resizable
	Fixed position on screen
	Freely selectable position on screen.
</description></item><item><title>Download AVS Video Editor 26.0.2.17</title><pubDate> Fri, 20 Feb 2026 17:22:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs-video-editor-426.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs-video-editor-426.html
</guid><description>
AVS Video Editor is software professional video editing for windows with full features useful, easy-to-use.  When using AVS Video Editor you can record a video, to impose various effects, create and burn DVD, export movies to various video formats, convert video to iPod, PSP, mobile phones and the other portable device.
Features AVS Video Editor
Format support
	AVS Video Editor supports all major video formats. Edit and save the video file in the codec AVI, VOB, MP4, DVD, WMV, 3GP,...
</description></item><item><title>Download reaConverter Pro 8.0.199</title><pubDate> Fri, 20 Feb 2026 17:21:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html
</guid><description>
reaConverter Pro is software image processing feature with batch conversion and image editing periodically becomes simple. eaConverter also provide command line utilities allow you to process images automatically, thus helping you shorten the time for other work.
reaConverter Pro integrated powerful tool of Uber with many great features. It provides advanced solutions to process and adjust images. Management of the conversion process the base image with the latest version of...
</description></item><item><title>Download AVS Video ReMaker 26.0.2.17</title><pubDate> Fri, 20 Feb 2026 17:21:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs-video-remaker-1196.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs-video-remaker-1196.html
</guid><description>
AVS Video ReMaker is software that support quick editing of video files without reducing the video quality. Detection algorithm scenes used in AVS Video ReMaker will save time when processing video images and split it into the set. So, no need to preview every frame of the video file to find the transitions manually. With the help of AVS Video ReMaker, you can delete the unwanted parts and TV commercials from video files or file format DVD, recorded by various cameras, various video...
</description></item><item><title>Download SanDisk Acronis True Image for SanDisk 30.0.1.42679</title><pubDate> Fri, 20 Feb 2026 17:20:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sandisk-acronis-true-image-for-sandisk-13756.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sandisk-acronis-true-image-for-sandisk-13756.html
</guid><description>
Acronis True Image for SanDisk is a specialized version of Acronis True Image backup and disk cloning software designed specifically for SanDisk and Western Digital devices. It offers comprehensive features including disk cloning, full system backup, application and settings backup, ransomware protection, and easy recovery of lost or deleted files. This software allows users to protect their operating system, applications, settings, and data and restore their system in the event of data...
</description></item><item><title>Download Luminar Neo 1.26.1 (16487)</title><pubDate> Fri, 20 Feb 2026 17:20:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-luminar-neoo-7194.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-luminar-neoo-7194.html
</guid><description>
Luminar Neo is an innovative image editor powered by futuristic AI technologies that simplifies complex editing workflows and allows creators to turn their boldest ideas into reality. Luminar Neo calculates image depth and generates 3D maps, allowing you to naturally scatter light in 3D across a 2D image. This opens the door to unleash your creativity to bring your artistic vision to life.
MaskAI automates the masking process by identifying objects in the image and creating the correct...
</description></item><item><title>Download Google Drive (Backup and Sync) 121.0.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 20 Feb 2026 17:18:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-drive-6751.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-drive-6751.html
</guid><description>
Using Google Drive is a great way to store your files safely in secure data centers, where your files will not be lost. Even if your computer, phone or tablet is broken, the files you store in the Google Drive are safe. Download photos, videos, documents, and other files that are important to you up to Google Drive. Continue with the memory up to 15GB. Free. Google Drive helps you access your file faster by recognizing the objects in your image and text in the scanned documents.
Easy to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Lightroom 9.2 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Fri, 20 Feb 2026 17:18:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-photoshop-lightroom-0008-5334.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-photoshop-lightroom-0008-5334.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Photoshop Lightroom is the most professional version completely redesigned and based on a performance architecture that is better responsive to ever expanding galleries, while also featuring unrivaled processing tools with noise reduction and sharpening tools to get the best picture quality. Adobe Photoshop Lightroom gives the basic ideas of software produced by Adobe in 2002, as one of the developers and gradually improving and the features of the ImageReady software are included.
...
</description></item><item><title>Download Calibre 9.3.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 20 Feb 2026 17:16:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-calibre-1669.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-calibre-1669.html
</guid><description>
Calibre  is an eBook library management application that allows you to manage your eBook collection, convert eBooks between different formats, Sync with popular e-reading devices and read your e-books with included viewer. You can sort books by author, title, date and other details, download meta information and book covers, add personalized tags and comments, and view your images in the cover display.
Collection of essential tools for adding metadata editing books or managing your...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube Downloader 3.9.18 (1902)</title><pubDate> Fri, 20 Feb 2026 17:15:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube Downloader  is a dedicated software that helps users  downloading youtube videos  Favorites on PC for offline viewing. With MediaHuman YouTube  Downloader  you can download videos from youtube website to your computer with  fast speed , with special software development technology that automatically receives videos from Websites, in addition to the ability to download videos from software websites, can convert downloaded video formats to various formats for the purpose...
</description></item><item><title>Download AVS4YOU Software AIO Installation Package 26.0.2.17</title><pubDate> Fri, 20 Feb 2026 17:14:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs4you-software-aio-installation-package-1200.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs4you-software-aio-installation-package-1200.html
</guid><description>
AVS4YOU Software AIO Installation Package is the package includes programs to work with video, audio, graphics, documents, and system cleaning. You can install as a complete package, or separate. Which program are presented: AVS Video Editor, AVS Video Converter, AVS Video ReMaker, AVS Media Player, AVS Audio Editor, AVS Audio Converter, AVS Disc Converter, AVS Image Converter, AVS Document Converter, AVS Registry Cleaner.
AVS4YOU Software AIO Installation Package - Full set of tools,...
</description></item><item><title>Download IsMyHdOK 4.48</title><pubDate> Fri, 20 Feb 2026 17:14:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ismyhdok-3225.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ismyhdok-3225.html
</guid><description>
IsMyHdOK is a small program but effective solution to easily check the performance of the volume of Windows, ex. Septum! There are many similar programs, but feel free and check free, start program IsMyHdOK. The first time you use, the program will show you screen license. Free program and license info is only displayed the first time (on each PC). Please select the Drive and Test Time and then the Start button!
IsMyHdOK - Check performance Windows
IsMyHdOK is not installed and can be...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cyberduck 9.4.0.44341</title><pubDate> Fri, 20 Feb 2026 17:13:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberduck-2637.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberduck-2637.html
</guid><description>
Cyberduck is a browser, file open-source and the client transferred to the hosting account FTP, SFTP, WebDAV, Cloud Files, Google Docs and Amazon S3. In addition to file transfers it offers features account management includes installing ACL, version group S3 configuration, Akamai and CloudFront, and more.
In addition, the Cyberduck also helps you can create bookmarks to quickly access favorite locations, edit files remotely using the editor you choose, import bookmarks from popular...
</description></item><item><title>Download Resolume Arena 7.24.2 rev 62935</title><pubDate> Fri, 20 Feb 2026 17:12:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-resolume-arena-001-760.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-resolume-arena-001-760.html
</guid><description>
Resolume Arena is software Visual Jockey for DJ help adjust, mix and match image combination screen displayed directly. Software control it from the lighting and synchronize with the DJ via SMPTE time code. Adjust the ratio and position of the clip to suit your needs. Apply effects to change the powerful interface of the video. Everything running on the card screen so you get fast performance and good image quality as possible.
Resolume Arena - software Visual Jockey for DJ
Features of...
</description></item><item><title>Download QOwnNotes 26.2.7</title><pubDate> Fri, 20 Feb 2026 17:12:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qownnotes-3178.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qownnotes-3178.html
</guid><description>
QOwnNotes is notes bookmark file simple text (GPL) open source application for GNU / Linux , Mac OS X and Windows of Patrizio Bekerle ( pbek on GitHub and IRC) (optional) activity along with the notes application of ownCloud or Nextcloud. QOwnNote store your notes as plain text files and can be synchronized with synchronization function file of ownCloud / Nextcloud. You can also use other apps like Syncthing or Dropbox . Just write out your thoughts as they appear, and edit them if...
</description></item><item><title>Download ExifTool 13.51</title><pubDate> Fri, 20 Feb 2026 17:11:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-exiftool-1685.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-exiftool-1685.html
</guid><description>
ExifTool is a library of Perl platform-independent plus a command line application for reading, writing, and editing meta information in various file types. ExifTool supports many metadata formats including EXIF , GPS , IPTC , XMP , JFIF , GeoTIFF , ICC Profile , Photoshop IRB , FlashPix , AFCP and ID3 , as well as notes of the manufacturer of many digital cameras by Canon , Casio , DJI , FLIR , FujiFilm , GE , GoPro , HP , JVC / Victor , Kodak , Leaf , Minolta / Konica-Minolta , Motorola...
</description></item><item><title>Download AntiPlagiarism.NET 4.155</title><pubDate> Fri, 20 Feb 2026 17:11:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-antiplagiarismnet-2457.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-antiplagiarismnet-2457.html
</guid><description>
AntiPlagiarism NET is software to check the originality of some given text, most people find a section of text on the Internet, often the search engines quickly put out the answer to this question. Sometimes the results can be wrong, because not all results are accurate, a hundred percent. Fortunately, there are other solutions to the problem, for example, AntiPlagiarism.NET it can help you determine the originality of some given text. Application to operate correctly, you need to install...
</description></item><item><title>Download NetSpot Unlimited Enterprise 5.1.0.707</title><pubDate> Fri, 20 Feb 2026 17:10:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-netspot-unlimited-enterprise-3952.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-netspot-unlimited-enterprise-3952.html
</guid><description>
NetSpot Unlimited Enterprise is a professional application only to the site survey, wireless, Wi-Fi and troubleshooting on Mac OS X and Windows. It is a analysis, FREE Wi-Fi. No need to be an expert network to improve the Wi-Fi at home or your office today! All you need is your MacBook running Mac OS X 10.10+, or any laptop with Windows 7/8/10 and NetSpot Unlimited Enterprise that operates on any 802.11 network.
NetSpot Unlimited Enterprise - Wifi network analysis
When working on a...
</description></item><item><title>Download AVS Audio Converter 26.0.2.17</title><pubDate> Fri, 20 Feb 2026 17:09:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs-audio-converter-1195.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs-audio-converter-1195.html
</guid><description>
AVS Audio Converter is a program that convert audio files from this format to other formats support many different formats. Support converting WAV, OGG Vorbis, MP3, MP2, Microsoft ADPCM, WMA, VOX, AAC, M4A, AMR and other audio formats. Before transition, the program determines the frequency, number of channels and other parameters of audio files. In addition, the AVS Audio Converter allows you to make settings for the format MP3 and OGG formats when converting audio files and change the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Brave Browser 1.87.190</title><pubDate> Fri, 20 Feb 2026 17:03:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-brave-browser-2874.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-brave-browser-2874.html
</guid><description>
Brave Browser is a browser based on Chromium, the basic principle is that operation fast and privacy of users. The program can block pop-up windows and other ads, plus it blocked the mechanism for monitoring the online activities of your. Therefore, you can purchase and safely browse the website you are interested in without having to worry about the fact that your activity will be monitored and then you will be shown the necessary advertising or service provider of parties...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter 3.9.18 (1902)</title><pubDate> Fri, 20 Feb 2026 17:02:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-to-mp3-converter-1744.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-to-mp3-converter-1744.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter is the software support download youtube video and convert video to mp3 format fast and most simple. MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter allows you download and convert videos from YouTube and other websites to MP3 format by pasting the YouTube URL into the application. When you paste the URL, the program will display thumbnails for videos and you have the option to customize the title information, artist and album before you begin the process of...
</description></item><item><title>Download FastFlix 6.1.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 20 Feb 2026 17:02:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fastflix-10169.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fastflix-10169.html
</guid><description>
FastFlix is a simple and user-friendly GUI for video encoding. The application has a user-friendly GUI that includes all the necessary tools and configuration options for video encoding. FastFlix provides support for a variety of formats, including MP4, MKV, MOV, M4V, AVI, DIVX, WebM, MPG, MP2, MPEG, OGG, MOV, M4P, FLV, and more. HEVC and YUV videos are also among the compatible formats.
You can choose the output format through a simple drop-down menu in the main window. FastFlix can...
</description></item><item><title>Download AVS Audio Editor 26.0.2.17</title><pubDate> Fri, 20 Feb 2026 17:01:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs-audio-editor-1194.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs-audio-editor-1194.html
</guid><description>
AVS Audio Editor is editor audio professional allows you to edit, record and encode music. The program has more than 20 effects and filters built in, including delay, flanger, chorus, reverb, filters to remove irritating sounds such as "vuvuzelas", new sound effects, strange, unique.
AVS Audio Editor - audio editing
Features of AVS Audio Editor
Save to all major formats
	Edit and save audio files into MP3, FLAC, WAV, M4A, WMA, AAC, MP2, AMR, OGG and other files with the help of AVS...
</description></item><item><title>Download Trillian 6.6 Build 13</title><pubDate> Fri, 20 Feb 2026 17:00:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-trillian-2638.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-trillian-2638.html
</guid><description>
Trillian is the chat help you sign in to more the registered name of a certain service or you can log on at the same time many services in a working window. It integrates multiple services such as Yahoo! MSN, IRC, AIM and ICQ. In addition, you can manage Email accounts, Facebook and Twitter friends - all in just one application.
Login is easy; just click on the network or the appropriate website and log in as normal. Trillian requires access your data (accepted) and post to friends...
</description></item></channel></rss>