<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 09:05:22 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 09:05:22 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download MuseScore 4.6.3 + Portable</title><pubDate> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 00:33:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musescore-2857.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musescore-2857.html
</guid><description>
MuseScore is the tool score for Windows, macOS and Linux, can compare with Finale and Sibelius, support multiple file formats and input methods. It is released as free software and open source under The GNU general public License.
MuseScore - The application composer
Features of MuseScore
	Design WYSIWYG, notes are entered on a "virtual notice"
	TrueType fonts for printing and display allows split ratio high quality for all sizes
	Enter notes easily and quickly
	Many editing...
</description></item><item><title>Download IObit Uninstaller Pro 15.1.0.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 00:32:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iobit-uninstaller-pro-339.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iobit-uninstaller-pro-339.html
</guid><description>
IObit Uninstaller Pro is software to delete programs not needed easily even when Windows "Remove Programs" operation not successful. IObit Uninstaller Pro will uninstall the app Windows, browser toolbars, software packages and plug-ins added. It comes with a scan function is powerful and a tool, Force Uninstall, both of which help to easily and completely remove the app stubborn, and the excess useless, to release more disk space.
With IObit Uninstaller Pro you will have peace of mind...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cubase Pro 14.0.40</title><pubDate> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 00:32:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-steinberg-cubase-pro-3528.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-steinberg-cubase-pro-3528.html
</guid><description>
Steinberg Cubase Pro - The highest and most professional from the publisher Steinberg. Current program Steinberg Cubase Pro is priced near$ 600. But we will provide versions completely free for you. Can you might also like more simple versions, you can download version Cubase Elements at our website.
Steinberg Cubase Pro - music Production professional
Steinberg Cubase Pro is one of the pack music creation software, the most powerful in the world. With a variety of tools, unparalleled...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ashampoo Photo Commander 19.0.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 00:31:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-photo-commander-273.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-photo-commander-273.html
</guid><description>
Ashampoo Photo Commander software brings user photo management tool effectively cover view, sort, edit, convert photos and images to the web. Ashampoo Photo Commander 16 will surprise you immediately! Interface modern user will quickly learn the features of your favorite and adjust accordingly for faster access. The slideshow images appear in the mode 4K stunning and the panoramic feature will steals the show.
Ashampoo Photo Commander - photo editing
Software Ashampoo Photo Commander...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ashampoo Privacy Inspector 3.00.10</title><pubDate> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 00:30:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-privacy-inspector-8733.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-privacy-inspector-8733.html
</guid><description>
Windows keeps extensive records of what you do and when you do it on your PC (offline and online). So what is logged and more importantly, what can you do about it? Ashampoo Privacy Inspector lifts the veil of secrecy and shows you exactly what activities are logged along with the ability to erase your data and regain your privacy.
Features of Ashampoo Privacy Inspector
	See used objects neatly organized
	Delete confidential usage data securely
	Analysis of browsing behavior for all...
</description></item><item><title>Download iTubeGo YouTube Downloader 10.9.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 00:30:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-itubego-youtube-downloader-3681.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-itubego-youtube-downloader-3681.html
</guid><description>
iTubeGo YouTube Downloader  is the best way to download live video from 1000+ streaming sites. iTubeGo YouTube Downloader is a powerful download tool that allows you to save video and audio for free. The output format of high speed converter is high quality MP4, MP3. Fully compatible with iPhone, iPad, iTunes, iMovie, Android Phone and more.
iTubeGo YouTube Downloader - Solution for downloading high quality Youtube video 
Features of iTubeGo YouTube Downloader
	Download videos from...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube Downloader 3.9.17 (2110)</title><pubDate> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 00:29:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube Downloader  is a dedicated software that helps users  downloading youtube videos  Favorites on PC for offline viewing. With MediaHuman YouTube  Downloader  you can download videos from youtube website to your computer with  fast speed , with special software development technology that automatically receives videos from Websites, in addition to the ability to download videos from software websites, can convert downloaded video formats to various formats for the purpose...
</description></item><item><title>Download Steinberg Nuendo 14.0.40</title><pubDate> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 00:29:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-steinberg-nuendo-7928.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-steinberg-nuendo-7928.html
</guid><description>
As the most advanced audio post-production solution available, Nuendo is the choice of professionals in the motion picture, television, game and immersive sound industries. all around the world. Since its initial release, Nuendo has been an important tool in creating the soundtracks for many well-known works, productions and settings.
Regular updates with new features, workflow improvements, and additional, user-requested functions mean that the Nuendo is constantly exceeding the...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Saver Pro 10.9.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 00:28:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-saver-6830.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-saver-6830.html
</guid><description>
YT Saver is a software that supports downloading Video, Audio, Playlist from 10,000+ websites, Convert Video to MP4, MOV, AAC, WAV and more. YT Saver is a powerful downloader that allows you to save video and audio for free. The output format of the high-speed converter is high-quality MP4, MP3. Fully compatible with iPhone, iPad, iTunes, iMovie, Android Phone and more.
Supported Input Formats:
	Video: MP4, M4V, 3GP, MPEG, DAT, AVI, ASF, WMV, VOB, MKV, FLV, 3GS, 3G2, F4V, WEBM, TS,...
</description></item><item><title>Download CopyQ 13.0.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 00:28:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-copyq-1368.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-copyq-1368.html
</guid><description>
CopyQ is software clipboard manager for windows that helps you easily copy, save, text, clipboard. CopyQ absolutely free on taiwebs.com it allows you to save more than one default entry to the clipboard is limited to Windows. Each time you copy or cut something, it will be saved to the clipboard expansion of CopyQ , both files and text can all be saved.
CopyQ - clipboard Manager
Features of CopyQ
	Support for Linux, Windows and OS X 10.9+
	Store text, HTML, image or any customized...
</description></item><item><title>Download iDownerGo 10.9.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 00:27:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idownergo-12439.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idownergo-12439.html
</guid><description>
iDownerGo is the best tool that allows users to download videos, music and playlists from more than 10,000 streaming sites. It can easily convert videos to MP4, MOV, MKV, 3GP, AAC, WAV, FLAC and other formats on PC and Mac. With this amazing program, users can enjoy their favorite media content without restrictions.
iDownerGo Features
	Download any video up to 8K resolution
	Download 1080p videos online from over 10,000 popular streaming sites easily.
	Save any video in various...
</description></item><item><title>Download PHP 8.4.14</title><pubDate> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 00:27:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-php-1878.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-php-1878.html
</guid><description>
PHP (abbreviation regression: "P... Hypertext Preprocessor", "Personal Home Page") is a programming language script or a kind of code primarily used to develop the application write for server, open source, used for general purposes. It is very suitable with the web and can easily embed into your HTML. Due to be optimized for web applications, speed fast, compact syntax like C and Java, easy to learn and time building the product is relatively shorter compared to other languages, so PHP...
</description></item><item><title>Download The Dude 7.20.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 00:26:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-the-dude-3238.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-the-dude-3238.html
</guid><description>
The Dude is a new application by MikroTik which can dramatically improve the way you manage your network environment. It will automatically scan all devices in the subnet is specified, draw and layout a map of your networks, monitor services of your devices and alert you in case some service has problems.is a new application by MikroTik which can dramatically improve the way you manage your network environment. It will automatically scan all devices in the subnet is specified, draw and...
</description></item><item><title>Download PPTube 10.9.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 00:25:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pptube-12556.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pptube-12556.html
</guid><description>
PPTube Video Downloader allows you to download HD videos easily, from 720p, 1080p, 2K, 4K and 8K. You can save multiple videos at the same time. Just copy multiple video URLs from various websites and paste them into PPTube Downloader, then you can download multiple videos in seconds.
In addition, you can download HD videos from Instagram, TikTok, Facebook, Apple Music, Vimeo, adult websites, etc. and convert them to MP4, MP3, MOV, AAC and more than 20 other output formats. PPTube...
</description></item><item><title>Download Office 2013-2024 C2R Install v7.7.7.7 r27 + Lite Version</title><pubDate> Wed, 22 Oct 2025 16:05:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-2013-2019-c2r-install-5531.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-2013-2019-c2r-install-5531.html
</guid><description>
Office 2013-2024 Install is an online installer for Microsoft Office 2019, Microsoft Office 2016, or Microsoft Office 2013 on your PC. The advantage of the program is the ability to install individual Office 2016 components, as well as choose the language of the installed Office suite. Office 2013-2024 Install C2R will automatically download and install any component of MS Office 2013/2016/2019 (x86 / x64) with Selectable Languages. And then, with just one click, it will be activated for...
</description></item><item><title>Download Perfectly Clear WorkBench 4.8.0.2870</title><pubDate> Wed, 22 Oct 2025 16:05:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfectly-clear-workbench-6892.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfectly-clear-workbench-6892.html
</guid><description>
Perfectly Clear Workbench is an application that uses image editing libraries Perfectly Clear by Athentech and is provided to demonstrate the capabilities of the Perfectly Clear processing libraries, which recognize faces and allow quick export of processing settings for use.
One of the key features in Workbench is the ability to "export to API" when saving a Preset. This allows you to make image edits in Workbench and adjust the settings to suit your editing style and needs. You can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Office Installer Plus 1.30</title><pubDate> Wed, 22 Oct 2025 16:04:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-installer-plus-11616.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-installer-plus-11616.html
</guid><description>
Office Installer Plus is the next version of Ratiborus that helps you download, install, update, uninstall, activate office 2024, 2021, 2019, 2016 and it has added an Office activator to the program. submit. Office Installer+ is considered a useful application that helps users install and manage office applications from Microsoft Office easily and quickly. This application is designed to help users save time and effort when installing popular office applications such as Word, Excel,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Office Installer by Ratiborus 1.30</title><pubDate> Wed, 22 Oct 2025 16:04:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-installer-11545.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-installer-11545.html
</guid><description>
Office Installer is a software program by Ratiborus used to install Microsoft Office on computers or devices. Office is a productivity suite that includes programs like Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Outlook, and more. The installer ensures that all required Microsoft Office files and components are installed, properly configured, and ready for use on the user's computer.
Office Installer allows users to choose which Office applications they want to install, select the installation location,...
</description></item><item><title>Download InPixio Photo Focus Pro 4.3.8626.22532</title><pubDate> Wed, 22 Oct 2025 16:03:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-inpixio-photo-focus-pro-4292.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-inpixio-photo-focus-pro-4292.html
</guid><description>
InPixio Photo Focus Pro is the perfect tool to help improve the sharpness for the photo! To get sharp images is not always easy, especially with the photos taken spontaneously. InPixio Photo Focus Pro solved this problem in the blink of an eye and create clear, crisp images, high resolution. You can add sharpness, focal length soft and the blurred area on your image. This helps you to highlight more the differences between background and center sharpness of the image.
InPixio Photo...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ant Download Manager Pro 2.16.1 Build 91718</title><pubDate> Wed, 22 Oct 2025 16:02:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ant-download-manager-pro-137.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ant-download-manager-pro-137.html
</guid><description>
Ant Download Manager Pro is software support download has the same features as IDM, even it has many prominent features, more user friendly more and have speed download data incredible. Ant Download Manager is a Internet content downloader quickly with support download at video! Function: fully Integrated with the web browsers most popular: Internet Explorer 8+, Mozilla Firefox 32 +, Google Chrome 31+ and the copies of them (Pale Moon, Opera, Vivaldi, Slimjet, ComodoDragon, etc.). you...
</description></item><item><title>Download EMCO Ping Monitor 9.2.1.6517</title><pubDate> Wed, 22 Oct 2025 16:02:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-emco-ping-monitor-2272.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-emco-ping-monitor-2272.html
</guid><description>
EMCO Ping Monitor is a very powerful utility allows you to monitor network connections, has support to send text messages. After starting the tool will automatically monitor the connection to the server you choose, it can be address locally or any one on the Internet. After the connection is found, you can view the status of the host, ping will be performed at the intervals you set, everything is very simple. If ping does not pass several times in a row, you will be notified...
</description></item><item><title>Download InPixio Photo Maximizer Pro 5.3.8626.22532</title><pubDate> Wed, 22 Oct 2025 16:01:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-inpixio-photo-maximizer-pro-4293.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-inpixio-photo-maximizer-pro-4293.html
</guid><description>
InPixio Photo Maximizer Pro is software that allows you to zoom quickly and easily the specific details you want to make the main focus of the photo, then make adjustments to keep the sharpness and clarity you want. No pixilation, no blurry images, just picture perfect. InPixio Photo Maximizer Pro provides the zoom function powerful can enlarge images up to 1000% and let you know the target size of the image in pixels or centimetres.
InPixio Photo Maximizer Pro - Zoom images
With the 7...
</description></item><item><title>Download VCap Downloader Pro 0.1.39.6773</title><pubDate> Wed, 22 Oct 2025 16:01:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vcap-downloader-pro-8474.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vcap-downloader-pro-8474.html
</guid><description>
VCap Downloader Pro (VCapDL) is a popular piece of software that allows you to record video and audio from websites on the internet. The interface of the software is similar to a normal browser, making it easy for users to get used to and work with this software. User just need to copy video url from favorite browser and convert it to VCap Downloader Pro. It will capture the video and make the quality available for download. You can also extract the audio track from any video and convert...
</description></item><item><title>Download AI Ebook to Audio Converter 1.1.26</title><pubDate> Wed, 22 Oct 2025 16:00:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ai-ebook-to-audio-converter-13863.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ai-ebook-to-audio-converter-13863.html
</guid><description>
AI Ebook to Audio Converter converts your ebooks into high-quality audiobooks with advanced AI voice technology. Convert EPUB, PDF, and TXT files to MP3 audiobooks with natural voices, all while working completely offline with no subscription fees.
Advanced voice technology
	High-quality AI voice synthesis with natural-sounding results
	Voice mixing system - blend multiple voices together to create custom sounds
	Save and load pre-set voice settings for consistent results
	Test voice...
</description></item><item><title>Download Intel Ethernet Adapter Complete Driver Pack 30.5</title><pubDate> Wed, 22 Oct 2025 16:00:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intel-ethernet-adapter-complete-driver-pack-7424.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intel-ethernet-adapter-complete-driver-pack-7424.html
</guid><description>
Intel Ethernet Adapter Complete Driver Pack contains all Intel® Ethernet networking software and drivers for Windows, Linux and FreeBSD versions currently supported for most Intel Ethernet Adapters. Not all Intel Ethernet Adapters and Intel Ethernet Controllers are supported in all versions of Windows, Linux, or FreeBSD.
What's new in this release:
In this point release, NVM Update Package 3.20 has been updated. If you currently have the 3.20 update package installed and are running...
</description></item></channel></rss>