<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 16:08:25 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 16:08:25 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download PDF-XChange Editor Plus 10.8.4.409</title><pubDate> Thu, 26 Feb 2026 18:27:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-xchange-editor-plus-645.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-xchange-editor-plus-645.html
</guid><description>
PDF-XChange Editor Plus is the editor, PDF viewer, compact, fast with many features, add-ons, professional. When using the PDF-XChange Editor Plus, easy for users to create, view, edit, annotate, OCR and digital signing PDF files, plus much more.
PDF-XChange Editor is a PDF editing full-featured. With the help of it, you can edit, fix, add, or delete text easily. Graphics can also be moved, resized or removed.
Features PDF-XChange Editor Plus
Edit documents
	Use a variety of editing...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDF-XChange Pro 10.8.4.409</title><pubDate> Thu, 26 Feb 2026 18:26:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-xchange-editor-pro-3422.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-xchange-editor-pro-3422.html
</guid><description>
PDF-XChange Editor Pro is an application to manipulate and create PDF versatile, offering a wide range of useful features and powerful will help you to easily work with PDF files. This application is very flexible and allows you to easily create and modify PDF files. PDF-XChange Editor Pro provides a powerful set of tools and flexibility to work with PDF files, such as editor PDF-XChange new, utilities series, OFFice2PDF and the Addin tool Bar allows you to easily convert multiple file...
</description></item><item><title>Download AIDA64 Extreme / Engineer 8.25.8200</title><pubDate> Thu, 26 Feb 2026 18:26:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aida64-1297.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aida64-1297.html
</guid><description>
AIDA64 is a powerful tool to identify and test virtually all components of personal computers running operating systems Windows.  AIDA64 give you detailed information on all hardware and software, in addition, with the integrated modules for testing and calibration can be checked more for each subsystem PC individually. Display detailed information about all hardware and software is installed on your system.
AIDA64 Extreme/Engineer
Features AIDA64
	Level information about motherboard...
</description></item><item><title>Download Total Commander 11.57 Beta 1</title><pubDate> Thu, 26 Feb 2026 18:24:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-total-commander-1148.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-total-commander-1148.html
</guid><description>
Total Commander is a file manager popular allows you to perform various actions with any files on the hard drive, work with archives, data, multimedia... Open top is Total Commander has a new user interface is updated with the button in Windows XP, new icons of files, store, button, drive, etc.
Total Commander - file Manager program
Besides, Total Commander has the ability to set different colors for the files and folder background. A editable mode and sync manually when you compare...
</description></item><item><title>Download WavePad Sound Editor Master 24.02</title><pubDate> Thu, 26 Feb 2026 18:23:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wavepad-sound-editor-1149.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wavepad-sound-editor-1149.html
</guid><description>
WavePad Sound Editor is editor software and improve the quality of sound create recordings music best quality. WavePad is mootij in the editor software sound good for the computer are configured midrange and low. Because WavePad very compact only about 4MB of space is you already own the software editor sounds good.
WavePad Sound Editor - Side audio quality
WavePad help you edit audio created the Nightcore quality. WavePad Sound Editor there are many options is very impressive as add...
</description></item><item><title>Download WavePad 24.02</title><pubDate> Thu, 26 Feb 2026 18:22:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wavepad-46.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wavepad-46.html
</guid><description>
WavePad is the sound editor allows you to create and edit recordings and audio files, supports a number of file formats including wav, mp3, vox, gsm, real audio, au, aif and more. It allows you to cut, copy and paste parts of recording and optionally apply effects like echo, amplification and noise reduction. In addition, you can insert silence, fade in / out, auto-trim and more.
WavePad supports sample rates from 6000 to 96000Hz, stereo or mono, 8, 16, or 32 bits. The program also...
</description></item><item><title>Download MixPad Masters Edition 14.01</title><pubDate> Thu, 26 Feb 2026 17:18:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mixpad-masters-edition-505.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mixpad-masters-edition-505.html
</guid><description>
MixPad Masters Edition is software mixing many different songs, mix music files available, or the recording is completed and combine them. MixPad Masters Edition is software recording and mixing music is designed to produce sounds easily. Mix music, vocal and audio, adjust the volume, pan, fade and more with MixPad as your digital mixing your.
MixPad Masters Edition will save the sound under the popular formats such as MP3,WAV, AIF, WMA, VOX, M4A, GSM,... user can create, add and remove...
</description></item><item><title>Download QuickMemoryTestOK 5.33</title><pubDate> Thu, 26 Feb 2026 17:17:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quickmemorytestok-3327.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quickmemorytestok-3327.html
</guid><description>
QuickMemoryTestOK is a free utility to check RAM of your PC. QuickMemoryTestOK will be useful when you buy a PC have 16, 32, 64, 128, etc., RAM GB. For example, for most users, the part of this often never be used or handled. For this reason, should undergo a test to ensure that no area is error in main memory. QuickMemoryTestOK can also be used to check your Windows PC if there is any behavior in high memory that may be the cause of a system error other serious not.
QuickMemoryTestOK -...
</description></item><item><title>Download OpenCloseDriveEject 3.51</title><pubDate> Thu, 26 Feb 2026 17:16:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-openclosedriveeject-4783.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-openclosedriveeject-4783.html
</guid><description>
OpenCloseDriveEject is a small program and effective when it comes to Open, Close, DVD-, CD, Blue-Ray Drive Eject USB and SSD, SD,... unlike other programs that only function part in routine tasks this, you will find everything under one roof, removed the drive safely and open the DVD drive, Blue-Ray will be a regular work and easy as Microsoft has provided for all Windows operating system. Here, you can still open the disk in the drive to set the drive name directly, this can be very...
</description></item><item><title>Download GeoGebra 6.0.916-2</title><pubDate> Thu, 26 Feb 2026 17:15:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-geogebra-992.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-geogebra-992.html
</guid><description>
GeoGebra is software the mathematics on the computer for you to solve problems more quickly and accurately data problem given. GeoGebra supports connect geometry, algebra and elements of mathematics other in an interactive way and tight. Besides, GeoGebra also allows users to directly enter and manipulate mathematical equations and coordinates, and make use of the points, vector, lines, triangles, cones..
GeoGebra - graph the function
GeoGebra is designed for math classes in junior...
</description></item><item><title>Download AndreaMosaic 3.55.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 26 Feb 2026 17:14:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-andreamosaic-1684.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-andreamosaic-1684.html
</guid><description>
AndreaMosaic is a other tool allows you to transform photos into mosaics created from collection of photos of you. The manner of operation of the program is very simple, but it does not always give you the results you are looking for. The user must choose the image collection you want to use to create the mosaic and the photo will be converted on AndreaMosaic.
&amp;nbsp;
AndreaMosaic allows you to configure a number of options, such as width the last of the mosaic, the number of images on...
</description></item><item><title>Download PilotEdit Pro 20.7.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 26 Feb 2026 17:14:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pilotedit-979.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pilotedit-979.html
</guid><description>
PilotEdit is software edit the textfile to help you execute scripts, extract strings and edit large files. PilotEdit is the editing file will help you search and replace multi-line text, edit files, FTP or even download and upload files and folders FTP. With edit file PilotEdit becomes easier.
PilotEdit - edit text files
PilotEdit is a hex-editor and advanced text support opening files larger than 4GB. It provides syntax to customize and highlight keywords, advanced search and replace...
</description></item><item><title>Download LibreWolf 148.0-1</title><pubDate> Thu, 26 Feb 2026 17:12:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-librewolf-11967.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-librewolf-11967.html
</guid><description>
LibreWolf is a customized and independent version of Firefox, with the main goals being user privacy, security and freedom. LibreWolf is designed to provide increased protection against tracking and fingerprinting techniques and includes a number of security enhancements. This is achieved through our security and privacy oriented settings and patches. LibreWolf also aims to remove all telemetry, data collection and annoyances, as well as disable anti-free features like DRM.
LibreWolf...
</description></item><item><title>Download Debut Video Capture Software Pro 12.05</title><pubDate> Thu, 26 Feb 2026 17:11:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-debut-video-capture-software-pro-951.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-debut-video-capture-software-pro-951.html
</guid><description>
Debut Video Capture Software Pro is software record and capture video from any source and features editing video color, resolution, and output settings. Debut Video Capture Software Pro is designed to use very easy and intuitive, giving you the ability to record everything from the video recording from your webcam, screen or video input device such as recorder, VHS in few minutes after download.
Debut Video Capture Software Pro - Recording and video recording
The main features of Debut...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube Downloader 3.9.18 (2502)</title><pubDate> Thu, 26 Feb 2026 17:10:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube Downloader  is a dedicated software that helps users  downloading youtube videos  Favorites on PC for offline viewing. With MediaHuman YouTube  Downloader  you can download videos from youtube website to your computer with  fast speed , with special software development technology that automatically receives videos from Websites, in addition to the ability to download videos from software websites, can convert downloaded video formats to various formats for the purpose...
</description></item><item><title>Download K-Lite Codec Pack Update 19.5.3</title><pubDate> Thu, 26 Feb 2026 17:09:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-update-5145.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-update-5145.html
</guid><description>
K-Lite Codec Pack Update is the update of the set of codecs and related tools. Codec stands for Compressor-decompressor. Codec is necessary to encode and decode (play) audio and video. K-Lite Codec Pack Update is designed as a user-friendly solution with users to play all movie files your. With Codec Pack K-Lite, you can play 99% of all the movies found on your computer. A number of packages codec is not friendly with computers, as they tend to slow down Windows, break down multimedia...
</description></item><item><title>Download Classroom Spy Professional 5.6.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 26 Feb 2026 17:08:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-classroom-spy-professional-916.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-classroom-spy-professional-916.html
</guid><description>
Classroom Spy Professional is a software classroom management effective. Manage and track activities of all the computers of students remotely. Plus, you can share your screen with the activity record of the student, the computer controls for performance, limit the use of the Internet, the application blocks and more.
Classroom Spy Professional - software classroom management
The main features of Classroom Spy Professional
	Display live images of the remote computer.
	You can control...
</description></item><item><title>Download SecretDNS 3.8.6</title><pubDate> Thu, 26 Feb 2026 17:07:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secretdns-12481.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secretdns-12481.html
</guid><description>
SecretDNS provides a quick means to deploy DNS over HTPS, meaning it allows DNS (short for Domain Name Server) resolution to be performed remotely using the HTTPS protocol to encrypts data between the client and the DNS resolver. Its purpose, obviously, is related to data security and user privacy, to prevent unauthorized interception and manipulation of DNS data.
Default DNS settings in SecretDNS use CloudFlare to ensure security. You can change DNS configuration in the dedicated tab...
</description></item><item><title>Download HFS: HTTP File Server (version 3) 3.0.4</title><pubDate> Thu, 26 Feb 2026 17:07:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hfs-http-file-server-11851.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hfs-http-file-server-11851.html
</guid><description>
HFS is a web file server to run on your computer. Share a folder or even a file thanks to the virtual file system. Essentially, this application turns your computer into an HTTP server and all users who want to connect and download files can do so by loading a simple website in their browser. HFS includes many configuration settings, so you can basically change each part of the application, starting with how users download files and ending with the appearance of the created website.
HFS...
</description></item><item><title>Download PhotoPad Image Editor Pro 15.00</title><pubDate> Thu, 26 Feb 2026 17:05:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photopad-image-editor-572.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photopad-image-editor-572.html
</guid><description>
PhotoPad Image Editor is a software to help edit photos and supports lots of features like edit, cut, rotate, resize and flip digital photos. With PhotoPad Image Editor, you can freely perform the basic editing for their images and also can add some neat effect. It has the option to create a photo collage and mosaic images from your photos, and you can also add text and captions. If you prefer, you can complete your masterpiece by adding the frame or contour is simple.
The main features...
</description></item><item><title>Download Zoom Player Max 22.2.0.2220</title><pubDate> Thu, 26 Feb 2026 17:05:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zoom-player-max-104.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zoom-player-max-104.html
</guid><description>
Zoom Player MAX help you to see the film on DVD, Blu-ray, Flash movies and HD format with high quality and the ability to display subtitles in English very well. The advantage of software is that takes up very little system resources to play the movie with quick speed, change the wallpaper options while viewing movies.
Zoom Player MAX is the movies, browse high-quality photos on the computer with the advantages such as compact size, quick start, built-in codec. The application supports...
</description></item><item><title>Download Brave Browser 1.87.191</title><pubDate> Thu, 26 Feb 2026 17:04:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-brave-browser-2874.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-brave-browser-2874.html
</guid><description>
Brave Browser is a browser based on Chromium, the basic principle is that operation fast and privacy of users. The program can block pop-up windows and other ads, plus it blocked the mechanism for monitoring the online activities of your. Therefore, you can purchase and safely browse the website you are interested in without having to worry about the fact that your activity will be monitored and then you will be shown the necessary advertising or service provider of parties...
</description></item><item><title>Download QuickTextPaste 9.41</title><pubDate> Thu, 26 Feb 2026 17:03:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quicktextpaste-2905.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quicktextpaste-2905.html
</guid><description>
QuickTextPaste is a mobile application that allows you to add (paste) the text to be predetermined quickly in any Microsoft Windows program through keyboard shortcuts. You can copy the software on any USB flash drive or other portable device and carry it with you whenever you have to automate the task, paste text messages quickly and easily without having to redo the installation steps.
QuickTextPaste - Create shortcut paste text
Although this app seems geared to users who have more...
</description></item><item><title>Download Vov Music Player 12.3</title><pubDate> Thu, 26 Feb 2026 17:03:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vov-music-player-2512.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vov-music-player-2512.html
</guid><description>
Vov Music Player is a program very easy to use, can play all your favourite music from the desired folder directly from the taskbar. Listening to music is an enjoyable activity, we often do it when sitting in front of computer just to dilute the situation, that is, this is not the main purpose of the in PC. Usually listen to music to as a complement for those moments when you are busy, for example, doing something more interesting, work or play. With this in mind, program Vov Music Player...
</description></item><item><title>Download VovSoft Batch Translator 5.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 26 Feb 2026 17:02:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-batch-translator-6323.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-batch-translator-6323.html
</guid><description>
If you have a web or product that needs translation, it will take time to translate each text by the traditional translation tools. Vovsoft Batch Translator can help you translate multiple texts at once.
VovSoft Batch Translator supports over 50 different languages: Arabic, Basque, Bengali, Bosnian, Bulgarian, Catalan, Chinese (Simplified), Chinese (Traditional), Croatian, Czech, Danish, Dutch, English, Estonian, Finnish, French, German, Greek, Gujarati, Hebrew, Hindi, Hungarian, Irish,...
</description></item></channel></rss>