<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 17:35:44 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 17:35:44 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Wise Care 365 Pro 7.3.1.715</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Sep 2025 17:24:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wise-care-365-pro-106.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wise-care-365-pro-106.html
</guid><description>
Wise Care 365 pro is a package of utilities registry, disk, and other systems important for your PC. Easy to use and effective, Wise Care 365 is the best solution to improve the performance of your computer. Get Wise Care 365 and your computer will never run slow again!
Wise Care 365 pro is what?
Wise Care 365 Pro
	Check PC a clicks
	Pc cleaning &amp;amp; speed up
	Inventory hardware
	Protecting your privacy
	Protect real-time system
	Silent mode
	Boot speed faster
	Freeing up disk...
</description></item><item><title>Download DVDFab 13.0.4.9</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Sep 2025 17:24:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dvdfab-67.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dvdfab-67.html
</guid><description>
DVDFab All-In-One is a multi-purpose combo of nearly all powerful DVDFab products-DVD replication, Ripper DVD, Blu-ray Ripper, Blu-ray Ripper, Copy UHD, Blu-ray to DVD, DVD to Blu-ray Transaction, DVD Creator, Blu-ray Creator, video conversion, Cinavia DVD removal, Windows DVD removal, DRM elimination for Apple, Screen Recorder and Editor for iOS, Hi-Fi Sound and File Transfer. It provides a complete solution to all of your DVD/Blu-ray/video problems and the perfect execution.
DvDFab -...
</description></item><item><title>Download RadioBOSS Ultimate 7.1.5.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Sep 2025 17:23:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-radioboss-advanced-599.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-radioboss-advanced-599.html
</guid><description>
The application programming radio professional, tradition designed for the traditional radio can and is expected to pay thousands of dollars for software is extremely complex and complicated. But if that's not you? If you need a simple, affordable, reliable solution to automating demand your broadcast, RadioBOSS is the solution you've been looking for.
Whether it's building and scheduling programming cross for radio ground or your Internet, create sound atmosphere suitable in restaurant...
</description></item><item><title>Download MAGIX VEGAS Pro 23.0.0.302</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Sep 2025 17:23:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-magix-vegas-pro-81.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-magix-vegas-pro-81.html
</guid><description>
MAGIX VEGAS Pro provides an interface fully customizable brings maximum flexibility. Full of new features, both inside and outside, MAGIX VEGAS Pro create the power for your creativity. Whether you work in HD or 4K, VEGAS Pro willing to become a partner of your creativity. Video / Audio production, and DVD / Blu-ray authoring all in one powerful software package.
FEATURES, CHARACTERISTICS MAGIX VEGAS Pro
VEGAS Pro provides all the tools you need to edit your video quickly. Coding...
</description></item><item><title>Download ZWCAD Professional 2026 v26.10 Build 2025.09.05</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Sep 2025 17:21:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zwcad-5431.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zwcad-5431.html
</guid><description>
ZWCAD is a professional software application that provides a handy set of tools to help users design 2D and 3D drawings. While it is packed with many dedicated parameters, it boasts a clean layout that allows the user to create a new drawing from scratch, using a very useful, step-by-step approach. is for beginners as they are given assistance in the entire process or choosing one of the template files.
Application allows you to choose between imperial or metric units, enlarge or reduce...
</description></item><item><title>Download UniFab 3.0.2.9</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Sep 2025 17:21:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-unifab-10377.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-unifab-10377.html
</guid><description>
UniFab is software to efficiently convert, compress and edit more than 1000 video formats for playback on any device without losing quality. Enlarge video/audio to 1080p/DTS 7.1 and upgrade video to HDR10 or Dolby Vision with AI Enhancer. UniFab Pro provides the best AI-powered zoom tool that allows you to enlarge videos from low resolutions, such as 360p, 480p and 720p, to 1080p without losing any quality. Clearer and sharper image details will bring you an exceptional viewing...
</description></item><item><title>Download Photo Supreme 2025.3.3.8101</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Sep 2025 17:21:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photo-supreme-430.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photo-supreme-430.html
</guid><description>
Photo Supreme is a software product management professional pictures of idimager. With Photo Supreme you can arrange, manage back stock photo archive of yourself and share them with you here and relatives easily via Email or Facebook. Photo Supreme provides users method to sort images effective, logical, as well as edit and share your photos with friends and relatives in the family. Especially the Photo Supreme allows to work with multiple image formats and support mounting support,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tenorshare 4DDiG 10.5.8.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Sep 2025 17:12:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tenorshare-4ddig-pro-5629.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tenorshare-4ddig-pro-5629.html
</guid><description>
Tenorshare 4DDiG is software to recover data from laptop / PC, external drive or USB flash disk. Recover Windows partitions, such as raw partitions, formatted partitions, damaged partitions, etc. Recover lost or deleted photos, videos, audio, videos, documents, etc.
With 4DDiG, you can recover many different types of data from this powerful Windows Data Recovery Tool feature. No matter what you have lost, 4DDiG is capable of recovering deleted files Windows 10 / 8.1 / 8/7 /...
</description></item><item><title>Download XYplorer 28.00.0100</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Sep 2025 17:08:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-533.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-533.html
</guid><description>
XYplorer - File Manager for Windows is software that supports users to manage files on the Window quickly and to arrange the folder tidy. XYplorer features tabbed browsing, search, files, powerful, preview, flexible, highly customizable interface, dual frame options and a variety of unique ways to automate effective tasks often repeat. It's fast, lightweight, and portable.
Features XYplorer
	XYplorer is a file manager mobile. It does not require any settings, store all configuration...
</description></item><item><title>Download Xmanager Power Suite 8.0.0015</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Sep 2025 17:07:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xmanager-power-suite-4036.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xmanager-power-suite-4036.html
</guid><description>
Xmanager Power Suite is the network connection complete. The products include: Xmanager (server, PC X high performance); Xshell (SSH client, strong); Xftp (client-SFTP / FTP); Xlpd (a print management tools work). Xmanager Power Suite is a solution all-in-one includes Xmanager, Xshell, Xftp and Xlpd in a single set. Xmanager run the app window X and Xshell manage servers Unix / Linux remotely with a terminal safety. Xftp transfers files between systems securely, and Xlpd runs in locally...
</description></item><item><title>Download Audio Modeling SWAM Solo Woodwinds 3.10.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Sep 2025 17:02:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-audio-modeling-swam-solo-woodwinds-bundle-10444.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-audio-modeling-swam-solo-woodwinds-bundle-10444.html
</guid><description>
Audio Modeling SWAM Solo Woodwinds Bundle is a collection of sound musical instruments including: Clarinets, Saxophones, Flutes, Double Reeds. These tools are developed using a synergistic combination of innovative performance techniques, physical modeling, behavioral modeling, and multi-vector, phase-synchronized pattern morphing.
It enables composers, musicians and performers to play - both in the recording studio and in live performances - the most realistic and expressive virtual...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mozilla Firefox 143.0.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Sep 2025 17:01:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-firefox-quantum-501.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-firefox-quantum-501.html
</guid><description>
Firefox Quantum is a web browser independently provide the tabbed browsing combined with numerous handy features like pop-up blocker, Bookmarks, direct (integrated RSS), password manager, and more. Functionality can be extended with dozens of plugins available for free (extensions).
Firefox Quantum are interface completely new, beautiful, neat, minimalistic and delicate, eats less RAM to 30% compared with the old version and solve the condition consuming capacity
Firefox can import all...
</description></item><item><title>Download SoftPerfect Network Scanner 25.9</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Sep 2025 17:01:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-softperfect-network-scanner-465.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-softperfect-network-scanner-465.html
</guid><description>
SoftPerfect Network Scanner is software scan ip address fast with many features for the programmer. With SoftPerfect Network Scanner you can completely scan IPv4 / IPv6 universal fast with many options. Program this powerful can ping computers, scan ports, discover the folder is shared and comes with filtering options and flexible display. It can take practically any information about the network device through WMI, SNMP, HTTP, SSH , and PowerShell. In addition, it can scan the remote...
</description></item><item><title>Download MailWasher Pro 7.15.43</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Sep 2025 17:00:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-firetrust-mailwasher-pro-825.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-firetrust-mailwasher-pro-825.html
</guid><description>
MailWasher Pro software is ready to filter all of your email accounts and blocked, remove the spam from the list of email. MailWasher allows you to preview all your email before to your computer or your mobile device, you allows you to read all your email securely, and instantly delete any unwanted emails or suspicious. Email good rest of you is download at PC or mobile devices, to help you not get any virus, spam or any email.
Firetrust MailWasher Pro - Blocker remove spam
The...
</description></item><item><title>Download ezAccounting 3.15.14</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Sep 2025 17:00:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ezaccounting-5300.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ezaccounting-5300.html
</guid><description>
ezAccounting is accounting software designed for the small business: simple, reliable and affordable. ezAccounting is the solution internal accounting suitable for small businesses need to record and report on cash flow in and out including sales, incomes and expenses and purchases. It also supports payroll processing and print tax forms.
The features of ezAccounting
	Company accounts unlimited
	Custom format form
	Custom format Czech
	Support multiple tax code
	Support multiple...
</description></item><item><title>Download Minimal Firewall 2.2.6</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Sep 2025 16:59:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minimal-firewall-13877.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minimal-firewall-13877.html
</guid><description>
Minimal Firewall works in conjunction with Windows Firewall to block all unknown connections by default, prompting you to create application-based rules to mitigate malware, telemetry, and data leaks. Completely eliminate applications that call home without your knowledge. Minimal Firewall provides a more secure and integrated approach by interacting directly with the native Windows Firewall, eliminating the need for risky system modifications.
Core Features
	Lockdown Mode: The core...
</description></item><item><title>Download Biniware Run 7.7.0.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Sep 2025 16:59:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-biniware-run-3095.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-biniware-run-3095.html
</guid><description>
Biniware Run provide you with quick access to links, files and folders page favorite sites from a single place. Just drag and drop any website link, file or folder inside the circle color from the computer to your desk. You can specify the category, move, sort, import, export, or customize the shortcuts at any time.
Biniware Run - app Access faster
Just drag and drop any website link, file or folder in color circle from the computer to your desk, and you can easily access all what you...
</description></item><item><title>Download BLEASS Complete Effects Bundle 2025.9.30</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Sep 2025 16:59:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bleass-complete-effects-bundle-11452.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bleass-complete-effects-bundle-11452.html
</guid><description>
BLEASS Complete Effects Bundle is a unique collection of 19 different sound plugins as well as 8 additional preset packs for the amazing BLEASS Alpha Synthesizer.
Sound plugins include:
	BLEASS Chorus
	BLEASS Compressor
	BLEASS Delay
	BLEASS Filter
	BLEASS Flanger
	BLEASS Phaser
	BLEASS Reverb
	BLEASS Saturator
	BLEASS Shimmer
	BLEASS Dragonfly
	BLEASS Fusion
	BLEASS Granulizer
	BLEASS Motion EQ
	BLEASS Motion FX
	BLEASS Phase Mutant
	BLEASS Sidekick
	BLEASS Slow Machine
	BLEASS...
</description></item><item><title>Download Trellix Stinger (McAfee Stinger) 13.0.0.546</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Sep 2025 16:55:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mcafee-stinger-202.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mcafee-stinger-202.html
</guid><description>
McAfee Stinger is a free utility that functions to scan, check and remove the hazards and obstacles as virus or malware for Windows, whether they are hiding deep into the system.
In addition, due to the ability to search for the correct folder, or the data at risk contains viruses to scan instead you have to remove a long time waiting for antivirus software to scan all system on your computer. Thus speed of work of the McAfee Stinger faster and somewhat more accurate.
Themselves McAfee...
</description></item><item><title>Download Windows 11 Media Creation Tool 10.0.26100.6584</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Sep 2025 16:54:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-11-media-creation-tool-6838.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-11-media-creation-tool-6838.html
</guid><description>
Windows 11 Media Creation Tool (also known as Create Windows 11 Installation Media) is a free tool from Microsoft and is less than 10MB in size. Windows 11 Media Creation Tool allows users to easily download Windows 11 ISOs directly from Microsoft without a product key. You can use it to clean install or upgrade to Windows 11.
Windows 11 Media Creation Tool can also be used to upgrade your existing PC to Windows 11 or to create a USB or DVD and install Windows 11 on another PC. The tool...
</description></item><item><title>Download Valentina Studio Pro 16.0.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Sep 2025 16:54:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-valentina-studio-pro-2122.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-valentina-studio-pro-2122.html
</guid><description>
Valentina Studio Pro is the best way to transform your data into meaningful information; create, manage, query and explore MySQL, Postgre MariaDB, MS SQL Server and SQLite database.
Valentina Studio Pro
Features of Valentina Studio Pro
SCHEMA EDITING &amp;amp; MAPPING
	Manage multiple databases in tabs and views that can be attached is
	Create / Drop / alter / Browse Tables, fields, index, trigger, constraints, links, views, stored procedures, properties, Sequences, Types, ...
	Edit the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Stellarium 25.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Sep 2025 16:51:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stellarium-2534.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stellarium-2534.html
</guid><description>
Stellarium is a software planetarium shows 3D simulation realistic about the night sky on your computer screen, you. It includes a default category with more than 600,000 stars, images of nebulae, galaxies fact, as well as the planets and satellites of them (additional categories available to download). You can click on each object to view the name, distance and other details and can also zoom to see more closely.
Stellarium - astronomical App
The program can show the sky based on the...
</description></item><item><title>Download DBF Recovery 4.56</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Sep 2025 16:50:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbf-recovery-7931.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbf-recovery-7931.html
</guid><description>
DBF Recovery is software that gives users the ability to restore a damaged database back to its original condition without the expertise required to complete that task. It fixes headers and data structures in an automated process that doesn't involve user interaction. With DBF Recovery, you will truly have a lean, honest DBF repair machine without any functionality.
Features of DBF Recovery
	Quick and simple to use DBF file repair software.
	Repair almost any DBF...
</description></item><item><title>Download dbForge Studio for MySQL Enterprise 2025.2.37</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Sep 2025 16:46:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbforge-studio-for-mysql-enterprise-edition-7743.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbforge-studio-for-mysql-enterprise-edition-7743.html
</guid><description>
dbForge Studio for MySQL is a popular GUI tool for developing, managing, and administering MySQL and MariaDB databases. The IDE allows you to create and execute queries, develop and debug stored procedures, automate database object management, and analyze table data through an intuitive interface. The MySQL client provides data and schema comparison and synchronization tools, database reporting tools, backup options with scheduling, and much more.
Features of dbForge Studio for...
</description></item><item><title>Download VovSoft Tree Notes 2.4</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Sep 2025 16:45:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-tree-notes-11294.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-tree-notes-11294.html
</guid><description>
Vovsoft Tree Notes is a decentralized note-taking application designed to improve your organizational efficiency and streamline your information management process. This powerful software provides users with a user-friendly platform to create, organize and access their notes with ease.
Tree Notes for Windows is a flexible and powerful note-taking solution that meets the needs of individuals, students, professionals, and creative minds alike. Boost your productivity, stay organized, and...
</description></item></channel></rss>