<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 13:44:00 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 13:44:00 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Conversations (Jabber / XMPP) 2.19.6 build 4216104</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 16:43:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-conversations-jabber-xmpp-11493.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-conversations-jabber-xmpp-11493.html
</guid><description>
Free and open source Jabber/XMPP client for Android. Easy to use, reliable, battery friendly. With built-in support for images, group chats and e2e encryption.
Main features
	End-to-end encryption with OMEMO or OpenPGP
	Encrypted audio and video calls (DLTS-SRTP)
	Send and receive images
	Intuitive user interface follows Android Design guidelines
	Image / Avatar for your Contacts
	Sync with desktop client
	Conference (with bookmark support)
	Address book integration
	Multiple accounts...
</description></item><item><title>Download Magnifier Plus with Flashlight 4.8.15</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 16:43:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-magnifier-plus-with-flashlight-8494.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-magnifier-plus-with-flashlight-8494.html
</guid><description>
Are you tired of trying to read labels with small fonts? Now you can use your Android device as the perfect digital magnifier! No need to use a magnifying glass to read small labels - this app lets you see text large and clearly. The magnifier has on-screen zoom and illumination controls for easy operation. You can also use the flash as a light to get a brighter image, and the negative mode inverts the colors so you can see this differently when they're hard to see.
Features of...
</description></item><item><title>Download LED Scroller - LED Banner 1.9.5</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 16:43:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-led-scroller-led-banner-11976.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-led-scroller-led-banner-11976.html
</guid><description>
LED Banners can turn your phone into an interesting electronic bulletin board. It can display banner advertising, electric signs, signs. LED Banners have a simple, easy-to-use interface, perfect for fun places like concerts and disco parties.
Features:
	Any language.
	Supports emoticons.
	Custom text color.
	Customize background color.
	Set image, video, GIF as background.
	Adjust text speed.
	Adjust text flicker.
	Reading direction can be adjusted.
	Pause scrolling.
	Different types...
</description></item><item><title>Download Radio: Record, Europa, Nashe, DFM 5.2.4 GP</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 16:42:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-radio-record-europa-nashe-dfm-11041.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-radio-record-europa-nashe-dfm-11041.html
</guid><description>
This is NOT the official app of the top radio stations! The application contains radio stations of the following radio companies: DFM, Radio Record, Europa plus, Nashe, Maximum.
Key features
	More than 50 radio stations + new radio stations every update
	Licensed BASS© audio library with excellent 32-bit sound quality!
	Powerful 10-band equalizer with additional sound settings
	Network buffer settings for stable playback even without a perfect internet connection
	Full-screen dock...
</description></item><item><title>Download CalenGoo - Calendar and Tasks 1.0.183 build 1692</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 16:42:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-calengoo-calendar-and-tasks-8600.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-calengoo-calendar-and-tasks-8600.html
</guid><description>
CalenGoo is a calendar app for Android devices that allows users to manage their schedules, appointments, and events. It syncs with Google Calendar and has features like a customizable interface, reminders, and the ability to view multiple calendars at once.
Features of CalenGoo for Android
	Sync all your past and future events with Google Calendar (just add your Google account in "Settings &amp;gt; Accounts" instead of syncing via Android calendar).&amp;lt; /li&amp;gt;
	Sync calendars with...
</description></item><item><title>Download Netmonitor: 5G, Cell &amp;amp; WiFi 1.27.3 build 438</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 16:41:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-netmonitor-cell-wifi-11660.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-netmonitor-cell-wifi-11660.html
</guid><description>
With Netmonitor, you can clearly know the strength of mobile and WiFi signals, and find out which corner of your office or home has the best reception. Netmonitor displays advanced 2G/3G/4G/5G (NSA and SA) mobile network information and helps you see the status of the mobile network by collecting data about cell towers. Also detects aggregate carriers (called LTE-Advanced).
Troubleshooting tools for voice and data service quality, RF (Telecommunication) optimization, and technical work...
</description></item><item><title>Download 365Scores: Live Scores &amp;amp; News 14.4.6</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 16:41:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-365scores-live-scores-news-8220.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-365scores-live-scores-news-8220.html
</guid><description>
365Scores is a sports app that provides users with real-time scores, statistics, and news for many sports including football, basketball, soccer, and more. Some features of the application include:
	Live scores and notifications: 365Scores provides live scores and push notifications for many sports, including football, soccer, basketball, baseball, etc.
	Match statistics: The app includes detailed match statistics such as ball control, number of shots on goal, etc.
	Latest News:...
</description></item><item><title>Download ElectroBox - Electronics v50</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 16:41:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-electrobox-electronics-11164.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-electrobox-electronics-11164.html
</guid><description>
A high-quality and easy-to-use toolbox, reference book and electronic calculator for electricians, engineers and students. A collection of information related to electronics, structured so that everyone from senior engineers to DIY enthusiasts and beginners can take advantage of it.
Large library of interfaces, resources, pinouts and calculators - from resistor color codes to voltage divider calculators. This app is a must have for students and engineers. New content is added...
</description></item><item><title>Download QOwnNotes 25.12.4</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 16:39:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qownnotes-3178.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qownnotes-3178.html
</guid><description>
QOwnNotes is notes bookmark file simple text (GPL) open source application for GNU / Linux , Mac OS X and Windows of Patrizio Bekerle ( pbek on GitHub and IRC) (optional) activity along with the notes application of ownCloud or Nextcloud. QOwnNote store your notes as plain text files and can be synchronized with synchronization function file of ownCloud / Nextcloud. You can also use other apps like Syncthing or Dropbox . Just write out your thoughts as they appear, and edit them if...
</description></item><item><title>Download Calibre 8.16.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 00:24:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-calibre-1669.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-calibre-1669.html
</guid><description>
Calibre  is an eBook library management application that allows you to manage your eBook collection, convert eBooks between different formats, Sync with popular e-reading devices and read your e-books with included viewer. You can sort books by author, title, date and other details, download meta information and book covers, add personalized tags and comments, and view your images in the cover display.
Collection of essential tools for adding metadata editing books or managing your...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinSetView 3.1.6</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 00:22:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winsetview-8971.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winsetview-8971.html
</guid><description>
WinSetView is a tool that allows you to easily set File Explorer's default folder view (including disabling grouping everywhere if desired). It works by setting registry values that File Explorer already supports. It does not modify Explorer or add any tasks or services.
Features of WinSetView
	Is a portabe application. That is, it requires no installation (just unzip and run) and it saves its settings in an INI file with the application. So you can easily run it from a flash drive or...
</description></item><item><title>Download PeaZip 10.8.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 00:21:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-peazip-1800.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-peazip-1800.html
</guid><description>
PeaZip is an Archive Utility And Compressed open-source, support multiple compression formats. It lets you create 7Z, ARC, BZ2, GZ, PAQ / ZPAQ, PEA, QUAD / BALZ, TAR, UPX, and ZIP, and enables you to open and extract 133 format additional storage, including RAR. PeaZip has the ability to open and extract over 150 file formats compressed downloads, have the ability to create and switch between multiple file formats, different background on an interface intuitive and easy to use. In...
</description></item><item><title>Download PrivaZer 4.0.115</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 00:20:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-privazer-66.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-privazer-66.html
</guid><description>
PrivaZer : the program performs the scan is very thorough not only includes the trace downloads like registration, Internet history, cookies, etc but also find the traces of potential in the field of free disk space of you. PrivaZer can permanently delete all traces by using the method of secure erase and also re-establish the sector disk free to 0 to remove all traces from the delete operation earlier. The process of scanning and cleaning the original can spend less time (20-30 minutes),...
</description></item><item><title>Download OBS Studio 32.0.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Dec 2025 17:15:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-open-broadcaster-software-2451.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-open-broadcaster-software-2451.html
</guid><description>
Open Broadcaster Software is abbreviated as OBS is a program to detect the type of multimedia content to the internet. It is worth noting that a simple interface and the presence of a good tool. You can adjust the quality of the audio and video before starting the broadcast, you can specify the URL, choose the resolution of the screen, etc. With strong desire, videos which you found can be saved to your hard drive.
Open Broadcaster Software - LiveStream on PC
The basic features of Open...
</description></item><item><title>Download CapCut PC 7.6.0.3123</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Dec 2025 17:14:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capcut-pc-9995.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capcut-pc-9995.html
</guid><description>
CapCut PC is a simple video editing tool that you can freely use anywhere. You can create videos on your browser, desktop and laptop, or on your phone. Versatile editing, magical AI tools, team collaboration, and built-in assets. Create videos in a whole new way.
You can edit videos based on editing the timeline, in the process you can add different elements and effects to the video to give the best effect to your work. It is a simple and intuitive set of editing tools and effects that...
</description></item><item><title>Download JRiver Media Center 35.0.27</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Dec 2025 17:13:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jriver-media-center-110.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jriver-media-center-110.html
</guid><description>
JRiver Media Center can help you strictly manage all your files media and enjoy them in a completely new way. Launching the application for the first time, users will be immediately impressed with the intuitive and eye-catching interface with many interesting features to explore. Most people who have used JRiver Media Center evaluate that the software interface design is youthful and modern.
The software for arranging cover art of music files is also extremely neat, especially Insert...
</description></item><item><title>Download Dont Sleep 9.93</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Dec 2025 17:13:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dont-sleep-89.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dont-sleep-89.html
</guid><description>
Don't Sleep allows you can set the date and custom time that you want to reactivate the feature manager usual sources or you can set a countdown fast to pause the power management in X hours.
Can temporarily disable the protection of your screen or off your computer at a certain time.
The main features of the Dont Sleep:
- Optimal power supply for computer
- Installation time power source according to
- Prevent computer reboot
Content update Dont Sleep 5.66:
The official website...
</description></item><item><title>Download Blank And Secure 8.23</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Dec 2025 17:12:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blank-and-secure-2934.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blank-and-secure-2934.html
</guid><description>
Blank And Secure is a application lightweight and portable allows you to completely erase your sensitive data without possibility to restore. This add-on accomplish this by overwriting your files with zeros (0) before you delete them. This method is also called "zeroing data / drives". You should know that once completed, the complete data can't be recovered, so you should only use this tool if you want to permanently delete your files.
Blank And Secure - Delete data permanently
Blank...
</description></item><item><title>Download Telegram for Desktop 6.3.6</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Dec 2025 17:12:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-telegram-3376.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-telegram-3376.html
</guid><description>
Telegram is an instant messaging service and voice over IP services on the cloud platform. Client application Telegram is available for Android, iOS, Windows Phone, Windows NT, macOS, and Linux. Users can send messages and exchange photos, videos, stickers, audio and files of any kind.
Telegram - Messaging and free phone calls
Telegram seamless sync across all your devices and can be used on desktop, tablet and phone. You can send unlimited amount of messages, photos, videos and files...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ocenaudio 3.16.5</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Dec 2025 17:11:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ocenaudio-837.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ocenaudio-837.html
</guid><description>
Ocenaudio: software for windows, this is the sound editing easy, fast and powerful. ocenaudio is a program for audio editing multi-platform, easy to use, fast and functional. This is the ideal software for those who need to edit and analyze audio files.
Ocenaudio - editor powerful audio for windows
This software is based on Ocen Framework , a powerful library developed to simplify and standardize the development of application analysis and sound processing on many platforms.
Features...
</description></item><item><title>Download GoodSync Enterprise 12.9.18.8</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Dec 2025 17:11:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-goodsync-enterprise-163.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-goodsync-enterprise-163.html
</guid><description>
GoodSync Enterprise is a software that saves files and files easily and is reliable. It automatically analyts, synchronize and backup your email, family photos, contacts, MP3, financial documentation and other important files-between desktop computers, laptops, servers, external drives and Windows Mobile devices as well as remotely via FTP , SFTP, WebDAV and more. The GoodSync synchronized software combines bulletproof reliability with an extremely easy interface to compare, synchronize...
</description></item><item><title>Download reaConverter Pro 8.0.165</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Dec 2025 17:11:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html
</guid><description>
reaConverter Pro is software image processing feature with batch conversion and image editing periodically becomes simple. eaConverter also provide command line utilities allow you to process images automatically, thus helping you shorten the time for other work.
reaConverter Pro integrated powerful tool of Uber with many great features. It provides advanced solutions to process and adjust images. Management of the conversion process the base image with the latest version of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Any Video Downloader Pro 10.0.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Dec 2025 17:10:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-video-downloader-pro-3731.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-video-downloader-pro-3731.html
</guid><description>
Any Video Downloader Pro is software support you can download video HD 720p, 1080p, 2K, 4K and 8K from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion, Vimeo, Metacafe and thousands of video sharing sites, other. It is a tool to speed up multi-threading can speed up your download faster up to 5 times. This helpful program support download at the same time. Any Video Downloader Pro lets you download multiple videos at the same time. Moreover, it allows you to pause and resume downloads if you need more...
</description></item><item><title>Download 4KSoftware 4K Downloader 6.0.10</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Dec 2025 17:10:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-downloader-3858.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-downloader-3858.html
</guid><description>
4K Downloader is a Windows application small but powerful to download and convert video in 4K and 8K Ultra HD from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion and thousands of other video-based websites. It speeds up your download by up to 5 times. Consider that most smart phones, TVS, computers, and tablets all support the high definition format, don't be surprised when many users want to enjoy quality content on their device. 4K Downloader is a lightweight software designed to help you grab videos...
</description></item><item><title>Download Syncovery Premium 11.11.4.134</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Dec 2025 17:09:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncovery-pro-enterprise-232.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncovery-pro-enterprise-232.html
</guid><description>
Syncovery Pro Enterprise is a great application used to back up data and to synchronize personal computers, servers, laptops, notepads and storage online. The software comes with support for FTP and secure FTP servers, SSH, WebDAV, Amazon S3, http, update the part file, ZIP compression, data encryption, and schedule automatic backups.
Syncovery Pro Enterprise have the ability to freely select files and folders across the whole folder hierarchy in tree view and supports email...
</description></item></channel></rss>