<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 20:08:58 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 20:08:58 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download iTop Voicy 1.1.0.1603</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:05:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-itop-voicy-14482.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-itop-voicy-14482.html
</guid><description>
Transform your voice into anyone you want in real time. iTop Voicy uses the most advanced AI tuning technology to change your age, gender, and voice style while maintaining a natural sound. Whether you want to set a cute girl's voice or a robot voice, this free voice changer software for PC will produce high-quality voices instantly, without lag or delay.
Features of iTop Voicy
	Real-time, lag-free voice changer software
	Voice changer software for audio/video files
	Audio voice...
</description></item><item><title>Download Nexus Risk Canvas Pro Edition 1.0.0.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:05:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nexus-risk-canvas-pro-edition-14502.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nexus-risk-canvas-pro-edition-14502.html
</guid><description>
Nexus Risk Canvas is your gateway to visual risk management. Based on the industry-standard BowTie methodology, this application allows you to map complex risk scenarios, connecting threats to leading events and consequences through barriers and controls. Unlock the full power of visual risk assessment with Nexus Risk Canvas Pro. Designed for risk professionals, consultants, and security managers who need to record, archive, and share their work.
Why upgrade to the Pro version?
While...
</description></item><item><title>Download PingInfoView 3.25</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:04:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pinginfoview-2700.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pinginfoview-2700.html
</guid><description>
PingInfoView is a small utility that allows you to easily ping multiple host names and IP addresses and watch the result in one table. It automatically ping to all hosts every number of seconds that you specify, and displays the number of times the ping success and failure, as well as the ping time average. You can also save the ping result into text / html / xml or copy it to the clipboard.
PingInfoView doesn't require any installation process or additional dll file. To start using, just...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe After Effects 2025 v25.6.4.003 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:59:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-after-effects-0010-2793.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-after-effects-0010-2793.html
</guid><description>
Adobe After Effects is a powerful digital visual effects, motion graphics, and compositing application developed by Adobe Inc. The software is widely used in the film, television, and video game industries to animate and enhance video content.
After Effects allows users to create stunning motion graphics and visual effects by animating text, images, and video clips. Its capabilities include keying, tracking, compositing, and basic audio editing, making it a versatile tool for...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Audition 2025 v25.6.4 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:58:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-audition-0004-1246.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-audition-0004-1246.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Autdition 2024 is a professional tool for professionals active in the field of audio processing and video, offering them the ability to almost unlimited. Ease of use combined with flexibility of work, allows you to create the main copy of the highest class, edit, mix, handle, impose more sound effects especially. In fact, users have to be on my computer a recording studio powerful full with the tool easy to use at the same time, the tool is quite professional.
Adobe autdition CC -...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare PDFelement Pro 12.1.6.3963</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:57:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-pdfelement-pro-105.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-pdfelement-pro-105.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare PDFelement Pro support users to convert PDF to office documents for easier use, modify in every situation. Is one of the software conversion material is rated best today, integrated with many features. We recommend that you should use experience software many useful features this.
Wondershare PDFelement Pro - conversion Fie PDF more features, multi-language
Wondershare PDFelement Pro what?
Convert PDF into Word, Excel, PowerPoint...
• Convert PDF and protected PDF into...
</description></item><item><title>Download Private Photo Move 1.1.0.6</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:57:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-private-photo-move-14501.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-private-photo-move-14501.html
</guid><description>
Optimize your PC performance and protect your privacy with Private Photo Move – a tool that helps you organize your photos intelligently without relying on the cloud. If your computer is cluttered with thousands of photos and you're worried about uploading them to the cloud, this is the solution for you. No more slow or privacy-risky sorting methods, Private Photo Move for Windows offers a completely different experience.
The application leverages the power of NVIDIA or AMD GPUs along...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Substance 3D Painter 11.1.2.5115 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:57:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-substance-painter-1279.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-substance-painter-1279.html
</guid><description>
Substance Painter is a drawing application 3D completely new with the possibility of unprecedented and workflow is optimized, help in creating graphics easier than ever. To create sprites or 3D characters, no need to have knowledge about a painters professional animation, now it has become easy and accessible for the average user . The program is recognized in the world is creative tool and the most convenient to draw 3D create character models.
Substance Painter - App 3D drawing
The...
</description></item><item><title>Download EditPlus 6.1 Build 836</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:56:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-editplus-338.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-editplus-338.html
</guid><description>
EditPlus is editor text, editor, HTML and editor program for Windows. EditPlus works as a text editor as well as editor, PHP editor, HTML, editor, Java viewer and Hex. It supports syntax highlighting for many languages, such as HTML, CSS, Java, PHP, C / C ++, Perl, and Python, and can act as a web browser to preview the HTML page. EditPlus also provides some other useful features, such as auto completion, code folding, spell checking, search and replace, keyboard shortcuts, custom and HTML...
</description></item><item><title>Download Auslogics SSD Optimizer Pro 2.2.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:55:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-auslogics-ssd-optimizer-pro-12530.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-auslogics-ssd-optimizer-pro-12530.html
</guid><description>
Auslogics SSD Optimizer Pro is a specialized software tool designed to enhance the performance and longevity of solid state drives (SSDs). The software uses complex algorithms to optimize SSD performance, significantly improving read and write speeds, providing faster file access and overall system responsiveness. Users can check the health of their SSD, including real-time statistics on read and written data, helping to assess drive health and expected lifespan.
Features of Auslogics...
</description></item><item><title>Download Markdown Monster 4.0.4</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:55:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-markdown-monster-2640.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-markdown-monster-2640.html
</guid><description>
Markdown Monster is the edit and view Markdown allows you to edit Markdown by syntax highlighting and fast text input. Live preview can collapse, synchronized allows you to see the output of when you enter. You can easily embed images, links, emoticons and code in text form or by using the support UI lightness of we to simplify many operations. You can also paste and drag images directly into the editor.
Markdown Monster is a solution comprehensive software designed to solve almost any...
</description></item><item><title>Download PhotoCull 2.0.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:54:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photocull-14235.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photocull-14235.html
</guid><description>
PhotoCull is a completely redesigned Windows application that helps you send photos to your clients faster. PhotoCull simplifies photo selection and finishing. After shooting, you can quickly decide which photos to select or keep for further processing/color correction. PhotoCull lets you send photos faster with intuitive and fast selection, editing, and unique viewing features.
Features of PhotoCull
PhotoCull has many features that help you quickly select photos to keep and finish....
</description></item><item><title>Download KLS Backup Professional 2025 v14.0.3.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:54:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kls-backup-professional-2951.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kls-backup-professional-2951.html
</guid><description>
KLS Backup Professional is a tool to backup and synchronize powerful allows you to backup or synchronize your information with the local drive and network, cloud storage, media, CD and DVD, WebDAV and FTP server. The backup documents can be stored uncompressed or compressed in Zip format or 7z basic. Backup KLS can backup: files or folders from the local disk, database, network locations or cloud storage, the mailbox data and other specific program (profile). Management in turn can...
</description></item><item><title>Download reaConverter Pro 8.0.182</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:53:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html
</guid><description>
reaConverter Pro is software image processing feature with batch conversion and image editing periodically becomes simple. eaConverter also provide command line utilities allow you to process images automatically, thus helping you shorten the time for other work.
reaConverter Pro integrated powerful tool of Uber with many great features. It provides advanced solutions to process and adjust images. Management of the conversion process the base image with the latest version of...
</description></item><item><title>Download CoolUtils Total Doc Converter 5.1.0.369/141</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:53:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-total-doc-converter-84.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-total-doc-converter-84.html
</guid><description>
CoolUtils Total Doc Converter Program that will allow you to document conversion DOC to others, the list can be viewed on the official website or you can watch carefully the screenshot, I think the question would no longer can download CoolUtils Total Doc Converter below. There is batch processing,in general, everything is convenient, I hope you like it.
Total Doc Converter is conversion tools text comprehensive and multi-featured, very necessary when storing or printing the text. It also...
</description></item><item><title>Download IntraWEB Ultimate 16.1.10</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:52:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intraweb-ultimate-2007.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intraweb-ultimate-2007.html
</guid><description>
IntraWEB Ultimate is a tool to build the website. With this tool, the developer can create the page using the same method used to build the Windows program. Because the HTML page directly from the concept design to the user's computer does not download a bit more complicated and in fact is required from web server. So, the template IntraWeb on the server and download server and displays them to the user. Things technology direction of the IntraWEB Ultimate provides part flexibility and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Android Studio 2025.2.3.9</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:50:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-android-studio-3890.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-android-studio-3890.html
</guid><description>
Android Studio is an Android development environment, completely new, provides many improvements and new features compared to Eclipse ADT. This software solution will is IDE the official Android when is finishing. This tool provides many tools and features such as editing, layout, rich set of tools to capture usability, compatibility version, performance and other issues, create a lot APK, build system based on Gradle flexibility, extended support for Google Services, integrated support...
</description></item><item><title>Download SiteSync by Chiemsoft 1.0.10</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:50:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sitesync-by-chiemsoft-14500.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sitesync-by-chiemsoft-14500.html
</guid><description>
Chiemsoft's SiteSync is an indispensable tool for Syteline developers struggling with manually scripting form insertions.
Features of SiteSync
Export improved forms from FormSync in Syteline: Use SiteSync to collect only the FormComponents, EventHandlers, Variables, and Form Scripts that have changed from a scripted form compared to a form from another website.
Export insertion scripts from SiteSync: Load insertion scripts from SSMS into the website(s) where you want to import the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Valentina Studio Pro 16.5.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:44:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-valentina-studio-pro-2122.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-valentina-studio-pro-2122.html
</guid><description>
Valentina Studio Pro is the best way to transform your data into meaningful information; create, manage, query and explore MySQL, Postgre MariaDB, MS SQL Server and SQLite database.
Valentina Studio Pro
Features of Valentina Studio Pro
SCHEMA EDITING &amp;amp; MAPPING
	Manage multiple databases in tabs and views that can be attached is
	Create / Drop / alter / Browse Tables, fields, index, trigger, constraints, links, views, stored procedures, properties, Sequences, Types, ...
	Edit the...
</description></item><item><title>Download QOwnNotes 26.1.7</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:44:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qownnotes-3178.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qownnotes-3178.html
</guid><description>
QOwnNotes is notes bookmark file simple text (GPL) open source application for GNU / Linux , Mac OS X and Windows of Patrizio Bekerle ( pbek on GitHub and IRC) (optional) activity along with the notes application of ownCloud or Nextcloud. QOwnNote store your notes as plain text files and can be synchronized with synchronization function file of ownCloud / Nextcloud. You can also use other apps like Syncthing or Dropbox . Just write out your thoughts as they appear, and edit them if...
</description></item><item><title>Download Brave Browser 1.86.139</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:43:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-brave-browser-2874.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-brave-browser-2874.html
</guid><description>
Brave Browser is a browser based on Chromium, the basic principle is that operation fast and privacy of users. The program can block pop-up windows and other ads, plus it blocked the mechanism for monitoring the online activities of your. Therefore, you can purchase and safely browse the website you are interested in without having to worry about the fact that your activity will be monitored and then you will be shown the necessary advertising or service provider of parties...
</description></item><item><title>Download ET Optimizer 6.08.10</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:42:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-et-optimizer-9574.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-et-optimizer-9574.html
</guid><description>
ET-Optimizer is a free, open source script to improve your computer's overall performance and optimize it for your workflow through optimized scripting. With this optimization, setup takes little effort. The script is developed from many sources found on the Internet, tested and updated for different versions of the system. The whole script is contained in 1 file, it uses: command prompt, powershell, power plan configuration, startup configuration, registry changes, network interface...
</description></item><item><title>Download FabFilter Total Bundle 2026.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:42:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fabfilter-total-bundle-896.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fabfilter-total-bundle-896.html
</guid><description>
FabFilter Total Bundle is a collection of all the plugis FabFilter. Package includes EQ, compressor, limiter, de-esser, gate/expander, multi-band distortion, stereo delay, filter and synthesizer plug-ins available today.
FabFilter Total Bundle - synthesizer Plugins FabFilter
The inner pack software FabFilter Total Bundle includes:
	FabFilter Pro-Q 2 - Allround EQ plug-in for mixing and mastering purposes, with up to 24 bands and a gorgeous interface for easy and precise...
</description></item><item><title>Download GForce impOSCar 3 1.0.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:41:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gforce-imposcar-3-12011.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gforce-imposcar-3-12011.html
</guid><description>
GForce impOSCar 3 is the design of the legendary British hardware synthesizer OSCar. Like the original, its hybrid construction combines the precision of a digital oscillator with the warmth of an analog filter, delivering a wide range of sonic possibilities. Create expansive, lush, dark or ambient pads, resonant bells and precise leads with this exceptional recreation. Refined filters, matched with the new wavetable editor, combine the finest digital clarity with unparalleled analog...
</description></item><item><title>Download Valentina Server 16.5.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:41:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-valentina-server-10771.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-valentina-server-10771.html
</guid><description>
Valentina Server is software that provides reports from all major databases or with its own advanced object-relational database system. It will combine an enterprise reporting server and two database servers into a single solution. You get all the technical features of Valentina Server in terms of usage, more connections and live technical support.
Features of Valentina Server
	Enterprise report server turns data into highly formatted reports in the form of multimedia web pages, text,...
</description></item></channel></rss>