<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 15:44:47 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 15:44:47 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download R-Wipe &amp;amp; Clean 20.0 Build 2545</title><pubDate> Sat, 24 Jan 2026 18:42:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-wipe-clean-891.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-wipe-clean-891.html
</guid><description>
R-Wipe &amp;amp; Clean is software to delete junk files, unnecessary files from your computer to release the storage space and speed up your computer. In addition, R-Wipe &amp;amp; Clean also unleash the capacity of your drive and delete information invasion of privacy on different operations online and offline including your internet history and cookies, the list of downloaded files and documents were open, buffer different data, temporary files and many other items, created by the operating...
</description></item><item><title>Download Perfectly Clear WorkBench 5.0.1.3054</title><pubDate> Sat, 24 Jan 2026 18:41:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfectly-clear-workbench-6892.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfectly-clear-workbench-6892.html
</guid><description>
Perfectly Clear Workbench is an application that uses image editing libraries Perfectly Clear by Athentech and is provided to demonstrate the capabilities of the Perfectly Clear processing libraries, which recognize faces and allow quick export of processing settings for use.
One of the key features in Workbench is the ability to "export to API" when saving a Preset. This allows you to make image edits in Workbench and adjust the settings to suit your editing style and needs. You can...
</description></item><item><title>Download FastStone MaxView 3.5 Corporate</title><pubDate> Sat, 24 Jan 2026 18:41:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-faststone-maxview-871.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-faststone-maxview-871.html
</guid><description>
FastStone MaxView is an image viewer, digital fast, compact and innovative support all graphics formats the current. Intuitive layout of MaxView allows you to view images in many different ways. MaxView even allows you to view images in the file archive ZIP and to RAR be password protected directly and immediately, this is a perfect solution for viewing private images. FastStone MaxView is a handy tool for quickly viewing, rotating, resizing, cropping, annotating and printing...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare Repairit 6.6.2.12</title><pubDate> Sat, 24 Jan 2026 18:40:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-recoverit-video-repair-3889.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-recoverit-video-repair-3889.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare Recoverit Video Repair is a reliable application that helps you fix the broken video, Wondershare Recoverit Video Repair supports file formats MP4, MOV, M4V, M2TS, MKV, MTS, 3GP, AVI and FLV is corrupt and broken. Great service we provide. It fixes the video that there is corruption in the process of shooting, when done, file transfer, while editing, convert.
Wondershare Recoverit Video Repair - video repair broken
Features of Wondershare Recoverit Video Repair
	Repair...
</description></item><item><title>Download OkMap Desktop 19.2.5</title><pubDate> Sat, 24 Jan 2026 18:40:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-okmap-desktop-581.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-okmap-desktop-581.html
</guid><description>
OkMap Desktop is interactive software working on the computer with web maps or digital maps bought or scanned. OkMap can also import a data vector from the most common formats and data DEM related to information height.
Through the map you can organize your path by creating waypoints , routesand tracks on the screen your computer, and upload this data to your GPS . OkMap set data high speedautomatic and estimated moving time . Furthermore OkMap provides you also have autorouting and...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter 3.9.18 (2301)</title><pubDate> Sat, 24 Jan 2026 18:39:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-to-mp3-converter-1744.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-to-mp3-converter-1744.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter is the software support download youtube video and convert video to mp3 format fast and most simple. MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter allows you download and convert videos from YouTube and other websites to MP3 format by pasting the YouTube URL into the application. When you paste the URL, the program will display thumbnails for videos and you have the option to customize the title information, artist and album before you begin the process of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Avdshare Audio Converter 7.6.2.9498</title><pubDate> Sat, 24 Jan 2026 18:39:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avdshare-audio-converter-2879.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avdshare-audio-converter-2879.html
</guid><description>
Avdshare Audio Converter is the app conversion between audio formats with no quality lose; Extract audio from video; Directly play the media file, audio editing like merge, adjust audio volume, channel, bitrate, etc. the Program Avdshare Audio Converter supports multiple audio formats popular such as: AAC, AC3, Apple lossless ALAC, APE, AU, AUD, AIFF, AIF, AIFC, AMR, AWB, CAF, DTS, DSS, FLAC, GSM, MP3, M4A, M4B, M4R, MKA, MPC, MP1, MP2, MID, MIDI, OGG, OGA, OPUS, PCM, QCP, RA, RAM, RAW,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Zortam Mp3 Media Studio Pro 33.75</title><pubDate> Sat, 24 Jan 2026 18:38:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zortam-mp3-media-studio-pro-135.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zortam-mp3-media-studio-pro-135.html
</guid><description>
Zortam Mp3 Media Studio Pro brings you rich processing tools music includes extract and convert music from CD to Mp3 format, edit, music cards, music download....You can also create discs CD high-quality music, with Zortam Mp3 Media Studio search music files duplicated to remove them from the system, rename music files, switch back and forth between formats.
Zortam Mp3 Media Studio Pro is rated as perfect software in the processing of the MP3 files on the computer. First of all, you can...
</description></item><item><title>Download ExamDiff Pro Master Edition 16.0.1.20</title><pubDate> Sat, 24 Jan 2026 18:38:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-examdiff-pro-master-312.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-examdiff-pro-master-312.html
</guid><description>
ExamDiff Pro Master is a tool to compare files and folders intuitive and easy to use, intuitive and easy to use for Windows. ExamDiff Pro Master has unique features distinguishes ExamDiff Pro with the program compare other. ExamDiff Pro Master to help perform reviews of code and share other reports with your colleagues and compare local website with FTP server by plug-ins more integrated.
ExamDiff Pro Master can create a snapshot folder for comparison and storage in the future, compare...
</description></item><item><title>Download AssistMyTeam PDF Studio 7.2.295.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 24 Jan 2026 18:37:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-assistmyteam-pdf-studio-14149.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-assistmyteam-pdf-studio-14149.html
</guid><description>
The AssistMyTeam PDF Studio add-on integrates your Windows Explorer with a PDF reader, converter, editor, organizer, splitter, merger, file extractor and even OCR in an instant one-click operation.
What sets this application apart from most other bloated, complex commercial PDF applications is its relative ease of use and efficiency with a simple, minimalistic yet intuitive and unobtrusive interface—just right-click on a file in Windows Explorer and perform the action you want to your...
</description></item><item><title>Download Aidfile Recovery Software Professional 3.7.9.4</title><pubDate> Sat, 24 Jan 2026 18:37:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aidfile-recovery-software-professional-4316.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aidfile-recovery-software-professional-4316.html
</guid><description>
Aidfile Recovery Software Professional is a software small but powerful will assist you to recover files lost, deleted or damaged. It is ideal to restore data such as videos, files, office, images, folders and many other things. Professional tool this will help you to perform full scan and in-depth hard drive and partition, USB drive, memory card or removable media , to fully restore your data. This software can restore the data file from the file system partition FAT32, NTFS and ExFAT,...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube Downloader 3.9.18 (2301)</title><pubDate> Sat, 24 Jan 2026 18:36:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube Downloader  is a dedicated software that helps users  downloading youtube videos  Favorites on PC for offline viewing. With MediaHuman YouTube  Downloader  you can download videos from youtube website to your computer with  fast speed , with special software development technology that automatically receives videos from Websites, in addition to the ability to download videos from software websites, can convert downloaded video formats to various formats for the purpose...
</description></item><item><title>Download proDAD Hide 2.0.218.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 24 Jan 2026 18:36:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-prodad-hide-6054.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-prodad-hide-6054.html
</guid><description>
proDAD Hide is a real problem recetor when something that gets into your frame can cause loss of focus or not in the right place. In most cases, these problems became apparent in the editing process. After an analysis process, proDAD Hide will replace the object with its original background-all automatically performed in the shortest time without any manual effort. For this process, proDAD Hide will need a few moments before and after the object needs to be removed from view.
The...
</description></item><item><title>Download CalendarTask (formerly DesktopCal) 3.26.265.8454</title><pubDate> Sat, 24 Jan 2026 18:31:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopcal-1831.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopcal-1831.html
</guid><description>
CalendarTask (formerly DesktopCal) is a simple desktop calendar that blends into your desktop without blocking access to your desktop icons. You can double-click on a date to quickly add notes and also jump to specific dates in the past or future.
CalendarTask - Computer calendar
CalendarTask can use your current wallpaper or loop through images from your folder and update your desktop every few minutes. The program helps you make appointments, make plans... Not only that, the Screen...
</description></item><item><title>Download Any Video Downloader Pro 10.1.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 24 Jan 2026 18:30:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-video-downloader-pro-3731.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-video-downloader-pro-3731.html
</guid><description>
Any Video Downloader Pro is software support you can download video HD 720p, 1080p, 2K, 4K and 8K from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion, Vimeo, Metacafe and thousands of video sharing sites, other. It is a tool to speed up multi-threading can speed up your download faster up to 5 times. This helpful program support download at the same time. Any Video Downloader Pro lets you download multiple videos at the same time. Moreover, it allows you to pause and resume downloads if you need more...
</description></item><item><title>Download XL-Connector 3.6.42.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 24 Jan 2026 18:26:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xl-connector-12415.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xl-connector-12415.html
</guid><description>
XL-Connector is a popular plugin that securely integrates Excel and Salesforce to export, import, refresh and transform data seamlessly with ultra-fast api connection. It provides Salesforce administrators with a comprehensive toolbox that easily performs data and metadata management activities in a familiar Excel environment.
Features
Export from Salesforce to Excel
	Get data from existing Salesforce reports or build your own SOQL queries directly into Excel.
Import data into...
</description></item><item><title>Download MiniTool Video Converter 4.6.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 24 Jan 2026 18:22:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minitool-video-converter-5358.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minitool-video-converter-5358.html
</guid><description>
MiniTool Video Converter is the most direct solution for converting audio and video files to a wide variety of formats. This free video converter is available to convert audio to video and convert video to audio. This free video converter supports over 1000 conversion formats including 4K / FHD / HD files MP4, MOV, MKV, AVI, WMV, M4V and audio formats like MP3, WAV, M4A, WMA High Quality, AAC, AC3.
MiniTool Video Converter allows you to convert batches of files at the same time. Just...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft Edge 144.0.3719.92</title><pubDate> Sat, 24 Jan 2026 18:21:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-edge-3940.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-edge-3940.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft Edge is web browser developed specifically for Windows operating system 10 alternatives to Internet Explorer is the default browser on Windows. Browser Microsoft Edge built-in assistant Cortana brings content and website based on the user's preferences, there are also system utilities quite extensive help you to customize according to individual. Microsoft Edge has the similarity with Google Chrome quite large, except the target is marked more of the interface and the rounded...
</description></item><item><title>Download QILING Deep Data Recovery 4.6.0 Build 20260106</title><pubDate> Sat, 24 Jan 2026 18:21:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qiling-deep-data-recovery-14091.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qiling-deep-data-recovery-14091.html
</guid><description>
Mistakenly deleted, formatted drive or inaccessible RAW drive? Don't worry, Deep Data Recovery software will help you quickly scan and recover deleted and lost files. QILING Deep Data Recovery is a reliable data recovery software for Windows, designed to help users effectively recover deleted, lost or inaccessible files from various storage devices such as hard drives, USB drives, SD cards and digital cameras. The software can recover a wide range of files, including photos, videos, audio...
</description></item><item><title>Download Photomatix Pro 7.1.4 Beta 4</title><pubDate> Sat, 24 Jan 2026 18:16:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photomatix-pro-2535.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photomatix-pro-2535.html
</guid><description>
Photomatix Pro is software to help merge the photos were taken at the level of different exposures into a HDR image only for see all the details, highlights and shadows, with the option to automatically align the photo handheld, removing ghosts, and reducing noise and chromatic aberration. Then, the picture is mixed can be adjusted by a variety of options and settings to get the look that users want from the results look natural by using fusion to photos, graphics, super real or surreal...
</description></item><item><title>Download VovSoft Desktop Diary 3.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 24 Jan 2026 18:15:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-desktop-diary-6934.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-desktop-diary-6934.html
</guid><description>
Vovsoft Desktop Diary is a handy diary application that allows you to lock your account with a password, preventing others from accessing your private data. You can use it to write down your memories, as well as save important appointments. This is a daily diary application for Windows that allows you to save your daily notes on your desktop or laptop computer.
VovSoft Desktop Diary Features
	Write your memories or dates easily
	The program has multiple themes and allows you to...
</description></item><item><title>Download TubeDownload Pro 7.1.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 24 Jan 2026 18:10:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubedownload-pro-12035.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubedownload-pro-12035.html
</guid><description>
TubeDownload Pro is a professional Windows application for downloading your favorite videos from YouTube and hundreds of other video sites. TubeDownload Pro can increase download speed up to 500% or even more.
Features of TubeDownload Pro
	Download your favorite videos from YouTube and hundreds of other video sites.
	Increase download speed up to 500% or even more.
	Download 720p, 1080p, 2K, 4K and 8K HD videos from YouTube.
	Download entire playlists in just a few clicks.
	Download...
</description></item><item><title>Download AssistMyTeam PDF Converter 7.2.295.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 24 Jan 2026 18:02:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-assistmyteam-pdf-converter-7856.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-assistmyteam-pdf-converter-7856.html
</guid><description>
AssistMyTeam PDF Converter is a software to convert files to PDF, it is used to save all kinds of documents, such as Word, Excel, PowerPoint, web pages, images, emails. or even ZIP to PDF files. Best of all, Windows Explorer Shell Integration makes this significantly easier, with one-click instant PDF.
Features of AssistMyTeam PDF Converter
	Convert different types of documents to PDF quickly.
	Support to convert 120+ file types to PDF.
	Save the compressed ZIP file to PDF.
	Convert...
</description></item><item><title>Download Yuhan Blu-ray DVD Creator 4.8.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 24 Jan 2026 18:02:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yuhan-blu-ray-creator-13480.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yuhan-blu-ray-creator-13480.html
</guid><description>
Yuhan Blu-ray Creator is an all-in-one authoring software for creating high-quality DVD, Blu-ray and 4K UHD discs. The software supports many popular video formats (e.g. MP4, MKV, AVI, MOV) and image formats (including HEIC from iPhone), making it flexible with a variety of media sources.
Key features include:
	Supports DVD (PAL, NTSC), Blu-ray (720p, 1080p), and 4K UHD Blu-ray authoring.
	Preserves advanced video and audio standards such as Dolby Vision, HDR10, Blu-ray PCM, TrueHD,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Basilisk Browser 2026.01.23</title><pubDate> Sat, 24 Jan 2026 18:02:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-basilisk-browser-3923.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-basilisk-browser-3923.html
</guid><description>
Basilisk Browser is a browser based on the XUL free and has many features, provides the interface is well designed and simple manipulation. The program is built based on the tool output and layout of the Goanna and based on the platform XUL merge, similar to Mozilla Firefox. Basilisk Browser was created as a reference program for the development of the platform XUL. You can use this app in replacement for Mozilla Firefox. This utility includes support many types of features needed for...
</description></item></channel></rss>