<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 00:01:50 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 00:01:50 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Privacy Eraser Pro 6.26.0.5480</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 01:51:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-privacy-eraser-1141.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-privacy-eraser-1141.html
</guid><description>
Privacy Eraser is the cleanup for computer help to clear the tracks, junk files and traces of recent activity of the computer. Privacy Eraser support the popular web browsers like Internet Explorer, Mozilla Firefox, Google Chrome, Safari and Opera. The program can quickly erase the browser cache, cookies, browsing history, website history, website URL entered, form data, auto complete, file index.dat, file swapping, temporary directory and the position in other common.
Privacy Eraser -...
</description></item><item><title>Download Nero AI Video Upscaler Pro 1.3.13.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 01:50:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nero-ai-video-upscaler-pro-14415.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nero-ai-video-upscaler-pro-14415.html
</guid><description>
Nero AI Video Upscaler Pro is software for Windows that uses artificial intelligence to improve video quality by upscaling resolution to 4K and increasing frame rates for smoother playback. It also includes features such as noise reduction, clip-level resolution upscaling, face enhancement, and AI-based frame interpolation, enabling smoother motion and sharper detail in both real footage and AI-generated content.
Users can choose from multiple AI models (Fast, Animated, Realistic) to...
</description></item><item><title>Download CyberLink PowerDirector Ultimate 2026 v24.1.1328.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 01:50:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-powerdirector-ultimate-425.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-powerdirector-ultimate-425.html
</guid><description>
CyberLink PowerDirector Ultimate is software editor, edit video and make movies on the computer from a variety of templates are made available, complete with effects, transitions, animations, and music. CyberLink PowerDirector 17 is a combination of video editing software with advanced video editing features powerful. Cblowing need to add your clips into the time line and click on 'Production'!
The tool design video in CyberLink PowerDirector have the ability to customize helps you...
</description></item><item><title>Download VideoProc Converter AI 8.8</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 01:49:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-videoproc-2473.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-videoproc-2473.html
</guid><description>
VideoProc (an improved version of WinX HD Video Converter Deluxe) - processing software the most powerful video designed to edit, cut, crop, merge, adjust, convert and compress (4K) video with full Hardware Acceleration. Is the heir to be improved a lot, VideoProc integrated conversion / compression video UHD, the download at videos (YouTube) with the video editor, gives you the power to control optimal for every video file much music, SD, HD and 4K on your PC. With technology hardware...
</description></item><item><title>Download CyberLink PhotoDirector Ultra 2026 v17.1.1327.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 01:49:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-photodirector-ultra-129.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-photodirector-ultra-129.html
</guid><description>
Cyberlink PhotoDirector Ultra is known to be photo editing tools and videos with the effect is extremely rich, help you to change the style for the individual images or the videos of his favorite. This software integrated the 3D engine helps to speed up Video processing, which allows accessing the repository effect online and extract the Videos into the movies 3D Bru-ray, 3D AVCHD.
Cyberlink PhotoDirector Ultra to offer users a more professional tool to handle their images, remove...
</description></item><item><title>Download Hasleo Disk Clone Professional 5.6.2.0 / Enterprise / Technician</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 01:48:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hasleo-disk-clone-professional-14012.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hasleo-disk-clone-professional-14012.html
</guid><description>
Hasleo Disk Clone Professional is a comprehensive disk and partition cloning software for Windows, which allows users to clone entire disks, specific partitions, and migrate Windows operating system from one disk to another without reinstalling the application. It is a professional Windows cloning software, providing multiple disk alignment modes, sector-by-sector copy of disks and partitions, flexible partition adjustment (location/size on target disk), and MBR/GPT disk conversion during...
</description></item><item><title>Download Rufus 4.12 + Portable</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 01:48:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rufus-2442.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rufus-2442.html
</guid><description>
Rufus support create a USB install Windows operating system like installing from a Windows installation disc often. Rufus offers to users the features from simple to lift the cap fit the needs as well as the ability of many objects. Rufus also has useful functions such as automatic identification, USB, display information about the connected USB.
A new version of a small program has been released that allows you to create and format the USB flash drive that can boot, it also can operate...
</description></item><item><title>Download ActivePresenter Pro 10.1.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 01:47:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-activepresenter-pro-598.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-activepresenter-pro-598.html
</guid><description>
ActivePresenter Pro is a solution to create a video screencast, development, manuals, documents and training presentations interactive. With the full editing features, ActivePresenter allows you to edit audio / video adjust interface content and specify the script branching with ease and efficiency. HTML5 support latest web standards and ability to integrate with management Systems, learning content created with ActivePresenter can be sent virtually to any device and any...
</description></item><item><title>Download Office Timeline Plus 13.25.01.00 Expert / Pro / Pro+ Edition</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 01:47:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-timeline-2106.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-timeline-2106.html
</guid><description>
Office Timeline is an add-on very useful and powerful software for Microsoft PowerPoint. With add-ons, you can create PowerPoint documents look more beautiful. With add-ons, you can add the time Line on the project by yourself. Application time for the composition and different segments of the document, your PowerPoint will not only increase the beauty for your work, but also for customers and your manager. The people who created this product is also believe that add-ons this is the only...
</description></item><item><title>Download WYSIWYG Web Builder 20.4.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 01:46:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wysiwyg-web-builder-177.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wysiwyg-web-builder-177.html
</guid><description>
WYSIWYG Web Builder : The construction of the website from scratch using HTML code isn't a pleasant process, even when you know what you are doing. The website can be built using WYSIWYG Web Builder with using the element similar to the package published on the desktop: text and images placed in frames and tables on the page, so very little surprised when most of the efforts to make the web become a experience user-friendly than. the controls do you use to build your pages.
WYSIWYG Web...
</description></item><item><title>Download Perfectly Clear WorkBench 5.0.1.3068</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 01:46:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfectly-clear-workbench-6892.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfectly-clear-workbench-6892.html
</guid><description>
Perfectly Clear Workbench is an application that uses image editing libraries Perfectly Clear by Athentech and is provided to demonstrate the capabilities of the Perfectly Clear processing libraries, which recognize faces and allow quick export of processing settings for use.
One of the key features in Workbench is the ability to "export to API" when saving a Preset. This allows you to make image edits in Workbench and adjust the settings to suit your editing style and needs. You can...
</description></item><item><title>Download ActivePresenter Professional 10.1.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 01:45:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-activepresenter-professional-895.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-activepresenter-professional-895.html
</guid><description>
ActivePresenter Professional is a professional software to create video screencast, development, instructions for use, documents, and presentations, interactive training. In addition, ActivePresenter allows you to edit audio / video adjust interface content and specify the script branching with ease and efficiency. HTML5 support latest web standards and ability to integrate with management systems, learning content created with activepresenter can be delivered to virtually any device and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Winxvideo AI 4.7.0.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 01:44:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winxvideo-ai-10981.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winxvideo-ai-10981.html
</guid><description>
Winxvideo AI is an innovative video editing app that leverages the power of artificial intelligence to provide users with advanced video editing capabilities. With advanced features and a user-friendly interface, Winxvideo AI is designed to streamline the video editing process and empower creators to create professional-quality videos.
Winxvideo AI meets all your audio/video conversion needs and compresses your 4K/8K footage from GB to MB without compromising on quality, powered by...
</description></item><item><title>Download Privacy Eraser Free 6.26.0 Build 5480</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 01:43:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-privacy-eraser-free-9160.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-privacy-eraser-free-9160.html
</guid><description>
Privacy Eraser is a software tool that helps protect user privacy by securely erasing or deleting unwanted data from their computer or device. This tool is designed to delete browsing history, cookies, cache, temporary files and other sensitive information that may be stored on the computer.
Privacy Eraser can be used to clear browsing history of popular web browsers such as Google Chrome, Mozilla Firefox and Microsoft Edge. It can also clear the history and cache of other applications,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Abelssoft YouTube Song Downloader Plus 2026 v26.05</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 01:43:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-abelssoft-youtube-song-downloader-plus-111.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-abelssoft-youtube-song-downloader-plus-111.html
</guid><description>
Abelssoft YouTube Song Downloader Plus 2018.18.17 Program YouTube Song Downloader Plus will help you search the music and video files from YouTube, after you can download them at. To search for music you just need to enter song name in the required field and you will get results, then you can download all videos and audio files. The program can search the entire album, this function will help to find individual songs from separate albums, because of this we specify the name of the artist...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tails 7.4.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 01:42:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tails-3241.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tails-3241.html
</guid><description>
Tails is a live operating system that you can boot on almost any computer from a USB memory stick or DVD. Tails does this by using the distribution classic Gnome of Linux. The top navigation bar allows you quick access to "Applications" and "Places" so you can easily access what you need quickly and easily and not lost.
Tails - independent operating System for security
Menu "apps" provide shortcuts for bundled software, including graphics, audio and video, office, system tools, and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Abelssoft SendMe (Send2Phone) 2026 v2.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 01:42:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-abelssoft-send2phone-2198.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-abelssoft-send2phone-2198.html
</guid><description>
Abelssoft Send2Phone is a program that allows you to send files from personal computer to phone your mobile, you can now easily share links, images, any files from PC to mobile or vice versa. Traffic will be encrypted using AES-256, so the authors assure you that you should not worry about blocking data, but I won't believe in a hundred percent. Thanks to the user interface simple, clear and pleasant. you can send the file just by a click of the mouse, the software can be integrated into...
</description></item><item><title>Download DLNow Video Downloader 1.55.2026.01.29</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 01:41:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dlnow-video-downloader-3843.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dlnow-video-downloader-3843.html
</guid><description>
DLNow Video Downloader  is a small, fast, useful, practical and powerful application that will allow you to easily download video content from the web and major social networks. DLNow Video Downloader comes with a clean and simple interface. DLNow Video Downloader allows you to save downloaded videos into a variety of formats, including .mpeg, .avi, .flv, .wmv. All you have to do is paste the web URL of the video into the tool, use Add and the document will be downloaded to the specified...
</description></item><item><title>Download Any Video Downloader Pro 10.1.6</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 01:41:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-video-downloader-pro-3731.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-video-downloader-pro-3731.html
</guid><description>
Any Video Downloader Pro is software support you can download video HD 720p, 1080p, 2K, 4K and 8K from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion, Vimeo, Metacafe and thousands of video sharing sites, other. It is a tool to speed up multi-threading can speed up your download faster up to 5 times. This helpful program support download at the same time. Any Video Downloader Pro lets you download multiple videos at the same time. Moreover, it allows you to pause and resume downloads if you need more...
</description></item><item><title>Download Hasleo Disk Clone 5.6.2.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 01:41:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hasleo-disk-clone-6017.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hasleo-disk-clone-6017.html
</guid><description>
Hasleo Disk Clone is a free Windows copy software and all of one can help you move Windows to another disk, copy one disk to another or copy a partition to another.
The benefits of Hasleo Disk Clone:
1. Move Windows to SSD or HDD (smaller or larger) without reinstalling Windows and applications.
2. Copy one disc to another (smaller or larger) disk as backup.
3. Copy a partition to another location without losing any data.
Features of Hasleo Disk Clone
	System, Disk and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Gitea Enterprise 24.8.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 01:40:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gitea-enterprise-11663.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gitea-enterprise-11663.html
</guid><description>
Gitea Enterprise is an enhanced version of the open source project Gitea. It includes all the functionalities of Gitea and is designed to meet the needs of enterprise-level users. Gitea Enterprise is designed to be lightweight, easy to use, and highly customizable, making it an ideal choice for both small teams and large organizations.
Why choose Gitea Enterprise?
	While maintaining the core benefits of Gitea, Gitea Enterprise offers additional benefits such as providing advanced...
</description></item><item><title>Download KS DB Merge Tools for Cross-DBMS 1.17</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 01:40:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ks-db-merge-tools-for-cross-dbms-12825.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ks-db-merge-tools-for-cross-dbms-12825.html
</guid><description>
Designed specifically for comparing two different databases, KS DB Merge Tools for Cross-DBMS provides a fast way to run comparisons in parallel and ensure the databases are synchronized. It can run side-by-side comparisons of schemas, data, and programming objects, highlighting differences, so you can easily synchronize two databases.
Key Features
	Compare both schema and data across different DBMS
	Quick filters to show all/new/changed
	Merge table data changes in both...
</description></item><item><title>Download Solid Explorer File Manager 3.3.0 build 303001</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 01:38:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-solid-explorer-file-manager-8924.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-solid-explorer-file-manager-8924.html
</guid><description>
Solid Explorer is a file management application inspired by old file management applications. Solid Explorer is a popular file management app for Android devices that allows users to manage and organize their files and folders in an intuitive and user-friendly interface. It offers many features that make it stand out from other file management apps.
Solid Explorer allows you to navigate to files stored on your device and automatically organize them into collections. You can view,...
</description></item><item><title>Download SD Card Test Pro 3.1 build 91</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 01:38:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sd-card-test-pro-8928.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sd-card-test-pro-8928.html
</guid><description>
SD Card Test Pro is an application for Android devices that allows users to test the performance and speed of SD cards. This application is designed to help users determine whether their SD card is functioning properly and whether it is capable of meeting their performance and memory needs.
Features of SD Card Test Pro
	Measuring the speed of an external (removable) SD card
	Measure your internal memory speed
	Verify written data: detect damaged or fake cards
	Read/write tests in...
</description></item><item><title>Download Photo Lab Picture Editor &amp;amp; Art 3.13.82</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 01:38:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-photo-lab-picture-editor-art-13190.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-photo-lab-picture-editor-art-13190.html
</guid><description>
Join AI Photo Lab photo editor that lets you edit photos with face filters for photos, fashion photo effects and many photo art ideas. Amazing face collage maker, photo frames, photo effects and filters are here for you to enjoy. A smart and fast new way to turn any photo into a work of art — choose from over 50 preset styles and experience enhanced photo editing with the introduction of AI photo styles.
Key Features
	Photo Frames: Whether you want to highlight a memorable moment or...
</description></item></channel></rss>