<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 21:35:50 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 21:35:50 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Angry IP Scanner 3.9.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 00:35:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-angry-ip-scanner-2138.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-angry-ip-scanner-2138.html
</guid><description>
Angry IP Scanner can scan IP addresses in any range as well as any port of them. It is multi-platform and lightweight. Does not require any installation, it can be copied and used freely anywhere. Angry IP Scanner simply pings each IP address to check if it's alive or not, then optionally it is resolving the server name of it, determines the MAC address, scans ports, etc., the Amount of gathered data about each host can be extended by plugin.
Angry IP Scanner - Scan IP address
Scan...
</description></item><item><title>Download Internet Video Downloader 7.5</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 00:29:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hdapplications-hd-downloader-6041.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hdapplications-hd-downloader-6041.html
</guid><description>
Internet Video Downloader is a small tool designed to help you download video clips from YouTube, Dailymotion and many other similar sites with high quality that can easily run on smartphones, tablets or the latest Xbox devices. After the quick and simple installation process, you will be welcomed by a user-friendly interface without the ability to cause any problems for you.
Although you can set the app start to download immediately, but you can also create a download list that can be...
</description></item><item><title>Download Master Packager Pro 25.6.9358</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 00:29:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-master-packager-pro-7982.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-master-packager-pro-7982.html
</guid><description>
Master Packager Pro is an application packaging tool for creating and editing Microsoft Windows Installer (MSI) files and repackaging other installations to MSI format. Its job is to make application packaging easy, fast, accessible to everyone from freelancers, small companies, and application packaging businesses.
Features of Master Packager Pro
	Create MSI and MST files from scratch or modify the Vendor Microsoft Windows installer.
	Simple design made to be as user-friendly as...
</description></item><item><title>Download Robin YouTube Video Downloader Pro 6.16</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 00:28:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-video-downloader-pro-2828.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-video-downloader-pro-2828.html
</guid><description>
YouTube Video Downloader Pro is a Windows application professional to download and convert videos from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion and thousands of video sharing sites, other. It accelerates your download up to 5 times. YouTube Video Downloader Pro allows you to download multiple videos at the same time. It also allows you to pause, resume and cancel a download at any time.
YouTube Video Downloader Pro - Download online videos on social networks
Features of YouTube Video Downloader...
</description></item><item><title>Download App Builder 2025.23</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 00:28:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-app-builder-241.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-app-builder-241.html
</guid><description>
App Builder is a software application developer to help create and design apps, HTML5, web app, web app PWA on both platforms mobile and desktop. App Builder is professional software supports users to create the program HTML5 without writing code. It is very easy to use, suitable with all users who lack of professional knowledge in the field of programming and application design.
App Builder brings to 22 different themes that users can use to design for your app. You can choose 1 or a...
</description></item><item><title>Download TubeDownload Pro 6.29</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 00:27:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubedownload-pro-12035.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubedownload-pro-12035.html
</guid><description>
TubeDownload Pro is a professional Windows application for downloading your favorite videos from YouTube and hundreds of other video sites. TubeDownload Pro can increase download speed up to 500% or even more.
Features of TubeDownload Pro
	Download your favorite videos from YouTube and hundreds of other video sites.
	Increase download speed up to 500% or even more.
	Download 720p, 1080p, 2K, 4K and 8K HD videos from YouTube.
	Download entire playlists in just a few clicks.
	Download...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT-DL 11.5</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 00:27:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-dl-5876.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-dl-5876.html
</guid><description>
YT-DL is a small program to download videos from YouTube and other video sites. Our goal is to make the program as simple as its name.
The features of YT-DL
	Download the video from YouTube and other video sites
	Increase download speed up to 400%
	Download multiple videos at the same time
	Pause and continue to download at any time
	Preview video content while downloading
</description></item><item><title>Download FTPGetter Professional 5.97.0.291</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 00:27:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ftpgetter-professional-1550.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ftpgetter-professional-1550.html
</guid><description>
FTPGetter Professional is software that automates the uploading and downloading of files, allowing scheduling file transfer between your computer with the FTP server and SFTP remote. If you often access FTP / SFTP to sync files between local computer and remote PC, to update your website or upload images, webcam, FTPGetter will save you lots of time and effort.
FTPGetter Professional comes with emulator terminal integration, allowing you to connect and execute commands on remote server...
</description></item><item><title>Download FX Science Tools MultiDocs 25.08.19</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 00:26:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fx-science-tools-3744.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fx-science-tools-3744.html
</guid><description>
FX Science Tools provided to teachers of chemistry and physics the effective means to create equations and chemical structures. Just type and create. FX Chem FX Chem makes writing chemical equations become simple. You just type and FX Chem know enough about chemistry to put all the components of the equation at the right point. FX Chem can even create the chemical equations for nuclear - a very difficult thing in the Word. FX ChemSturation FX ChemSturation made the organic structure, what...
</description></item><item><title>Download Social Media Downloader 7.7</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 00:25:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-socialmediaapps-facebook-video-downloader-3742.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-socialmediaapps-facebook-video-downloader-3742.html
</guid><description>
SocialVideo Downloader (formerly SocialMediaApps Facebook Video Downloader) is a Windows application to download and convert your favorite videos from Facebook and hundreds of other video sharing sites. It increases your loading speed by up to 500%, or even more! The application has a simple and intuitive user interface, its main functions and features are quite obvious to anyone. , regardless of prior experience with similar purpose tools.
&amp;nbsp;
SocialVideo Downloader
The main...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Geek YTDL Pro 11.5</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 00:25:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-geek-ytdl-pro-9895.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-geek-ytdl-pro-9895.html
</guid><description>
YT Geek YTDL Pro is software that helps users easily download videos from YouTube and hundreds of other video sites. It is very easy to use, just paste the video URL and you can download the video while keeping the original quality. Not only videos on Youtube, users can download any video from social networking sites like Facebook, Vimeo, Myspace video,...
Features of YT Geek YTDL Pro
	Download videos from YouTube and other video sites.
	Increase download speed up to 400%.
	Download...
</description></item><item><title>Download RE:VisionFX Color Genius Plus 2025.4</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 21:34:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-revisionfx-color-genius-plus-14070.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-revisionfx-color-genius-plus-14070.html
</guid><description>
RE:VisionFX Color Genius Plus is a one-click, AI-powered video enhancement tool designed to automatically color correct and enhance videos. It is available as a standalone application and a plugin for various video editing software such as After Effects, Premiere Pro, Resolve, and others.
Key Features
	Simple drag-and-drop interface with in/out point settings, intensity, and color balance adjustments.
	Automatically restore highlights, improve contours and depth, enhance skin tones,...
</description></item><item><title>Download MobiPDF: PDF Editor &amp;amp; Scanner 11.8.267269</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 19:55:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pdf-extra-scan-edit-sign-8390.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pdf-extra-scan-edit-sign-8390.html
</guid><description>
PDF Extra PDF Editor &amp;amp; Scanner is a mobile application that allows users to create, edit and sign PDF documents on their Android or iOS devices. It includes many tools and features that make it easy to work with PDF files, including scanning, editing, and signing. This application also allows users to combine multiple PDF files into a single document and export PDF files in various file formats, such as JPEG, PNG, and Microsoft Word.
Features of PDF Extra PDF Editor &amp;amp;...
</description></item><item><title>Download MobiOffice: Word, Sheets, PDF 15.8.57529</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 19:55:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-officesuite-word-sheets-pdf-8508.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-officesuite-word-sheets-pdf-8508.html
</guid><description>
OfficeSuite allows you to easily view, edit, and create Word, Excel, and PowerPoint documents and perform advanced PDF operations. Our integrated file manager, Chat app with document exchange capabilities, and tons of other handy tools make this the most feature-rich mobile office solution available on Android. Pre-installed by leading manufacturers including Sony, ZTE, Amazon, Sharp, Acer, CAT, Alcatel, Kyocera, Toshiba, etc.
Features of OfficeSuite for Android
	View, create, and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Photo Studio PRO 2.8.5.4438</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 19:55:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-photo-studio-pro-8247.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-photo-studio-pro-8247.html
</guid><description>
Photo Studio APK is a powerful multifunctional photo editing application for photographers of all levels. It contains a huge set of editing tools for basic and advanced editing of your photos. Turn each of your photos into a finished work of art using a variety of effects, filters, text editing and color enhancement tools, and many other available features.
Features of Photo Studio Pro APK
	More than 200 unique filters, amazing special effects, large collection of picture-in-picture...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Photoshop Express Photo Editor 17.7.12 build 1986</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 19:54:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-photoshop-express-photo-editor-02en-8249.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-photoshop-express-photo-editor-02en-8249.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Photoshop Express is a mobile photo editing app that allows users to edit photos quickly and easily on their Android devices. Join millions of creators who trust and use Adobe Photoshop Express, one of the best photo editors and collage makers on Android for fast, easy, and powerful editing on mobile devices.
Premium version / No Adobe ID account required
Features of Adobe Photoshop Express APK
	Basic photo editing: Users can crop, rotate, adjust brightness, contrast and...
</description></item><item><title>Download AnExplorer Pro File Transfer 5.8.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 19:54:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-file-manager-pro-tv-usb-otg-8358.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-file-manager-pro-tv-usb-otg-8358.html
</guid><description>
AnExplorer File Explorer is a unique file manager for TV and Watch file management tool. It is simple, small, fast and efficient File Explorer. Only file managers support RTL and display the size of folders on storage. It is designed for all devices including Phones, Phablets, Tablets, Watches and TVs. It is completely designed using Material Design.
Pro TV USBOTG File Manager Features
	Full-featured It provides all file management features including cut, copy, delete, rename,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Lightroom Photo &amp;amp; Video Editor 10.5.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 19:53:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-adobe-lightroom-photo-video-editor-8401.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-adobe-lightroom-photo-video-editor-8401.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Photoshop Lightroom is a powerful, free camera app and photo editor that empowers your photography, helping you capture and edit stunning images. Easy image editing tools like sliders and filters simplify photo editing. Edit full-resolution photos, apply photo filters, or start editing photos anytime, anywhere.
It offers a variety of editing tools, including basic adjustments like cropping, rotation, and brightness control as well as advanced features like color grading, selective...
</description></item><item><title>Download Pulsar Music Player Pro 1.13.5 build 280</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 19:53:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pulsar-music-player-pro-9602.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pulsar-music-player-pro-9602.html
</guid><description>
Pulsar Music Player has long been one of the best music players on Android. It is an ad-free offline audio player. Its beautiful user interface matches every detail of material design principles. Pulsar contains almost every feature needed to satisfy all your musical needs, including: seamless playback, lyrics display, interlacing, playback speed adjustment, tag editing, Last recording .fm, Chromecast, voice command, Android Auto, equalizer, music visualizer, equalizer, ReplayGain, sleep...
</description></item><item><title>Download Easy Notes - Note Taking Apps 1.3.21.0811</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 19:52:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-easy-notes-notebook-notepad-8388.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-easy-notes-notebook-notepad-8388.html
</guid><description>
Easy Notes - Great note taking app, Notepad, Notebook, Free Notes is a free easy to use note taking app for notes app. With this easy notebook and notepad app, take quick notes with colorful backgrounds and checklists to organize notes and tasks easily. Use this aesthetic note taker and note taker to add photos or audio to your notes. Easy Notes is a useful notebook and note-taking app for taking notes and organizing work.
Features of Easy Notes - Notebook, Notepad
	Free Notepad and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Elevate - Brain Training Games 5.202.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 19:52:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-elevate-brain-training-games-8564.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-elevate-brain-training-games-8564.html
</guid><description>
Elevate is a brain training program designed to improve speech, processing speed, memory skills, mental math, and more. Each person is provided with their own personalized learning program, which is adjusted over time to maximize results.
The more you practice with Elevate, the more you'll improve key cognitive skills proven to increase productivity, earning potential, and confidence. More than 90% said their vocabulary, memory, math skills and overall acuity improved when they...
</description></item><item><title>Download AccuWeather: Weather Radar 21.1.1-6-rc</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 19:52:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-accuweather-weather-radar-8893.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-accuweather-weather-radar-8893.html
</guid><description>
Weather warnings from AccuWeather are exceptionally accurate. Whether it's windy, sunny or rainy, you can stay one step ahead with AccuWeather weather radar. Be prepared for daily forecasts or sudden changes in weather with live alerts and accurate weather forecasts. Daily weather snapshots provide storm warnings, weather updates and RealFeel Temperature®, helping to predict today's weather.
With AccuWeather's superior accuracy™ for local forecasts, you'll never miss a memorable...
</description></item><item><title>Download Listen Audiobook Player 5.3.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 19:51:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-listen-audiobook-player-8511.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-listen-audiobook-player-8511.html
</guid><description>
Listen Audiobook Player is a mobile app for playing audiobooks on your phone or tablet. It lets you play, pause, rewind, and fast-forward audiobooks with ease, while also providing a convenient way to track your listening progress.
Some key features of Listen Audiobook Player include:
	Library Management: Allows you to store and organize your audiobooks in a virtual library for easy access.
	Bookmark: Automatically saves your listening position so you can pick up where you left...
</description></item><item><title>Download TuneIn Radio Pro - Live Radio 39.8.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 19:51:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-tunein-radio-pro-live-radio-8217.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-tunein-radio-pro-live-radio-8217.html
</guid><description>
TuneIn Radio Pro allows users to listen to many radio stations and podcasts from around the world. The Pro version offers additional features like the ability to record live stations, remove ads, and access more premium content. It is available for download on Google Play Store as an apk file.
All your sounds in one app:
	News: Listen and update live news 24/7 from local, national and global news sources, including CNBC, CNN, MSNBC and FOX News Radio.
	Sports: Listen live to NFL, NHL...
</description></item><item><title>Download ClevCalc - Calculator 2.23.16</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 19:51:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-clevcalc-calculator-8333.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-clevcalc-calculator-8333.html
</guid><description>
ClevCalc - Calculator is a mobile application that provides calculator functionality for Android devices. This is a simple, easy-to-use calculator application that can perform basic mathematical operations such as addition, subtraction, multiplication and division as well as more advanced functions such as square roots, logarithms and trigonometric functions.&amp;lt; /p&amp;gt;
Features of ClevCalc - Calculator
	Basic math operations such as addition, subtraction, multiplication and...
</description></item></channel></rss>