<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 13:45:07 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 13:45:07 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download HTTP Downloader 1.0.6.7</title><pubDate> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 16:35:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-http-downloader-1821.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-http-downloader-1821.html
</guid><description>
HTTP Downloader is a download manager for HTTP protocol(S). Maximize throughput download at your using the port complete input / output high-performance (I / o completion ports). HTTP Downloader can open thousands of connections at the same time and consumes very little system resources. You can Start, pause, stop, and queue up to 100 downloads at the same time and every download can be divided into 100 parts.
HTTP Downloader - Support downloading protocol HTTP
Other features include...
</description></item><item><title>Download Red Button 6.7</title><pubDate> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 16:30:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-red-button-3355.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-red-button-3355.html
</guid><description>
Red Button is a powerful tool for optimization and cleaning your Windows PC. It will delete the junk files and unnecessary components of Windows, free up disk space, delete the Internet activity traces and fingerprint digital, protect your privacy, clean and optimize registry, activate hundreds of Windows installations offline, allowing your computer to run faster and speed up computer performance overall. You will get everything needed for maintaining Windows in a perfect condition....
</description></item><item><title>Download Brave Browser 1.84.132</title><pubDate> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 16:30:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-brave-browser-2874.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-brave-browser-2874.html
</guid><description>
Brave Browser is a browser based on Chromium, the basic principle is that operation fast and privacy of users. The program can block pop-up windows and other ads, plus it blocked the mechanism for monitoring the online activities of your. Therefore, you can purchase and safely browse the website you are interested in without having to worry about the fact that your activity will be monitored and then you will be shown the necessary advertising or service provider of parties...
</description></item><item><title>Download JangaFX EmberGen Enterprise 1.2.5</title><pubDate> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 16:29:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jangafx-embergen-enterprise-9820.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jangafx-embergen-enterprise-9820.html
</guid><description>
JangaFX EmberGen Enterprise is professional grade real-time fluid simulation and particle rendering software developed by JangaFX. It is specially designed to create realistic and high quality fire, smoke and liquid effects for use in various industries, including movies, games, virtual reality, and more.
EmberGen Enterprise provides advanced features and capabilities to meet the needs of large-scale production environments. It allows users to create and simulate dynamic fluid effects...
</description></item><item><title>Download JangaFX LiquiGen 1.0.3</title><pubDate> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 16:29:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jangafx-liquigen-14152.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jangafx-liquigen-14152.html
</guid><description>
JangaFX LiquiGen is a real-time fluid simulation software designed to create fluid simulations such as water, liquids, and dynamic fluid effects. The software uses GPU acceleration to enable near real-time fluid simulation and mesh generation with advanced features such as a PIC/FLIP solver that can simulate swirling water effects including spray, foam, and bubbles. LiquiGen supports the simulation of viscous fluids like honey and oil, reproducing complex behaviors like rolling and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Plug And Mix VIP Bundle 4.1.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 16:28:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-plug-and-mix-vip-bundle-9931.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-plug-and-mix-vip-bundle-9931.html
</guid><description>
Plug And Mix VIP Bundle is a set of 50 high-quality audio plug-ins that will help you achieve great sound in a timely manner. Each plug-in is designed to accomplish just one task, making dialing in effects or processing an audio track incredibly quick and easy.
For example, if you want to add a simple phaser effect to your guitar track, just load the P&amp;amp;M Phaser, try a few presets, adjust the effect with just 2 or 3 knobs and you're good to go. finished the next track.
Visit the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Fiedler Audio Mastering Console 2.0.8</title><pubDate> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 16:28:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fiedler-audio-mastering-console-14200.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fiedler-audio-mastering-console-14200.html
</guid><description>
Do you want to master your ADM/BWF files, just like you've been mastering stereo mixes for decades? Mastering Console is a complete Dolby Atmos mastering solution with OBAM plug-in hosting, conveniently processing your entire Dolby Atmos mix, giving it the perfect look. Create albums with crossfade effects, sophisticated volume metering, and the fastest workflow on the market.
Key Features
	Dolby Atmos Mastering - Dolby Labs approved
	Combine Dolby Atmos and Stereo mixes
	Supports 48...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sante PACS Server PG 4.3.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 16:27:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sante-pacs-server-pg-7540.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sante-pacs-server-pg-7540.html
</guid><description>
Sante PACS Server PG is an HTTP server (web) for DICOM files and a recorder and In CD/DVD with high performance and reliability. It provides connectivity with all the DICOM (CT, MR, US, CR, NM, XA, MG, DX, etc.). The review of the DICOM image can be done with the Sante PACS Viewer.
Integrated web servers can be used as a free cloud server for DICOM files!
</description></item><item><title>Download MusicPod 2.14.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 16:27:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musicpod-11990.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musicpod-11990.html
</guid><description>
MusicPod is a free music, radio, TV and podcast player that allows you to stream your favorite songs, listen to your favorite radio stations and enjoy all your favorite podcasts. in the same place. User-friendly interface and intuitive controls make it easy to navigate through your music library and quickly access your favorite tracks.
MusicPod Features
	Play local audio files (mp3, flac, mp4, ogg)
	Find your local audio library organized by metadata
	Search local audio files sorted...
</description></item><item><title>Download JangaFX GeoGen 0.5.1 Beta</title><pubDate> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 16:26:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jangafx-geogen-13966.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jangafx-geogen-13966.html
</guid><description>
JangaFX GeoGen is a real-time terrain generator, designed to create detailed and realistic landscapes, as well as entire 3D planets. It features a GPU-accelerated, node-based procedural workflow, allowing for non-destructive terrain editing. Users can control terrain features using a variety of nodes, modifiers, and filters, with granularity for noise, erosion, and masks. GeoGen supports high resolution terrain creation (up to 8192x8192 pixels) and planets at various scales with...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sante PACS Server 4.3.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 16:26:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sante-pacs-server-7541.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sante-pacs-server-7541.html
</guid><description>
Sante PACS Server is an HTTP (web) server for DICOM files and a CD/DVD Burn and Print server that offers high performance and reliability at an affordable price. It provides connectivity to all DICOM methods (CT, MR, US, CR, NM, XA, MG, DX, etc.). Reviewing of DICOM images can be done using the Sante PACS Viewer (the system's built-in, full-featured DICOM Viewer). The built-in web server can be used as a free cloud server for DICOM files!
Tools of Sante PACS Server
	The Migration Tool...
</description></item><item><title>Download JangaFX IlluGen 1.0.3</title><pubDate> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 16:25:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jangafx-illugen-13967.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jangafx-illugen-13967.html
</guid><description>
IlluGen is the world's first tool specifically built for VFX and real-time technical content creation. When creating special effects for games, we spend a lot of time fine-tuning cinematic tools to fit our unique content creation workflow. Visual effects are essential to delivering gameplay to players, but we rarely get direct support for the tools we need. We felt it was time to give real-time FX artists the tool of their dreams.
Summarize your workflow
IlluGen was built to summarize...
</description></item><item><title>Download Trillian 6.6 Build 8</title><pubDate> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 16:09:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-trillian-2638.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-trillian-2638.html
</guid><description>
Trillian is the chat help you sign in to more the registered name of a certain service or you can log on at the same time many services in a working window. It integrates multiple services such as Yahoo! MSN, IRC, AIM and ICQ. In addition, you can manage Email accounts, Facebook and Twitter friends - all in just one application.
Login is easy; just click on the network or the appropriate website and log in as normal. Trillian requires access your data (accepted) and post to friends...
</description></item><item><title>Download JPEG Saver 5.43</title><pubDate> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 16:08:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jpeg-saver-4333.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jpeg-saver-4333.html
</guid><description>
JPEG Saver is a display image screen saver allows you to display photos of his favorite form saver Windows screen with the transition effect different. Program JPEG Saver provides many configuration options allow you to customize how to display his image and in what order they are displayed. You can select multiple folder location as the source for pictures, screensavers, and more control images are displayed by setting custom filters based on file name, date and other criteria.
JPEG...
</description></item><item><title>Download Calcpad 7.5.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 16:07:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-calcpad-12576.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-calcpad-12576.html
</guid><description>
Calcpad is free software for mathematical and engineering calculations. It is a flexible and modern programmable calculator with Html report generator. Calcpad uses a simple programming language that is fast and easy to learn. It does not require any special programming skills, which makes it suitable for engineers without any computer programming background. You can create calculation notes simply by writing your formula and text, enclosed in 'quotation marks'.
The program includes...
</description></item><item><title>Download Picture Window Pro 8.0.535</title><pubDate> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 16:06:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-picture-window-pro-7452.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-picture-window-pro-7452.html
</guid><description>
Picture Window Pro is a powerful image editing tool designed for serious photographers with strict creative and quality standards. Its comprehensive set of photo editing and editing tools let you control and shape every aspect of your images.
Picture Window Pro 8 is a complete rewrite of Picture Window Pro 7. It features non-destructive image editing through a novel interface based on an image tree. It also fully supports large, high-resolution displays and can be used in dual monitor...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Photoshop 2026 v27.0.0.25 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 13:31:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-0010-adobe-photoshop-737.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-0010-adobe-photoshop-737.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Photoshop is a powerful raster graphics editor developed by Adobe Systems, primarily used for image editing, photo editing, and graphic design. Currently,&amp;nbsp;Adobe Photoshop 2025 is considered a graphic design software, creating and enhancing images, illustrations, and 3D artwork. In addition, it also supports website and mobile app design, video editing, real-life painting simulation, and more.
Adobe Photoshop 2025 - Graphic design
When it comes to Adobe Photoshop, it is...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe-GenP 3.7.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 12:31:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-genp-0013-9964.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-genp-0013-9964.html
</guid><description>
Adobe-GenP is a patch developed to unlock the latest versions of Adobe Creative Cloud applications 2019, 2020, 2021, 2022, 2023, 2024, 2024, 2025 (such as Photoshop, Premiere Pro) , After Effect....) easily and effectively. GenP is easy to use, works after your one click.
List of supported products:
	Adobe Acrobat DC 2023 - 2025
	Adobe After Effects CC 2019 – 2025, 2026
	Adobe Animate CC 2019 – 2025, 2026
	Adobe Audition CC 2019 – 2025, 2026
	Adobe Bridge CC 2019 – 2025,...
</description></item><item><title>Download PrivaZer Pro Donors 4.0.114</title><pubDate> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 00:16:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-privazer-donors-198.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-privazer-donors-198.html
</guid><description>
PrivaZer Donors  cleans and removes filth traces from the system. Intensive cleaning of unwanted traces of what you've done, viewed, downloaded, deleted, etc. Take ownership of your security and freedom - Free up disk space. Keep your PC snug and secure !!!
With one click, PrivaZer can safely clean: Internet browsers, Index.dat, Cookies, Tor Cookies, Flash Cookies, Silverlight Cookies, DOM Storing, IndexedDB, AppCache Registry, RAM, Pagefile.sys and Hiberfil.sys files.  PrivaZer  can...
</description></item><item><title>Download CyberLink AudioDirector Ultra 2026 v16.0.5822.10</title><pubDate> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 00:16:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-audiodirector-ultra-288.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-audiodirector-ultra-288.html
</guid><description>
Sound is half the movie experience and improving the audio in the project video will greatly enhance the final result. AudioDirector contains advanced tools help edit and edit the audio quickly and simply. With the audio feature and seamless integration with PowerDirector.
We provide CyberLink AudioDirector Ultra editor software, mix, and adjust the soundtrack, effects, audio for video, and all the passages spoken in the video. CyberLink AudioDirector Ultra is the upgrade version of...
</description></item><item><title>Download VideoProc Converter AI 8.5</title><pubDate> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 00:15:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-videoproc-2473.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-videoproc-2473.html
</guid><description>
VideoProc (an improved version of WinX HD Video Converter Deluxe) - processing software the most powerful video designed to edit, cut, crop, merge, adjust, convert and compress (4K) video with full Hardware Acceleration. Is the heir to be improved a lot, VideoProc integrated conversion / compression video UHD, the download at videos (YouTube) with the video editor, gives you the power to control optimal for every video file much music, SD, HD and 4K on your PC. With technology hardware...
</description></item><item><title>Download Capture One Pro 16.7.0.3201 + Enterprise</title><pubDate> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 00:07:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capture-one-pro-624.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capture-one-pro-624.html
</guid><description>
Capture One Pro is the software solution complete photo editing. With powerful tools to organize, color grading, editing grades, and more, you have full control over the images and process his work. Capture One has been developed with quality images and easy to use. Every tool is designed to give you full control over all aspects of the process editing - preserve, restore and optimize all information from the file RAW of you. Full the tool provides the ability to expand to always achieve...
</description></item><item><title>Download Gilisoft Total Repair 11.0.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 00:06:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-total-repair-12836.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-total-repair-12836.html
</guid><description>
Total Repair Toolkit is an all-in-one system maintenance tool that integrates smart diagnosis, in-depth repair, and performance optimization. It has a one-click smart repair engine that can automatically resolve over 500 common problems such as system lag, game crashes, and file corruption. Meanwhile, it provides a professional manual repair module to meet advanced requirements.
Gilisoft Total Repair Features
	Application error repair based on a large DLL library
	In-depth diagnosis...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cisdem Video Compressor 2.4.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 00:06:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cisdem-video-compressor-12046.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cisdem-video-compressor-12046.html
</guid><description>
Cisdem Video Compressor is a software program designed to reduce video file size without losing quality. It provides a user-friendly interface and various compression settings to help users optimize their video files for different purposes, such as sharing online, saving storage space or improve video streaming performance.
Cisdem Video Compressor supports many input video formats, including MP4, MOV, AVI, MKV, etc. It allows users to choose different compression methods, such as...
</description></item><item><title>Download Viber for PC 26.5.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 00:05:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-viber-2406.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-viber-2406.html
</guid><description>
Viber is a software of instant messaging, based on VoIP protocols, multi-platform due to the Viber Media development for smart phones used to send sms and make calls over the internet. Along with text messaging, users can exchange images, video and audio.
Viber - software news message, chat online
This is a program that is quite popular is mainly designed for mobile phones, but now we are talking about the version for Windows, so immediately. It will allow you to send messages to other...
</description></item></channel></rss>