<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 20:11:45 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 20:11:45 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download MPV-EASY Player 0.41.0.3</title><pubDate> Sun, 01 Mar 2026 19:16:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mpv-easy-player-3110.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mpv-easy-player-3110.html
</guid><description>
MPV-EASY Player is movies player based on mpv. It comes with easy to use interface, you can quickly adjust many parameters, the default settings are carefully adjusted will be able to stimulate all the performance of the mpv, so use mpv player simple than before a lot.
Basically, MPV-EASY Player is the assembly and combination of MPV, configuring mpv files, the command lua (including all scripts to be shared by other people on github), and the command js with the to read and fully...
</description></item><item><title>Download Metatogger 7.7.1.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 01 Mar 2026 19:15:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-metatogger-62.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-metatogger-62.html
</guid><description>
Metatogger enables you to tag, rename and arrange the files Ogg Vorbis, FLAC, Speex and MP3 your. It allows you to rename files based on the existing cards of them and also follow the links folder of them (useful if the folder path of your contains artist name, and album are related).
Interface work modern
The interface of the utility is clean and intuitive. Import the audio track into the workspace is done by using the browser files, folder view, or the method of "drag and drop"; you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cockos REAPER 7.62</title><pubDate> Sun, 01 Mar 2026 19:15:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cockos-reaper-889.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cockos-reaper-889.html
</guid><description>
Cockos REAPER is a powerful software for for windows, chp lets you record, arrange, edit, and display the audio waveform multi-track. Cockos REAPER offers an extensive feature set includes many effects and a sample project. REAPER supports ASIO, Kernel Streaming, WaveOut, and DirectSound for playback and recording. It reads the files in WAV, OGG and MP3 files and records WAV files. You can arrange any number of items in any number of tracks and use plug-in sound processing (DirectX and...
</description></item><item><title>Download AllMapSoft Offline Map Maker 8.371</title><pubDate> Sun, 01 Mar 2026 19:14:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-offline-map-maker-656.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-offline-map-maker-656.html
</guid><description>
AllMapSoft Offline Map Maker is software create, organize, offline map from Google Maps, Yahoo maps, Bing maps and Openstreetmap. You can view offline maps downloaded with map viewer offline. And you can zoom out or zoom in the offline map or export map under the file format .BMP with file world xxx.bpw, and can output files xxx.map for OziExplorer. If you want to make a offline map of your city by yourself, it is very useful for you.
Features AllMapSoft Offline Map Maker
	You can...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube Downloader 3.9.18 (2802)</title><pubDate> Sun, 01 Mar 2026 19:13:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube Downloader  is a dedicated software that helps users  downloading youtube videos  Favorites on PC for offline viewing. With MediaHuman YouTube  Downloader  you can download videos from youtube website to your computer with  fast speed , with special software development technology that automatically receives videos from Websites, in addition to the ability to download videos from software websites, can convert downloaded video formats to various formats for the purpose...
</description></item><item><title>Download MultiPar 1.3.3.6 beta</title><pubDate> Sun, 01 Mar 2026 19:12:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-multipar-12575.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-multipar-12575.html
</guid><description>
MultiPar provides multi-functional file and folder protection and more. It will perform file verification, error correction, error detection and recovery to protect your files and folders from deletion, downloading, copying, software and hardware errors, virus infections, tampering Malicious and all kinds of other data corruption can make your day. You can also create an Archive that can be used to check file integrity or to recover damaged documents.
Features of MultiPar
	Friendly,...
</description></item><item><title>Download K-Lite Codec Pack Update 19.5.4</title><pubDate> Sun, 01 Mar 2026 19:11:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-update-5145.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-update-5145.html
</guid><description>
K-Lite Codec Pack Update is the update of the set of codecs and related tools. Codec stands for Compressor-decompressor. Codec is necessary to encode and decode (play) audio and video. K-Lite Codec Pack Update is designed as a user-friendly solution with users to play all movie files your. With Codec Pack K-Lite, you can play 99% of all the movies found on your computer. A number of packages codec is not friendly with computers, as they tend to slow down Windows, break down multimedia...
</description></item><item><title>Download Easy System Utility Pro 1.1.54</title><pubDate> Sun, 01 Mar 2026 19:09:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easy-system-utility-pro-12380.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easy-system-utility-pro-12380.html
</guid><description>
Easy System Utility Pro is a powerful, all-in-one program designed for Windows 10 and 11 users. This versatile tool should be your primary choice to improve your computing experience ! This is the complete version with additional and enhanced features. It will help you easily determine your computer's hardware specifications with a system overview. You can view the operating system, CPU model, GPU, Memory, Motherboard, Network and even drivers.
It also supports launching programs,...
</description></item><item><title>Download AllMapSoft Universal Maps Downloader 10.240</title><pubDate> Sun, 01 Mar 2026 19:09:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-universal-maps-downloader-736.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-universal-maps-downloader-736.html
</guid><description>
AllMapSoft Universal Maps Downloader is software download map images on the computer for offline viewing support many types such as Google Maps, Yahoo maps, Bing maps, OpenStreet Maps, Yandex Maps, Ovi Maps, MapQuest Maps. All the downloaded photos will be saved on disk. You can view downloaded maps by Maps Viewer Or you can combine them into one big bmp, or jpg file tif by Maps Combiner, and also you can export all the tiles into a database format MBTiles.
AllMapSoft Universal Maps...
</description></item><item><title>Download Markdown Monster 4.1.7</title><pubDate> Sun, 01 Mar 2026 19:06:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-markdown-monster-2640.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-markdown-monster-2640.html
</guid><description>
Markdown Monster is the edit and view Markdown allows you to edit Markdown by syntax highlighting and fast text input. Live preview can collapse, synchronized allows you to see the output of when you enter. You can easily embed images, links, emoticons and code in text form or by using the support UI lightness of we to simplify many operations. You can also paste and drag images directly into the editor.
Markdown Monster is a solution comprehensive software designed to solve almost any...
</description></item><item><title>Download Fan Control v261</title><pubDate> Sun, 01 Mar 2026 19:05:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fancontrol-5749.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fancontrol-5749.html
</guid><description>
FanControl is a highly customizable fan control software for Windows. Stay in control of every aspect of your PC's GPU and CPU fan with the help of this highly customizable fan control app.
Features of FanControl
	Save, edit and load multiple configurations
	Multiple temperature sources (CPU, GPU, motherboard, hard drive, ".sensor" files)
	Custom fan curve
	Fine tune fan control response with steps,% start,% stop, response time and delay
	Mix different curves and sensors...
</description></item><item><title>Download ReShade 6.7.3</title><pubDate> Sun, 01 Mar 2026 18:49:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-450-3227.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-450-3227.html
</guid><description>
ReShade is an open Source tool help improve the look of the old games on modern video cards as well as allow additional display technology / new video over on the old game doesn't support the technology that.
ReShade, technically, is a tool processing general for the games and video software. Imagine you see your favorite game yourself with the obscure-around, effects market the true depth or color correction. Function ReShade by showing in an automatic way and general access to...
</description></item><item><title>Download RFFlow 5.07 Revision 1</title><pubDate> Sun, 01 Mar 2026 18:48:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rfflow-13326.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rfflow-13326.html
</guid><description>
RFFlow is a software program for drawing flowcharts, organizational charts and other diagrams. RFFlow works well with Microsoft Office and Corel WordPerfect Office. After drawing a diagram, you can copy and paste it into Microsoft Word Microsoft Word Icon, Microsoft PowerPoint Microsoft PowerPoint Icon, Corel WordPerfect Corel WordPerfect Icon or any other Windows Application.
RFFlow supports Object Linking and Embedding in Windows as an OLE Server. This makes it very easy to use RFFlow...
</description></item><item><title>Download Withdata DataFileSplitter 2.4.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 01 Mar 2026 16:02:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-withdata-datafilesplitter-14585.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-withdata-datafilesplitter-14585.html
</guid><description>
Split large CSV, TSV, JSON, XML, TXT, Excel, SQL, and LOG files in minutes with fully local processing capabilities. No data upload required, no security risks - perfect for business data analysis and processing.
DataFileSplitter's features meet all your needs
	DataFileSplitter provides flexible splitting options to meet all your large data file processing requirements.
	All file splitting takes place on your local device - no data is lost Uploaded to our servers. Ensuring complete...
</description></item><item><title>Download Privacy Eraser Pro 6.27.0.5500</title><pubDate> Sun, 01 Mar 2026 02:41:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-privacy-eraser-1141.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-privacy-eraser-1141.html
</guid><description>
Privacy Eraser is the cleanup for computer help to clear the tracks, junk files and traces of recent activity of the computer. Privacy Eraser support the popular web browsers like Internet Explorer, Mozilla Firefox, Google Chrome, Safari and Opera. The program can quickly erase the browser cache, cookies, browsing history, website history, website URL entered, form data, auto complete, file index.dat, file swapping, temporary directory and the position in other common.
Privacy Eraser -...
</description></item><item><title>Download Perfectly Clear WorkBench 5.0.3.3125</title><pubDate> Sun, 01 Mar 2026 02:40:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfectly-clear-workbench-6892.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfectly-clear-workbench-6892.html
</guid><description>
Perfectly Clear Workbench is an application that uses image editing libraries Perfectly Clear by Athentech and is provided to demonstrate the capabilities of the Perfectly Clear processing libraries, which recognize faces and allow quick export of processing settings for use.
One of the key features in Workbench is the ability to "export to API" when saving a Preset. This allows you to make image edits in Workbench and adjust the settings to suit your editing style and needs. You can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Privacy Eraser Free 6.27.0.5500</title><pubDate> Sun, 01 Mar 2026 02:40:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-privacy-eraser-free-9160.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-privacy-eraser-free-9160.html
</guid><description>
Privacy Eraser is a software tool that helps protect user privacy by securely erasing or deleting unwanted data from their computer or device. This tool is designed to delete browsing history, cookies, cache, temporary files and other sensitive information that may be stored on the computer.
Privacy Eraser can be used to clear browsing history of popular web browsers such as Google Chrome, Mozilla Firefox and Microsoft Edge. It can also clear the history and cache of other applications,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Topaz Photo Pro 1.3.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 01 Mar 2026 02:39:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-photo-ai-8105.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-photo-ai-8105.html
</guid><description>
What is Topaz Photo AI?
Topaz Photo AI is a professional software that automatically adjusts for your image quality needs. Simply import images into Topaz Photo AI and it will use specially trained AI models to first detect unique details, clarity, and resolution issues before applying the intelligently adjusts to maximize your image quality.
For users experienced with Topaz Labs image quality applications, it combines the functionality of DeNoise AI, Sharpen AI and Gigapixel AI into...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ant Download Manager Pro 2.16.7 Build 92593</title><pubDate> Sun, 01 Mar 2026 02:39:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ant-download-manager-pro-137.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ant-download-manager-pro-137.html
</guid><description>
Ant Download Manager Pro is software support download has the same features as IDM, even it has many prominent features, more user friendly more and have speed download data incredible. Ant Download Manager is a Internet content downloader quickly with support download at video! Function: fully Integrated with the web browsers most popular: Internet Explorer 8+, Mozilla Firefox 32 +, Google Chrome 31+ and the copies of them (Pale Moon, Opera, Vivaldi, Slimjet, ComodoDragon, etc.). you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Advanced Installer Architect 23.5.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 01 Mar 2026 02:38:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-installer-128.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-installer-128.html
</guid><description>
Advanced Installer is a Windows utility designed to help you build the package Windows Installer in a working environment clean and intuitive.
Although it has many parameters dedicated but the user interface is very simple and gives users the ability to create new projects by selecting the type, namely installer (for example: application Visual Studio or .NET, pack 32/64-bit mixture), Java , updates, support, mobile devices, and other things.
Advanced Installer - An environment for...
</description></item><item><title>Download PassFab 4EasyPartition 3.10.1.11</title><pubDate> Sun, 01 Mar 2026 02:37:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-passfab-4easypartition-7983.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-passfab-4easypartition-7983.html
</guid><description>
After using your PC for many years, there are bound to be many files you want to transfer to your new PC. PassFab 4EasyPartition can perform a one-click migration saving you hours of reinstalling operating systems and applications. It has an intuitive interface and step-by-step wizard that makes migrating the system in just a few steps. PassFab 4EasyPartition will effectively solve the problem of low disk space, speed up your computer and make it run faster.
Features of PassFab...
</description></item><item><title>Download Telestream Wirecast Pro 16.5.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 01 Mar 2026 02:36:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-telestream-wirecast-pro-739.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-telestream-wirecast-pro-739.html
</guid><description>
Telestream Wirecast Pro is software to broadcast live video, turn your computer into a tv studio directly. Live streaming with just your webcam or connect multiple cameras, scoreboard, graphics, and guests from far away. Wirecast makes it easy to stream great-looking live and pre-recorded video to Facebook Live, YouTube, Twitter, Periscope and many more.
Telestream Wirecast Pro - live broadcast
Wirecast is used everywhere to transmit online your program to OTT and the social platform....
</description></item><item><title>Download Fast Video Cutter Joiner 7.0.3</title><pubDate> Sun, 01 Mar 2026 02:35:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fast-video-cutter-joiner-7542.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fast-video-cutter-joiner-7542.html
</guid><description>
Fast Video Cutter Joiner is a fast video cutter and joiner with an easy to use interface. It allows users to trim parts of a video quickly while maintaining the quality of the original video. It supports various formats like AVI, MPEG, MP4, WMV, 3GP, FLV...
This tool helps you to cut video files into small parts, to keep only the parts you need and remove unwanted parts like trailers and advertisements in a movie. The clips you cut can then be used for other video productions or for a...
</description></item><item><title>Download Helium Music Manager Premium 18.0.697</title><pubDate> Sun, 01 Mar 2026 02:35:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-helium-music-manager-premium-164.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-helium-music-manager-premium-164.html
</guid><description>
Helium Music Manager is a music manager that can rip, tag, play, browse, search, rename, burn and synchronize your music with the mobile. You can control your music collection with Helium Music Manager. Stop using time looking for the file on your computer or looking through CDS, vinyl records and tapes - instead, simply enjoy and explore your music! Helium Music Manager can replace the ripper, the player, tag editor and related software to audio your other.
Helium Music Manager...
</description></item><item><title>Download 4DDiG Partition Manager 3.10.1.11</title><pubDate> Sun, 01 Mar 2026 02:34:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4ddig-partition-manager-2024-9781.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4ddig-partition-manager-2024-9781.html
</guid><description>
4DDiG Partition Manager is a powerful Windows disk partition software expert in system migration, disk cloning and disk partition management. It can effectively clone your entire disk or partition, providing a reliable solution for data backup.
This is Windows 10 fast system and data transfer solution &amp;amp; 11. 4DDiG Partition Manager can move the system and large files or folders from one disk partition to a larger one with just one click. Or you can use it to move the system and large...
</description></item></channel></rss>