<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:59:41 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:59:41 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download CalendarTask (formerly DesktopCal) 3.26.262.8321</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 00:11:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopcal-1831.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopcal-1831.html
</guid><description>
CalendarTask (formerly DesktopCal) is a simple desktop calendar that blends into your desktop without blocking access to your desktop icons. You can double-click on a date to quickly add notes and also jump to specific dates in the past or future.
CalendarTask - Computer calendar
CalendarTask can use your current wallpaper or loop through images from your folder and update your desktop every few minutes. The program helps you make appointments, make plans... Not only that, the Screen...
</description></item><item><title>Download CapCut PC 7.7.0.3143 / 7.8.0.3245 Beta 6</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 00:10:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capcut-pc-9995.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capcut-pc-9995.html
</guid><description>
CapCut PC is a simple video editing tool that you can freely use anywhere. You can create videos on your browser, desktop and laptop, or on your phone. Versatile editing, magical AI tools, team collaboration, and built-in assets. Create videos in a whole new way.
You can edit videos based on editing the timeline, in the process you can add different elements and effects to the video to give the best effect to your work. It is a simple and intuitive set of editing tools and effects that...
</description></item><item><title>Download Better File Rename 6.29</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 00:08:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-better-file-rename-1433.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-better-file-rename-1433.html
</guid><description>
Better File Rename is software rename files, the most comprehensive with a lot of functions to handle, rename files, add, remove, insert and replace characters... Better File Rename is considered as a handy industrial strength fast, flexible, reliable and easy to use. That is why since 1999, thousands of hobbyists, professionals and businesses depend on to Change the name of the file to better organize and maintain their files.
Better File Rename - Change the name of the file
Better...
</description></item><item><title>Download IObit Driver Booster Pro Portable 13.1.0.171</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 00:07:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iobit-driver-booster-pro-portable-4169.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iobit-driver-booster-pro-portable-4169.html
</guid><description>
IObit Driver Booster Pro Portable is a portable version developed with IObit's most advanced driver update technology, which automatically identifies and scans for outdated, downloaded drivers and install the correct update for you with just one click, saving you a lot of time. In addition, IObit Driver Booster Pro Portable is specially developed to enhance drivers for better gaming performance and ensure better computer performance by improving update security with Restore, Uninstall...
</description></item><item><title>Download Garden Planner 3.8.81</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 00:06:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-garden-planner-186.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-garden-planner-186.html
</guid><description>
Garden Planner : If you want to create a garden plan, create a landscape by activity or simply be curious, then you can download Garden Planner .   Garden Planner is a program that helps the user to design a dream garden through the layout and arrangement of plants, plants, buildings and objects, creating living spaces. style is consistent with the user's criteria and standards.
Garden Planner application is very simple, just select bushes, other plants, trees, pond and drag them into...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare UniConverter Portable 17.1.1.457</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 00:06:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-uniconverter-portable-12162.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-uniconverter-portable-12162.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare UniConverter Portable - a portable version (unofficial), formerly known as Wondershare Video Converter Ultimate, is a comprehensive media conversion software developed by Wondershare. It offers a wide range of features to convert, edit and enhance multimedia files. Convert, download, compress, edit, record videos in 1000 formats and do more.
With this comprehensive program, you can customize your home movies through advanced editing features and get professional work in...
</description></item><item><title>Download ThisIsMyFile 4.48</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 00:05:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thisismyfile-2247.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thisismyfile-2247.html
</guid><description>
ThisIsMyFile is a program that is positive, will remove the open files affected from the appropriate program, and perform necessary action. If it is launch in mode administrator, you may need to know what you do. If not, it leads to instability to the operating system.
ThisIsMyFile - Delete protected files
Application does not need installation, after unpacking the archive file, we immediately start and can use it.We need a little, you just specify a folder or a specific file, then you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Password Depot 19.0.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 00:05:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-password-depot-1048.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-password-depot-1048.html
</guid><description>
Password Depot is a password manager powerful helps organize all your passwords, credit information or software licenses. Password Depot offers the ability to store your passwords in a secure way, ensuring you use the data safe and help you have secure passwords.
Password Depot does not only guarantee security: It also has the ability to convenient to use, customization ability, high flexibility, markedly when interacting with other devices and, last but not last long, flexibility is...
</description></item><item><title>Download XL-Connector 3.6.36.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 00:04:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xl-connector-12415.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xl-connector-12415.html
</guid><description>
XL-Connector is a popular plugin that securely integrates Excel and Salesforce to export, import, refresh and transform data seamlessly with ultra-fast api connection. It provides Salesforce administrators with a comprehensive toolbox that easily performs data and metadata management activities in a familiar Excel environment.
Features
Export from Salesforce to Excel
	Get data from existing Salesforce reports or build your own SOQL queries directly into Excel.
Import data into...
</description></item><item><title>Download Allavsoft Video Downloader Converter Portable 3.28.7.9473</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 00:03:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allavsoft-video-downloader-converter-portable-12064.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allavsoft-video-downloader-converter-portable-12064.html
</guid><description>
Allavsoft Video Downloader Converter Portable is a portable version of the software application that allows users to download videos from various websites and convert them to different formats. It supports popular video sharing platforms such as YouTube Vimeo, Dailymotion and many others.
Besides downloading videos in their original format, Allavsoft also has a one-click feature to download as well as convert downloaded videos to popular video formats like MP4, AVI, WMV, MOV, MPEG-1,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Agisoft Metashape Professional 2.3.0 Build 21848</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 00:03:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-agisoft-metashape-professional-1731.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-agisoft-metashape-professional-1731.html
</guid><description>
Agisoft Metashape (formerly PhotoScan) is a software product independently perform image processing and digital data creation, 3D space used in GIS applications, material cultural heritage and the production visual effects as well as the indirect measurement of the different subjects scale. Technical digital photography is deployed wisely is applied with the method of computer vision led to the system processor, smart auto, on the one hand, can be managed by a new person in the field of...
</description></item><item><title>Download ApowerREC Portable 1.8.3.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 00:02:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-apowerrec-portable-12165.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-apowerrec-portable-12165.html
</guid><description>
ApowerREC Portable (an unofficial portable version) can record anything on your screen, including desktop activities, live streaming video, web meetings, and more. You can record your activity in full screen or in a custom zone, specifically placed on the screen along with the audio, and it has the great ability to keep the video synchronized with the audio. In addition, recording a webcam or taking screenshots with a webcam is also possible, you can record chat videos or make tutorial...
</description></item><item><title>Download Advanced Trigonometry Calculator 2.1.6</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 00:01:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-trigonometry-calculator-2927.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-trigonometry-calculator-2927.html
</guid><description>
Advanced Trigonometry Calculator is a computer advanced and reliable will help you perform complex calculations. This program also can carry is so you can carry on a portable drive and use it on any computer without installation. All what you have to do is enter for your expressions, complex math and click the "Enter" button and the program will provide solutions for your expressions. Utilities use a syntax similar to handheld computer science.
Advanced Trigonometry Calculator - League...
</description></item><item><title>Download Advanced Installer Architect Portable 23.3.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 28 Dec 2025 23:59:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-installer-architect-portable-3537.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-installer-architect-portable-3537.html
</guid><description>
Advanced Installer Architect Portable is a professional software to create the file set for the application. This powerful software allows you to build the installer package for the software in graphics technology based on MSI, EXE, and Windows in a graphics environment simple. The software was designed and released with 5 versions: free, Professional, Java, Enterprise and architect.
Advanced Installer Architect Portable - Create the setup file for the software
Features of Advanced...
</description></item><item><title>Download SIW Technicians Portable 2025 v15.11.1119a</title><pubDate> Sun, 28 Dec 2025 23:58:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-siw-technicians-portable-3583.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-siw-technicians-portable-3583.html
</guid><description>
SIW Technicians Portable is a tool to information system complexity, for Microsoft Windows, check your PC and collect detailed data about the properties and system settings and displays it in a way very easy to understand. SIW Technicians Portable provides full information about the system and the properties of each computer component. The application organizes all the components in the tree view and the menu different arrangement of components respectively. It has a user interface simple...
</description></item><item><title>Download Notepad++ 8.9 + Portable</title><pubDate> Sun, 28 Dec 2025 16:29:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-notepad-1062.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-notepad-1062.html
</guid><description>
Notepad++ is software editor programming editor and edit source code support on Windows platform, working with many other programming languages like ASP, PHP, Java, C#, Python, Jsp... Notepad++ is a source code editor is many programmers choice with many functions than men of it is Notepad.
Notepad++ - tool editor programming
Notepad++ has many features, simple interface, and can combine with many programming languages different. Notepad++ supports you to automatically perform various...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube Downloader 3.9.18 (2512)</title><pubDate> Sun, 28 Dec 2025 16:20:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube Downloader  is a dedicated software that helps users  downloading youtube videos  Favorites on PC for offline viewing. With MediaHuman YouTube  Downloader  you can download videos from youtube website to your computer with  fast speed , with special software development technology that automatically receives videos from Websites, in addition to the ability to download videos from software websites, can convert downloaded video formats to various formats for the purpose...
</description></item><item><title>Download Kotato All Video Downloader Pro 10.0.9</title><pubDate> Sun, 28 Dec 2025 16:19:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kotato-all-video-downloader-pro-5228.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kotato-all-video-downloader-pro-5228.html
</guid><description>
Kotato All Video Downloader Pro is a Windows application professional to download and convert your favorite videos from the video sharing website. It speeds up your downloads up to 5 times! Kotato All Video Downloader Pro can download videos from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion and hundreds of video sharing sites, other. After downloading, you will be able to play them smoother on your PC or your mobile device, even when you don't have Internet access.
The main features of Kotato All...
</description></item><item><title>Download Network LookOut Administrator Pro 5.3.8</title><pubDate> Sun, 28 Dec 2025 16:19:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-network-lookout-administrator-pro-1414.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-network-lookout-administrator-pro-1414.html
</guid><description>
Network LookOut Administrator Pro is application software to control the screen of the computer on the network to help full the right to monitor your computer remotely. Network LookOut Administrator use the most appropriate for LAN network, the benefits that it brought back really great, you can control the computer remotely using the mouse and keyboard , without the need to use these tools other troubles. When employees get into trouble, you only have to help from far away that still...
</description></item><item><title>Download ToolsToo Pro 12.0.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 28 Dec 2025 16:09:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-toolstoo-4430.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-toolstoo-4430.html
</guid><description>
ToolsToo - enhance the capabilities of PowerPoint with the help of additional yield useful and simple this comes with more than 85 powerful tool. Although it may be considered somewhat limiting and likely even too complicated for some people, the PowerPoint, without a doubt, is one of the best options when creating presentations and illustrations. Among other things, the effect of it stems from the fact that it managed to pack a lot of useful features wrapped around a Office UI...
</description></item><item><title>Download WildBit Viewer Pro 6.19 Commercial</title><pubDate> Sun, 28 Dec 2025 16:09:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wildbit-viewer-pro-1694.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wildbit-viewer-pro-1694.html
</guid><description>
WildBit Viewer is compact photo viewer and quick with slideshow and editor. Look in the folder fast, the file list and the thumbnail view. Viewer includes also image info with meta data EXIF support for JPEG and TIFF information and IPTC (IIMV4) (such as information file PhotoShop) from JPEG and TIFF, Thumbview can change the view mode, sorting and thumbnail size is predefined to set thumbnail size quickly.
WildBit Viewer Pro
WildBit Viewer also includes a toolbar shell, you can drop...
</description></item><item><title>Download Net Monitor for Employees Professional 6.4.14</title><pubDate> Sun, 28 Dec 2025 16:08:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-network-lookout-net-monitor-for-employees-professional-2098.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-network-lookout-net-monitor-for-employees-professional-2098.html
</guid><description>
Network LookOut Net Monitor for Employees Professional is a software platform to help manage user activity, gives the ability to inspect and control computer activities, as well as record activity on the screen as AVI file. Net Monitor for Employees Professional allows access from remote computers. This feature proved particularly useful when you want to see the activity of each user on the computer, or assist them perform the work on the computer with the mouse manipulation or the...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter 3.9.18 (2612)</title><pubDate> Sun, 28 Dec 2025 16:01:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-to-mp3-converter-1744.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-to-mp3-converter-1744.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter is the software support download youtube video and convert video to mp3 format fast and most simple. MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter allows you download and convert videos from YouTube and other websites to MP3 format by pasting the YouTube URL into the application. When you paste the URL, the program will display thumbnails for videos and you have the option to customize the title information, artist and album before you begin the process of...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinScan2PDF 9.49 + Portable</title><pubDate> Sun, 28 Dec 2025 16:00:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winscan2pdf-2117.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winscan2pdf-2117.html
</guid><description>
WinScan2PDF is a simple tool that allows you to scan documents from scanner and save them as PDF files. The program also supports multi-page scanning, then will be combined into one PDF document. Useful if your scanning software does not provide PDF conversion.
WinScan2PDF - Scan document to computer
WinScan2PDF allows users to perform scans the entire text or document at the same time to serve for the saved PDF format. Not only that, you also can choose the page any of a text to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Classroom Spy Professional 5.4.13</title><pubDate> Sun, 28 Dec 2025 16:00:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-classroom-spy-professional-916.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-classroom-spy-professional-916.html
</guid><description>
Classroom Spy Professional is a software classroom management effective. Manage and track activities of all the computers of students remotely. Plus, you can share your screen with the activity record of the student, the computer controls for performance, limit the use of the Internet, the application blocks and more.
Classroom Spy Professional - software classroom management
The main features of Classroom Spy Professional
	Display live images of the remote computer.
	You can control...
</description></item></channel></rss>