<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 22:09:56 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 22:09:56 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download TidyWindow 4.7.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 24 Feb 2026 00:08:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tidywindow-14454.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tidywindow-14454.html
</guid><description>
TidyWindow is a Windows desktop assistant that automates developer PC setup, cleanup, diagnostics, software package installation, registry tweaking, and driver updates—powered by a WPF interface and robust PowerShell 7 automation capabilities in the background.
Key Features
	Essentials Repair Center (docs/essentials.md): Queues selected automation tasks Filter for network, Defender, printing, and Windows Update issues. Each task supports preview run, sequential execution, restore...
</description></item><item><title>Download Hasleo Windows ISO Downloader 3.0.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 24 Feb 2026 00:06:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hasleo-windows-iso-downloader-7497.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hasleo-windows-iso-downloader-7497.html
</guid><description>
Hasleo Windows ISO Downloader is a small application that allows us to download the Windows 8.1/10/11 ISO installation from the official Microsoft website. It is a lightweight utility, capable of downloading the latest Windows ISOs from the Microsoft website, simple and straightforward. Users can choose between versions 8.1, 10, and 11 and they can start downloading right away.
If you're looking to install Windows 8.1 or 10, you can choose to download the 32 or 64 bit version through...
</description></item><item><title>Download CyberLink PowerDirector Ultimate 2026 v24.2.1412.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 24 Feb 2026 00:05:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-powerdirector-ultimate-425.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-powerdirector-ultimate-425.html
</guid><description>
CyberLink PowerDirector Ultimate is software editor, edit video and make movies on the computer from a variety of templates are made available, complete with effects, transitions, animations, and music. CyberLink PowerDirector 17 is a combination of video editing software with advanced video editing features powerful. Cblowing need to add your clips into the time line and click on 'Production'!
The tool design video in CyberLink PowerDirector have the ability to customize helps you...
</description></item><item><title>Download ConceptDraw Office 10.2.0.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 24 Feb 2026 00:04:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-concept-draw-office-2031.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-concept-draw-office-2031.html
</guid><description>
ConceptDraw OFFICE v5 is a powerful software specially designed for the business management of all kinds, but also designed the entire interface for any business task you are doing. It consists of three software products to be integrated by technology to exchange data unique. The software combines business diagrams, mind mapping, and software project management. Concept Draw Office v5 is essential to provide charts, diagrams, mind maps, project plans, dashboards, presentations, and more...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDFsam Pro+OCR Enhanced 7.0.81.15223</title><pubDate> Tue, 24 Feb 2026 00:03:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdfsam-enhanced-5124.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdfsam-enhanced-5124.html
</guid><description>
PDFsam Enhanced is edit, PDF professional to convert, review, fill out the form, OCR, signing, security, and edit PDF files. Try the module View and Create free to read any PDF file and convert to PDF from Word, Excel, PowerPoint and many file formats to another.
With PDFsam Enhanced users to easily open and view any PDF file, ePub, or comic books (.cbr / .cbz), see in mode Single, Continuous, or Full screen, navigation, bookmarks, zoom in and zoom out and rotate the page. Convert to...
</description></item><item><title>Download KMPlayer (KMP) 2026.2.23.17 x64 / 4.2.3.32 x86</title><pubDate> Tue, 24 Feb 2026 00:02:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kmplayer-kmp-902.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kmplayer-kmp-902.html
</guid><description>
KMPlayer (KMP) is software watch movies listen to music multi-function for video enthusiasts. KMPlayer development is many types of the format different. KMPlayer has improved on sound quality, images when listening to music and watching movies, the playback speed of video is faster, more codec player is added to the software video decoder is optimized.
KMPlayer also supports a variety of audio formats and video and offers a the interface can be customized with the preview coverflow and...
</description></item><item><title>Download AITextTune 1.7.5</title><pubDate> Tue, 24 Feb 2026 00:00:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aitexttune-12973.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aitexttune-12973.html
</guid><description>
AITextTune is an AI-powered tool designed to enhance and refine text content. It offers features such as improving clarity and coherence, generating summaries, and translating text into multiple languages. Users can easily adjust their writing style from formal to creative. This tool is very flexible and can be used on many different software and platforms.
AITextTune Features
	WRITE PERFECTLY: Improve the clarity and coherence of your writing! Create summaries and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Markdown Monster 4.1.5.5</title><pubDate> Mon, 23 Feb 2026 23:59:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-markdown-monster-2640.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-markdown-monster-2640.html
</guid><description>
Markdown Monster is the edit and view Markdown allows you to edit Markdown by syntax highlighting and fast text input. Live preview can collapse, synchronized allows you to see the output of when you enter. You can easily embed images, links, emoticons and code in text form or by using the support UI lightness of we to simplify many operations. You can also paste and drag images directly into the editor.
Markdown Monster is a solution comprehensive software designed to solve almost any...
</description></item><item><title>Download Xara Photo &amp;amp; Graphic Designer+ 25.1.0.72372</title><pubDate> Mon, 23 Feb 2026 23:59:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xara-photo-graphic-designer-1051.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xara-photo-graphic-designer-1051.html
</guid><description>
Xara Photo &amp;amp; Graphic Designer is photo editing software detail, drawing, creative and professional design. To materialize all the ideas as cut paste photos to print documents and works of art, digital: Get impressive results quickly! Combine text with graphics and images to create your own design for invitations, posters, or post on social media. Design your projects in an elegant way with the text function new in Xara Photo &amp;amp; Graphic Designer.
Xara Photo &amp;amp; Graphic Designer...
</description></item><item><title>Download Screencapt Professional 3.003</title><pubDate> Mon, 23 Feb 2026 23:58:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-screencapt-professional-12260.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-screencapt-professional-12260.html
</guid><description>
Screencapt Professional is powerful Windows software for screen recording that allows you to accurately and easily record any on-screen activity. Whether you want to create tutorials, record webinars, or simply record your favorite games, Screencapt gives you all the tools you need.
With Screencapt, you can record the entire screen, a selected area, or a specific window. This flexibility makes Screencapt the perfect screen recorder for any type of application. Thanks to the built-in...
</description></item><item><title>Download CyberLink PhotoDirector Ultra 2026 v17.2.1413.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 23 Feb 2026 23:57:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-photodirector-ultra-129.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-photodirector-ultra-129.html
</guid><description>
Cyberlink PhotoDirector Ultra is known to be photo editing tools and videos with the effect is extremely rich, help you to change the style for the individual images or the videos of his favorite. This software integrated the 3D engine helps to speed up Video processing, which allows accessing the repository effect online and extract the Videos into the movies 3D Bru-ray, 3D AVCHD.
Cyberlink PhotoDirector Ultra to offer users a more professional tool to handle their images, remove...
</description></item><item><title>Download ConceptDraw MINDMAP 15.1.1.296</title><pubDate> Mon, 23 Feb 2026 23:57:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-conceptdraw-mindmap-5592.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-conceptdraw-mindmap-5592.html
</guid><description>
ConceptDraw MINDMAP 12 is a leading mind mapping software tool that includes a comprehensive set of solutions for designing and building time-saving mind maps. Create mind maps that visually illustrate your thinking process. Organize ideas and data with a comprehensive, flexible, and easy-to-use productivity tool. Creates a wide range of document styles and formats. Make presentations directly from mind maps and then export them to MS PowerPoint or Web pages. Perfect for brainstorming,...
</description></item><item><title>Download JSoft PDF Reducer 8.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 23 Feb 2026 23:56:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jsoft-pdf-reducer-8994.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jsoft-pdf-reducer-8994.html
</guid><description>
JSoft PDF Reducer is a software application designed to compress and reduce the size of PDF files. The program provides many features and tools to optimize PDF files, such as removing unused objects, compressing images, and removing bookmarks and annotations. You are also allowed to rearrange, delete pages, add or remove text, and secure your PDF files with Watermarks, passwords and digital signatures. It's set up in a wizard format, so you'll be guided through the steps.
Features of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Xara Designer Pro+ 25.1.0.72372</title><pubDate> Mon, 23 Feb 2026 23:55:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xara-designer-pro-plus-5361.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xara-designer-pro-plus-5361.html
</guid><description>
Xara Designer Pro Plus is professional software for graphic design, web design, image editing, illustration and DTP. Xara Designer Pro X Optimized packages for your designs. Xara Designer Pro Plus combines graphics and web design, illustration, photo editing, and desktop publishing - all in one compact workspace.
Powerful drawing tools let you draw lines, shapes and curves using vectors and adjust the proportions without losing quality. Your images look sharp to the smallest detail. This...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wipe Pro 2026.02</title><pubDate> Mon, 23 Feb 2026 23:54:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wipe-pro-710.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wipe-pro-710.html
</guid><description>
Wipe Pro is software that helps clean up litter, increase in hard drive space besides also protect your privacy on the Internet, it removes records about personal activity on the computer. You will be able to delete browser history and the cache, the file index.dat, registry, files, cookies, internet history, auto complete, temporary internet files and many other items. This program also delete all activities other individuals that you made when using the PC and regardless of which...
</description></item><item><title>Download ConceptDraw DIAGRAM 17.1.1.316</title><pubDate> Mon, 23 Feb 2026 23:54:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-conceptdraw-diagram-7622.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-conceptdraw-diagram-7622.html
</guid><description>
ConceptDraw DIAGRAM is the world's leading professional and easy-to-use business charting software. ConceptDraw DIAGRAM offers a complete range of business graphic document solutions with thousands of stencils and hundreds of templates for quick diagramming. It is considered a versatile diagramming tool that provides for sharing of drawings and supports team collaboration through presentations and multiple export options.
Features of ConceptDraw DIAGRAM
	A great alternative to MS...
</description></item><item><title>Download Revo Uninstaller 2.6.8</title><pubDate> Mon, 23 Feb 2026 23:53:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-revo-uninstaller-free-6752.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-revo-uninstaller-free-6752.html
</guid><description>
Revo Uninstaller is a freeware that helps you to uninstall software and remove unwanted programs easily. Revo Uninstaller acts as a replacement and complement to the built-in functionality of Windows by running the built-in uninstaller for the program first and then scanning for leftover data, making it obsolete. become your best option when it comes to removing stubborn pieces completely. Programs, temporary files, and other unnecessary program data are left behind after the standard...
</description></item><item><title>Download Syncovery Premium 11.13.0.170</title><pubDate> Mon, 23 Feb 2026 23:52:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncovery-pro-enterprise-232.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncovery-pro-enterprise-232.html
</guid><description>
Syncovery Pro Enterprise is a great application used to back up data and to synchronize personal computers, servers, laptops, notepads and storage online. The software comes with support for FTP and secure FTP servers, SSH, WebDAV, Amazon S3, http, update the part file, ZIP compression, data encryption, and schedule automatic backups.
Syncovery Pro Enterprise have the ability to freely select files and folders across the whole folder hierarchy in tree view and supports email...
</description></item><item><title>Download App Builder 2026.6</title><pubDate> Mon, 23 Feb 2026 23:51:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-app-builder-241.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-app-builder-241.html
</guid><description>
App Builder is a software application developer to help create and design apps, HTML5, web app, web app PWA on both platforms mobile and desktop. App Builder is professional software supports users to create the program HTML5 without writing code. It is very easy to use, suitable with all users who lack of professional knowledge in the field of programming and application design.
App Builder brings to 22 different themes that users can use to design for your app. You can choose 1 or a...
</description></item><item><title>Download Xara Web Designer+ 25.1.0.72372</title><pubDate> Mon, 23 Feb 2026 23:50:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xara-web-designer-premium-1035.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xara-web-designer-premium-1035.html
</guid><description>
Xara Web Designer Premium is software that creates professional websites using a variety of templates are professionally designed are available. Xara Web Designer Premium allows you to create multiple versions of your website, for example, the version for desktop, tablet and mobile devices which you can export as an HTML file individually. Accurately display your website on every terminal, from PC to smartphones and tablets. It's easy and does not require programming knowledge.
Xara Web...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sante DICOM Viewer Pro 14.3.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 23 Feb 2026 23:49:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sante-dicom-viewer-pro-11761.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sante-dicom-viewer-pro-11761.html
</guid><description>
Sante DICOM Viewer Pro is a professional DICOM viewer, anonymizer, converter, PACS client, mini PACS server, patient CD/DVD burner (with viewer) and more. This is a unique program with unique capabilities, designed and developed by us in-house from the ground up, with the most advanced programming tools and is the result of extensive research and development on DICOM image over the past two decades. Sante DICOM Viewer Pro has been developed since 1999 and is one of the most popular...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sante DICOM Editor 10.3.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 23 Feb 2026 23:48:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sante-dicom-editor-11760.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sante-dicom-editor-11760.html
</guid><description>
Sante DICOM Editor is a professional DICOM editor, viewer, anonymizer, converter, dicomizer, PACS client, mini PACS server, patient CD/DVD burner (with viewer) and more that too.
Sante DICOM Editor is the industry's leading post-processing application for editing, converting and processing DICOM files, it is used by most major corporations and medical device manufacturers and is DICOM drafting is chosen by the largest universities and colleges. hospitals around the world. Among other...
</description></item><item><title>Download Fast Video Cutter Joiner 7.0.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 23 Feb 2026 23:48:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fast-video-cutter-joiner-7542.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fast-video-cutter-joiner-7542.html
</guid><description>
Fast Video Cutter Joiner is a fast video cutter and joiner with an easy to use interface. It allows users to trim parts of a video quickly while maintaining the quality of the original video. It supports various formats like AVI, MPEG, MP4, WMV, 3GP, FLV...
This tool helps you to cut video files into small parts, to keep only the parts you need and remove unwanted parts like trailers and advertisements in a movie. The clips you cut can then be used for other video productions or for a...
</description></item><item><title>Download Directory Opus Pro 13.21.6 Beta</title><pubDate> Mon, 23 Feb 2026 23:47:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-opus-pro-779.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-opus-pro-779.html
</guid><description>
Directory Opus Pro is a software replacement for Explorer with traditional strength and function more than any manager other files. Directory Opus Pro full support for high DPI screen (for example 4K and 5K) with the rename dialog is redesigned, with new features. Besides being a recording macro only allows you to perform mass renaming complex that don't need regular expressions. In addition, Directory Opus Pro also enhances the ability to script.Better handling of renaming recursive and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Psiphon 186.20260222</title><pubDate> Mon, 23 Feb 2026 23:46:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-psiphon-7347.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-psiphon-7347.html
</guid><description>
Psiphon is a firewall bypass tool by Psiphon Inc. Uses VPN, SSH and HTTP Proxy technology to give you uncensored access to Internet content. Your Psiphon app automatically learns about new hotspots to maximize your chances of bypassing censorship.
The way the software works is that Psiphon constantly changes the proxy, so the user's IP address is also constantly changing, the server will not detect the user's real address, so you can feel free. roof. access to websites and software...
</description></item></channel></rss>