<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:47:40 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:47:40 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download COAA PlanePlotter 6.7.2.3</title><pubDate> Wed, 13 Aug 2025 16:47:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coaa-planeplotter-7840.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coaa-planeplotter-7840.html
</guid><description>
PlanePlotter receives and decodes digital position reports directly from the aircraft and plots them on a chart. Using PlanePlotter, you can see the radar-like display of all aircraft around you transmitting the appropriate digital messages including ACARS, ADS-B and HFDL.
PlanePlotter Features
	PlanePlotter displays a table showing messages received and decoded from direct plane transmissions.
	PlanePlotter stores all digital data it receives and decodes into a log...
</description></item><item><title>Download Blue Cats Connector 1.41</title><pubDate> Wed, 13 Aug 2025 16:40:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blue-cats-connector-8952.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blue-cats-connector-8952.html
</guid><description>
Blue Cats Connector is an audio streaming plug-in &amp;amp; MIDI can be used to transmit audio and MIDI signals in real time between several computers or applications, or create your own routing in an application with minimal latency. With precise buffer control, you can achieve the lowest latency possible: down to 0 samples, when used in an application.
Plugin provides a flexible and customizable interface that allows users to create complex routing schemes easily. It includes a wide range...
</description></item><item><title>Download Blue Cat Audio Spinal Vibe 1.0.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:46:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blue-cat-audio-spinal-vibe-14047.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blue-cat-audio-spinal-vibe-14047.html
</guid><description>
Spinal Vibe offers up to 3 rotating speakers, with complete control over the rotational behavior of each speaker: you can not only choose their rotation speed and rotation curve, but also independently select the amount of Doppler, amplitude modulation and damping, as well as their acceleration and deceleration characteristics.
The plugin offers a simple control to choose slow or fast speeds and any speeds in between, along with a brake to stop the rotation instantly.
The rotation can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Teletone Audio Silver Spring 1.0.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:43:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-teletone-audio-silver-spring-14046.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-teletone-audio-silver-spring-14046.html
</guid><description>
Silver Spring by Teletone Audio is a virtual audio effects plugin that simulates the Spring Reverb effect. It features 17 legendary analog Spring Reverb effects, meticulously sampled and arranged into five groups.
These effects range from classic studio effects to bolder modulation textures designed to explore space. The product aims to deliver the experience of "instant live Spring Reverb effect", combining classic analog inspiration with the flexibility of modern sound...
</description></item><item><title>Download K-Lite Codec Pack Full 19.1.5</title><pubDate> Wed, 13 Aug 2025 01:44:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-115.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-115.html
</guid><description>
K Lite Codec Pack Full brings pc users an optimal solution for watching movies, listening to music, support most popular format today by using collection codec rich. This software also allows you to refine the quality of videos and music to enjoy, create a list of music and video to comfortable enjoy.
Prompt to software, listen to music, watch movies, currently, part, user will prompt to programs like VLC or KMP ... With VLC, it was too familiar with users, not just watch videos, listen...
</description></item><item><title>Download K-Lite Codec Pack Mega 19.1.5</title><pubDate> Wed, 13 Aug 2025 01:43:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-mega-3202.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-mega-3202.html
</guid><description>
K-Lite Mega Codec Pack is a collection of components needed for audio playback and the video in the player DirectShow like Windows Media Player, Media Center, and Media Player Classic. This is the latest beta version, Pack Codec K-Lite latest stable. The Mega variant is the biggest of the four variants of the codec pack. It provides everything you need to play all audio and video files. In addition, it also contains some codecs ACM / VFW can be used by the application coding / video...
</description></item><item><title>Download Media Player Classic Home Cinema 2.5.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 13 Aug 2025 00:01:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-media-player-classic-home-cinema-2839.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-media-player-classic-home-cinema-2839.html
</guid><description>
Media Player Classic Home Cinema is a multimedia compact for Microsoft Windows 32 bit and 64 bit. MPC mimics the interface of Windows Media Player 6.4, but provides most options and features available in the modern means. Media Player Classic Home Cinema for free 100% no advertising, so you can directly access content and enjoy media playback without being distracted.
With Media Player Classic Home, you can now change the design a multimedia of the custom toolbar. There is a range to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Notepad++ 8.8.4 + Portable</title><pubDate> Wed, 13 Aug 2025 00:00:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-notepad-1062.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-notepad-1062.html
</guid><description>
Notepad++ is software editor programming editor and edit source code support on Windows platform, working with many other programming languages like ASP, PHP, Java, C#, Python, Jsp... Notepad++ is a source code editor is many programmers choice with many functions than men of it is Notepad.
Notepad++ - tool editor programming
Notepad++ has many features, simple interface, and can combine with many programming languages different. Notepad++ supports you to automatically perform various...
</description></item><item><title>Download TeamViewer 15.68.6 + Portable</title><pubDate> Tue, 12 Aug 2025 23:59:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-teamviewer-528.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-teamviewer-528.html
</guid><description>
TeamViewer is software that functions to connect and control the remote computer, the ability to connect with any system anywhere from all over the place. This is a support tool users is very convenient. TeamViewer to help users control remote computer becomes much more simple, help you interact and collaborate with others in the exchange and share of information, instruction manual, application software or fix the computer.
TeamViewer as a revolution of computer science. when you have...
</description></item><item><title>Download Drive SnapShot 1.50.0.1743</title><pubDate> Tue, 12 Aug 2025 23:58:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-drive-snapshot-701.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-drive-snapshot-701.html
</guid><description>
Drive SnapShot is a backup software, Restore disk, including operating system, installed programs, your data and all security attributes - while windows is running and you continue to work. With Drive SnapShot you backup partition or hard drive and it can also create disk image of your system. If a disaster occurs (a virus, trojan or the fixed hard disk), the recover complete and accurate your system will be able to accomplish after only a few minutes. The image file can be mounted as...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare UniConverter 16.5.9.323</title><pubDate> Tue, 12 Aug 2025 23:57:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-uniconverter-4808.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-uniconverter-4808.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare UniConverter ( old name is Wondershare Video Converter Ultimate) which allows you to convert the video format. You can cut, splice, move, or add effects, subtitles a easy way. When using software you easily cut, splice, move, as well as add the effects, the subtitles to the video.... Or can switch the clods SD, HD video to any format popular for use with iPod (Classic, Nano and Touch), iPhone, Apple TV, Zune, PSP, Pocket PC...
Wondershare UniConverter helps convert formats...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube Downloader 3.9.16 (1208)</title><pubDate> Tue, 12 Aug 2025 23:57:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube Downloader  is a dedicated software that helps users  downloading youtube videos  Favorites on PC for offline viewing. With MediaHuman YouTube  Downloader  you can download videos from youtube website to your computer with  fast speed , with special software development technology that automatically receives videos from Websites, in addition to the ability to download videos from software websites, can convert downloaded video formats to various formats for the purpose...
</description></item><item><title>Download SoftMaker FlexiPDF Professional 2025.412.0808</title><pubDate> Tue, 12 Aug 2025 23:56:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-softmaker-flexipdf-professional-1513.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-softmaker-flexipdf-professional-1513.html
</guid><description>
SoftMaker FlexiPDF Professional is the perfect software to edit and create pdf files. With this program, you can easily open any pdf file in environment task simple and easy. Change the text you want. Change the color of text and paragraphs. Like software Word, you can create a section of text or italics. Can you are not satisfied with the font of the pdf, you can open the file and save it with the font you want to pdf. In addition to text, you can add forms, graphics, photos, comments,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Acrobat Pro DC 2025.001.20623 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Tue, 12 Aug 2025 23:56:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-001en-adobe-acrobat-pro-458.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-001en-adobe-acrobat-pro-458.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Acrobat Pro DC is a comprehensive software that helps you create and edit the PDF&amp;nbsp;document, or create form, sign, protect PDF, connect, split PDF, export PDF to various formats. The Acrobat Pro DC is the latest version of Adobe with improvements in the interface with the polished ribbon bar and the ability to create and handle pdf files as well as its male versions.
The highlight of the Acrobat Pro DC is probably the ability to connect, store documents on the cloud, you can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Advanced Renamer Commercial 4.15</title><pubDate> Tue, 12 Aug 2025 23:54:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-renamer-2647.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-renamer-2647.html
</guid><description>
Advanced Renamer is a program to rename multiple files and folders at the same time. By configuring the method name change, the name can be manipulated in many different ways. It's easy to set up a batch job using multiple methods on a large number of files. 14 different modes allow you to change the name, attributes and timestamp of the file in once. The file can also be copied or moved to new location based on information in the file.
The program can rename files in many different ways,...
</description></item><item><title>Download HWiNFO 8.30 Build 5800</title><pubDate> Tue, 12 Aug 2025 23:54:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hwinfo-1828.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hwinfo-1828.html
</guid><description>
HWiNFO (HWiNFO32) is a diagnostic tool and hardware information, recognizes and displays detailed information about all the hardware components of you. HWiNFO will hold the component in the tree view and provide the report easy to read for each category.
HWiNFO - Hardware Diagnostics
HWiNFO is especially useful so you don't have to install it on each computer and completely for free. Just run the direct program and you will have full information of the computer that you need. The...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinTools.net Professional / Premium / Classic 25.9.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 12 Aug 2025 23:53:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wintoolsnet-304.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wintoolsnet-304.html
</guid><description>
WinTools.net is an optimal tool working performance of the operating system and delete the unnecessary program from the hard drive and control the start-up process of Windows.
WinTools.net integrates many useful tools, to support increased processing speed and ability, stable operation for the computer include: Clean Uninstaller, Scan Files, Scan Registry, Start Up, Tweak UI, Net Tweaker, The Privacy. Scan Files are often used to scan the hard drive periodically, search for junk files or...
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 7.1.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 12 Aug 2025 23:53:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-11-7760.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-11-7760.html
</guid><description>
TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 is a program that allows users to discover hidden settings in Windows 11. This application is specially designed for Windows 11, groups many registry settings and distribute them from the easy and secure user interface. With TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 you can move the Windows taskbar to the top and resize the taskbar by editing the registry value. With any application that modifies the registry, we recommend that you have a backup copy...
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 7.1.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 12 Aug 2025 23:53:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-10-7759.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-10-7759.html
</guid><description>
TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 is a utility that allows users to discover hidden settings in Windows 10. This application is specially designed for Windows 10, groups many registry settings and provide them from an easy and secure user interface. With TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 you can move the Windows taskbar to the top and resize the taskbar by editing the registry value. With any application that modifies the registry, we recommend that you have a backup copy to...
</description></item><item><title>Download HWiNFO Portable 8.30.5800</title><pubDate> Tue, 12 Aug 2025 23:52:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hwinfo-portable-11340.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hwinfo-portable-11340.html
</guid><description>
HWiNFO Portable is a professional hardware information and diagnostic tool that supports the latest components, technologies and industry standards. These tools are designed to collect and present the maximum amount of information possible about computer hardware, making them suitable for users looking for driver updates, computer manufacturers, system integrators as well as technical experts. Retrieved information is presented in a logical, easy-to-understand format and can be exported...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter 3.9.16 (1208)</title><pubDate> Tue, 12 Aug 2025 23:52:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-to-mp3-converter-1744.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-to-mp3-converter-1744.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter is the software support download youtube video and convert video to mp3 format fast and most simple. MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter allows you download and convert videos from YouTube and other websites to MP3 format by pasting the YouTube URL into the application. When you paste the URL, the program will display thumbnails for videos and you have the option to customize the title information, artist and album before you begin the process of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Hard Disk Sentinel Pro 6.30.2 Beta</title><pubDate> Tue, 12 Aug 2025 23:48:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hard-disk-sentinel-pro-562.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hard-disk-sentinel-pro-562.html
</guid><description>
Hard Disk Sentinel Pro is a tool for monitoring and optimal performance for hard drive HDD and help diagnose the HDD as well as SSD. Version of Hard Disk Sentinel Pro is a professional version, the most advanced of Hard Disk with many advanced features that meet basic needs, check the hard drive for the user.
The goal of it is to find, test, diagnose and repair the malfunction, hard drive, report and display the health status of the SSD and hard drive failure, decreased performance and...
</description></item><item><title>Download ZHPDiag 2025.8.12.16</title><pubDate> Tue, 12 Aug 2025 23:48:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zhpdiag-1662.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zhpdiag-1662.html
</guid><description>
ZHPDiag software is absolutely free and easy to use to diagnose malware and viruses the risk of damaging the computer. ZHPDiag will detect the threat as virus or other malware has the ability to affect the system, alerting users to these sensitive areas may potentially malicious code.
ZHPDiag - Diagnosis code single
ZHPDiag analysis comprehensive system and detect Trojan, virus, adware, PUP and other types of other malware. Version ZHPLite also have the same function, which helps...
</description></item><item><title>Download EstlCAM 12.143</title><pubDate> Tue, 12 Aug 2025 23:47:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-estlcam-13476.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-estlcam-13476.html
</guid><description>
EstlCAM is a user-friendly CNC and CAM (Computer-Aided Manufacturing) control software, designed to generate toolpaths and G-code for CNC machines, especially suitable for 2D, 2.5D and 3D milling operations. The software supports importing a variety of design file formats, including 2D drawings (.dxf, .svg, .png, .jpg) and 3D models (.stl), allowing users to position, scale, and rotate designs before generating toolpaths.
The software is especially popular among enthusiasts and...
</description></item><item><title>Download TubeMate Downloader 5.21.6</title><pubDate> Tue, 12 Aug 2025 23:47:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubemate-downloader-4250.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubemate-downloader-4250.html
</guid><description>
TubeMate Downloader is a smart application that lets you download any clip you want from the website hosting the main video and convert them in when download at or then. If you need a simple and effective tool to download videos, you can give it a try. With TubeMate Downloader, you can directly drag and drop video link from your browser into the drop-down box or application window to start downloading. You don't even need to copy and paste the video URL.
TubeMate Downloader - Support...
</description></item></channel></rss>