<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 13:39:03 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 13:39:03 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download MDScan + OCR 3.9.87</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Sep 2025 16:21:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-mobile-doc-scanner-mdscan-ocr-8307.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-mobile-doc-scanner-mdscan-ocr-8307.html
</guid><description>
Mobile Doc Scanner (MDS) is an application that allows users to scan, edit and save documents using the Android device's camera. It's designed to work as a portable scanner so you can easily digitize documents, receipts, business cards, and more.
All image processing is done on your device only! No material will be posted online without your wishes! Take photos with your camera, edit them with many advanced features, save to your favorite format and share on social networks, email,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Office Reader - WORD/PDF/EXCEL 2.1.21</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Sep 2025 16:21:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-office-reader-wordpdfexcel-10769.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-office-reader-wordpdfexcel-10769.html
</guid><description>
By using the Office Document Reader application, you can view all documents under one roof. You do not need to install multiple applications to open the application on different platforms. It is a simple, fast and lightweight file viewer, specially designed for those who want to view and edit their documents in one application. This application allows users to manage their documents. Its fast file opening process and interactive layout make this application fun and easy to use.
Office...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sygic GPS Navigation &amp;amp; Maps 25.4.1-2456</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Sep 2025 16:20:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sygic-gps-navigation-maps-8606.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sygic-gps-navigation-maps-8606.html
</guid><description>
Sygic GPS Navigation &amp;amp; Maps is the most downloaded GPS navigation app in the world, trusted by more than 200 million drivers. Offline 3D maps stored on your phone for GPS navigation without an internet connection. We update our maps for free multiple times each year so you can always rely on Sygic GPS Navigation.
Navigate anywhere, even without an Internet connection
	Offline maps of all the countries in the world, from TomTom and other providers
	Free map updates several times...
</description></item><item><title>Download Duolingo: language lessons 6.48.4</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Sep 2025 16:20:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-duolingo-language-lessons-8265.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-duolingo-language-lessons-8265.html
</guid><description>
Duolingo is a popular language learning app that offers interactive lessons to help users learn new languages. This application offers many languages for you to choose from, including Spanish, French, German, Italian, Portuguese, Chinese, Japanese and many more.
This app offers an gamified learning experience with interactive lessons, exercises, and quizzes designed to help users learn new words, phrases, and grammar rules. This app is designed to be easy to use and suitable for people...
</description></item><item><title>Download Black Screen: video screen off 1.9.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Sep 2025 16:20:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-black-screen-video-screen-off-8740.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-black-screen-video-screen-off-8740.html
</guid><description>
Black Screen allows you to play videos when the screen is off. Turn off the screen at any time and save battery. The black screen can be used to watch music videos, listen to podcasts, record videos, take selfies, and more. when your screen is off. This helps save battery in AMOLED and OLED devices because the screen turns off completely when displaying black.
Use the floating button to quickly turn off the screen and unlock it by tapping the screen.
Black Screen feature: turn off...
</description></item><item><title>Download analiti - Speed Test WiFi Analyzer 2025.09.89920</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Sep 2025 16:20:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-speed-test-wifi-analyzer-8353.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-speed-test-wifi-analyzer-8353.html
</guid><description>
Speed ​​Test WiFi Analyzer is a tool that can be used to test the performance of a wireless network. It can measure various metrics, such as signal strength, channel interference, and network throughput.
Features of Speed ​​Test WiFi Analyzer
Speed ​​test:
	Internet or iPerf3 speed test (including server and client)
	Simultaneous ping, DNS and HTTP latency results – to multiple servers with configurable load
	Monitor uptime remotely 24/7 for downtime or slowdown
360...
</description></item><item><title>Download Screen Recorder - AZ Recorder 6.7.6</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Sep 2025 16:19:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-screen-recorder-az-recorder-8402.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-screen-recorder-az-recorder-8402.html
</guid><description>
AZ Screen Recorder is the best app to record your Lollipop screen. It requires NO root access, no time limit, no watermark, no ads and very easy to use with one action to start and stop recording. This screen recording app will let you create beautiful screencasts by providing all the features you need in a simple and elegant user experience design.
AZ Screen Recorder allows you to record your screen to HD and FullHD videos, and it is the only screen recording app on the Android market...
</description></item><item><title>Download mcpro24fps manual video camera 043</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Sep 2025 16:19:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-mcpro24fps-manual-video-camera-8325.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-mcpro24fps-manual-video-camera-8325.html
</guid><description>
Probably the most advanced and powerful professional video camera app on Android! McPro24FPS opens up incredible video recording possibilities on your phone, something previously only available on professional camcorders.
Features of mcpro24fps manual video camera
	Capture in 10 bits for a large number of devices. HLG / HDR10 HDR Video
	record video to log without turning on the GPU, just like on Big Big's big camera
	Huge number of log modes for every situation. Post-production...
</description></item><item><title>Download SD Maid 2/SE - System Cleaner 1.5.1-rc0</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Sep 2025 16:19:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sd-maid-2se-system-cleaner-10472.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sd-maid-2se-system-cleaner-10472.html
</guid><description>
SD Maid 2/SE - System Cleaner is a reliable helper for your Android, keeping the device clean &amp;amp; orderly. SD Maid SE has optional features that use the AccessibilityService API to automate tedious actions. Using the AccessibilityService API, SD Maid SE can click buttons for you to perform cross-app operations, for example, clear cache. SD Maid SE does not use the AccessibilityService API to collect information.
No one is perfect and neither is Android
	Apps you deleted will leave...
</description></item><item><title>Download Total Launcher 3.3.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Sep 2025 16:18:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-total-launcher-8673.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-total-launcher-8673.html
</guid><description>
Total Launcher is a custom launcher for Android devices. The launcher is the interface that controls the home screen, app drawer, and overall look and feel of your Android device. Total Launcher offers a high level of customization and allows users to personalize their device to suit their personal needs and preferences.
Total Launcher Features
	Customizable home screen: Users can arrange icons, widgets, and shortcuts on the home screen to their liking.
	Themes and icon packs: Total...
</description></item><item><title>Download Reverso Translate and Learn 14.6.0 build 12000058</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Sep 2025 16:18:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-reverso-translate-and-learn-8356.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-reverso-translate-and-learn-8356.html
</guid><description>
Reverso is a comprehensive tool that helps you get high-quality translations and continuously improve your language skills. The best part about the Reverso app? It is available for free. Teachers or translators, students or business professionals, beginners or advanced learners use Reverso to enrich their vocabulary and read, write and speak more accurately and confidently.
Download the Reverso app and you'll have millions of words and expressions at your fingertips, with their...
</description></item><item><title>Download Chomp SMS 9.25 build 9092574</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Sep 2025 16:17:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-chomp-sms-8403.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-chomp-sms-8403.html
</guid><description>
Comes with many great features, especially passcode app lock, privacy options, scheduled SMS sender (reminders, birthday wishes), stopping messages while sending , pin favorites to top, backup, SMS blacklist/blocker, signature, excerpt text, quick reply popup (even on lock screen), multi-select photo gallery, dual sim, better MMS and GROUP messaging, etc...
Plus unlimited customization options for LED color, ringtone, vibration pattern, screen color, font type, font size and wallpaper....
</description></item><item><title>Download Knots 3D 10.2.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Sep 2025 16:13:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-knots-3d-8500.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-knots-3d-8500.html
</guid><description>
Knots 3D is a mobile application that provides visual and interactive instructions for tying different types of knots. This app can be used to learn and practice different knots, with detailed animations and illustrations showing the correct technique for each knot. Used by arborists, fishermen, firefighters, climbers, military, and boy and girl scouts worldwide, Knots 3D will quickly teach you how to tie even the most difficult knots!
With more than 175 nautical miles, Knots 3D will be...
</description></item><item><title>Download Smart Launcher 6 ‧ Home Screen 6.5 build 046</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Sep 2025 16:13:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-smart-launcher-8412.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-smart-launcher-8412.html
</guid><description>
Smart Launcher is a mobile app that provides users with a customized home screen and app launcher on their Android devices. It includes features like minimalist interface, automatic app sorting, and gesture controls. The app also includes many customizable settings, such as the ability to change the theme, icon size, and screen layout, as well as the ability to create custom categories for the app.
Smart Launcher Features
	Ambient theme: Smart launcher automatically changes theme...
</description></item><item><title>Download Easy Notes - Note Taking Apps 1.3.25.0913</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Sep 2025 16:12:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-easy-notes-notebook-notepad-8388.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-easy-notes-notebook-notepad-8388.html
</guid><description>
Easy Notes - Great note taking app, Notepad, Notebook, Free Notes is a free easy to use note taking app for notes app. With this easy notebook and notepad app, take quick notes with colorful backgrounds and checklists to organize notes and tasks easily. Use this aesthetic note taker and note taker to add photos or audio to your notes. Easy Notes is a useful notebook and note-taking app for taking notes and organizing work.
Features of Easy Notes - Notebook, Notepad
	Free Notepad and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Shazam: Find Music &amp;amp; Concerts 16.10.0-250911</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Sep 2025 16:08:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-shazam-music-discovery-10763.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-shazam-music-discovery-10763.html
</guid><description>
Shazam will identify any song in seconds. Discover, artists, lyrics, videos &amp;amp; playlists, all for free. Over 1 billion installs and counting. Use Pop-up Shazam to identify music in any app - Instagram, YouTube, TikTok... No connection? No problem! Shazam while offline.
Features of Shazam: Music Discovery
	Find the name of any song in seconds.
	Listen and add to Apple Music playlists.
	Follow along with time-synced lyrics.
	Watch music videos from Apple Music or YouTube.
	Enable...
</description></item><item><title>Download PeakFinder 4.8.56</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Sep 2025 16:07:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-peakfinder-10050.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-peakfinder-10050.html
</guid><description>
Explore more mountains than any other climber! PeakFinder AR makes it possible… and shows the names of all the mountains and peaks with a 360° panoramic display. This functionality is completely offline - and worldwide! PeakFinder knows more than 650,000 mountain peaks - from Mount Everest to that little hill on the corner.
PeakFinder Features
	Works offline and worldwide
	Includes more than 650,000 peak names
	Install the camera image using a panoramic drawing *
	Display real-time...
</description></item><item><title>Download Internet Radio Player - TuneFm 1.10.58</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Sep 2025 16:07:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-internet-radio-player-tunefm-13412.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-internet-radio-player-tunefm-13412.html
</guid><description>
TuneFM - Radio Player is the best way to listen to radio stations from all over the world! There are more than 7 thousand radio stations. The application offers a very simple and intuitive interface. TuneFM is Chromecast ready.
Key Features
	Listen to all-time favorites.
	Bookmark stations for instant access.
	Discover new music and save to Spotify.
	Sleep well with our sleep timer.
	Add unique radio stations to our growing list.
	Personalize with color themes.
	️ Seamless...
</description></item><item><title>Download Twilight: Blue light filter 14.10 build 573</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Sep 2025 16:07:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-twilight-blue-light-filter-12193.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-twilight-blue-light-filter-12193.html
</guid><description>
Are you having trouble falling asleep? Is your child hyperactive when playing with the tablet before going to bed? The Twilight app helps your device's screen adapt to the time of day. It filters the blue light emitted from your phone or tablet after sunset and protects your eyes with a soft and pleasant red filter. Filter intensity is smoothly adjusted to the solar cycle based on your local sunset and sunrise times.
Get more from Twilight
	- Reading in bed: Twilight is more...
</description></item><item><title>Download CalenGoo - Calendar and Tasks 1.0.183 build 1684</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Sep 2025 16:06:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-calengoo-calendar-and-tasks-8600.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-calengoo-calendar-and-tasks-8600.html
</guid><description>
CalenGoo is a calendar app for Android devices that allows users to manage their schedules, appointments, and events. It syncs with Google Calendar and has features like a customizable interface, reminders, and the ability to view multiple calendars at once.
Features of CalenGoo for Android
	Sync all your past and future events with Google Calendar (just add your Google account in "Settings &amp;gt; Accounts" instead of syncing via Android calendar).&amp;lt; /li&amp;gt;
	Sync calendars with...
</description></item><item><title>Download IMDb: Movies &amp;amp; TV Shows 9.2.1.109210300</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Sep 2025 16:06:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-imdb-movies-tv-shows-8258.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-imdb-movies-tv-shows-8258.html
</guid><description>
IMDb (Internet Movie Database) is a popular application that provides information about movies, TV shows, and other video content. This app allows users to search and browse information about a variety of movies and TV shows, including cast and crew information, user ratings and reviews, trailers, and more. Users can also create watchlists and rate the movies and shows they've watched.
Some key features of the IMDb application include:
	Browse movies and TV shows by popularity,...
</description></item><item><title>Download English Idioms &amp;amp; Slang Phrases 2.0.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Sep 2025 16:06:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-english-idioms-slang-phrases-10458.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-english-idioms-slang-phrases-10458.html
</guid><description>
Are you just starting to learn English or looking to improve your current English skills? English Idioms &amp;amp; Slang Phrases are a great vocabulary builder for beginners and advanced language learners who want to reach native speaker level. Also, it will be useful for those who want to find a good job or higher education in the US, UK, Canada, Australia. This is a great way to prepare to successfully pass TOEFL and IELTS.
In our English learning app, we have collected over 700 of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Busuu: Learn &amp;amp; Speak Languages 32.21.2(1443182)</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Sep 2025 16:05:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-busuu-learn-languages-8400.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-busuu-learn-languages-8400.html
</guid><description>
Busuu: Learn Languages is a mobile application that allows users to learn and practice various languages ​​on their Android devices. It includes various features such as interactive lessons, flashcards, quizzes, and exercises designed to help users learn and practice vocabulary, grammar, and conversation skills. The app also includes many customizable settings, such as the ability to choose between different languages ​​and set learning goals.
Busuu Features: Learn...
</description></item><item><title>Download DAVx⁵ – CalDAV CardDAV WebDAV 4.5.4-gplay</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Sep 2025 16:05:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-davx-caldav-carddav-webdav-8633.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-davx-caldav-carddav-webdav-8633.html
</guid><description>
DAVx is the only all-in-one app for everything CalDAV, CardDAV and WebDAV! This is a full-featured synchronization solution for your contacts (CardDAV), calendar (CalDAV), and tasks (based on VTODO). The app is easy to install and integrates seamlessly with your favorite calendar/contacts apps (including default apps). It can also be used separately if you have CalDAV, CardDAV or just Tasks. DAVx can also be used to access your remote WebDAV files.
Features of DAVx for Android
	Sync...
</description></item><item><title>Download Flashlight Plus: Bright Light 2.8.13</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Sep 2025 16:05:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-flashlight-plus-bright-light-12999.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-flashlight-plus-bright-light-12999.html
</guid><description>
Turn your mobile phone into a flashlight and a magnifying glass! This is a new flashlight app. This smart two-in-one app has both a flashlight and a magnifying glass. OpticView™ lets you see what you're lighting on the screen, turning your phone into one of the most compact and powerful gadgets you've ever owned!
Features
	A simple and free flashlight app, great for emergencies
	Use your device's LED as a torch and bring the brightest flashlight on your phone!
	Turn on the...
</description></item></channel></rss>