<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 13:46:37 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 13:46:37 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download PDF-XChange Editor Plus 10.7.5.403.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 16:46:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-xchange-editor-plus-645.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-xchange-editor-plus-645.html
</guid><description>
PDF-XChange Editor Plus is the editor, PDF viewer, compact, fast with many features, add-ons, professional. When using the PDF-XChange Editor Plus, easy for users to create, view, edit, annotate, OCR and digital signing PDF files, plus much more.
PDF-XChange Editor is a PDF editing full-featured. With the help of it, you can edit, fix, add, or delete text easily. Graphics can also be moved, resized or removed.
Features PDF-XChange Editor Plus
Edit documents
	Use a variety of editing...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDF-XChange Pro 10.7.5.403.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 16:45:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-xchange-editor-pro-3422.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-xchange-editor-pro-3422.html
</guid><description>
PDF-XChange Editor Pro is an application to manipulate and create PDF versatile, offering a wide range of useful features and powerful will help you to easily work with PDF files. This application is very flexible and allows you to easily create and modify PDF files. PDF-XChange Editor Pro provides a powerful set of tools and flexibility to work with PDF files, such as editor PDF-XChange new, utilities series, OFFice2PDF and the Addin tool Bar allows you to easily convert multiple file...
</description></item><item><title>Download CyberLink PowerDirector Ultimate 2026 v24.0.1027.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 16:44:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-powerdirector-ultimate-425.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-powerdirector-ultimate-425.html
</guid><description>
CyberLink PowerDirector Ultimate is software editor, edit video and make movies on the computer from a variety of templates are made available, complete with effects, transitions, animations, and music. CyberLink PowerDirector 17 is a combination of video editing software with advanced video editing features powerful. Cblowing need to add your clips into the time line and click on 'Production'!
The tool design video in CyberLink PowerDirector have the ability to customize helps you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Vov Music Player 11.7</title><pubDate> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 16:44:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vov-music-player-2512.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vov-music-player-2512.html
</guid><description>
Vov Music Player is a program very easy to use, can play all your favourite music from the desired folder directly from the taskbar. Listening to music is an enjoyable activity, we often do it when sitting in front of computer just to dilute the situation, that is, this is not the main purpose of the in PC. Usually listen to music to as a complement for those moments when you are busy, for example, doing something more interesting, work or play. With this in mind, program Vov Music Player...
</description></item><item><title>Download Q-Dir 12.39</title><pubDate> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 16:43:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-q-dir-348.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-q-dir-348.html
</guid><description>
Q-Dir is software to manage the entire file and folder on the computer, allowing to see file in same time 4 different positions (viewport quadro) while still maintaining all the standard features of the Explorer.
It also provides a variety of management features, additional files included the filter file color-coding, layouts and columns can be customized, quick access to file and folder favorites and more.
Other features of Q-Dir , including directory listings (.txt, .doc .html .csv),...
</description></item><item><title>Download Exif Pilot 6.28.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 16:43:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-exif-pilot-3900.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-exif-pilot-3900.html
</guid><description>
Exif Pilot is a tool that small and simple will help you to easily edit the EXIF data contained in digital photos of you. Using this tool, you will be able to view and manage multiple types of data, such as IPTC, EXIF, GPS, XMP, etc. the program also allows you to create data EXIF, IPTC and GPS. The new card also can be added to your photo. Exif Pilot allows you to import and export data, IPTC and EXIF from / to files, MS Excel, CSV and XML. The program allows you to add, delete and edit...
</description></item><item><title>Download iTubeGo YouTube Downloader 10.9.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 16:42:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-itubego-youtube-downloader-3681.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-itubego-youtube-downloader-3681.html
</guid><description>
iTubeGo YouTube Downloader  is the best way to download live video from 1000+ streaming sites. iTubeGo YouTube Downloader is a powerful download tool that allows you to save video and audio for free. The output format of high speed converter is high quality MP4, MP3. Fully compatible with iPhone, iPad, iTunes, iMovie, Android Phone and more.
iTubeGo YouTube Downloader - Solution for downloading high quality Youtube video 
Features of iTubeGo YouTube Downloader
	Download videos from...
</description></item><item><title>Download DefenderUI 1.45</title><pubDate> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 16:42:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-defenderui-6893.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-defenderui-6893.html
</guid><description>
DefenderUI greatly improves the usability and unlocks many hidden Windows Security features in Windows 10 and 11. DefenderUI puts you in full control of your settings. Microsoft Defender security features. It is easy to use, it has different security profiles, and it features one-click access to both basic and advanced security settings. With its help, Microsoft Defender is no longer a background antivirus but a full-featured security tool with various settings and options.
There are...
</description></item><item><title>Download VideoPad Video Editor Pro 17.51 Beta</title><pubDate> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 16:41:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-videopad-video-editor-pro-268.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-videopad-video-editor-pro-268.html
</guid><description>
VideoPad Video Editor Pro is software edit video from any camcorder, DV camcorder, VHS player or webcam for best quality. The interface of this utility is divided into several parts (for example: list of multi-media, Effects, transitions, Files, Clips, video track, audio track, overlay), which makes everything seem difficult to operate. You can capture videos from camcorder or other devices like webcam or capture card TV and after you have added files and sequence clips to the queue, you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mozilla Firefox 144.0.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 16:41:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-firefox-quantum-501.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-firefox-quantum-501.html
</guid><description>
Firefox Quantum is a web browser independently provide the tabbed browsing combined with numerous handy features like pop-up blocker, Bookmarks, direct (integrated RSS), password manager, and more. Functionality can be extended with dozens of plugins available for free (extensions).
Firefox Quantum are interface completely new, beautiful, neat, minimalistic and delicate, eats less RAM to 30% compared with the old version and solve the condition consuming capacity
Firefox can import all...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Saver Pro 10.9.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 16:40:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-saver-6830.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-saver-6830.html
</guid><description>
YT Saver is a software that supports downloading Video, Audio, Playlist from 10,000+ websites, Convert Video to MP4, MOV, AAC, WAV and more. YT Saver is a powerful downloader that allows you to save video and audio for free. The output format of the high-speed converter is high-quality MP4, MP3. Fully compatible with iPhone, iPad, iTunes, iMovie, Android Phone and more.
Supported Input Formats:
	Video: MP4, M4V, 3GP, MPEG, DAT, AVI, ASF, WMV, VOB, MKV, FLV, 3GS, 3G2, F4V, WEBM, TS,...
</description></item><item><title>Download ResumeMaker Professional Deluxe 20.4.0.7025</title><pubDate> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 16:40:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-resumemaker-professional-deluxe-720.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-resumemaker-professional-deluxe-720.html
</guid><description>
ResumeMaker Professional Deluxe is a software that support creating a resume professional demonstrating experience, skills, and your ability to apply for the position your work and share it on the social media network to get better jobs.
ResumeMaker Professional Deluxe - Create resume, professional resume
The features of ResumeMaker Professional Deluxe
	Choose from 60 styles and custom fonts, graphics and colors to reflect the skills and unique experience of you.
	Get the script...
</description></item><item><title>Download PPTube 10.9.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 16:39:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pptube-12556.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pptube-12556.html
</guid><description>
PPTube Video Downloader allows you to download HD videos easily, from 720p, 1080p, 2K, 4K and 8K. You can save multiple videos at the same time. Just copy multiple video URLs from various websites and paste them into PPTube Downloader, then you can download multiple videos in seconds.
In addition, you can download HD videos from Instagram, TikTok, Facebook, Apple Music, Vimeo, adult websites, etc. and convert them to MP4, MP3, MOV, AAC and more than 20 other output formats. PPTube...
</description></item><item><title>Download Pulsar Modular Complete Effects Bundle 2025.10.27</title><pubDate> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 16:39:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pulsar-modular-complete-effects-bundle-11871.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pulsar-modular-complete-effects-bundle-11871.html
</guid><description>
Pulsar module complete effects package for high quality audio mixing and mastering, is a powerful and thorough passive EQ plugin. The program combines the power of the leading passive equalizers from 70 years ago with several unique design elements to create a completely original sound. With extremely rich sources such as synth pads or synth bass, it can also be used as a sculpting tool. It has a simple and user-friendly graphical interface with a quick and adaptable process to produce...
</description></item><item><title>Download ChromeCookiesView 1.84</title><pubDate> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 16:39:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chromecookiesview-2341.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chromecookiesview-2341.html
</guid><description>
ChromeCookiesView is an alternative to the view cookies internal standard of Google Chrome browser Web. it displays the list of all cookies stored by Google Chrome browser Web and allows you to easily delete cookies unwanted. It also allows you export the cookies into text / csv / html / xml. For each cookie, the following information is displayed: host Name, Path, Name, value, Secure (Yes / No) Cookies only HTTP (Yes / No), Time last accessed, Time created, Time...
</description></item><item><title>Download Patch My PC 5.3.3.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 16:38:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-patch-my-pc-3748.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-patch-my-pc-3748.html
</guid><description>
Patch My PC is a comprehensive application and reliable will provide the simple solution for managing patch party Tuesday. The category Enterprise SCUP will provide an incentive simple and unique about the updates and the application updates of the Tuesday easy and updated. The update application can be easily installed on your computer in a few minutes, through the function software updates are integrated into The configuration manager center system MS. No additional agent or server...
</description></item><item><title>Download QueueExplorer Professional 5.0.60</title><pubDate> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 16:38:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-queueexplorer-professional-4823.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-queueexplorer-professional-4823.html
</guid><description>
QueueExplorer is a tool indispensable to work with queues and messages: understand and manage your system, find the error and fix it. Or you can use QueueExplorer to sort them by any field available. Because of the sort display the messages in another order with them will be handled, QueueExplorer more columns of Ms Ms # # so you can still see what is processed first.
The features of QueueExplorer
Move, copy or delete messages
	Messages can be handled the same as in process explorer,...
</description></item><item><title>Download iDownerGo 10.9.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 16:37:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idownergo-12439.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idownergo-12439.html
</guid><description>
iDownerGo is the best tool that allows users to download videos, music and playlists from more than 10,000 streaming sites. It can easily convert videos to MP4, MOV, MKV, 3GP, AAC, WAV, FLAC and other formats on PC and Mac. With this amazing program, users can enjoy their favorite media content without restrictions.
iDownerGo Features
	Download any video up to 8K resolution
	Download 1080p videos online from over 10,000 popular streaming sites easily.
	Save any video in various...
</description></item><item><title>Download Softwarenetz Invoice Rechnung 11.24</title><pubDate> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 16:37:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-softwarenetz-invoice-5588.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-softwarenetz-invoice-5588.html
</guid><description>
Softwarenetz Invoice is a useful program for self-employed, freelancers and small companies who are in need of a simple and user-friendly program for invoicing. The invoice program contains the complete address / customer database. You can see at a glance all invoices, payments and reminders for a particular customer. The memo field gives you the opportunity to enter customer specific information. Importing existing client from csv file is also included.
You can print your invoice on your...
</description></item><item><title>Download Giada 1.3.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 16:33:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-giada-2790.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-giada-2790.html
</guid><description>
How it works? Just grab your sample drop it in any channel and start the program using software little this as a loop machine, drum machine, create sequence, the sampling directly or host effects (VST). Giada aims to be a virtual device compact and mobile for Linux, Mac OS X and Windows for production use and live sets.
Giada - audio tool
Tweak your sound with sampling directly from the external source, the quantum direct, edit, broadcast integration, the recording action and the edit...
</description></item><item><title>Download MyPhoneExplorer 2.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 16:31:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-myphoneexplorer-1824.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-myphoneexplorer-1824.html
</guid><description>
MyPhoneExplorer allows you to connect your Android phone via WiFi, cable or Bluetooth with the computer and manage all content on your phone. With the utility of software MyPhoneExplorer, you can view all phone book contacts, read and play back text messages, view call logs, browse files in the phone memory, view and manage your calendar, view your phone memory and battery status, etc.
MyPhoneExplorer - Manage your phone Android
In addition, the software MyPhoneExplorer also can sync...
</description></item><item><title>Download WDAC Lockdown 1.45</title><pubDate> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 16:30:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wdac-lockdown-13875.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wdac-lockdown-13875.html
</guid><description>
WDAC is a security feature in Windows that can filter which applications are allowed to run code on the local system. Only software authorized by the user can execute code while the WDAC service is running, making it a whitelist-based filter for the operating system. Aimed at streamlining WDAC management and enhancing its default functionality, WDAC Lockdown provides users with the means to create custom policies and whitelist configurations, while also providing additional security...
</description></item><item><title>Download CALCU Stylish Basic Calculator 4.7.12</title><pubDate> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 16:28:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-stylish-calculator-calcu-8716.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-stylish-calculator-calcu-8716.html
</guid><description>
Express your style with a computer made just for you. Choose a stylish, colorful theme to brighten your day while you calculate with ease. CALCU™ is easy to use for everyday calculations, with all the scientific capabilities you need for work and school at a swipe. And for your most demanding needs, CALCU™ lets you add or remove the functions and constants you need to create the perfect calculator you designed for you.
Features of Fashion Calculator - CALCU
	Try our new Material...
</description></item><item><title>Download Reverso Translate and Learn 14.8.0 Build 120063</title><pubDate> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 16:27:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-reverso-translate-and-learn-8356.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-reverso-translate-and-learn-8356.html
</guid><description>
Reverso is a comprehensive tool that helps you get high-quality translations and continuously improve your language skills. The best part about the Reverso app? It is available for free. Teachers or translators, students or business professionals, beginners or advanced learners use Reverso to enrich their vocabulary and read, write and speak more accurately and confidently.
Download the Reverso app and you'll have millions of words and expressions at your fingertips, with their...
</description></item><item><title>Download Powerful RAM Monitor Pro 11.0.9</title><pubDate> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 16:27:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-powerful-cleaner-pro-9435.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-powerful-cleaner-pro-9435.html
</guid><description>
Powerful Cleaner Pro is a mobile app designed to optimize and improve the performance of Android devices. This app helps users clean up junk files, remove unused apps, and manage their device's storage space, resulting in faster and smoother performance.
With the powerful Cleaner Pro, users can easily scan their devices for junk files, temporary files, and cache files and delete them with a single tap. The app also allows users to uninstall apps that they no longer need and to clear the...
</description></item></channel></rss>