<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 05:36:13 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 05:36:13 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Solid Explorer File Manager 3.2.11 build 200352</title><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jan 2026 01:30:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-solid-explorer-file-manager-8924.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-solid-explorer-file-manager-8924.html
</guid><description>
Solid Explorer is a file management application inspired by old file management applications. Solid Explorer is a popular file management app for Android devices that allows users to manage and organize their files and folders in an intuitive and user-friendly interface. It offers many features that make it stand out from other file management apps.
Solid Explorer allows you to navigate to files stored on your device and automatically organize them into collections. You can view,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Volume Control 6.5.3</title><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jan 2026 01:30:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-volume-control-9600.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-volume-control-9600.html
</guid><description>
Volume Control is a great app that lets you control your device's volume – instead of being controlled by it! Simply adjust existing volume profiles or create new predefined volume profiles and switch between them with a single tap. Individual profiles include: Alarm, Media, Ringer, Notifications, Voice (in-call), Bluetooth, and overall system volume.
Volume Control Features
	Volume control also detects when you plug in headphones or activate Bluetooth and automatically switches to...
</description></item><item><title>Download TickTick:To Do List &amp;amp; Calendar 7.7.3.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jan 2026 01:30:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ticktick-to-do-list-tasks-8702.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ticktick-to-do-list-tasks-8702.html
</guid><description>
TickTick is a simple and effective task management and to-do list application that helps you schedule, manage time, remind about deadlines and organize your life at work, at home. home and everywhere else. TickTick is here to help you make the most of your day and get things done (gtd). Whether there's an idea you want to capture, a personal goal to achieve, a job to complete, or collaborating with other colleagues, even create a shopping list (with the help of a list creator). book)....
</description></item><item><title>Download IPTV Pro 9.1.15</title><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jan 2026 01:30:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-iptv-pro-9093.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-iptv-pro-9093.html
</guid><description>
IPTV Pro is an Android application that allows you to watch live TV channels and movies on your Android device. It provides access to many channels from around the world, including sports, news, movies, and entertainment channels. IPTV Pro supports both M3U and XSPF playlists, and allows you to add your own playlists.
IPTV Pro Features
	Supports M3U and XSPF playlists
	Playlist history
	Play a multicast stream using a UDP proxy (the proxy needs to be installed in your LAN)
	Grid, list...
</description></item><item><title>Download WiFi Mouse Pro 5.7.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jan 2026 01:29:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wifi-mouse-pro-8925.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wifi-mouse-pro-8925.html
</guid><description>
Convert your phone into a wireless mouse, keyboard and trackpad for your computer, it allows you to control your PC/Mac/Linux easily via local network connection. Media Controller, Presentation Controller and Remote File Explorer are all included in this controller app.
Now you can relax on the sofa and control movies or games in the comfort of your own home, replacing your broken mouse and keyboard with this app.
Features of WiFi Mouse Pro
	Fully simulated mouse
	Built-in support...
</description></item><item><title>Download Power VPN: Fast &amp;amp; Secure VPN 2.3 build 422</title><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jan 2026 01:29:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-power-vpn-fast-secure-vpn-10109.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-power-vpn-fast-secure-vpn-10109.html
</guid><description>
Power VPN - Free Unlimited VPN Master for Android. Now you can easily access blocked Internet Content with just one click with PowerVPN's Fast and Secure VPN Tunnel. Power VPN Free VPN is the fastest VPN with a secure server network worldwide.
Power VPN Features: Fast and Secure VPN
	This is the best VPN (free VPN) ever created. Create your IPVanish
	Simple interface. Just click to connect
	Over 30 different server locations worldwide to connect to.
	Allows torrenting, P2P, and file...
</description></item><item><title>Download YoWindow Weather - Unlimited 2.54.13</title><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jan 2026 01:29:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-yowindow-weather-unlimited-8421.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-yowindow-weather-unlimited-8421.html
</guid><description>
YoWindow is a unique new weather app. The magic of YoWindow is a living landscape that reflects your real-life weather. For example, if it rains - it will rain in YoWindow. Sunset and sunrise in YoWindow take place at the same time as in real life. But the cool thing is you can roll time forward. Just swipe the screen and you'll see how the weather changes throughout the day.
YoWindow Weather Features - Unlimited
	All the weather at your fingertips. You see the current weather,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Video Converter, Compressor 17.0.6</title><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jan 2026 01:28:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-video-converter-compressor-13301.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-video-converter-compressor-13301.html
</guid><description>
The fastest video converter and compressor on the market supports almost all video formats: MP4, MKV, AVI, 3GP, MOV, MTS, MPEG, MPG, WMV, M4V, VOB, FLV, etc. This converter and compressor supports converting, compressing, changing resolution, Frame Rate (FPS), bitrate of video files. It can also convert video files to audio formats like MP3, AAC, AC3, OGG, M4A, WAV, etc.
Key Features
	Convert and compress your videos to almost any video and audio format. Choose from predefined 4K to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Location Changer - Fake GPS 3.46</title><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jan 2026 01:28:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-location-changer-fake-gps-11087.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-location-changer-fake-gps-11087.html
</guid><description>
Change your GPS location with this simple fake location app using Joystick. Prevent apps and websites from tracking your physical location and protect your privacy. Test apps based on your location. The app also displays detailed location information so it can be used as a powerful location status tool. Place a pin on the map by pressing and holding (just like Google Maps), you can also double tap to zoom in/out on the map. Will also continue to work if you restart your phone. To turn...
</description></item><item><title>Download FBReader Premium 3.8.22</title><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jan 2026 01:28:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-fbreader-premium-8512.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-fbreader-premium-8512.html
</guid><description>
FBReader Premium is an e-book reading application for mobile devices. It provides a convenient way to read e-books on your phone or tablet and offers several features to enhance your reading experience. FBReader supports synchronization of your library and/or reading locations with the FBReader book network (https://books.fbreader.org/), a cloud service based on Google Drive™. Sync is disabled by default; To enable and configure it, use the options dialog.
This reader also includes a...
</description></item><item><title>Download Signal Strength 29.1.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jan 2026 01:27:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-signal-strength-8179.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-signal-strength-8179.html
</guid><description>
Signal Strength APK App is a type of app that allows users to view the mobile and/or Wi-Fi signal strength on their devices. These types of applications typically display signal strength as a numerical value (e.g., in dBm) or as a visual representation (e.g., using a series of bars, similar to those shown above). mobile phone).
In addition, some apps can also provide you with advanced information such as network type and service provider, IP address, etc. These apps can be used to...
</description></item><item><title>Download HiPaint -Sketch Draw Paint it! 6.2.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jan 2026 01:27:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-hipaint-sketch-draw-paint-it-13803.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-hipaint-sketch-draw-paint-it-13803.html
</guid><description>
HiPaint is a professional digital painting and drawing app and one of the easiest to use drawing and painting apps, providing you with professional tools organized in a user-friendly way, allowing artists to create outstanding sketches, paintings, illustrations.
User Interface
	The simple user interface provides more space for thinking and creativity, and allows you to focus into the digital drawing itself.
	Quick slider allows you to quickly adjust the thickness and opacity of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tapatalk - 200,000+ Forums 8.9.32.F</title><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jan 2026 01:27:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-tapatalk-8754.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-tapatalk-8754.html
</guid><description>
Tapatalk is the mobile home of more than 200,000 online forums worldwide. On Tapatalk, you will interact with like-minded people to develop meaningful conversations about topics that interest you. You'll never have to wait until you get home to upload funny images to your favorite forums. Instant push notifications will let you never miss any theme updates.
Features of Tapatalk for Android
	Access over 200,000 forums across a variety of categories and topics
	Ability to search and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Taskito: To-Do List, Planner 1.1.7 build 1171</title><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jan 2026 01:26:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-taskito-to-do-list-planner-8449.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-taskito-to-do-list-planner-8449.html
</guid><description>
Taskito is a simple yet powerful daily organizer app. It helps you organize tasks, events, notes, and reminders in one place by creating a timeline.
Features of Taskito for Android
	Plan your day.
	Get a better overview of your day and week with Timeline.
	Create daily tasks &amp;amp; To-Do Lists to track your progress.
	Gain more control over your schedule by importing Google Calendar to consolidate your events in the timeline..
	Create grocery lists, shopping lists with checklist...
</description></item><item><title>Download CITIZEN Calculator Pro 2.3.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jan 2026 01:26:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-citizen-calculator-pro-12904.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-citizen-calculator-pro-12904.html
</guid><description>
This application is a fully functioning emulator of the CT-555N/CT-555W citizen calculator. The useful error checking and correction feature to verify long calculations without re-entering values ​​and is ideal for general and business purposes.
Features
	Basic math operations (addition, subtraction, multiplication, division)
	Error checking and correction
	Automatic playback
	Percentage calculation
	Tax calculation
	Memory calculation
	Increment and decrement price...
</description></item><item><title>Download Storage Space 29.0.5</title><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jan 2026 01:26:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-storage-space-8139.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-storage-space-8139.html
</guid><description>
Storage Space is an APK application designed to help users manage the storage space on their devices and free up space by deleting unnecessary files and identifying large files that can be moved to another location.
Storage Space APK Features
	Overview: A simple overview of your storage space, clearly showing the amount of memory available for your apps and files you.
	App Manager: How many apps are installed and how much space do they take up? Convenient links to uninstall apps and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Bluelight Filter for Eye Care 6.5.14</title><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jan 2026 01:26:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-bluelight-filter-for-eye-care-8192.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-bluelight-filter-for-eye-care-8192.html
</guid><description>
Blue light from smartphones or tablets causes eye strain and makes it difficult to sleep at night. This app adjusts your screen color to reduce blue light and relax your eyes, helping you sleep better.
Features of Blue Light Filter for Eye Care
	Free screen filter app to protect your eyes
	Screen filter with natural colors
	Easy operation
	Turn on or off quickly and easily
	Automatic start
	Eye care on your smartphone or tablet
	This app works on most smartphones like Samsung Galaxy,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Lockscreen Widgets and Drawer 3.0.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jan 2026 01:25:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-lockscreen-widgets-and-drawer-8656.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-lockscreen-widgets-and-drawer-8656.html
</guid><description>
Widgets and drawers on the lock screen: A long time ago, Android introduced a feature that allowed you to display certain widgets on the lock screen. For some reason, this useful feature was removed with the release of Android 5.0 Lollipop, limiting widgets to the home screen only. While some manufacturers, such as Samsung, have brought back limited versions of lock screen widgets, you're usually limited to the widgets the manufacturer has created for you. Well, not anymore! Lock screen...
</description></item><item><title>Download Automatic Tag Editor 2.2.4.16</title><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jan 2026 01:25:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-automatic-tag-editor-10964.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-automatic-tag-editor-10964.html
</guid><description>
Do you remember the first time you decided to organize your music library more neatly? You found that the only solution was to manually fill in all the song information, one by one. Those days are over! The Automatic Tag Editor analyzes your library and selects the suitable tag for you, just tap on the tag you like and you're done. It will only take five seconds per song...Guaranteed! And that's not all: it also provides you with some high-resolution square images that you can use as...
</description></item><item><title>Download GPS Data 3.0.00</title><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jan 2026 01:24:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-gps-data-11519.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-gps-data-11519.html
</guid><description>
GPS Data App - you can check all necessary GPS data. If you like sports, climbing, journeying, running, you can use it to check your results or external parameters such as speed, altitude, location, etc. In this app you have access to essential mobile data, you don't need navigation, GPS tracker or GPS Watch. With this app, you can check sunrise and sunset times for the day, local UTC time, location on the world map, and more.
Using this app you will get
	Altitude and elevation...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sleep as Android: Smart alarm 20251203 Final</title><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jan 2026 01:23:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sleep-as-android-smart-alarm-8661.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sleep-as-android-smart-alarm-8661.html
</guid><description>
Sleep as Android is an alarm clock and sleep tracking app for Android devices. The app uses your phone's accelerometer to track your movements and detect when you're in deep sleep, light sleep, or awake. Based on this information, Sleep as Android gives you detailed sleep statistics, including total sleep time, efficiency, and sleep cycle graphs.
Sleep mode features like Android
	Gentle alarm clock: The app uses increasing volume and natural sounds to gently wake you at the optimal...
</description></item><item><title>Download Relax Rain: sleep sounds 9.3.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jan 2026 01:23:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-relax-rain-sleep-sounds-13416.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-relax-rain-sleep-sounds-13416.html
</guid><description>
The largest collection of relaxing rain sounds for Android. Over 50 rain sounds (free and HD) that can be combined with thunder and music to reach a state of complete relaxation. You can adjust the volume of rain, thunder and music individually to find the ideal combination and thus promote deep relaxation of the mind.
Rain sounds and relaxing music have a beneficial effect on the body and calm the mind because, by masking the noise of the external environment, they promote relaxation...
</description></item><item><title>Download inCarDoc Pro | OBD2 8.0.0 build 15272</title><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jan 2026 01:22:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-incardoc-pro-9775.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-incardoc-pro-9775.html
</guid><description>
inCarDoc Pro - the best doctor for your car: Tool to test, diagnose, scan, monitor and log engine codes: read stored and real-time diagnostic parameters from the car's ECU complying with the USB-II diagnostic system.
Requires ELM327 scanner or compatible diagnostic device. Support:OBD-II (Bluetooth, WiFi, Kiwi 3 (BLE), V-Gate iCar 3 (BLE), Veepeak (BLE), Carista, Vinli); GPS and Demo only mode. Read more at inCarDoc.com Limited functionality available without ELM327 only in GPS mode:...
</description></item><item><title>Download OH Private Web Browser 3.0.8</title><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jan 2026 01:22:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-oh-private-web-browser-privacy-by-design-10753.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-oh-private-web-browser-privacy-by-design-10753.html
</guid><description>
Auto cleanup &amp;amp; always clean! Automatically delete everything (history, cookies, cache, form data, web storage, etc.) on exit! No complicated settings required! OH doesn't need any unnecessary dangerous permissions. So you can surf the internet with absolute peace of mind.
OH Private Web Browser Features
OH comes with the essential features. No plug-ins needed! Some of the features are...
	Multiple search engine support
	Ad blocker
	PDF converter
	Web archive converter
	Download...
</description></item><item><title>Download Turbo Alarm: Alarm clock 10.0.25</title><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jan 2026 01:21:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-turbo-alarm-alarm-clock-10935.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-turbo-alarm-alarm-clock-10935.html
</guid><description>
Turbo Alarm is the most complete and advanced alarm clock available. It has everything you need to get out of bed easier. Perfect for both heavy sleepers and early risers. Elegant, simple, reliable material design, allowing you to play your own music.
Main features of Turbo Alarm
	Music playlist - set a folder of your songs or music playlist as ringtone to have a different music alarm clock every day!
	Skip any day of the week – long press a day to skip and you'll never forget to...
</description></item></channel></rss>