<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 15:37:24 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 15:37:24 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro 15.25.1122</title><pubDate> Sun, 23 Nov 2025 17:35:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-videotube-downloader-pro-1276.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-videotube-downloader-pro-1276.html
</guid><description>
ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro is the professional version support download videos and playlists from YouTube, videos from Dailymotion, BBC iPlayer, ITV Player, ABC,  FOX,CBS.com Vimeo, Prosieben, Metacafe, Blip.tv CBC.ca many more video sites. After the video is downloaded, you can convert them to the formats compatible with iPad, iPhone, iPod, MPEG-4, H. 264, MP3, AC3.
ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro - Download videos on Youtube
This is one of the software download the most...
</description></item><item><title>Download CapCut PC 7.5.0.3053 / 7.6.0.3090 Beta</title><pubDate> Sun, 23 Nov 2025 17:34:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capcut-pc-9995.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capcut-pc-9995.html
</guid><description>
CapCut PC is a simple video editing tool that you can freely use anywhere. You can create videos on your browser, desktop and laptop, or on your phone. Versatile editing, magical AI tools, team collaboration, and built-in assets. Create videos in a whole new way.
You can edit videos based on editing the timeline, in the process you can add different elements and effects to the video to give the best effect to your work. It is a simple and intuitive set of editing tools and effects that...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare Recoverit 14.0.7.3</title><pubDate> Sun, 23 Nov 2025 17:33:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-recoverits-374.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-recoverits-374.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare Recoverit is a data recovery software that is easily lost at a rapid rate and is used by many people. You will do what happens if one day your data is suddenly lost due to the virus or deleted it, .. Wondershare Recoverit will provide you with an environment to protect important data.
Wondershare Recoverit has all the scanning processes that are divided into multiple types, from the typical recovery of the deleted files that are deleted to the recovery of missing files due...
</description></item><item><title>Download Doro PDF Writer 2.26</title><pubDate> Sun, 23 Nov 2025 17:32:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-doro-pdf-writer-124.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-doro-pdf-writer-124.html
</guid><description>
Today creating a PDF document is no longer hard work anymore. Because there are a lot software introduction support users to make this a convenient and quickly. Doro PDF Writer is one of them, with this utility you don't need a PDF editor expensive that can still create a high-quality material and professional.
Doro PDF Writer allows you to convert any printable document (or image) to PDF format.The program installs as a virtual print driver and is available from the dialog Windows Print....
</description></item><item><title>Download Internet Download Manager Portable 6.42 Build 53</title><pubDate> Sun, 23 Nov 2025 17:32:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-internet-download-manager-portable-11965.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-internet-download-manager-portable-11965.html
</guid><description>
Internet Download Manager (IDM) is a popular software tool that helps users download files from the internet at faster speeds. It is designed to increase download speeds up to five times, resume and schedule downloads, and support multiple download queues. IDM also has many features that make it easy to use and customize to fit your needs.
IDM has a simple and friendly interface that makes it easy to use. The software integrates seamlessly with popular web browsers such as Google Chrome,...
</description></item><item><title>Download OkMap Desktop 19.2.3</title><pubDate> Sun, 23 Nov 2025 17:31:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-okmap-desktop-581.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-okmap-desktop-581.html
</guid><description>
OkMap Desktop is interactive software working on the computer with web maps or digital maps bought or scanned. OkMap can also import a data vector from the most common formats and data DEM related to information height.
Through the map you can organize your path by creating waypoints , routesand tracks on the screen your computer, and upload this data to your GPS . OkMap set data high speedautomatic and estimated moving time . Furthermore OkMap provides you also have autorouting and...
</description></item><item><title>Download n-Track Studio Suite 10.2.3.10356</title><pubDate> Sun, 23 Nov 2025 17:31:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-n-track-studio-2991.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-n-track-studio-2991.html
</guid><description>
n-Track Studio is a recording software allows you record and create MIDI music and sounds top quality. The software allows you to add effects, VST3, DirectX, AU (Mac), VST and ReWire different on each track or channel. This program also allows you to automatically fade out, fade in and fade out or increase the volume of the music to indicate the voice of the singer.
n-Track Studio can record and playback the number of audio, MIDI and sound unlimited. In addition, you can handle the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Balabolka 2.15.0.909</title><pubDate> Sun, 23 Nov 2025 17:30:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-balaboka-142.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-balaboka-142.html
</guid><description>
Balabolka is a text-to-speech (TTS) program. It can read text on your screen in a human-like voice. You can use Balabolka to listen to text from a variety of file formats, convert text to spoken audio files, and adjust speech parameters such as speed and pitch. It is often used for accessibility purposes, helping people who have difficulty reading or multi-tasking by listening to text while doing other activities. Balabolka supports multiple languages and uses different TTS engines,...
</description></item><item><title>Download proDAD Mercalli plug-ins for Adobe 6.0.678.3</title><pubDate> Sun, 23 Nov 2025 17:30:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-prodad-mercalli-plug-ins-for-adobe-12262.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-prodad-mercalli-plug-ins-for-adobe-12262.html
</guid><description>
News editors, documentary makers, amateur videographers or YouTubers all know this:
	There's a moment that's so unique and important - and it needs to be captured NOW.
	Just shoot now - and don't spend time worrying about settings or image stabilization hardware...
That's exactly what Mercalli allows you to do, as you can easily and quickly make the most of that unique moment - now even powered by artificial intelligence! No matter where you are on the road, capture your best moments...
</description></item><item><title>Download Private Windows Script (PrivWindoze) 5.8.3</title><pubDate> Sun, 23 Nov 2025 17:30:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-private-windows-script-12878.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-private-windows-script-12878.html
</guid><description>
Are you concerned about your personal information sent to others? Or do you feel that your Windows settings have many programs that you never use? Private Windows Script (or Privwindoze) provides a comprehensive anti -remote monitoring set designed to enhance your privacy when using Windows operating system.
The main features
	End the positive process. All unnecessary processes are turned off while the scanning program. A small white list is maintained.
	Clean up the positive runonce....
</description></item><item><title>Download Watchdog Anti-Malware Premium / Business 4.3.520</title><pubDate> Sun, 23 Nov 2025 17:29:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-watchdog-anti-malware-7110.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-watchdog-anti-malware-7110.html
</guid><description>
Watchdog Anti-Malware is an anti-malware with many highly rated tools to help keep your computer safe. Watchdog Anti-Malware will help you with Advanced Malware Detection and Removal, Browser Hijacker Removal, Effective Rootkit and Bootkit Detection and Removal, Real-Time Protection, Anti-ransomware Protection Module.
Watchdog Anti-Malware is extremely optimized and lightweight. Software engineers designed it to work efficiently without having to tweak confusing settings. Just start...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinBin2Iso 6.55</title><pubDate> Sun, 23 Nov 2025 17:29:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winbin2iso-1777.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winbin2iso-1777.html
</guid><description>
WinBin2Iso is a small program and simple application that allows you to convert the file .bin format .iso. WinBin2Iso support files larger than 2 gigabytes and does not require installation. The interface is quite simple WinBin2Iso only 1 window embodying the features of the software, you can choose the button WinBin2Iso to convert images bin to iso then choose select folder containing source files and output, all the settings are done in just a few seconds for you to implement features of...
</description></item><item><title>Download 3DP Chip 25.11</title><pubDate> Sun, 23 Nov 2025 17:28:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-3dp-chip-2282.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-3dp-chip-2282.html
</guid><description>
3DP Chip is software commonly used in the update of the version latest driver for your computer. The advantage of this software is completely free, compact and easy to use. 3DP Chip will help the hardware always works in the best state, with the 3DP Chip, you can know the driver has been outdated, then let the software automatically searches for the latest version and installed for your system.
3DP Chip - Download and update driver
With the 3DP Chip you can learn everything about the...
</description></item><item><title>Download QuadSpinner Gaea 2.2.6</title><pubDate> Sun, 23 Nov 2025 17:27:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quadspinner-gaea-3870.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quadspinner-gaea-3870.html
</guid><description>
QuadSpinner Gaea is design software terrain, sophisticated and modern for results the top in moments. The top tools of QuadSpinner Gaea makes realism became the basis. Workflows are streamlined, allowing you to easily gain visibility and work in parallel with your team. Interface is extremely modern and our multitude of gadgets stimulate creativity, not limit it. Working at Gaea very interesting and can help you set a performance standard new.
QuadSpinner Gaea - design software...
</description></item><item><title>Download ShaperBox 3 3.6.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 23 Nov 2025 17:27:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-shaperbox-3630.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-shaperbox-3630.html
</guid><description>
Six effects Cableguys strong in a plugin. For with a mixture of modern and inspiring infinite. With six powerful effect - TimeShaper 2 , CrushShaper , VolumeShaper 6 , FilterShaper Core 2 , PanShaper 3 &amp;amp; WidthShaper 2 - ShaperBox 2 to create the effect of music, great rhythm and help solve the problem of mixing complex.
Cableguys ShaperBox 2
Inspired: transform loops, beats, vocals, melodies or bass into the hook addictive to launch the next song of you. Then, finishing a remix of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Serv-U MFT Server (Serv-U File Server Platinum) 15.5.3.106</title><pubDate> Sun, 23 Nov 2025 17:26:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-serv-u-file-server-platinum-8457.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-serv-u-file-server-platinum-8457.html
</guid><description>
Serv-U File Server Platinum is a software solution for creating and managing file transfer servers. It allows you to securely transfer files, manage user access rights, and monitor file transfers. It is designed for use in businesses, government agencies, and other organizations that need to securely transfer large files or sensitive data.
Features of Serv-U File Server Platinum
	Secure File Transfer Protocols (SFTP, FTP, FTPS, HTTP, HTTPS)
	Supports large file transfers (up to...
</description></item><item><title>Download IP-Toolbox 5.8.7</title><pubDate> Sun, 23 Nov 2025 17:26:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ip-toolbox-10655.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ip-toolbox-10655.html
</guid><description>
IP-Toolbox is a free utility for setting up various IP-related tasks through a modern user interface. You can ICMP Ping an unlimited number of destinations, perform additional checks (IP-Ping) over TCP, UDP or HTTP, monitor groups or single IPs, add/remove temporary IP addresses, or permanently, perform network segment scanning via ARP and more. There is support for IPv4, IPv6 and URIs.
Features of IP-Toolbox
	ICMP Ping for unlimited destinations
	Support IPv4, IPv6, URI
	Additional...
</description></item><item><title>Download MDScan + OCR 3.9.93</title><pubDate> Sun, 23 Nov 2025 16:58:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-mobile-doc-scanner-mdscan-ocr-8307.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-mobile-doc-scanner-mdscan-ocr-8307.html
</guid><description>
Mobile Doc Scanner (MDS) is an application that allows users to scan, edit and save documents using the Android device's camera. It's designed to work as a portable scanner so you can easily digitize documents, receipts, business cards, and more.
All image processing is done on your device only! No material will be posted online without your wishes! Take photos with your camera, edit them with many advanced features, save to your favorite format and share on social networks, email,...
</description></item><item><title>Download WPS Office - PDF, Word, Excel, PPT 18.22.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 23 Nov 2025 16:57:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wps-office-pdf-word-excel-ppt-8244.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wps-office-pdf-word-excel-ppt-8244.html
</guid><description>
WPS Office is a mobile office suite app that allows users to view, edit and create documents, spreadsheets, and presentations on their Android device. The app is available for download from the Google Play Store and is compatible with a wide range of file formats, including Microsoft Office documents.
WPS Office - Free Office suite for Word, PDF, Excel, is an all-in-one office suite that integrates Word, PDF, Excel, PowerPoint, Forms, Cloud Storage, Online Editing, Template library and...
</description></item><item><title>Download AI Video Editor - VideoShow AI 11.0.2.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 23 Nov 2025 16:57:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-video-editor-maker-videoshow-8149.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-video-editor-maker-videoshow-8149.html
</guid><description>
Video Editor &amp;amp; Maker VideoShow is a video editing and movie making app that allows you to create and edit videos on your mobile device. With this movie maker, creating memes, creating videos or slideshows with photos, images, music, stickers and sound effects is easy and fun. Providing the latest Halloween materials! Young filmmakers can even beautify videos with text, FX, effects, GIFs, trendy filters, transitions or live dubbing in a creative and personalized way.
All-in-one...
</description></item><item><title>Download Screen Recorder - XRecorder 2.4.6.6</title><pubDate> Sun, 23 Nov 2025 16:56:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-screen-recorder-xrecorder-13293.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-screen-recorder-xrecorder-13293.html
</guid><description>
Screen Recorder &amp;amp; Video Recorder - XRecorder helps you record smooth &amp;amp; clear screen videos, screenshots in the easiest way. Just tap the floating ball, you can record HD tutorial videos, video calls and undownloadable videos. And you will never miss live game shows and important moments again.
TOP FEATURES:
	Screenshot to capture clear Screenshots
	Record Games on your phone
	Record internal audio without noise (Android 10 and above ONLY)
	Live stream YouTube &amp;amp; RTMP:...
</description></item><item><title>Download CCleaner – Phone Cleaner 25.23.0 build 800011306</title><pubDate> Sun, 23 Nov 2025 16:56:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ccleaner-pro-for-android-3428.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ccleaner-pro-for-android-3428.html
</guid><description>
CCleaner is a system cleaning and optimization tool for Android devices. CCleaner for Android allows users to delete unnecessary files, such as temporary files and caches, as well as identify and uninstall applications that are taking up too much space on the device. It also includes a task kill to close running applications and free up memory. This can help free up storage space and improve device performance. In addition, CCleaner for Android also has a security feature that allows you...
</description></item><item><title>Download All PDF Editor &amp;amp; Reader | Xodo 10.9.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 23 Nov 2025 16:56:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-xodo-pdf-reader-editor-8451.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-xodo-pdf-reader-editor-8451.html
</guid><description>
Xodo PDF Reader &amp;amp; Editor is a mobile application for reading and editing PDF documents on Android and iOS devices. The app allows users to view, annotate, and edit PDF files using a variety of tools, including highlighting, underlining, and adding notes. With Xodo, you can read, annotate, sign, and share PDFs and fill out PDF forms, all while syncing with Google Drive, Dropbox, and OneDrive.
Xodo PDF Reader &amp;amp; Editor Features
	PDF Viewer: Application that allows users to view...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDF Scanner app - TapScanner 3.0.91</title><pubDate> Sun, 23 Nov 2025 16:55:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pdf-scanner-app-tapscanner-12104.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pdf-scanner-app-tapscanner-12104.html
</guid><description>
TapScanner is a mobile application that allows you to scan documents with your smartphone camera and convert them into PDF files or image formats. It essentially turns your device into a portable scanner, making capturing and digitizing physical documents convenient on the go.
TapScanner Features
	Scan documents, receipts, QRs and business cards
	Document Scanner App - Automatic Border Detection
	Tweak your images with multiple filters to achieve perfection
	Easily manage your...
</description></item><item><title>Download ProShot 8.32.2.1 build 538</title><pubDate> Sun, 23 Nov 2025 16:54:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-proshot-8195.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-proshot-8195.html
</guid><description>
ProShot is a camera app for Android devices that offers advanced manual controls for photography enthusiasts. It allows users to manually adjust settings such as shutter speed, ISO, white balance, and focus. It also offers a level of integration, a powerful time-lapse mode, and many other features for advanced photography. It's designed for advanced users who want more control over their photos than the default camera app offers.
Camera features of ProShot
	Auto, Program, Manual and...
</description></item></channel></rss>