<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 20:05:43 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 20:05:43 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download DVD Audio Extractor 8.8.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 25 Jan 2026 20:52:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dvd-audio-extractor-3357.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dvd-audio-extractor-3357.html
</guid><description>
DVD Audio Extractor is a powerful application and high efficiency allows you to extract or extract audio from DVD his with minimal effort. Using this tool, you will be able to extract audio content from the DVD-Audio, Blu-Ray and DVD-Video favorite. The audio stream is extracted can be saved as MP3 files, OGG, Flac or WAV on your hard drive. Moreover, the program can transfer the audio stream straight to the file, PCM, AC3, MLP, MPA or DTS. Thanks to the ability to create photo CD comes,...
</description></item><item><title>Download CapCut PC 7.9.0.3294 / 8.0.0.3351 Beta 8</title><pubDate> Sun, 25 Jan 2026 20:51:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capcut-pc-9995.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capcut-pc-9995.html
</guid><description>
CapCut PC is a simple video editing tool that you can freely use anywhere. You can create videos on your browser, desktop and laptop, or on your phone. Versatile editing, magical AI tools, team collaboration, and built-in assets. Create videos in a whole new way.
You can edit videos based on editing the timeline, in the process you can add different elements and effects to the video to give the best effect to your work. It is a simple and intuitive set of editing tools and effects that...
</description></item><item><title>Download Karaosoft Karma 2026.1.24</title><pubDate> Sun, 25 Jan 2026 20:50:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-karma-2379.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-karma-2379.html
</guid><description>
Karma is an enhancement program that helps you tune, karaoke can view the text of the files sound different. At first glance, after launch, the layout may seem complicated, unclear where to start. You can customize the display prompts to understand the function of each parameter is highlighted integrated.
Management program your karaoke a easy way. Search no need to click, drag and drop feature and many other unique features designed to bring you the easiest management for the program...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe After Effects 2026 v26.0.0.67 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Sun, 25 Jan 2026 17:53:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-after-effects-0012-2793.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-after-effects-0012-2793.html
</guid><description>
Adobe After Effects is a powerful digital visual effects, motion graphics, and compositing application developed by Adobe Inc. The software is widely used in the film, television, and video game industries to animate and enhance video content.
After Effects allows users to create stunning motion graphics and visual effects by animating text, images, and video clips. Its capabilities include keying, tracking, compositing, and basic audio editing, making it a versatile tool for...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Audition 2026 v26.0.0.56 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Sun, 25 Jan 2026 17:53:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-audition-0004-1246.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-audition-0004-1246.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Autdition 2024 is a professional tool for professionals active in the field of audio processing and video, offering them the ability to almost unlimited. Ease of use combined with flexibility of work, allows you to create the main copy of the highest class, edit, mix, handle, impose more sound effects especially. In fact, users have to be on my computer a recording studio powerful full with the tool easy to use at the same time, the tool is quite professional.
Adobe autdition CC -...
</description></item><item><title>Download Photo Pos Pro Premium 4.18 Build 48</title><pubDate> Sun, 25 Jan 2026 17:45:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photo-pos-pro-premium-672.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photo-pos-pro-premium-672.html
</guid><description>
Photo Pos Pro Premium is the photo editing most popular worldwide in the areas of image enhancement and image editing and in the field of design of computer graphics. Version 3 has the photo editing features for free and premium, you can perform various tasks from the basic tasks of simple to complex tasks or can edit existing images, create new works based on existing images, create new works from scratch and more.
Software Photo Pos Pro Premium is packed with adjustments and...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter 3.9.18 (2401)</title><pubDate> Sun, 25 Jan 2026 17:43:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-to-mp3-converter-1744.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-to-mp3-converter-1744.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter is the software support download youtube video and convert video to mp3 format fast and most simple. MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter allows you download and convert videos from YouTube and other websites to MP3 format by pasting the YouTube URL into the application. When you paste the URL, the program will display thumbnails for videos and you have the option to customize the title information, artist and album before you begin the process of...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaMonkey Gold 2024.2.1.3206 Beta</title><pubDate> Sun, 25 Jan 2026 17:40:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediamonkey-gold-231.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediamonkey-gold-231.html
</guid><description>
MediaMonkey Gold is music manager and music player multimedia for the music collection and iPod users. MediaMonkey lists the audio file of you as CD, OGG, WMA, MPC, FLAC, APE, WAV and MP3 and includes the edit smart card and an automatic file and folder to arrange your music library.
MediaMonkey Gold also has CD ripper, CD / DVD Burner, and audio converter for saving music, and manual or editor list automatically to create mixed music.
Features MediaMonkey Gold
	Automatically find...
</description></item><item><title>Download TidyWindow 4.1.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 25 Jan 2026 16:15:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tidywindow-14454.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tidywindow-14454.html
</guid><description>
TidyWindow is a Windows desktop assistant that automates developer PC setup, cleanup, diagnostics, software package installation, registry tweaking, and driver updates—powered by a WPF interface and robust PowerShell 7 automation capabilities in the background.
Key Features
	Essentials Repair Center (docs/essentials.md): Queues selected automation tasks Filter for network, Defender, printing, and Windows Update issues. Each task supports preview run, sequential execution, restore...
</description></item><item><title>Download NewFileTime 8.16</title><pubDate> Sun, 25 Jan 2026 16:14:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-newfiletime-1918.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-newfiletime-1918.html
</guid><description>
NewFileTime is a small utility independence allows you to change date modified, Created and Accessed of any file. You can modify the dates for one or multiple files, even entire folder structures at the same time. The date can be changed to a date and time specific or you can choose to make each file "older" or "younger," according to a certain number of days.
NewFileTime - edit time files
You can add files simply via Drag and Drop or by import from a folder. In any case, it opens...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube Downloader 3.9.18 (2401)</title><pubDate> Sun, 25 Jan 2026 16:13:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube Downloader  is a dedicated software that helps users  downloading youtube videos  Favorites on PC for offline viewing. With MediaHuman YouTube  Downloader  you can download videos from youtube website to your computer with  fast speed , with special software development technology that automatically receives videos from Websites, in addition to the ability to download videos from software websites, can convert downloaded video formats to various formats for the purpose...
</description></item><item><title>Download HopToDesk 1.45.6</title><pubDate> Sun, 25 Jan 2026 16:13:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hoptodesk-11056.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hoptodesk-11056.html
</guid><description>
HopToDesk is a remote desktop application that allows users to access their remote computer or server from anywhere using a mobile device or browser their website. It provides a secure and convenient way to control and manage computers remotely, making it easier for individuals and teams to work remotely or access their files and applications on the go.
With HopToDesk, users can establish a secure connection to a remote computer or server and perform tasks as if they were sitting in...
</description></item><item><title>Download UltraViewer 6.6.127</title><pubDate> Sun, 25 Jan 2026 16:13:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ultraviewer-4740.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ultraviewer-4740.html
</guid><description>
UltraViewer is software that helps you remote control your computer with the installation process quickly, is not necessary and you can connect to the remote computer immediately, especially because the program does not require any additional configuration whatsoever. When launched, you are greeted by a window table, double visually displays the ID and your password as well as login information of your partner.
The features of our services
	Absolutely free
	Fast connection with...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Downloader 10.1.6</title><pubDate> Sun, 25 Jan 2026 16:12:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html
</guid><description>
YTD Youtube Downloader is an application that reliable and intuitive, allowing you to quickly download YouTube videos and save them to your computer. You can also convert the media files to the format desired video or extract audio streams and save separately. YTD Youtube Downloader lets you save your favorite clips of yourself from Youtube, Facebook, Vimeo and Dailymotion to your desktop. The software supports URLS from many web site hosting, multimedia and allows you to download desired...
</description></item><item><title>Download Blumentals WeBuilder 2025 v18.5.0.273</title><pubDate> Sun, 25 Jan 2026 16:12:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blumentals-webuilder-1572.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blumentals-webuilder-1572.html
</guid><description>
Blumentals WeBuilder is a powerful app to edit the HTML code, CSS, JavaScript, PHP and ASP in an environment simple and user friendly. WeBuilder is a versatile application for web developers to edit code.
The application Blumentals WeBuilder this supports the programming languages HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, Ruby, Python, ASP, SSI and Perl. The integrated tool of this software allows you to verify, re-use and redirect your code and expand them according to how efficient and complex....
</description></item><item><title>Download Syncovery Premium 11.12.2.154</title><pubDate> Sun, 25 Jan 2026 16:11:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncovery-pro-enterprise-232.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncovery-pro-enterprise-232.html
</guid><description>
Syncovery Pro Enterprise is a great application used to back up data and to synchronize personal computers, servers, laptops, notepads and storage online. The software comes with support for FTP and secure FTP servers, SSH, WebDAV, Amazon S3, http, update the part file, ZIP compression, data encryption, and schedule automatic backups.
Syncovery Pro Enterprise have the ability to freely select files and folders across the whole folder hierarchy in tree view and supports email...
</description></item><item><title>Download Everything 1.4.1.1032</title><pubDate> Sun, 25 Jan 2026 16:11:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-everything-385.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-everything-385.html
</guid><description>
Everything is a search tool on the desktop that lets you find files and folders instantly by entering the name software or certain applications. The interesting thing for Everything that can be indexed for the whole of your computer in a few seconds and automatically updates the index.
The software is split into two main controls: the search box and the results page. When you first run Everything it will create an index of all the files and folders on your machine. Unless you have...
</description></item><item><title>Download Blumentals Rapid PHP 2025 v18.5.0.273</title><pubDate> Sun, 25 Jan 2026 16:10:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blumentals-rapid-php-2996.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blumentals-rapid-php-2996.html
</guid><description>
Blumentals Rapid PHP is an editor PHP powerful and fast mixing function of the Environment integrated development PHP complete along with the speed of the Notepad. This is a comprehensive software that will support you coding CSS, HTML, PHP, JavaScript and other programming languages. Rapid PHP provides a set of advanced tools to validate, reuse, debugging, navigate and format your code. This software allows you to save valuable time and increase productivity by writing code in a way...
</description></item><item><title>Download Diffchecker 6.7.7</title><pubDate> Sun, 25 Jan 2026 16:09:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-diffchecker-5025.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-diffchecker-5025.html
</guid><description>
Diffchecker is a application compare text, images and powerful file to desktop of your. Available for Windows, macOS. Compare text files, documents, PDF. Compare photos, graphics. Because Diffchecker Desktop running entirely on your computer, so it does not have to communicate with our servers to create your difference. This means that there is no other way in addition you can view your sensitive data, you.
Diffchecker Desktop run offline, that means you can use it anytime, anywhere and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Speech to Text for Premiere Pro 2026 v2.1.6 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Sun, 25 Jan 2026 16:09:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-speech-to-text-for-premiere-pro-7190.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-speech-to-text-for-premiere-pro-7190.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Speech to Text is a plugin that automatically generates transcriptions and adds subtitles to your videos to improve reach and increase engagement with speech-to-text version in Premiere Pro. With Adobe Speech to Text, you can automatically generate transcripts of video conversations and add subtitles to your videos to increase audience reach and engagement.
When your video editing is nearing completion, use Adobe Speech to Text to duplicate your footage. Add voice-paced captions...
</description></item><item><title>Download PC Internals Pro 2.101</title><pubDate> Sun, 25 Jan 2026 16:07:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pc-internals-pro-13002.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pc-internals-pro-13002.html
</guid><description>
PC Internals Pro is a new solution that allows Windows users to comprehensively analyze the system components and reliable monitoring of the hard drive. This software is aimed at individual users as well as IT experts and retail agents attach importance to transparency, early detection and data security. PC Internals provides detailed information about the processor, RAM, graphics card, drive and other system components. The chart directly displays the current load, while the specific...
</description></item><item><title>Download Registry Finder 2.61</title><pubDate> Sun, 25 Jan 2026 16:07:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-registry-finder-1016.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-registry-finder-1016.html
</guid><description>
Registry Finder is management software Registry help you check the Registry and see the results returned are displayed in the list. Registry Finder is a reliable software capable of finding a particular keyword in the register of Windows and displays all the matching items.
Registry Finder - Check the Registry
Registry Finder allows you to perform thorough search through the register Windows, to determine the desired string. The Windows registry is a file base system acts as a database...
</description></item><item><title>Download DP Animation Maker 3.5.46</title><pubDate> Sun, 25 Jan 2026 16:06:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dp-animation-maker-2860.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dp-animation-maker-2860.html
</guid><description>
DP Animation Maker - 2D animation software smart allows you to turn static images into motion directly. The world is a living, breathing from your still images with minimal effort. DP Animation Maker lets you make natural scenes burst with vibrancy and bring out the motion to people and objects.
DP Animation Maker - Create and edit animated GIF
Animation Maker has the tools rich that you need to put all the pieces together. When you select pictures of yourself, it's easy to move from...
</description></item><item><title>Download Hasleo Backup Suite WinPE 5.6.2.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 25 Jan 2026 16:06:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hasleo-backup-suite-winpe-11366.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hasleo-backup-suite-winpe-11366.html
</guid><description>
Hasleo Backup Suite is Windows backup and recovery software, integrating backup, restore, and replication features. This software is designed for Windows operating system users and can be used on both Windows PCs and Servers. Hasleo Backup Suite's backup and restore feature can help you back up and restore your Windows operating system, drives, and partitions to protect the security of your Windows operating system and personal data. Hasleo Backup Suite's cloning feature can help you...
</description></item><item><title>Download HTMLPad 2025 v18.5.0.273</title><pubDate> Sun, 25 Jan 2026 16:05:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-htmlpad-2997.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-htmlpad-2997.html
</guid><description>
HTMLPad is a HTML editor, JavaScript, and CSS smart, be so many experts and learners in over 50 countries trust. Full of features and comprehensive options, HTMLPad allows you to make, edit, re-use, verify, navigate and use the HTML code, CSS and JavaScript faster and simpler than ever. HTMLPad include CSS studio and editor JavaScript strong bring you the best value.
HTMLPad - editor, HTML, CSS, JavaScript
Features of HTMLPad
	Quick and lightweight loads much faster than any other...
</description></item></channel></rss>