<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 13:47:02 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 13:47:02 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download OsmAnd+ — Maps &amp;amp; GPS Offline 5.2.8</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:33:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-osmand-maps-gps-offline-8245.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-osmand-maps-gps-offline-8245.html
</guid><description>
OsmAnd+ (OSM Automatic Navigation Directions) is a mapping and navigation application with access to free, global, and high-quality OpenStreetMap (OSM) data. Enjoy voice and optical navigation, view POIs (points of interest), create and manage GPX routes, use contour visualization and elevation information, choose between driving modes, cyclists, pedestrians, OSM editing, etc.
This is a mobile navigation app that uses OpenStreetMap (OSM) data to provide users with detailed maps and...
</description></item><item><title>Download SAI: Split APKs Installer 2.1.7</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:33:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sai-split-apks-installer-14094.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sai-split-apks-installer-14094.html
</guid><description>
SAI – Fast Split APK Installer for Android. Easily install APK, XAPK, APKM and split APK on your Android device. Whether you need to install large games, APK packages or .apks files, SAI makes it fast, safe and easy.
Key Features
Fast APK &amp;amp; XAPK Installer: Install APK, XAPK and APKM formats without errors. Supports large apps, games, and APK packages of any size.
APK Installer &amp;amp; Split APK Packages: Easily install split APKs and APK packages from any source. Batch...
</description></item><item><title>Download ASR Voice Recorder v545</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:33:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-asr-voice-recorder-9094.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-asr-voice-recorder-9094.html
</guid><description>
ASR Voice Recorder is an Android app that allows you to record audio using your phone's microphone. It can be used to record lectures, meetings, interviews, and other audio events. This app supports a variety of audio formats, including MP3, WAV, and FLAC, and allows you to adjust the sound quality and bitrate to suit your needs.
ASR Voice Recorder Features
	Many recording formats such as MP3, WAV, OGG, FLAC, M4A, AMR
	Support cloud upload integration (Pro) for Google Drive, Dropbox,...
</description></item><item><title>Download RAR for Android 7.20 build 128</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:32:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-rar-for-android-8780.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-rar-for-android-8780.html
</guid><description>
RAR for Android is an application that allows users to create, manage and extract compressed files in RAR and ZIP formats on their Android devices. This application is developed by RARLAB, the same company that created the popular WinRAR software for Windows.
RAR can create RAR and ZIP and decompress RAR, ZIP, TAR, GZ, BZ2, XX, 7z, ISO, ARJ archives. List of functions includes command to repair damaged ZIP and RAR files, benchmarking function compatible with RARLAB's WinRAR benchmark,...
</description></item><item><title>Download ProShot 8.32.1.2 build 534</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:32:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-proshot-8195.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-proshot-8195.html
</guid><description>
ProShot is a camera app for Android devices that offers advanced manual controls for photography enthusiasts. It allows users to manually adjust settings such as shutter speed, ISO, white balance, and focus. It also offers a level of integration, a powerful time-lapse mode, and many other features for advanced photography. It's designed for advanced users who want more control over their photos than the default camera app offers.
Camera features of ProShot
	Auto, Program, Manual and...
</description></item><item><title>Download FolderSync Pro 4.8.0 build 2020100185</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:32:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-foldersync-pro-8221.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-foldersync-pro-8221.html
</guid><description>
FolderSync Pro allows users to synchronize files and folders between their mobile devices and various cloud storage services, such as Dropbox, Google Drive and OneDrive. Back up music, pictures, and other important files from your phone to your cloud storage, or vice versa. It has never been easier. Automation support with Tasker and similar programs allows granular control over your synchronization process.
FolderSync contains a full file manager, allowing you to manage your files...
</description></item><item><title>Download WiFi Speed Test Pro 6.7</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:31:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wifi-speed-test-pro-11765.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wifi-speed-test-pro-11765.html
</guid><description>
WiFi Speed ​​Test Pro is a wifi and local network (LAN) speed meter. Check the best speed for your Ethernet network!
Main features
	Test the speed of wireless and wired networks
	Test download and upload speed
	Automatically saves previous Wifi speed test results, including download and upload speed, ping, signal strength, network name, IP address
	Display IP address, network information, latency, signal strength, channel information
	Share speed test results easily
	Test Windows...
</description></item><item><title>Download Soul Browser 1.4.80</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:31:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-soul-browser-9955.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-soul-browser-9955.html
</guid><description>
The most important thing in a browser is viewing content in a pleasant way. To achieve this goal, Soul Browser offers a variety of features. All features are fast and powerful. Intuitive designed for ease of use. Every effort has been made to deliver the unique value of Soul Browser. Soul Browser wishes to become a valuable application that has been loved for a long time.
Features of Soul Browser APK
Clean mode
	Fast and clean.
	Integrated cleaner optimized for browsers.
	You can add...
</description></item><item><title>Download Smart Launcher 6 ‧ Home Screen 6.5 build 052</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:31:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-smart-launcher-8412.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-smart-launcher-8412.html
</guid><description>
Smart Launcher is a mobile app that provides users with a customized home screen and app launcher on their Android devices. It includes features like minimalist interface, automatic app sorting, and gesture controls. The app also includes many customizable settings, such as the ability to change the theme, icon size, and screen layout, as well as the ability to create custom categories for the app.
Smart Launcher Features
	Ambient theme: Smart launcher automatically changes theme...
</description></item><item><title>Download WiFi Direct + 10.0.24</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:30:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wifi-direct-10153.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wifi-direct-10153.html
</guid><description>
Wi-Fi Direct is a Wi-Fi standard for peer-to-peer wireless connections that allows two devices to establish a direct Wi-Fi connection without the need for an intermediate wireless access point, router, or Internet connection.
Features of WiFi Direct +
	Fast
	Completely free, no intrusive ads.
	Supports all file transfers.
	Supports multiple file transfers.
	Supports folder transfer.
	Supports file transfer to and from external sdcard.
	Tested on many devices.
	Advanced file chooser.
</description></item><item><title>Download Black Screen: video screen off 1.9.4</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:30:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-black-screen-video-screen-off-8740.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-black-screen-video-screen-off-8740.html
</guid><description>
Black Screen allows you to play videos when the screen is off. Turn off the screen at any time and save battery. The black screen can be used to watch music videos, listen to podcasts, record videos, take selfies, and more. when your screen is off. This helps save battery in AMOLED and OLED devices because the screen turns off completely when displaying black.
Use the floating button to quickly turn off the screen and unlock it by tapping the screen.
Black Screen feature: turn off...
</description></item><item><title>Download Battery Guru: Battery Info 2.4.2 build 639</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:30:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-battery-guru-battery-health-8651.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-battery-guru-battery-health-8651.html
</guid><description>
Battery Guru displays battery usage information, measures battery capacity (mAh), shows estimates, and helps you change your charging habits with helpful tips to extend battery life and increase battery life up 200%.
Features of Battery Guru for Android
	Batteries have a limited lifespan, each time you charge your device, the battery wears out, reducing its total (design) capacity.
	Now you can reduce wear and tear, spend less time tethering your device to the charger, and get the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Podcast Republic - Podcast app 25.11.3R</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:29:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-podcast-republic-podcast-app-8131.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-podcast-republic-podcast-app-8131.html
</guid><description>
Podcast Republic is a podcast app that allows users to discover, download and listen to podcasts on their mobile devices. Podcast Republic is a top quality Podcast App on Android with 4+ million downloads, 76k+ authentic reviews, 600k+ podcasts, and 40+ million episodes worldwide. It offers features like automatic downloading, variable playback speed, and the ability to create and manage playlists. Podcast Republic also supports Android Auto and Chromecast, so you can listen to podcasts...
</description></item><item><title>Download AdGuard Ad Blocker 4.14.4 Nightly</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:29:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-adguard-block-ads-without-root-8215.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-adguard-block-ads-without-root-8215.html
</guid><description>
AdGuard for Android is the only root-free ad blocker for Android that removes ads in apps and browsers, protects your privacy, and helps you manage your apps. Adguard is designed to block unwanted ads, pop-ups and banners while you browse the web on your device. It uses a combination of local VPN technology and a custom DNS server to block ads, meaning it can block ads in apps as well as in web browsers.
In addition, Adguard also blocks tracking scripts from collecting information about...
</description></item><item><title>Download YoWindow Weather - Unlimited 2.53.11</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:29:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-yowindow-weather-unlimited-8421.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-yowindow-weather-unlimited-8421.html
</guid><description>
YoWindow is a unique new weather app. The magic of YoWindow is a living landscape that reflects your real-life weather. For example, if it rains - it will rain in YoWindow. Sunset and sunrise in YoWindow take place at the same time as in real life. But the cool thing is you can roll time forward. Just swipe the screen and you'll see how the weather changes throughout the day.
YoWindow Weather Features - Unlimited
	All the weather at your fingertips. You see the current weather,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Weatherzone: Weather Forecasts 7.4.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:28:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-weatherzone-weather-forecasts-11723.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-weatherzone-weather-forecasts-11723.html
</guid><description>
Weatherzone is Australia's favorite weather app, giving you access to current conditions, 10-day forecasts, rain radar, storm and lightning tracking, real-time alerts, and more. Weatherzone is an internationally award-winning weather app recognized by the World Meteorological Organization for its data quality and reliability, weather alerts and user interface. Weatherzone is committed to bringing the best weather application experience to users.
Local weather updates
	Observe the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Smart Tools 2 v2.1.16</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:28:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-smart-tools-8136.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-smart-tools-8136.html
</guid><description>
Smart Tools is a complete package of 6 individual applications. It has 6 sets below with a total of 15 tools.
	Offline support (Wi-Fi tablets only): Open this section multiple times using internet, you can open it without internet.
	Magnetic sensor required. So this app cannot support some Android devices (e.g. HTC One V).
	This is one of the essential applications of Google Play for Education.
6 application sets include:
	Set 1. Smart Ruler Pro: length, angle, slope, level,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Auto Text: Schedule Messages 5.8.6</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:27:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-auto-text-auto-send-message-8447.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-auto-text-auto-send-message-8447.html
</guid><description>
Auto Text: Auto send WA &amp;amp; SMS is a feature or application that allows users to automatically send pre-written text messages at a specific time or in response to a request. specific activation. This feature can be useful in many situations, such as sending reminders, sending messages to loved ones at a specific time, or sending messages in response to certain events, such as calls to or location-based triggers.
Auto Text features: Auto send WA &amp;amp; SMS
	Automatically send happy...
</description></item><item><title>Download Busuu: Learn &amp;amp; Speak Languages 32.25.0(1482127)</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:27:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-busuu-learn-languages-8400.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-busuu-learn-languages-8400.html
</guid><description>
Busuu: Learn Languages is a mobile application that allows users to learn and practice various languages ​​on their Android devices. It includes various features such as interactive lessons, flashcards, quizzes, and exercises designed to help users learn and practice vocabulary, grammar, and conversation skills. The app also includes many customizable settings, such as the ability to choose between different languages ​​and set learning goals.
Busuu Features: Learn...
</description></item><item><title>Download Speed test 4G 5G WiFi &amp;amp; maps 2.15.17</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:26:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-speed-test-4g-5g-wifi-maps-9642.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-speed-test-4g-5g-wifi-maps-9642.html
</guid><description>
More than just a simple speed test, nPerf offers you the best and most complete mobile connection quality measurement tool with speeds up to 1 Gbps! All your results are saved in history with all test locations on the map. Easily share your results on social networks with the nPerf share image that presents a useful summary of your test. Customize your app by switching the background theme using Settings.
Features of Speed ​​test 4G 5G WiFi &amp;amp; maps
	Full QoS test: In seconds,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Floor Plan Creator 3.7 build 548</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:25:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-floor-plan-creator-8875.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-floor-plan-creator-8875.html
</guid><description>
Create detailed and accurate ground diagram. See them in 3D form. Add furniture to design your home interior. Bring the ground diagram when shopping to check if there is enough room for new furniture.
Features of Floor Plan Creator
	Projects may have many floors with rooms with any shape (only straight wall).
	Automatically calculate room area, wall and ground; perimeter; Count the symbol.
	S-pen and mouse support.
	3D sightseeing mode.
	Symbol library: doors, windows, furniture,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Pacer Pedometer &amp;amp; Step Tracker vp12.11.1 build 2025111000</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:25:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pacer-pedometer-step-tracker-11194.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pacer-pedometer-step-tracker-11194.html
</guid><description>
Pacer App: “Pedometer, Pedometer, and Weight Loss Tracker App” that syncs steps and calories with MyFitnessPal and Fitbit! Track your steps, walking and weight loss with this free health counter. Lose weight and track distance walked and calories burned using 24/7 step counting from our pedometer, pedometer and health tracker app.
Main features:
	Best pedometer for any phone
	Accurate activity and step tracking
	Lose weight, track BMI and count calories burned
	Daily exercise...
</description></item><item><title>Download Route4Me Route Planner 5.0.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:24:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-route4me-route-planner-13077.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-route4me-route-planner-13077.html
</guid><description>
It is the most downloaded multi-stop route planning software on the planet. Route4Me is used by Thousands of Businesses &amp;amp; Drivers - in Hundreds of different Industries, for Last Mile Delivery Planning &amp;amp; Services (grocery, package + other deliveries)
AND it has been used by many UPS, FedEx and professional delivery drivers as the ultimate route navigation app. This app is for professional drivers &amp;amp; couriers... not recreational road users.
It's a better route planner than...
</description></item><item><title>Download Flymat: Live Flight Tracker 2.1.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:24:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-flymat-live-flight-tracker-13248.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-flymat-live-flight-tracker-13248.html
</guid><description>
Check the status of the flight you are about to fly or your loved ones are flying. Discover detailed flight information, including but not limited to Airline name, departure city, arrival city, altitude, manufacturer and more.
Features of Flymat
	Track live flights worldwide.
	Search for flights by flight number, route, airline, date and track the flight throughout the entire journey.
	Save the flights and airports you want to track and easily access flight status and flight...
</description></item><item><title>Download Guardian Feast: Cook &amp;amp; Explore 1.0.0.583</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:23:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-guardian-feast-cook-explore-13455.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-guardian-feast-cook-explore-13455.html
</guid><description>
With over 6,000 recipes to choose from, find unique flavors, explore different cuisines and expand your repertoire of regular dishes, with a 14-day free trial of the Feast app. Or if you're already a Guardian subscriber, log in to see if Feast is part of your subscription.
The Feast app is packed with daily inspiration from our world-class chefs – including Meera Sodha, Yotam Ottolenghi, Benjamina Ebuehi, Nigel Slater, Rachel Roddy and many more. Our food editors carefully curate the...
</description></item></channel></rss>