<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 13:53:00 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 13:53:00 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download AnExplorer Pro File Manager 5.9.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:31:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-file-manager-pro-tv-usb-otg-8358.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-file-manager-pro-tv-usb-otg-8358.html
</guid><description>
AnExplorer File Explorer is a unique file manager for TV and Watch file management tool. It is simple, small, fast and efficient File Explorer. Only file managers support RTL and display the size of folders on storage. It is designed for all devices including Phones, Phablets, Tablets, Watches and TVs. It is completely designed using Material Design.
Pro TV USBOTG File Manager Features
	Full-featured It provides all file management features including cut, copy, delete, rename,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Equalizer &amp;amp; Bass Booster - XEQ 33.0.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:30:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-equalizer-bass-booster-xeq-10095.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-equalizer-bass-booster-xeq-10095.html
</guid><description>
This XEQ app is a powerful yet easy-to-use Music Equalizer with Bass Boost, Volume Boost, Auto Volume Boost and 3D Virtualizer effects, which can improve the sound quality of your device. your Android device.
This is the only equalizer fx app you will ever need for your smartphone. With this feature, you can not only equalize the bass boost, but also increase the normal sound volume of your Android phone, add virtual 3D effects, save custom presets, automatically recall presets of audio...
</description></item><item><title>Download Photo Studio PRO 2.8.8.4717</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:30:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-photo-studio-pro-8247.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-photo-studio-pro-8247.html
</guid><description>
Photo Studio APK is a powerful multifunctional photo editing application for photographers of all levels. It contains a huge set of editing tools for basic and advanced editing of your photos. Turn each of your photos into a finished work of art using a variety of effects, filters, text editing and color enhancement tools, and many other available features.
Features of Photo Studio Pro APK
	More than 200 unique filters, amazing special effects, large collection of picture-in-picture...
</description></item><item><title>Download Chat Smith: AI Chatbot &amp;amp; Agent 8.251229.2 build 1247</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:29:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ai-chat-smith-smart-assistant-13276.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ai-chat-smith-smart-assistant-13276.html
</guid><description>
Ask AI Chat Smith Smart Assistant anything about the latest AI Models and get instant answers. Open &amp;amp; Chat with the most advanced AI! With advanced artificial intelligence, enjoy a personalized experience and chat with your AI Chatbot personal assistant. Chat Smith's intuitive and user-friendly interface makes it easy to interact and get informative responses to your questions.
AI Chatbot Chat Smith offers a variety of useful smart assistants to choose from: Business, Content,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Zero Cleaner: clear cache 26.1.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:29:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-zero-cleaner-clear-cache-10667.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-zero-cleaner-clear-cache-10667.html
</guid><description>
Zero Cleaner is a mobile application that specializes in removing cache files from your device. Cache files are temporary data stored by applications and websites to improve their performance and load times. Over time, cache files can accumulate and take up valuable storage space on your device.
Some key features of Zero Cleaner include:
	Cache Cleaner: The app will scan your device for cache files created by apps and web browsers, allowing you to clear them with just a tap. This...
</description></item><item><title>Download Logo Maker : Graphic Designer 2.2.8</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:29:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-logo-maker-graphic-designer-13419.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-logo-maker-graphic-designer-13419.html
</guid><description>
Are you tired of struggling with complicated graphic design software? Look no further! Introducing Logo Maker Design Creator, the all-in-one solution to quickly create a professional brand. Whether you are a business owner, a gamer, a website developer, or someone who wants to personalize their brand, this logo maker app is the graphic design tool for you. Say goodbye to design challenges and hello to instant branding with Logo Generator: Graphic Designer!
Key Features of Graphic...
</description></item><item><title>Download OTT Player 1.7.4.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:28:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ott-player-12910.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ott-player-12910.html
</guid><description>
OTT Player is an IPTV streaming application that allows users to watch IPTV content from their Internet Service Provider (ISP) or other sources on devices such as smartphones, tablets, set-top boxes and smart TVs.
Features
	watch live TV
	automatically group favorite channels and categories
	start playing the last channel on startup run
	time-shift support for providers with archives
	recall interesting programs
	view archived programs and media library
	filter by channel, category,...
</description></item><item><title>Download StbEmu (Pro) 2.0.18</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:28:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-stbemu-pro-9840.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-stbemu-pro-9840.html
</guid><description>
StbEmu is an application for Android 5.0+, allowing downloading IPTV web portals, designed to run on IPTV STB (Set-Top-Box), on devices running Android, such as phones, tablets tablets and TV boxes. Currently, the application supports simulation of many STBs created by the Ukrainian company Infomir, such as MAG 250, MAG 270 or MAG 322.
StbEmu (Pro) for IPTV: Remember that this application is configured for a demo IPTV portal for testing purposes. If you want to use the app, you must...
</description></item><item><title>Download WiFi Direct + 10.0.34</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:28:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wifi-direct-10153.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wifi-direct-10153.html
</guid><description>
Wi-Fi Direct is a Wi-Fi standard for peer-to-peer wireless connections that allows two devices to establish a direct Wi-Fi connection without the need for an intermediate wireless access point, router, or Internet connection.
Features of WiFi Direct +
	Fast
	Completely free, no intrusive ads.
	Supports all file transfers.
	Supports multiple file transfers.
	Supports folder transfer.
	Supports file transfer to and from external sdcard.
	Tested on many devices.
	Advanced file chooser.
</description></item><item><title>Download Windy.app - Enhanced forecast 87.0.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:27:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-windyapp-windy-weather-map-10522.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-windyapp-windy-weather-map-10522.html
</guid><description>
WINDY - wind, wave and weather forecast app for surfers, kitesurfers, windsurfers and sailors.
Features
	Wind reports, forecasts and statistics: wind compass, wind map, wind speed meter, wind gusts and wind direction. It is very useful for extreme wind sports.
	Weather history (archived) 2012-2016: view wind data, temperature (day and night) and atmospheric pressure. The weather archive will help you choose the best month to go to that location.
	Local forecast from NOAA: temperature...
</description></item><item><title>Download QuickEdit Text Editor Pro 1.12.5 build 259</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:27:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-quickedit-text-editor-pro-9059.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-quickedit-text-editor-pro-9059.html
</guid><description>
QuickEdit is a fast, stable and full-featured text editor for Android devices. It has been optimized for both phones and tablets. This app is designed to provide a variety of features and tools that make editing and formatting text on mobile devices as easy and efficient as possible.
QuickEdit Text Editor Pro Features
	Advanced notepad application with many improvements.
	Code editor and syntax highlighting for over 40 languages ​​(C++, C#, Java, XML, Javascript, Markdown, PHP,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Code Editor - Compiler &amp;amp; IDE 0.11.4 build 106</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:27:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-code-editor-compiler-ide-8735.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-code-editor-compiler-ide-8735.html
</guid><description>
Code editor is an optimized text editor focused on coding. It is a useful tool for developing on Android. It contains essential features for coding, including syntax highlighting, auto-indenting, code support, auto-completion, etc.
Features of Code Editor for Android
	Syntax highlighting for over 110 languages ​​(c++, java, javascript, html, markdown, php, Perl, python, lua, Dart, etc.).
	Supports code folding and auto-completion.
	Easy navigation between multiple tabs.
	Unlimited...
</description></item><item><title>Download Auto Text: Schedule Messages 5.9.4</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:27:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-auto-text-auto-send-message-8447.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-auto-text-auto-send-message-8447.html
</guid><description>
Auto Text: Auto send WA &amp;amp; SMS is a feature or application that allows users to automatically send pre-written text messages at a specific time or in response to a request. specific activation. This feature can be useful in many situations, such as sending reminders, sending messages to loved ones at a specific time, or sending messages in response to certain events, such as calls to or location-based triggers.
Auto Text features: Auto send WA &amp;amp; SMS
	Automatically send happy...
</description></item><item><title>Download Math Tricks Workout 2.7.5</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:26:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-math-tricks-workout-8232.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-math-tricks-workout-8232.html
</guid><description>
Math Tricks Exercises can be an Android app designed to help users improve their math skills and speed through the use of various tricks and techniques. Math Tricks Exercises is one of the best math tricks app that brings you the most interesting exercises and practice to test and improve your math skills. Inspired by Vedic Maths, This is the most fun and free math learning app ever!
Features of Math Tricks Workout
	Various math problems, including addition, subtraction,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Bluelight Filter for Eye Care 6.5.15</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:26:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-bluelight-filter-for-eye-care-8192.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-bluelight-filter-for-eye-care-8192.html
</guid><description>
Blue light from smartphones or tablets causes eye strain and makes it difficult to sleep at night. This app adjusts your screen color to reduce blue light and relax your eyes, helping you sleep better.
Features of Blue Light Filter for Eye Care
	Free screen filter app to protect your eyes
	Screen filter with natural colors
	Easy operation
	Turn on or off quickly and easily
	Automatic start
	Eye care on your smartphone or tablet
	This app works on most smartphones like Samsung Galaxy,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wakey Alarm Clock 3.7 - Aether - Build 30736</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:26:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wakey-alarm-clock-13454.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wakey-alarm-clock-13454.html
</guid><description>
Wakey Alarm Clock is a cute and gentle wake-up companion with a spectacular design and immersive animations, aiming to make waking up a fun experience. It includes features such as bedtime reminders, sleep sounds, wake-up challenges (e.g. math problems or typing sequences), nap options, customizable snooze mode, and snooze alarm mode. The app is ad-free and optimized for modern Android devices, designed to transform your morning routine with a friendly interface and engaging...
</description></item><item><title>Download AppKiller: close apps 26.1.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:25:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-appkiller-close-apps-11977.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-appkiller-close-apps-11977.html
</guid><description>
AppKiller: close apps allows users to quickly and effectively kill background applications that are consuming system resources, such as RAM and CPU, which can help improve overall speed and performance. device responsiveness. By freeing up system resources, users can also see increased battery life because their devices are no longer consuming power on unnecessary background processes. This can be especially beneficial for users who use their devices throughout the day and need to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Transparent clock weather Pro 9.00.6</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:25:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-transparent-clock-weather-pro-8872.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-transparent-clock-weather-pro-8872.html
</guid><description>
Transparent Clock Weather Pro: Get Accurate Local or Worldwide Weather Forecasts Easily with Live Weather Updates, Hourly and Daily Weather Forecasts and Timely Weather Alerts. Check The Weather for Today, Tomorrow or the weekend with our Easy to use app and widgets.
Features of Transparent Clock Weather Pro
	local Weather: Automatically keep track or your location as you move and get accurate real time weather reports and alerts
	Different Weather Preded for More Accurate Weather...
</description></item><item><title>Download Stoxy PRO - Stock Market Live 7.0.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:25:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-stoxy-pro-stock-market-live-9366.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-stoxy-pro-stock-market-live-9366.html
</guid><description>
Stoxy Pro: Easily Follow Your Stocks, Indices, Futures From The US, EU, and Asian Markets. View Stocks Quotes and Daily Performance In Customizable Portfolios, Tap Any Ticker To See An Interactive Chart and Detailed Information. Read the Latest Investment and Business News from Top Publications Around The World.
Features of Stoxy PRO - Stock Market Live
	Stay on top of the changing us and global stocks markets. Get Real-time Stock Quotes and Prices: Apple Inc. (Aapl), Alphabet Inc....
</description></item><item><title>Download Peak – Brain Games &amp;amp; Training 4.30.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:24:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-peak-brain-games-training-8236.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-peak-brain-games-training-8236.html
</guid><description>
Peak is a brain training application aimed at improving cognitive abilities and brain activity. It has many games and exercises designed to target different areas of the brain such as memory, attention, problem solving and more. It only takes 10 minutes a day to complete a brain training exercise. And, with 45 brain games for adults and new brain training exercises every day, there's always a fun challenge waiting for you.
Some features of the application include:
	Daily brain...
</description></item><item><title>Download Hermit - Lite Apps Browser 31.1.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:17:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-hermit-lite-apps-browser-9896.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-hermit-lite-apps-browser-9896.html
</guid><description>
Hermit APK is a professional web browser with great built-in features that extend users' operations and productivity to new heights by allowing them to explore optimized applications and functions. good optimization. In addition, it automatically helps users search for Lite version specialized applications that they can use in the browser to save a lot of performance. It also includes integration of more extensions to take user personalization to the next level while exploring or...
</description></item><item><title>Download GSam Battery Monitor Pro 3.47 build 1903471</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:17:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-gsam-battery-monitor-pro-11081.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-gsam-battery-monitor-pro-11081.html
</guid><description>
Is your battery draining too quickly? Do you simply want to know how much time you have left before needing to recharge? Then GSam Battery Monitor will come to the rescue!
Features:
	Hunting down those battery-draining apps with the App Sucker
	Always knowing your battery status and remaining time with customizable status bar notifications
	Installing native battery icons with the icon pack add-on
	Learning more about how apps use your battery - including details about wake mode...
</description></item><item><title>Download Stick - Remote Control TV Pro 1.12</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 13:22:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-stick-remote-control-tv-pro-14435.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-stick-remote-control-tv-pro-14435.html
</guid><description>
The Stick Remote Control for TV app turns your phone into a TV remote! Now you have a versatile TV remote that can connect to many different TV brands such as Samsung, LG, Sony, Vizio, TCL, Insignia, Hisense, Roku, etc.
No more worrying about losing your remote! Your phone is now your TV remote. It's always with you, so you'll never lose your universal TV remote! Control all TV lines with just one app. The Stick can also be used as a remote for Roku, Insignia, Android TV, Samsung,...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinSetView 3.1.7</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 00:07:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winsetview-8971.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winsetview-8971.html
</guid><description>
WinSetView is a tool that allows you to easily set File Explorer's default folder view (including disabling grouping everywhere if desired). It works by setting registry values that File Explorer already supports. It does not modify Explorer or add any tasks or services.
Features of WinSetView
	Is a portabe application. That is, it requires no installation (just unzip and run) and it saves its settings in an INI file with the application. So you can easily run it from a flash drive or...
</description></item><item><title>Download Synchredible Professional 9.100</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 00:07:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-synchredible-professional-1923.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-synchredible-professional-1923.html
</guid><description>
Synchredible Professional is the most advanced version help synchronize the folder and your drive quickly and easily. Whether it is a single file or an entire drive - Synchredible Professional will synchronize, copy and save them for you. The software guide will assist you to identify the work that is scheduled in advance or be done through the USB connection. This way, you can keep your files in sync - automatically.
In the past years, the advanced technology of the us in Synchredible...
</description></item></channel></rss>