<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 17:39:10 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 17:39:10 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Intel Ethernet Adapter Complete Driver Pack 30.6</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Dec 2025 17:10:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intel-ethernet-adapter-complete-driver-pack-7424.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intel-ethernet-adapter-complete-driver-pack-7424.html
</guid><description>
Intel Ethernet Adapter Complete Driver Pack contains all Intel® Ethernet networking software and drivers for Windows, Linux and FreeBSD versions currently supported for most Intel Ethernet Adapters. Not all Intel Ethernet Adapters and Intel Ethernet Controllers are supported in all versions of Windows, Linux, or FreeBSD.
What's new in this release:
In this point release, NVM Update Package 3.20 has been updated. If you currently have the 3.20 update package installed and are running...
</description></item><item><title>Download Android Studio 2025.2.2.8</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Dec 2025 17:10:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-android-studio-3890.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-android-studio-3890.html
</guid><description>
Android Studio is an Android development environment, completely new, provides many improvements and new features compared to Eclipse ADT. This software solution will is IDE the official Android when is finishing. This tool provides many tools and features such as editing, layout, rich set of tools to capture usability, compatibility version, performance and other issues, create a lot APK, build system based on Gradle flexibility, extended support for Google Services, integrated support...
</description></item><item><title>Download Auslogics BoostSpeed 14.1.0.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Dec 2025 17:08:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-auslogics-boostspeed-140.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-auslogics-boostspeed-140.html
</guid><description>
Auslogics BoostSpeed is software support speed up an Internet connection for the computer with Auslogics BoostSpeed restrictions on your Internet speed will be corrective and limited to the lowest level to bring high efficiency in work as well as in their learning. Auslogics BoostSpeed improves the speed surfing the web for the computer through the way in data compression and image to gảm capacity when participating online, with the mechanism and how it works so users also software feel...
</description></item><item><title>Download Luminar Neo 1.26.0 (16162)</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Dec 2025 17:07:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-luminar-neoo-7194.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-luminar-neoo-7194.html
</guid><description>
Luminar Neo is an innovative image editor powered by futuristic AI technologies that simplifies complex editing workflows and allows creators to turn their boldest ideas into reality. Luminar Neo calculates image depth and generates 3D maps, allowing you to naturally scatter light in 3D across a 2D image. This opens the door to unleash your creativity to bring your artistic vision to life.
MaskAI automates the masking process by identifying objects in the image and creating the correct...
</description></item><item><title>Download AnyTrans for iOS 8.9.14.20251223</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Dec 2025 17:07:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anytrans-for-ios-755.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anytrans-for-ios-755.html
</guid><description>
AnyTrans for iOS is content manager essential fully managed iPhone, Android and content of your cloud. Including all mobile devices, all cloud drives from your iPhone, iPad, iPod touch to phones and tablets. From local disk to cloud storage. AnyTrans has protected them all, providing you convenient management for all data and your files, regardless of whether they are stored where.
AnyTrans is the one stop solution to meet all the management needs of your data. For the first time, you can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Auslogics Registry Cleaner Pro 11.1.0.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Dec 2025 17:06:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-auslogics-registry-cleaner-pro-1892.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-auslogics-registry-cleaner-pro-1892.html
</guid><description>
Auslogics Registry Cleaner Pro is the most advanced Version of the software cleans the registry stable help users delete the outdated Registry to speed up your pc. Auslogics Registry Cleaner Pro contains all the features of Auslogics Registry Cleaner Free. User easy download Auslogics Registry Cleaner on the website taiwebs.com with many new features. The software will fix all the errors in the registry of your Windows and clean it from obsolete entries. With Auslogics Registry Cleaner you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Auslogics Registry Cleaner 11.1.0.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Dec 2025 17:06:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-auslogics-registry-cleaner-1249.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-auslogics-registry-cleaner-1249.html
</guid><description>
Auslogics Registry Cleaner , so we introduce is proud to be cleaning software registry stable help users delete the outdated Registry to speed up your computer. User easy download Auslogics Registry Cleaner on our website taiwebs.com with many new features. The software will fix all the errors in the registry of your Windows and clean it from obsolete entries. With the Auslogics Registry Cleaner, you can avoid system malfunction and help your Windows running more stable.
Auslogics...
</description></item><item><title>Download Auslogics Disk Defrag Pro 12.1.0.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Dec 2025 17:05:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-auslogics-disk-defrag-pro-648.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-auslogics-disk-defrag-pro-648.html
</guid><description>
Auslogics Disk Defrag Pro is a software for your drive is optimized for maximum speed and maximum efficiency with its smart algorithms and technology, defragmentation boot time of the program this powerful. Auslogics Disk Defrag Pro is a full program features using the algorithm various optimizations to the best available space on your hard drive.
Auslogics Disk Defrag Pro - Watched the piece, system optimization
Auslogics Disk Defrag Pro based on an algorithm, a powerful optimization...
</description></item><item><title>Download Secure Delete Professional 2025 v215</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Dec 2025 17:04:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secure-delete-professional-4991.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secure-delete-professional-4991.html
</guid><description>
Secure Delete Professional is very simple tool but very effective to delete files and folders in a secure way. After using this tool, the files and folders selected will not be available for recovery. We have attached a number of security options so you can choose the security level that you need (this reflects the processing speed).
You can use this application in 3 ways. First, you can drag and drop the file or folder that you want to delete securely to the main window of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Auslogics Registry Defrag 15.1.0.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Dec 2025 17:04:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-auslogics-registry-defrag-1251.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-auslogics-registry-defrag-1251.html
</guid><description>
Auslogics Registry Defrag is software to defragment and optimize the Registry to speed fast, improve and enhance the pc performance. You easily download this software at taiwebs.com to have the latest version. With this app, the user will remove the error structure in the Registry, reduce the amount of audi tt passive memory Ram of the Registry, to speed up the application and help Windows run more stable.
Auslogics Registry Defrag - defragment the hard drive
Auslogics Registry Defrag...
</description></item><item><title>Download PostgreSQL PHP Generator Professional 22.0.8.22</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Dec 2025 17:04:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-postgresql-php-generator-professional-7953.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-postgresql-php-generator-professional-7953.html
</guid><description>
PostgreSQL PHP Generator Professional is professional software used to create professional quality data-driven web applications for your PostgreSQL database without programming.&amp;lt; /p&amp;gt;
Features of PostgreSQL PHP Generator Professional
	Lets you create beautiful apps on any device from mobile to desktop.
	Create easy-to-use data entry forms with lots of controls.
	Supports detailed master views with unlimited nesting.
	Provides reliable data protection with application, page, and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Auslogics Windows Slimmer Pro 5.1.0.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Dec 2025 17:03:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-auslogics-windows-slimmer-1252.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-auslogics-windows-slimmer-1252.html
</guid><description>
Auslogics Windows Slimmer is software recover hard disk space by removing the rest from older versions of Windows, files, Windows Update, system restore points old, and other items not required and engross your disk space. Use Auslogics Windows Slimmer is necessary because simple as running system maintenance periodically is mandatory, because the data are temporary and not necessary to continue piling up and may eventually occupy an amount of storage space substantially.
Auslogics...
</description></item><item><title>Download PerfectTUNES 2025-12-23</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Dec 2025 17:03:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfecttunes-7115.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfecttunes-7115.html
</guid><description>
PerfectTUNES is a versatile music file manager that lets you find album art, check music folders for duplicates, and scan your songs for rip errors. export. PerfectTUNES comes as a software package, containing three applications that handle each function individually. PerfectTUNES is an intuitive, yet easy-to-use tool that allows you to organize your albums and music files, remove damaged songs, or remove duplicates. You can use its functions to clean up your music folder as well as find...
</description></item><item><title>Download FileCenter Professional Suite 12.0.31</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Dec 2025 17:02:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-filecenter-professional-suite-3407.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-filecenter-professional-suite-3407.html
</guid><description>
FileCenter Professional Suite is a set of tools, file manager and powerful document. FileCenter Professional Suite is a management solution document full and effective designed for small businesses. The program blends organize files and scan easily with the ability to edit and create PDF advanced. In addition, the program also comes with a number of functions and features, such as Search, OCR, restore files, etc. Integrated with cloud services such as OneDrive, Google Drive and Dropbox,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Prey Basic 1.13.22</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Dec 2025 17:02:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-prey-5347.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-prey-5347.html
</guid><description>
Prey is free software that allows you to track and find your laptop, phone and tablet whenever stolen or missing - easily and all in one place. It's open source, lightweight, offering you full remote control, 24/7. You can quickly find out what the thief looks, what he is doing on your device and where he is actually hiding using GPS or WiFi geolocation. It's payback time.
Basically, you install a small agent in your PC or phone that will silently wait for the remote signal to wake up and...
</description></item><item><title>Download PHP Generator for MySQL Professional 22.8.0.22</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Dec 2025 17:01:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-php-generator-for-mysql-professional-4622.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-php-generator-for-mysql-professional-4622.html
</guid><description>
PHP Generator for MySQL Professional is software that helps you can create web applications data-driven quality professional for MySQL databases without programming. The PHP for MySQL allows you to create the application look good on all devices from mobile to desktop. PHP Generator for MySQL Professional enables you to quickly build a website from your database without programming. Web application was created that allows authorized users to view, edit, add and delete records to the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Task Explorer 1.7.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Dec 2025 17:01:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-task-explorer-4305.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-task-explorer-4305.html
</guid><description>
Task Explorer is a management application task navigate to advanced users can track and display details about the running apps, memory and more. For example: on the top of the page, you can find memory, GPU memory, object, Processor, GPU, TCP / IP and many more. Right click and you can customize what you can track exactly what you want easily. In addition, CPU, GPU, memory Read / Write and up / down are also displayed directly at the bottom.
Task Explorer - task Manager Windows
Related...
</description></item><item><title>Download Syncovery Premium 11.11.12.142</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Dec 2025 17:01:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncovery-pro-enterprise-232.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncovery-pro-enterprise-232.html
</guid><description>
Syncovery Pro Enterprise is a great application used to back up data and to synchronize personal computers, servers, laptops, notepads and storage online. The software comes with support for FTP and secure FTP servers, SSH, WebDAV, Amazon S3, http, update the part file, ZIP compression, data encryption, and schedule automatic backups.
Syncovery Pro Enterprise have the ability to freely select files and folders across the whole folder hierarchy in tree view and supports email...
</description></item><item><title>Download Firebird PHP Generator Professional 22.8.0.22</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Dec 2025 17:00:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-firebird-php-generator-professional-7955.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-firebird-php-generator-professional-7955.html
</guid><description>
Firebird PHP Generator Professional is a professional quality 100% responsive website creation software for your Firebird database without any programming. It allows you to quickly build a website based on your database without any programming! The created web application allows authorized users to perform data operations on your database.
Features of Firebird PHP Generator Professional
	High quality PHP website builder, 100% responsive design compatible with mobile devices and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Qmmp 2.3.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Dec 2025 17:00:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qmmp-3465.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qmmp-3465.html
</guid><description>
Qmmp is a audio player multi-platform free and open source similar to Winamp. It is written in C ++ using the toolkit widget in Qt for user interface. It officially supports the operating systems Linux, FreeBSD and Microsoft Windows. This program is an audio player, written with help of Qt library. User interface similar to winamp or xmms. User interface alternatives are also available.
Qmmp - audio Playback multi-platform
The features of Qmmp
&amp;nbsp;
	Ogg Vorbis
	Ogg Opus
	Native...
</description></item><item><title>Download Auslogics SSD Optimizer Pro 2.1.0.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Dec 2025 16:59:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-auslogics-ssd-optimizer-pro-12530.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-auslogics-ssd-optimizer-pro-12530.html
</guid><description>
Auslogics SSD Optimizer Pro is a specialized software tool designed to enhance the performance and longevity of solid state drives (SSDs). The software uses complex algorithms to optimize SSD performance, significantly improving read and write speeds, providing faster file access and overall system responsiveness. Users can check the health of their SSD, including real-time statistics on read and written data, helping to assess drive health and expected lifespan.
Features of Auslogics...
</description></item><item><title>Download Dup Scout Ultimate 17.6.18 + Enterprise + Pro</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Dec 2025 16:58:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dup-scout-ultimate-1460.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dup-scout-ultimate-1460.html
</guid><description>
Dup Scout Ultimate is professional software with the aim of helping you detect files duplicate is stored in your computer and delete them to free some space on disk. Management utility this file can clean up the file to duplicate from disc, folder, network share or storage device NAS.
Dup Scout Ultimate - Find and delete file duplicate
Dup Scout Ultimate offers you the ability to build a new profile by specifying the name and select the folder or network share, all hard disks, servers...
</description></item><item><title>Download BDtoAVCHD 3.1.9</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Dec 2025 16:58:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bdtoavchd-2570.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bdtoavchd-2570.html
</guid><description>
BDtoAVCHD is a free tool to create disc AVCHD from files Blu-Ray or HD MKV. When beginning out, we have the folder structure ready to burn to DVD5 or DVD9. AVCHD format allows playback the same type of content as Blu-Ray and holding high definition (1080p) but on media DVD5 or DVD9. It is ideal to backup Blu-Ray with much smaller size and maintaining high quality. The recorded disc is obtained compatible with most Blu-Ray players and PS3. Also can convert Blu-Ray to MKV and Blu-Ray 3D to...
</description></item><item><title>Download ClevNote - Notepad, Checklist 2.24.10</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Dec 2025 16:34:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-clevnote-notepad-checklist-8746.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-clevnote-notepad-checklist-8746.html
</guid><description>
ClevNote is a note-taking and checklist app for Android devices. It allows users to create and manage various types of notes, such as to-do lists, grocery lists, reminders, and more. ClevNote is a memo application that helps users write necessary daily memos
Features of ClevNote for Android
	Simple and easy-to-use interface
	Supports creating and managing multiple notes and checklists
	Ability to set reminders for specific notes or tasks
	Built-in templates for common note types, such...
</description></item><item><title>Download CalenGoo - Calendar and Tasks 1.0.183 build 1696</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Dec 2025 16:33:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-calengoo-calendar-and-tasks-8600.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-calengoo-calendar-and-tasks-8600.html
</guid><description>
CalenGoo is a calendar app for Android devices that allows users to manage their schedules, appointments, and events. It syncs with Google Calendar and has features like a customizable interface, reminders, and the ability to view multiple calendars at once.
Features of CalenGoo for Android
	Sync all your past and future events with Google Calendar (just add your Google account in "Settings &amp;gt; Accounts" instead of syncing via Android calendar).&amp;lt; /li&amp;gt;
	Sync calendars with...
</description></item></channel></rss>