<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 15:40:17 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 15:40:17 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Sleep Sounds: White Noise 2025.08.3</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 18:37:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sleep-sounds-white-noise-8874.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sleep-sounds-white-noise-8874.html
</guid><description>
White noise is background sound with high, medium and low frequencies, they are evenly distributed and emit the same volume, without difference. In life, we are often faced with white noise. It can be noise from rain, hair dryer, crackling fire, vacuum cleaner noise, air conditioning, etc.
Sounds for sleep and rest will help get rid of insomnia, start falling asleep like a baby, finally relax or concentrate and meditate.
Try it and be amazed at how easily you fall asleep with soothing...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tapatalk - 200,000+ Forums 8.9.24.F</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 18:37:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-tapatalk-8754.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-tapatalk-8754.html
</guid><description>
Tapatalk is the mobile home of more than 200,000 online forums worldwide. On Tapatalk, you will interact with like-minded people to develop meaningful conversations about topics that interest you. You'll never have to wait until you get home to upload funny images to your favorite forums. Instant push notifications will let you never miss any theme updates.
Features of Tapatalk for Android
	Access over 200,000 forums across a variety of categories and topics
	Ability to search and...
</description></item><item><title>Download UpNote - notes, diary, journal 9.13.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 18:34:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-upnote-notes-diary-journal-13596.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-upnote-notes-diary-journal-13596.html
</guid><description>
UpNote is an elegant and powerful note-taking app that works seamlessly across platforms: iOS, Mac, Android and Windows. UpNote is designed to help you take notes easily and focus on what matters most. UpNote has beautiful fonts and elegant themes that you can customize to make your writing experience as comfortable and enjoyable as possible. UpNote is an ideal place to keep your diary and journal. It has a powerful locking feature so you can rest assured that your notes are kept private...
</description></item><item><title>Download AOA: Always on Display 7.2.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 18:33:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-aoa-always-on-display-8461.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-aoa-always-on-display-8461.html
</guid><description>
AOA: Always On Display (AOD) is a feature found on some Android devices that keeps the screen on and displays important information, such as time, date, and notifications, even when the device is locked. This feature is intended to make it easier for users to view important information without having to unlock their device. This feature can be enabled and disabled in the device's settings, and the information displayed on the AOD can also be customized.
AOA features: Always on...
</description></item><item><title>Download Image to text - Text scanner 1.7.16</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 18:33:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-image-to-text-text-scanner-11903.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-image-to-text-text-scanner-11903.html
</guid><description>
Free online document scanner to text image to copy text program helps you with handwritten text recognition of optical characters and has them converted into characters. This photo to text converter has the function to scan text from image any type of scan and read into offline text located on photo and help you easily extract text from image text scanner scan Word from photo and translator Now you can scan handwriting to text converter free image to text converter program online all...
</description></item><item><title>Download My Diary - Daily Diary Journal 1.03.98.0818</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 18:32:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-my-diary-daily-diary-journal-11803.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-my-diary-daily-diary-journal-11803.html
</guid><description>
My Diary is a free online diary that you can use to record your daily diary, secret thoughts, journeys, moods and any private moments. A diary application with images and videos, supporting adding themes, stickers, fonts,... to make your personal diary more vivid and safe.
Daily diary with lock supports setting diary password to protect the safety of your private memories and diary. You will be able to sync your diary with Google Drive or Dropbox to ensure security and keep diary...
</description></item><item><title>Download Scientific Calculator Pro 6.10.13</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 18:32:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-scientific-calculator-pro-11445.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-scientific-calculator-pro-11445.html
</guid><description>
Turn your phone into the best scientific calculator you've ever used with this essential app. Basic, advanced, and graphing modes let you use only what you need, when you need it. It's fast, easy to use and looks real.
Main features
	No advertising
	Full-color graph
	Works in landscape and portrait mode
	Trigonometry, log, exponent
	Calculate fractions
	Complex numbers
	Linear equations and polynomials
	Basic statistical functions
	Binary, decimal, hexadecimal operations
	Bitwise...
</description></item><item><title>Download Resume Builder - CV Engineer 18.00.73</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 18:25:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-resume-builder-cv-engineer-13114.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-resume-builder-cv-engineer-13114.html
</guid><description>
Are you looking for a free CV application? CV Engineer is a simple way to create PDF CV for your application applications. With useful examples, tips and CV templates. All are written by a professional employer. We guarantee you have a perfect CV to impress the employer.
	Introduced on Play Store in 21 countries
	4,600,000 people used CV Engineer to create a CV and find a job
Some outstanding features
	Professional CV template: Choose from a series of CV models designed by an...
</description></item><item><title>Download Facemoji AI Emoji Keyboard 3.5.8.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 18:25:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-facemoji-ai-emoji-keyboard-13124.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-facemoji-ai-emoji-keyboard-13124.html
</guid><description>
Facemoji AI Emoji Keyboard is a free AI smart chatgpt app Awesome Custom Keyboard Fonts. With 5000+ emojis, WhatsApp stickers, Kaomoji, GIFs, cool fonts, TikTok emojis, stylish themes on this emoji keyboard.
Create stickers based on your inputs and share them with your friends via Whatsapp, Facebook and TikTok. Just type the phrase you want and create personalized stickers to add a unique touch to your chat. Try it and share your ideas with your friends, make every chat full of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Easy Voice Recorder Pro 2.9.3</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 18:24:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-easy-voice-recorder-pro-8778.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-easy-voice-recorder-pro-8778.html
</guid><description>
Easy Voice Recorder Pro is a popular voice recorder app for Android devices. It allows users to record audio using the device's built-in microphone or an external microphone and save the recordings in various audio formats, including MP3, WAV, AAC, and FLAC.
Easy Voice Recorder Pro is your daily companion for recording important moments. Capture meetings, personal notes, classes, songs, and more, with no time limits or ads!
Easy Voice Recorder Pro also offers a number of customizable...
</description></item><item><title>Download Yoga &amp;amp; Meditation | Gotta Yoga 2.1.22</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 18:17:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-yoga-meditation-gotta-yoga-13510.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-yoga-meditation-gotta-yoga-13510.html
</guid><description>
Gotta Yoga is a versatile yoga and meditation app designed for users of all levels, from beginners to advanced practitioners. The app offers over 350 classes, including styles like Vinyasa, Yin, Hatha, Ashtanga, Iyengar, meditation and pranayama, with session lengths ranging from 5 to 90 minutes, many of which can be taken offline.
Key features include:
	Live classes via Zoom with certified yoga teachers, providing real-time interaction and feedback.
	Integrated with Apple Health and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Home Workout - No Equipment 1.5.5</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 18:17:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-home-workout-no-equipment-13341.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-home-workout-no-equipment-13341.html
</guid><description>
Home Workouts provides daily workouts for all your major muscle groups. In just a few minutes a day, you can build muscle and maintain fitness at home without having to go to the gym. No equipment or trainer is required, all exercises can be done with just your body weight.
The app features exercises for abs, chest, legs, arms and buttocks as well as full-body workouts. All the exercises are designed by experts. None of them require any equipment, so you don't need to go to the gym....
</description></item><item><title>Download Cloudflare WARP 2025.6.1335.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 16:00:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cloudflare-warp-12256.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cloudflare-warp-12256.html
</guid><description>
Cloudflare WARP is a free application developed by Cloudflare that provides a secure and private connection to the internet. The app acts as a Virtual Private Network (VPN) service, encrypting users' internet traffic and routing it through Flare's global network. Cloudflare Zero Trust replaces legacy security perimeters with Cloudflare's global network, making the Internet faster and more secure for teams around the world. Consult our reference architecture to learn how to evolve your...
</description></item><item><title>Download AdwCleaner 8.6.0.613</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 15:59:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-malwarebytes-adwcleaner-1132.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-malwarebytes-adwcleaner-1132.html
</guid><description>
Malwarebytes AdwCleaner is ad blocking software on the browser, which helps you completely remove the annoying stuff every time Internet access. The software is completely free for users, also AdwCleaner can remove unwanted software or virus on your computer.
When on the website is not secure, appearance various types of advertising PUP. Very can will appear on the website contain malicious code that when you click on the sensitive area, the virus infected computer very likely to happen....
</description></item><item><title>Download ACDSee Luxea Video Editor Pro 8.0.1.3380</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 15:58:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-acdsee-luxea-video-editor-5312.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-acdsee-luxea-video-editor-5312.html
</guid><description>
ACDSee Luxea Video Editor is a software simple and effective to edit and edit all types of video files (with the ability to record video from the screen), unlike the video editing software professional and heavy the other, with the environment simple and easy, the task video editing for non-professional users he's doing that. Using software ACDSee Luxea Video Editor, you can edit or mixed film and do things like quickly edit audio and video of the video file, set video effects, simple to...
</description></item><item><title>Download HFS: HTTP File Server (version 3) 0.57.12</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 15:57:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hfs-http-file-server-11851.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hfs-http-file-server-11851.html
</guid><description>
HFS is a web file server to run on your computer. Share a folder or even a file thanks to the virtual file system. Essentially, this application turns your computer into an HTTP server and all users who want to connect and download files can do so by loading a simple website in their browser. HFS includes many configuration settings, so you can basically change each part of the application, starting with how users download files and ending with the appearance of the created website.
HFS...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tor Browser 14.5.6</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 15:57:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tor-browser-1833.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tor-browser-1833.html
</guid><description>
Tor Browser also has full name is Tor Browser Bundle is a web browser give you ability to access the internet safety and security your personal information as well as sensitive documents absolutely. By Tor Browser Bundle will automatically change the IP address on the machine to hide the identity when surfing the web. Tor Browser is free web browser full-featured basic and advanced allows you to leverage the Tor network anonymously without need to make any configuration changes or install...
</description></item><item><title>Download NetSpot Unlimited Enterprise 5.1.0.703</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 15:56:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-netspot-unlimited-enterprise-3952.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-netspot-unlimited-enterprise-3952.html
</guid><description>
NetSpot Unlimited Enterprise is a professional application only to the site survey, wireless, Wi-Fi and troubleshooting on Mac OS X and Windows. It is a analysis, FREE Wi-Fi. No need to be an expert network to improve the Wi-Fi at home or your office today! All you need is your MacBook running Mac OS X 10.10+, or any laptop with Windows 7/8/10 and NetSpot Unlimited Enterprise that operates on any 802.11 network.
NetSpot Unlimited Enterprise - Wifi network analysis
When working on a...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mozilla Thunderbird 142.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 15:56:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thunderbird-1788.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thunderbird-1788.html
</guid><description>
Thunderbird is an email program full featured with controls spam integration, mail filter, address book, news groups and more. It provides a clean interface and easy to use (customizable). Thunderbird also provides the security features such as S / MIME, digital signing, message encryption, support for certificates and security devices.
Before using this feature, you should review the settings IMAP, SMTP, and SSL/TLS his. Now, what all you need to do is provide your name, email address,...
</description></item><item><title>Download R-Wipe &amp;amp; Clean 20.0 Build 2522</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 15:55:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-wipe-clean-891.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-wipe-clean-891.html
</guid><description>
R-Wipe &amp;amp; Clean is software to delete junk files, unnecessary files from your computer to release the storage space and speed up your computer. In addition, R-Wipe &amp;amp; Clean also unleash the capacity of your drive and delete information invasion of privacy on different operations online and offline including your internet history and cookies, the list of downloaded files and documents were open, buffer different data, temporary files and many other items, created by the operating...
</description></item><item><title>Download Windows and Office Genuine ISO Verifier 12.25.50.25</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 15:55:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-and-office-genuine-iso-verifier-542.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-and-office-genuine-iso-verifier-542.html
</guid><description>
Windows and Office Genuine ISO Verifier is a small utility used to check for Microsoft Office and Windows ISO genuine or not by carrying out verification fast SHA-1 and MD5. The software has a friendly interface with the user and not cause you any real trouble whatsoever while navigating.
Users use tool requires to specify the file input and the application will automatically perform the rest of the work. Windows and Office Genuine ISO Verifier can compare the file SHA-1 with the...
</description></item><item><title>Download NetOptimizer 6.7.25.819</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 15:54:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-webminds-netoptimizer-7397.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-webminds-netoptimizer-7397.html
</guid><description>
NetOptimizer uses advanced techniques to speed up and optimize your PC's Internet connection. With NetOptimizer you will be able to optimize your Internet settings, allowing you to realize your peak Internet speed. NetOptimizer will let you fix all the misconfigurations and get your Internet working. You can easily configure your browser settings because NetOptimizer automatically applies optimal settings to all your browsers.
NetOptimizer can also clean up internet junk that tends to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Kingston SSD Manager 1.5.5.7</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 15:54:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kingston-ssd-manager-2810.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kingston-ssd-manager-2810.html
</guid><description>
Kingston SSD Manager is an application that gives users the ability to track and manage the various aspects of solid state drives Kingston® his.
Kingston SSD Manager - track, manage, drive SSD
&amp;nbsp;
The feature of Kingston SSD Manager
	Monitor the status and use of drive
	View the identification information drives, such as model name, serial number, firmware version and other related information
	Using The technology Self-monitoring analysis and report (SMART), and the detailed...
</description></item><item><title>Download Photo Supreme 2025.3.2.8022</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 15:53:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photo-supreme-430.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photo-supreme-430.html
</guid><description>
Photo Supreme is a software product management professional pictures of idimager. With Photo Supreme you can arrange, manage back stock photo archive of yourself and share them with you here and relatives easily via Email or Facebook. Photo Supreme provides users method to sort images effective, logical, as well as edit and share your photos with friends and relatives in the family. Especially the Photo Supreme allows to work with multiple image formats and support mounting support,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Google Chrome 139.0.7258.139</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 15:53:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-chrome-1012.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-chrome-1012.html
</guid><description>
Google Chrome web browser is the most used today. Support surf the web, listen to music, watch movies, play web game effective no jerky lag with the internet connection stable. When you are surfing the web or performing an important task, whether it is operation big or small, work or entertainment, then Chrome has the smart features and the speed you need to make, create and explore on the net.
The latest version of Google Chrome is the third 114. But we are providing for users Google...
</description></item></channel></rss>