<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 23:32:43 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 23:32:43 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download BitComet 2.17</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:46:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bitcomet-1220.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bitcomet-1220.html
</guid><description>
BitComet is the program that supports the download of torrent files quickly supports multiple security protocols and modern interface. BitComet is free software file-sharing p2p fully compatible with Bittorrent, this is one of the p2p protocols the most popular is designed for high-speed distribution of files with size 100MB or GB. BitComet is a bittorrent client powerful, clean, fast and easy to use. It support to download at the same time, download queue, downloads the selected in...
</description></item><item><title>Download MPV-EASY Player 0.40.0.4</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:45:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mpv-easy-player-3110.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mpv-easy-player-3110.html
</guid><description>
MPV-EASY Player is movies player based on mpv. It comes with easy to use interface, you can quickly adjust many parameters, the default settings are carefully adjusted will be able to stimulate all the performance of the mpv, so use mpv player simple than before a lot.
Basically, MPV-EASY Player is the assembly and combination of MPV, configuring mpv files, the command lua (including all scripts to be shared by other people on github), and the command js with the to read and fully...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Animate 2024 v24.0.12 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Sun, 28 Sep 2025 18:22:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-animate-05en-1221.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-animate-05en-1221.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Animate 2024 is an application to develop vector animation and raster interactive for games, applications, and websites. Vector animation design and bitmap interact for games, applications, and web. Making cartoons and banner ads became lively. And add the action to the instructions and the information. With the Adobe Animate CC, you can quickly publish on a variety of platforms and approach viewers on desktop computers, mobile devices and TVs.
Start your game. Developing...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wise Disk Cleaner 11.2.7.847</title><pubDate> Sun, 28 Sep 2025 18:20:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wise-disk-cleaner-392.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wise-disk-cleaner-392.html
</guid><description>
Wise Disk Cleaner software to clean hard drive by finding and deleting junk files downloads accumulate over time. Wise Disk Cleaner is pre-configured with about 50 types of extension files can usually be considered disposable, and you can extend the range by adding the file types of their own.
Wise Disk Cleaner to use the advanced algorithm with the ability to quick scan and comprehensive scan of hard drive space. Users can delete browsing history as well as the personal data important...
</description></item><item><title>Download Driver Easy Professional 7.1.0 Build 2641</title><pubDate> Sun, 28 Sep 2025 18:18:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-driver-easy-pro-431.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-driver-easy-pro-431.html
</guid><description>
DriverEasy Pro is a compact software that allows users to scan the computer system to find, download missing drivers for the computer or update outdated drivers on the system. DriverEasy Pro is considered the leading software in software used to install Drivers for computers.
The process of using DriverEasy Pro software is very simple. Users just need to download the software and install &amp;gt;&amp;gt; select "Scan Now" to scan Drivers on the system &amp;gt;&amp;gt; "Update All" Update. When using...
</description></item><item><title>Download AB Download Manager 1.6.14</title><pubDate> Sun, 28 Sep 2025 18:18:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ab-download-manager-12399.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ab-download-manager-12399.html
</guid><description>
With this application, you can easily download files from anywhere. Enjoy fast, free downloads with seamless browser extension support. It is built to be a desktop application that allows you to manage and organize your downloads better than before.
AB Download Manager features
	Simple and modern UI: Simple UI and dark mode by default
	Faster download speeds: Download files using multiple connections to increase your download speed by up to 500%
	Download Queue: Create and manage your...
</description></item><item><title>Download 3DP Chip 25.9</title><pubDate> Sun, 28 Sep 2025 18:17:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-3dp-chip-2282.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-3dp-chip-2282.html
</guid><description>
3DP Chip is software commonly used in the update of the version latest driver for your computer. The advantage of this software is completely free, compact and easy to use. 3DP Chip will help the hardware always works in the best state, with the 3DP Chip, you can know the driver has been outdated, then let the software automatically searches for the latest version and installed for your system.
3DP Chip - Download and update driver
With the 3DP Chip you can learn everything about the...
</description></item><item><title>Download ParkControl Pro 5.5.0.8</title><pubDate> Sun, 28 Sep 2025 18:17:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bitsum-parkcontrol-pro-6765.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bitsum-parkcontrol-pro-6765.html
</guid><description>
ParkControl Pro is free software to display and adjust CPU core settings in real time. It also has a bunch of free power automation features. Core Parking automatically disables CPU cores to save power when idle. Disabled cores are re-enabled as CPU load once again increases. This technology is very similar to frequency scaling, in that it seeks to throttle the CPU when idle.
These tweaks are completely safe for any properly configured PC. The only way they seem to be able to cause some...
</description></item><item><title>Download PortableApps.com Platform 30.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 28 Sep 2025 18:16:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-portableappscom-platform-1935.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-portableappscom-platform-1935.html
</guid><description>
PortableApps.com Platform is the open source application can be installed directly onto your USB thumb drive. It offers a wide range of mobile apps, including the mobile version of Firefox, Skype and many other applications. None of them comes, but you can download them directly from the application directory integrated.
PortableApps.com Platform - The launch the app
Other features include
	Integrated backup
	Theme modern interface
	Search options
	Support personal files, favorites...
</description></item><item><title>Download Acronis Cyber Protect Home Office Build 41126 Multilingual Bootable ISO</title><pubDate> Sun, 28 Sep 2025 18:15:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-acronis-true-image-bootable-iso-5344.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-acronis-true-image-bootable-iso-5344.html
</guid><description>
Acronis True Image for Windows PC for reliable backups because you always have reliable data copies so you can restore your entire system or individual files. Acronis True Image quickly restores your entire system or a specific file with confidence, knowing that the backup is just as good as the original.  Acronis True Image  will tell you everything about your backups at a glance. Monitor backup status, view file size and measure backup speed and view rendering.
Acronis True Image...
</description></item><item><title>Download Display Driver Uninstaller (DDU) 18.1.3.4</title><pubDate> Sun, 28 Sep 2025 18:13:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-display-driver-uninstaller-1999.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-display-driver-uninstaller-1999.html
</guid><description>
Display Driver Uninstaller (DDU) help to easily completely remove the packages and drivers graphics cards AMD, NVIDIA and Intel from your system without leaving any rest whatsoever. Display Driver Uninstaller will automatically detect your current GPU and allows you to delete drivers, registry and files related only by the click of a button. It will also prevent Windows automatically re-install drivers when you reboot your computer, leaving you a drivers graphics common until you install...
</description></item><item><title>Download BitRecover Email Duplicates Remover Wizard Enterprise 7.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 28 Sep 2025 18:12:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bitrecover-email-duplicates-remover-wizard-enterprise-11597.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bitrecover-email-duplicates-remover-wizard-enterprise-11597.html
</guid><description>
BitRecover Email Duplicates Remover Wizard is a useful application that helps users easily remove duplicate emails in their mailboxes. With a simple and effective interface, users can easily find and delete email duplicates quickly and conveniently.
This application supports many popular email formats such as PST, OST, EML, EMLX, MSG, MBOX, and many others. Users can select specific folders or entire mailboxes to scan and remove duplicate emails. BitRecover Email Duplicates Remover Wizard...
</description></item><item><title>Download Exportizer Enterprise 10.2.3.572</title><pubDate> Sun, 28 Sep 2025 18:12:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-exportizer-pro-470.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-exportizer-pro-470.html
</guid><description>
Exportizer Pro is software export base, robust data that allows view, edit and export the database to a data file, text, clipboard. Exportizer Pro is a software tool effective and simple, can be used to help individuals view, filter and copy an entire database to clipboard or convert it to another format.
Simple interface and no complex also indicates that Exportizer Pro meet the system requirements, the application can run on most operating systems.
The main window of Exportizer Pro...
</description></item><item><title>Download PureSync 8.0.3</title><pubDate> Sun, 28 Sep 2025 18:11:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-puresync-380.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-puresync-380.html
</guid><description>
PureSync is software backup and sync file can automatically keep backup files of your important. This is a Windows program to synchronize files and folders and to perform backups e.g. automatically in the background. PureSync will import files from a digital camera and synchronize the contents of multiple folders.
The program provides a step by step guide to configure the task to backup and synchronize your and set the advanced options such as exclude files, manage conflict, compare the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Executor 2.0.3</title><pubDate> Sun, 28 Sep 2025 18:11:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-executor-271.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-executor-271.html
</guid><description>
Executor for windows is a software alternative premium customization features for the Windows "Run" and "Search Programs". When you press WIN + Z and provides the search results instant, as-you-type for any keywords you enter. By default, Executor will index all the Desktop and Start Menu and you can easily expand the search range by adding the folder location additional.
Executor for windows
The program comes with a list of commands built in which you can use to quickly access many...
</description></item><item><title>Download Thea For SketchUp 4.0.1400.0158</title><pubDate> Sun, 28 Sep 2025 18:11:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thea-for-sketchup-4014.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thea-for-sketchup-4014.html
</guid><description>
Thea For SketchUp is a combination of the tool the powerful of Thea with the simplicity of SketchUp. Have the mode, the biased, unbiased and interactive, including GPU support at your fingertips, inside view SketchUp, is an enjoyable experience. The Plugin lets you enrich your models with detailed reviews, high content three dimensional, breaking the limitations of old related to complex pattern processing.
Thea For SketchUp allows you to run the interactive window, in Thea or directly...
</description></item><item><title>Download ReShade 6.6.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 28 Sep 2025 18:10:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-450-3227.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-450-3227.html
</guid><description>
ReShade is an open Source tool help improve the look of the old games on modern video cards as well as allow additional display technology / new video over on the old game doesn't support the technology that.
ReShade, technically, is a tool processing general for the games and video software. Imagine you see your favorite game yourself with the obscure-around, effects market the true depth or color correction. Function ReShade by showing in an automatic way and general access to...
</description></item><item><title>Download HE - Hardware Read and Write Utility 1.25.09.27</title><pubDate> Sun, 28 Sep 2025 18:10:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-he-hardware-read-and-write-utility-4287.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-he-hardware-read-and-write-utility-4287.html
</guid><description>
HE - Hardware Read and Write Utility is a powerful utility intended for hardware engineer, engineer, BIOS developer, driver, engineer, QA engineers, performance test engineers, diagnostic, etc., this utility access almost all the computer hardware, including PCI (PCI Express), index / Data, PCI, memory, index memory / Data space I / O, Index I / O / Data, Super I / O, DIMM SPD, CPU The registers MSR, screen, SMART, physical area of the hard drive identification data, ATA, dump tables ACPI...
</description></item><item><title>Download Clean Media Player 2025.9.27.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 28 Sep 2025 18:10:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-clean-media-player-12416.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-clean-media-player-12416.html
</guid><description>
If you've ever been offended by profanity in a movie, chances are you'll want the censored version of the movie. However, until the director decides to release it, you still have the option of muting unwanted scenes or editing the subtitles manually, if you are able to do so. The application mutes and displays subtitles without offensive words and phrases. Customize the profanity filter to your preferences. Skip inappropriate scenes by selecting their start and end times.
Clean Media...
</description></item><item><title>Download Vehicle Fleet Manager 2025.9.27</title><pubDate> Sun, 28 Sep 2025 18:09:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vehicle-fleet-manager-2326.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vehicle-fleet-manager-2326.html
</guid><description>
Vehicle Fleet Manager is an application easy to use for automotive companies want to manage the entire list with detailed information about expense tracking for car, employees, suppliers, parts and services. The interface of the tool at the time the first reviews seem too download, if you don't know English, it will be difficult to find it.
In fact, the program allows you to create a basic list of services, facilities, suppliers and employees, along with the maintenance schedule,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Minimal Firewall 2.2.4</title><pubDate> Sun, 28 Sep 2025 18:09:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minimal-firewall-13877.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minimal-firewall-13877.html
</guid><description>
Minimal Firewall works in conjunction with Windows Firewall to block all unknown connections by default, prompting you to create application-based rules to mitigate malware, telemetry, and data leaks. Completely eliminate applications that call home without your knowledge. Minimal Firewall provides a more secure and integrated approach by interacting directly with the native Windows Firewall, eliminating the need for risky system modifications.
Core Features
	Lockdown Mode: The core...
</description></item><item><title>Download Calcpad 7.4.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 28 Sep 2025 18:08:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-calcpad-12576.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-calcpad-12576.html
</guid><description>
Calcpad is free software for mathematical and engineering calculations. It is a flexible and modern programmable calculator with Html report generator. Calcpad uses a simple programming language that is fast and easy to learn. It does not require any special programming skills, which makes it suitable for engineers without any computer programming background. You can create calculation notes simply by writing your formula and text, enclosed in 'quotation marks'.
The program includes...
</description></item><item><title>Download Twenty 2nd Century Lightcube 1.3.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 28 Sep 2025 18:08:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-twenty-2nd-century-lightcube-12253.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-twenty-2nd-century-lightcube-12253.html
</guid><description>
Lightcube is a pixel art editing tool for game developers and artists, with many features including multiple layers, animation frames, and many tools including pen, eraser, wand selection spirit, paint bucket, line drawing and pattern brush. Lightcube has everything you need to easily turn your game development assets or creative visions into reality.
Whether you're a pixel artist or a game developer, the intuitive interface makes creating stunning pixel art easy. Immerse yourself in a...
</description></item><item><title>Download Gammadyne Clyton 36.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 28 Sep 2025 18:01:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gammadyne-clyton-7299.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gammadyne-clyton-7299.html
</guid><description>
Gammadyne Clyton is a feature-rich email client designed to keep your email private and filter spam messages. The spam filter is highly configurable and supports DNS blacklisting (DNSBL). Suspicious but unclear spam emails will be quarantined for 24 hours and then re-checked. The integrated address book supports personalized mass mailing. Received email cannot run scripts, download media, or use embedded objects without user consent.
Features of Gammadyne Clyton
	Clyton can be...
</description></item><item><title>Download DISMTools 0.7 Update 1</title><pubDate> Sun, 28 Sep 2025 17:56:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dismtools-12200.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dismtools-12200.html
</guid><description>
Inspired by Visual Studio, DISMTools is a user interface for DISM that allows you to manage Windows Imaging (WIM) files and much more. You can use it to uninstall apps, add driver or tool packages, etc.
DISM: This is a tool used to maintain and repair Windows images. This includes Windows Recovery Environment, Windows Setup, and Windows PE (WinPE). You can also use DISM to repair Windows images locally on your computer.
DISMTools: This is a user-friendly interface that allows you to...
</description></item></channel></rss>