<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 21:44:45 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 21:44:45 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Mirillis Action! 4.47.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 23:24:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mirillis-action-213.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mirillis-action-213.html
</guid><description>
Mirillis Action! is a game video recording software,  screen recording, take screenshot with impressive sharpness and 4K quality. It's a simple, reliable and effective software solution that's worth it when you need to access features like streaming and recording and work on desktop with unique HD video quality.
Mirillis Action makes exporting and uploading your recordings to popular services and social networks like YouTube and Facebook very easy. Work! provides predefined export...
</description></item><item><title>Download VectorStyler 1.3.007</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 23:24:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vectorstyler-7917.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vectorstyler-7917.html
</guid><description>
VectorStyler provides a complete set of drawing, design and illustration tools needed for modern design. Create illustrations, logos, icons, drawings, typography, vector art for screen, print and web. With many new features, VectorStyler redefines and extends the tools available to illustrators and designers, improving the creation of complex illustrations and designs.
Shape effects can be used to adjust the shape of objects, create different distortions, or add detail to shapes. Shape...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare UniConverter 17.1.5.476</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 23:23:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-uniconverter-4808.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-uniconverter-4808.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare UniConverter ( old name is Wondershare Video Converter Ultimate) which allows you to convert the video format. You can cut, splice, move, or add effects, subtitles a easy way. When using software you easily cut, splice, move, as well as add the effects, the subtitles to the video.... Or can switch the clods SD, HD video to any format popular for use with iPod (Classic, Nano and Touch), iPhone, Apple TV, Zune, PSP, Pocket PC...
Wondershare UniConverter helps convert formats...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ashampoo Backup Pro 27.5.41</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 23:23:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-backup-pro-716.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-backup-pro-716.html
</guid><description>
Ashampoo Backup Pro is software to backup and restore data professional to save the file, the important data for your computer. Ashampoo Backup Pro will remove the fear of viruses, ransomware, or hardware errors. Ashampoo® Backup Pro offers you various options to backup individual files or entire disk partitions on any storage media or on the cloud. User friendly, intuitive, fast. Even in case an error occurs the entire system, application integrated emergency can bring your...
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 7.8.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 23:21:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-11-7760.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-11-7760.html
</guid><description>
TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 is a program that allows users to discover hidden settings in Windows 11. This application is specially designed for Windows 11, groups many registry settings and distribute them from the easy and secure user interface. With TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 you can move the Windows taskbar to the top and resize the taskbar by editing the registry value. With any application that modifies the registry, we recommend that you have a backup copy...
</description></item><item><title>Download Aiseesoft HEIC Converter 1.0.50</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 23:21:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aiseesoft-heic-converter-7111.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aiseesoft-heic-converter-7111.html
</guid><description>
Aiseesoft HEIC Converter is a professional tool that allows you to convert iPhone, iPad, iPod photos from HEIC to JPG or PNG on Windows. With this powerful HEIC converter, you can convert all your HEIF (.heic) photos to JPG/JPEG or to PNG on your Windows or Mac computer without any hassle.
This highly efficient image format allows you to create and store images at a much smaller size without sacrificing image quality. With Aiseesoft HEIC Converter, you can simply convert HEIF (.heic)...
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 7.8.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 23:20:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-10-7759.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-10-7759.html
</guid><description>
TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 is a utility that allows users to discover hidden settings in Windows 10. This application is specially designed for Windows 10, groups many registry settings and provide them from an easy and secure user interface. With TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 you can move the Windows taskbar to the top and resize the taskbar by editing the registry value. With any application that modifies the registry, we recommend that you have a backup copy to...
</description></item><item><title>Download PC Internals Pro 2.100</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 23:20:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pc-internals-pro-13002.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pc-internals-pro-13002.html
</guid><description>
PC Internals Pro is a new solution that allows Windows users to comprehensively analyze the system components and reliable monitoring of the hard drive. This software is aimed at individual users as well as IT experts and retail agents attach importance to transparency, early detection and data security. PC Internals provides detailed information about the processor, RAM, graphics card, drive and other system components. The chart directly displays the current load, while the specific...
</description></item><item><title>Download PerfectTUNES 2026-01-16</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 23:19:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfecttunes-7115.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfecttunes-7115.html
</guid><description>
PerfectTUNES is a versatile music file manager that lets you find album art, check music folders for duplicates, and scan your songs for rip errors. export. PerfectTUNES comes as a software package, containing three applications that handle each function individually. PerfectTUNES is an intuitive, yet easy-to-use tool that allows you to organize your albums and music files, remove damaged songs, or remove duplicates. You can use its functions to clean up your music folder as well as find...
</description></item><item><title>Download Snappy Driver Installer 1.26.0 (R2600)</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 23:14:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-snappy-driver-installer-9472.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-snappy-driver-installer-9472.html
</guid><description>
Snappy Driver Installer is a free and open source software tool designed to help users install and update device drivers on Windows operating systems. Device drivers are software programs that allow the operating system to communicate with and control hardware devices such as graphics cards, sound cards, network adapters, etc.
It's important to note that while Snappy Driver Installer can be a useful tool for managing drivers on Windows systems, we always recommend caution when...
</description></item><item><title>Download KDEnlive 25.12.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 23:12:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kdenlive-3288.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kdenlive-3288.html
</guid><description>
Kdenlive is a video editor open source. The project was started in about 2003. Kdenlive is built on the Qt libraries and the KDE Frameworks. Most of the video processing is done by the MLT Framework, based on many open-source projects other as FFmpeg , frei0r , Movit, ladspa, sox, etc.
KDEnlive - video editing quickly
Our software is designed to meet most needs, from basic video editing to professional work. Kdenlive allows you to use and arrange a number of music and video, each can...
</description></item><item><title>Download TechSmith Snagit 2026 v26.0.0.9483</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 23:11:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-techsmith-snagit-01en-280.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-techsmith-snagit-01en-280.html
</guid><description>
TechSmith Snagit software screen capture anything on your screen, then easily add text arrows or effects and save the snapshot to a file or share it immediately by e-mail or IM. With TechSmith Snagit you can capture and share the article, photo or Web page directly from your screen.
TechSmith Snagit
TechSmith Snagit help you can take a photo screen in the form of roll, panoramic shooting, shooting photos of and easy photo editing after shooting. Besides it is feature - video recording...
</description></item><item><title>Download Accentize dxRevive Pro 1.2.8</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 23:11:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-accentize-dxrevive-pro-11436.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-accentize-dxrevive-pro-11436.html
</guid><description>
dxRevive Pro is a flexible voice recovery plugin, designed to enhance the quality of various dialogue recordings. Unlike many other recovery plugins, dxRevive does more than just filter signals. It goes even further, identifying and reintegrating missing frequency components, creating studio-like recordings from multi-source material.
Accentize dxRevive Pro Features
	Noise removal
	Resonance reduction
	Restore absent frequency
	Remove Codec components (for example, from Skype or Zoom...
</description></item><item><title>Download COAA PlanePlotter 6.7.3.6</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 23:11:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coaa-planeplotter-7840.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coaa-planeplotter-7840.html
</guid><description>
PlanePlotter receives and decodes digital position reports directly from the aircraft and plots them on a chart. Using PlanePlotter, you can see the radar-like display of all aircraft around you transmitting the appropriate digital messages including ACARS, ADS-B and HFDL.
PlanePlotter Features
	PlanePlotter displays a table showing messages received and decoded from direct plane transmissions.
	PlanePlotter stores all digital data it receives and decodes into a log...
</description></item><item><title>Download Accentize SpectralBalance2 1.0.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 23:10:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-accentize-spectralbalance-9280.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-accentize-spectralbalance-9280.html
</guid><description>
Accentize SpectralBalance is a software plugin designed for digital audio workstations (DAWs) that uses artificial intelligence (AI) to equalize the frequency spectrum of your audio. record. The plugin aims to enhance the clarity and definition of recordings by adjusting the levels of different frequency bands in real time.
By continuously analyzing the audio signal, it automatically adjusts its EQ curve to correct spectral imbalances to achieve a clear neutral voice. The efficient...
</description></item><item><title>Download Aon Tech Aon DocLift 2.1.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 20:18:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aon-tech-aon-doclift-14503.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aon-tech-aon-doclift-14503.html
</guid><description>
Aon DocLift by Aon Tech is a desktop application for Windows that converts PDF files into editable Word documents and images, designed to work completely offline for privacy- and security-sensitive use cases. It is positioned as a lightweight, local document conversion tool rather than a full-fledged cloud-based document automation platform.
Features of Aon DocLift
	Converts PDF files to Word documents and image formats while maintaining layout to the maximum extent.
	Runs as an...
</description></item><item><title>Download iTop Voicy 1.1.0.1603</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:05:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-itop-voicy-14482.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-itop-voicy-14482.html
</guid><description>
Transform your voice into anyone you want in real time. iTop Voicy uses the most advanced AI tuning technology to change your age, gender, and voice style while maintaining a natural sound. Whether you want to set a cute girl's voice or a robot voice, this free voice changer software for PC will produce high-quality voices instantly, without lag or delay.
Features of iTop Voicy
	Real-time, lag-free voice changer software
	Voice changer software for audio/video files
	Audio voice...
</description></item><item><title>Download Nexus Risk Canvas Pro Edition 1.0.0.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:05:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nexus-risk-canvas-pro-edition-14502.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nexus-risk-canvas-pro-edition-14502.html
</guid><description>
Nexus Risk Canvas is your gateway to visual risk management. Based on the industry-standard BowTie methodology, this application allows you to map complex risk scenarios, connecting threats to leading events and consequences through barriers and controls. Unlock the full power of visual risk assessment with Nexus Risk Canvas Pro. Designed for risk professionals, consultants, and security managers who need to record, archive, and share their work.
Why upgrade to the Pro version?
While...
</description></item><item><title>Download PingInfoView 3.25</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:04:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pinginfoview-2700.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pinginfoview-2700.html
</guid><description>
PingInfoView is a small utility that allows you to easily ping multiple host names and IP addresses and watch the result in one table. It automatically ping to all hosts every number of seconds that you specify, and displays the number of times the ping success and failure, as well as the ping time average. You can also save the ping result into text / html / xml or copy it to the clipboard.
PingInfoView doesn't require any installation process or additional dll file. To start using, just...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe After Effects 2025 v25.6.4.003 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:59:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-after-effects-0010-2793.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-after-effects-0010-2793.html
</guid><description>
Adobe After Effects is a powerful digital visual effects, motion graphics, and compositing application developed by Adobe Inc. The software is widely used in the film, television, and video game industries to animate and enhance video content.
After Effects allows users to create stunning motion graphics and visual effects by animating text, images, and video clips. Its capabilities include keying, tracking, compositing, and basic audio editing, making it a versatile tool for...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Audition 2025 v25.6.4 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:58:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-audition-0004-1246.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-audition-0004-1246.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Autdition 2024 is a professional tool for professionals active in the field of audio processing and video, offering them the ability to almost unlimited. Ease of use combined with flexibility of work, allows you to create the main copy of the highest class, edit, mix, handle, impose more sound effects especially. In fact, users have to be on my computer a recording studio powerful full with the tool easy to use at the same time, the tool is quite professional.
Adobe autdition CC -...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare PDFelement Pro 12.1.6.3963</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:57:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-pdfelement-pro-105.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-pdfelement-pro-105.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare PDFelement Pro support users to convert PDF to office documents for easier use, modify in every situation. Is one of the software conversion material is rated best today, integrated with many features. We recommend that you should use experience software many useful features this.
Wondershare PDFelement Pro - conversion Fie PDF more features, multi-language
Wondershare PDFelement Pro what?
Convert PDF into Word, Excel, PowerPoint...
• Convert PDF and protected PDF into...
</description></item><item><title>Download Private Photo Move 1.1.0.6</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:57:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-private-photo-move-14501.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-private-photo-move-14501.html
</guid><description>
Optimize your PC performance and protect your privacy with Private Photo Move – a tool that helps you organize your photos intelligently without relying on the cloud. If your computer is cluttered with thousands of photos and you're worried about uploading them to the cloud, this is the solution for you. No more slow or privacy-risky sorting methods, Private Photo Move for Windows offers a completely different experience.
The application leverages the power of NVIDIA or AMD GPUs along...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Substance 3D Painter 11.1.2.5115 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:57:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-substance-painter-1279.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-substance-painter-1279.html
</guid><description>
Substance Painter is a drawing application 3D completely new with the possibility of unprecedented and workflow is optimized, help in creating graphics easier than ever. To create sprites or 3D characters, no need to have knowledge about a painters professional animation, now it has become easy and accessible for the average user . The program is recognized in the world is creative tool and the most convenient to draw 3D create character models.
Substance Painter - App 3D drawing
The...
</description></item><item><title>Download EditPlus 6.1 Build 836</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:56:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-editplus-338.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-editplus-338.html
</guid><description>
EditPlus is editor text, editor, HTML and editor program for Windows. EditPlus works as a text editor as well as editor, PHP editor, HTML, editor, Java viewer and Hex. It supports syntax highlighting for many languages, such as HTML, CSS, Java, PHP, C / C ++, Perl, and Python, and can act as a web browser to preview the HTML page. EditPlus also provides some other useful features, such as auto completion, code folding, spell checking, search and replace, keyboard shortcuts, custom and HTML...
</description></item></channel></rss>