<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 05:43:35 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 05:43:35 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Balabolka 2.15.0.912</title><pubDate> Tue, 27 Jan 2026 02:25:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-balaboka-142.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-balaboka-142.html
</guid><description>
Balabolka is a text-to-speech (TTS) program. It can read text on your screen in a human-like voice. You can use Balabolka to listen to text from a variety of file formats, convert text to spoken audio files, and adjust speech parameters such as speed and pitch. It is often used for accessibility purposes, helping people who have difficulty reading or multi-tasking by listening to text while doing other activities. Balabolka supports multiple languages and uses different TTS engines,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Notepad++ 8.9.1 + Portable</title><pubDate> Tue, 27 Jan 2026 02:25:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-notepad-1062.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-notepad-1062.html
</guid><description>
Notepad++ is software editor programming editor and edit source code support on Windows platform, working with many other programming languages like ASP, PHP, Java, C#, Python, Jsp... Notepad++ is a source code editor is many programmers choice with many functions than men of it is Notepad.
Notepad++ - tool editor programming
Notepad++ has many features, simple interface, and can combine with many programming languages different. Notepad++ supports you to automatically perform various...
</description></item><item><title>Download ResizeScaleAI Pro 1.2.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 27 Jan 2026 02:23:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-resizescaleai-14510.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-resizescaleai-14510.html
</guid><description>
ResizeScaleAI enhances the sharpness and clarity of your old, blurry, or low-resolution photos. Using advanced Artificial Intelligence, the app precisely upgrades your images—preserving texture, fine detail, and natural image quality.
With intelligent face restoration, the app realistically reconstructs faces, restoring lost features while maintaining recognition and proportions. Unlike cloud-based tools, ResizeScaleAI runs entirely on your computer—no internet and no uploads...
</description></item><item><title>Download PhotoLikr 2026.0.0.11</title><pubDate> Tue, 27 Jan 2026 02:22:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photolikr-12758.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photolikr-12758.html
</guid><description>
PhotoLikr for Windows allows you to quickly rate and sort photos in a selected folder. Just use the up and down arrow keys to rate and left or right to navigate. After rating your photos, you can filter them and export your top picks to another folder or upload them to Dropbox and easily share links on social media like Facebook, Twitter or LinkedIn.
Key Features
	Fast photo viewer that supports all popular photo formats (including RAW)
	Multiple settings to create a cached...
</description></item><item><title>Download Perfectly Clear WorkBench 5.0.1.3057</title><pubDate> Tue, 27 Jan 2026 02:22:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfectly-clear-workbench-6892.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfectly-clear-workbench-6892.html
</guid><description>
Perfectly Clear Workbench is an application that uses image editing libraries Perfectly Clear by Athentech and is provided to demonstrate the capabilities of the Perfectly Clear processing libraries, which recognize faces and allow quick export of processing settings for use.
One of the key features in Workbench is the ability to "export to API" when saving a Preset. This allows you to make image edits in Workbench and adjust the settings to suit your editing style and needs. You can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Substance 3D Stager 3.1.7 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Tue, 27 Jan 2026 02:21:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-substance-3d-stager-6624.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-substance-3d-stager-6624.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Substance 3D Stager is a professional staging tool for designing and rendering scenes. Import content, arrange your scene, apply materials and textures, adjust both image-based and physical lighting, save the camera with different resolutions, and render realistic images , all in Stager!
Substance 3D Stager allows you to make creative decisions in context. Tweak and adjust your compositions in real time. Build your realistic 3D scenes with smart tools quickly and efficiently. With...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube Downloader 3.9.18 (2601)</title><pubDate> Tue, 27 Jan 2026 02:21:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube Downloader  is a dedicated software that helps users  downloading youtube videos  Favorites on PC for offline viewing. With MediaHuman YouTube  Downloader  you can download videos from youtube website to your computer with  fast speed , with special software development technology that automatically receives videos from Websites, in addition to the ability to download videos from software websites, can convert downloaded video formats to various formats for the purpose...
</description></item><item><title>Download Krita Studio 4.4.3 (x32) / 5.2.15 (x64)</title><pubDate> Tue, 27 Jan 2026 02:20:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-krita-studio-4058.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-krita-studio-4058.html
</guid><description>
Krita Studio is a drawing tool digital open-source and FREE are designed for the designer, illustrator, painter, texture painter and matte, as well as for the field of VFX (visual Effects). Krita has been in development for over ten years and has recently undergone a growth explosion. It provides many common features and creative to help both amateur and professional. Krita Studio provides support CMYK, grid perspective drawing, HDR, filters, assistant, drawing, painting, docker and many...
</description></item><item><title>Download DBF Recovery 4.65</title><pubDate> Tue, 27 Jan 2026 02:20:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbf-recovery-7931.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbf-recovery-7931.html
</guid><description>
DBF Recovery is software that gives users the ability to restore a damaged database back to its original condition without the expertise required to complete that task. It fixes headers and data structures in an automated process that doesn't involve user interaction. With DBF Recovery, you will truly have a lean, honest DBF repair machine without any functionality.
Features of DBF Recovery
	Quick and simple to use DBF file repair software.
	Repair almost any DBF...
</description></item><item><title>Download iTubeGo YouTube Downloader 10.13.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 27 Jan 2026 02:19:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-itubego-youtube-downloader-3681.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-itubego-youtube-downloader-3681.html
</guid><description>
iTubeGo YouTube Downloader  is the best way to download live video from 1000+ streaming sites. iTubeGo YouTube Downloader is a powerful download tool that allows you to save video and audio for free. The output format of high speed converter is high quality MP4, MP3. Fully compatible with iPhone, iPad, iTunes, iMovie, Android Phone and more.
iTubeGo YouTube Downloader - Solution for downloading high quality Youtube video 
Features of iTubeGo YouTube Downloader
	Download videos from...
</description></item><item><title>Download Net Disabler 1.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 27 Jan 2026 02:19:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-net-disabler-6415.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-net-disabler-6415.html
</guid><description>
On average, teenagers spend 9 hours a day using media for entertainment, which is time more than sleep time and more time studying. But as we all know, it's hard to get rid of things that are bad for us, for that reason. We may want to temporarily turn off the Internet. The reasons are varied and many, to prevent programs from calling home or updating, preventing your computer from receiving social media emails or alerts, etc. you can also use it to avoid being distracted during the...
</description></item><item><title>Download AssistMyTeam PDF Converter 7.2.300.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 27 Jan 2026 02:18:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-assistmyteam-pdf-converter-7856.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-assistmyteam-pdf-converter-7856.html
</guid><description>
AssistMyTeam PDF Converter is a software to convert files to PDF, it is used to save all kinds of documents, such as Word, Excel, PowerPoint, web pages, images, emails. or even ZIP to PDF files. Best of all, Windows Explorer Shell Integration makes this significantly easier, with one-click instant PDF.
Features of AssistMyTeam PDF Converter
	Convert different types of documents to PDF quickly.
	Support to convert 120+ file types to PDF.
	Save the compressed ZIP file to PDF.
	Convert...
</description></item><item><title>Download iTop Voicy 1.1.1.1621</title><pubDate> Tue, 27 Jan 2026 02:18:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-itop-voicy-14482.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-itop-voicy-14482.html
</guid><description>
Transform your voice into anyone you want in real time. iTop Voicy uses the most advanced AI tuning technology to change your age, gender, and voice style while maintaining a natural sound. Whether you want to set a cute girl's voice or a robot voice, this free voice changer software for PC will produce high-quality voices instantly, without lag or delay.
Features of iTop Voicy
	Real-time, lag-free voice changer software
	Voice changer software for audio/video files
	Audio voice...
</description></item><item><title>Download Epic Pen Pro 3.12.172</title><pubDate> Tue, 27 Jan 2026 02:18:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-epic-pen-pro-934.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-epic-pen-pro-934.html
</guid><description>
Epic Pen Pro is an annotation tool, the computer allows to draw, write and highlight directly on most of the applications to the Windows desktop, including software presentation, website, video, creative studio and even games. Simple interface with visual styles clean and no buttons or options difficult to understand. Epic Pen for everyone.
&amp;nbsp;
The main features of the Epic Pen Pro
	Full support for custom hotkeys can be used along with the hot key software standard.
	There is no...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ultracopier 3.0.1.5</title><pubDate> Tue, 27 Jan 2026 02:17:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-supercopier-2121.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-supercopier-2121.html
</guid><description>
SuperCopier is a replacement for advanced copy command Windows standard. Supercopier support pause and resume the copy operation is ongoing, install copy speed can adjust, automatically rename the old file, and more.
You can view a detailed list of queue copy and optionally move files up or down in the list, add additional files and also can delete or ignore the category when needed. This can be especially useful when you copy large number of files.
Supercopier - copy...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter 3.9.18 (2501)</title><pubDate> Tue, 27 Jan 2026 02:17:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-to-mp3-converter-1744.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-to-mp3-converter-1744.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter is the software support download youtube video and convert video to mp3 format fast and most simple. MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter allows you download and convert videos from YouTube and other websites to MP3 format by pasting the YouTube URL into the application. When you paste the URL, the program will display thumbnails for videos and you have the option to customize the title information, artist and album before you begin the process of...
</description></item><item><title>Download ESET AV Remover tool 1.6.11.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 27 Jan 2026 02:16:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-eset-av-remover-tool-9612.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-eset-av-remover-tool-9612.html
</guid><description>
ESET AV Remover tool is free software designed to remove any existing anti-virus programs that were installed on your computer before you installed ESET. Alternatively, you can also use other uninstallers like Revo Uninstaller Pro or IObit Uninstaller Pro
You will need to restart your computer once done, so make sure to finish your work and save all relevant data before launching ESET AV Remover. Things to keep in mind: before using the ESET AV Remover tool tool or uninstalling any...
</description></item><item><title>Download MaxCut Business Edition 2.9.6.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 27 Jan 2026 02:16:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-maxcut-business-edition-3912.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-maxcut-business-edition-3912.html
</guid><description>
MaxCut Business Edition is a software to create cutting diagrams, accurate, and cost estimate for the wood industry, cabinets and metal,.. You enter the size and material, MaxCut will do the rest! Produce optimized cutting diagrams, create estimates, orders, and labels - it's just a click. Run the application MaxCut Business Edition brings a pretty clean interface and slick quickly get you up and running. Most space represents the editing area, with the main function are stored cleverly in...
</description></item><item><title>Download Futuremark SystemInfo 5.90.1458</title><pubDate> Tue, 27 Jan 2026 02:16:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-futuremark-systeminfo-2568.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-futuremark-systeminfo-2568.html
</guid><description>
Futuremark SystemInfo is a small program created to conduct diagnostic analysis complete all kinds of processes, as well as equipment used on a personal computer of you. According to the author, you can use this tool as a component reference in the application be supported, it will determine the version of your operating system and other information about the hardware.
Note that Windows XP, 3DMark06, and PCMark05 are no longer be Futuremark support. Function SystemInfo on Windows XP is...
</description></item><item><title>Download Room Arranger 10.3.3.741</title><pubDate> Tue, 27 Jan 2026 02:15:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-room-arranger-3779.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-room-arranger-3779.html
</guid><description>
Room Arranger is a 3D application lets you easily plan for the room, office or his apartment just a few mouse clicks. The application comes with a simple interface will significantly simplify your work. You can draw many kinds of objects and items to create furniture of your own. This app also includes a library of object rich.
Software Room Arranger enables you to view your project in 3D form. You can also upload the 3D scene interact on your blog or your website. The application uses...
</description></item><item><title>Download AssistMyTeam PDF Studio 7.2.300.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 27 Jan 2026 02:14:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-assistmyteam-pdf-studio-14149.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-assistmyteam-pdf-studio-14149.html
</guid><description>
The AssistMyTeam PDF Studio add-on integrates your Windows Explorer with a PDF reader, converter, editor, organizer, splitter, merger, file extractor and even OCR in an instant one-click operation.
What sets this application apart from most other bloated, complex commercial PDF applications is its relative ease of use and efficiency with a simple, minimalistic yet intuitive and unobtrusive interface—just right-click on a file in Windows Explorer and perform the action you want to your...
</description></item><item><title>Download Avast Ransomware Decryption Tools 1.0.0.816</title><pubDate> Tue, 27 Jan 2026 02:14:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avast-ransomware-decryption-tools-5371.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avast-ransomware-decryption-tools-5371.html
</guid><description>
Avast Ransomware Decryption Tools is a package of ransomware decryption tools to help you get back files from 20 different ransomware encrypted. Avast Ransomware Decryption Tools supports decryption AES_NI, Alcatraz Locker, Apocalypse, BadBlock, Bart, BTCWare, Crypt888, CryptoMix (Offline), CrySiS, EncrypTile, FindZip, Globe HiddenTear, Jigsaw, Legion NoobCrypt, Stampado, SZFLocker, TeslaCrypt, XData.
Features of Avast Ransomware Decryption Tools
	Easily remove ransomware
	Decrypt and...
</description></item><item><title>Download CFTurbo 2026 R1.1.128 + CFTurbo FEA v2026 R1.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 27 Jan 2026 02:10:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cfturbo-3713.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cfturbo-3713.html
</guid><description>
CFTurbo is a powerful program but easy to use software for pump design can help you design pumps from scratch or redesign the rotor is there. Simply tell it the flow rate, head, RPM and any vortex before (optional) and CFTurbo which will automatically generate a pump design. Then you have the option to go back and change any detail of design with the guidance of CFTurbo. Easy but flexible, this approach to pump design saves you time and still lets you get exactly the pump design you...
</description></item><item><title>Download LastPass Password Manager 5.4.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 27 Jan 2026 02:03:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lastpass-269.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lastpass-269.html
</guid><description>
LastPass is a free software to help manage passwords allows you to store all the login information of your site in a warehouse password cross-platform compatibility only. Instead of remember the user name and personal password, you only need to remember the main password to open the lock the password of his safe.
LastPass
LastPass can automatically fill in the login box for all the account website is your hosting. Whenever you log into a website has stored your vault, the program will...
</description></item><item><title>Download Inno Setup Unpacker 2.2.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 27 Jan 2026 02:03:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-inno-setup-unpacker-12546.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-inno-setup-unpacker-12546.html
</guid><description>
Inno Setup is a popular and reliable application that creates program installers by helping you create scripts. Extracting the installation files from their container, resulting from compiling code with Inno Setup, can only be done through self-extracting files. In other words, you need to create a self-extracting executable to shell the installation documents.
Inno Setup Unpacker can help you avoid such actions, which is especially useful because some system security protocols block...
</description></item></channel></rss>