<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 15:52:37 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 15:52:37 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download DesktopOK 12.27</title><pubDate> Tue, 20 Jan 2026 17:03:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopok-1635.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopok-1635.html
</guid><description>
DesktopOK is software save and restore the positions of icons. DesktopOK also offers a solution small but effective for the user to change the screen resolution often. DesktopOK is not installed and can be executed easily from the desktop, and can be carried on a small USB or memory device to another. Start of the program. The first time you use the program, the program will show you screen license. Free program and license info is only displayed the first time (on each PC).
DesktopOK -...
</description></item><item><title>Download lessmsi 2.11.7</title><pubDate> Tue, 20 Jan 2026 17:03:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lessmsi-12392.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lessmsi-12392.html
</guid><description>
Lessmsi (Less MSIerables) is a free and portable application that allows users to view and extract the contents of MSI files.
How does it work? Files with the .msi extension are not as widely used as their .exe cousins, but both contain programs for Windows. The main difference between them is that the latter does not always come with an installer, while it comes standard with the former. However, there will be cases where you just need to view or want to extract specific content from...
</description></item><item><title>Download Perfectly Clear WorkBench 5.0.1.3051</title><pubDate> Tue, 20 Jan 2026 16:55:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfectly-clear-workbench-6892.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfectly-clear-workbench-6892.html
</guid><description>
Perfectly Clear Workbench is an application that uses image editing libraries Perfectly Clear by Athentech and is provided to demonstrate the capabilities of the Perfectly Clear processing libraries, which recognize faces and allow quick export of processing settings for use.
One of the key features in Workbench is the ability to "export to API" when saving a Preset. This allows you to make image edits in Workbench and adjust the settings to suit your editing style and needs. You can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Visual Similarity Duplicate Image Finder Pro 9.6.0.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 20 Jan 2026 16:55:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-visual-similarity-duplicate-image-finder-corporate-7847.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-visual-similarity-duplicate-image-finder-corporate-7847.html
</guid><description>
Visual Similarity Duplicate Image Finder Pro Pro is a program that helps you find all the same and duplicate images in a folder and its subfolders, computer or network to organize the photos. . Duplicate photo finder uses advanced algorithms to find duplicate photos the way humans do. Due to that fact, it can find duplicate images even if they are in different image formats, bit depths, and image sizes.
It can expand your results or specify an exact match that only differs in image...
</description></item><item><title>Download XMedia Recode 3.6.2.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 20 Jan 2026 16:54:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xmedia-recode-919.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xmedia-recode-919.html
</guid><description>
XMedia Recode is software to change the quality for video files on windows operating system, it has the ability to change quality, video format. XMedia Recode supports the format conversion such as 3GP, 3GPP, 3GPP2, AAC, AC3, AIFF, AMR, ASF, AU, AVI, DIVX, DTS, DVR-MS, FLV, H. 261, H. 263, H. 264, M4A, M1V, M2V, M4V, MKV.
Parameters advanced
The user can step into the more advanced and modify bitrate, frame interval the frame rate, modes, speed control and many other settings regarding...
</description></item><item><title>Download Driver Magician 6.5</title><pubDate> Tue, 20 Jan 2026 16:54:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-driver-magician-lite-117.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-driver-magician-lite-117.html
</guid><description>
Driver Magician: The program automatically marks non-standard drivers (not included with Windows), allowing you to quickly find drivers that have been added by devices such as printers, the web orange etc ... Improve driver backup and restore performance
The application Driver Magician also backs up all the drivers in the machine for restoration in case of malfunction or reinstallation. All the drivers for the devices are gathered in an exe self-installer file and only need to run this...
</description></item><item><title>Download XYplorer 28.10.0500</title><pubDate> Tue, 20 Jan 2026 16:53:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-533.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-533.html
</guid><description>
XYplorer - File Manager for Windows is software that supports users to manage files on the Window quickly and to arrange the folder tidy. XYplorer features tabbed browsing, search, files, powerful, preview, flexible, highly customizable interface, dual frame options and a variety of unique ways to automate effective tasks often repeat. It's fast, lightweight, and portable.
Features XYplorer
	XYplorer is a file manager mobile. It does not require any settings, store all configuration...
</description></item><item><title>Download Argente System Repair 1.0.4.8</title><pubDate> Tue, 20 Jan 2026 16:53:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-argente-system-repair-13813.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-argente-system-repair-13813.html
</guid><description>
Argente System Repair is a lightweight utility designed to diagnose and fix common Windows system problems. It scans your system to identify errors in operating system components, file systems, installation files, and other system components, and then applies targeted fixes to resolve these problems. The tool provides different scan modes, including simple scan, recommended scan, and custom scan, allowing users to customize the repair process according to their needs.
System Repair...
</description></item><item><title>Download MyLanViewer Enterprise 6.7.4</title><pubDate> Tue, 20 Jan 2026 16:52:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mylanviewer-enterprise-1274.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mylanviewer-enterprise-1274.html
</guid><description>
MyLanViewer is a program for scanning IP address, Netbios and LAN / Network powerful for Windows tool whois and traceroute, remote shutdown and process management Wake On LAN (WOL), scan and monitor wireless networks. This app will help you find all IP addresses, MAC addresses and shared folders of computers on the network wired or wireless (Wi-Fi).
MyLanViewer Enterprise - Scan IP address LAN/Network
The program scans network and displays the computer network in your window, friends...
</description></item><item><title>Download WSCC Windows System Control Center 10.0.2.6 Commercial</title><pubDate> Tue, 20 Jan 2026 16:52:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wscc-windows-system-control-center-1599.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wscc-windows-system-control-center-1599.html
</guid><description>
WSCC Windows System Control Center can automatically install and update the add-ons are supported. Alternatively, WSCC can use the http protocol to download and run the program. WSCC is portable device, no installation required. Extract content of zip archive downloaded into any folder on your computer.
The interface is very simple and intuitive, thus allowing any type of user how to find his way, regardless of the experience of their previous with the IT world. Besides, it includes a...
</description></item><item><title>Download EverNote 11.0.4.60353</title><pubDate> Tue, 20 Jan 2026 16:51:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-evernote-3261.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-evernote-3261.html
</guid><description>
EverNote is the all in one tool allows you to track notes, todo items, memos, outlines, excerpts, websites, ideas and other things and automatically synchronize them between multiple computers and mobile devices (iPhone, Android, etc.). You can choose to sort their notes into categories, password protect them, export them to XML and more. EverNote supports a number of pattern notes allow you to add to-do list, spreadsheet like Excel to calculate costs (automatic sum), notes, phone, contact...
</description></item><item><title>Download Free Download Manager 6.33.0.6626</title><pubDate> Tue, 20 Jan 2026 16:51:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-download-manager-3105.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-download-manager-3105.html
</guid><description>
Free Download Manager is free application download manager, Free Download Manager will significantly increase downloads by splitting the files into several smaller parts and then downloads at the same time. Speed your download will be significantly increased. Manager download free can also continue to download at broken or not responding, so you don't need start downloading from the beginning after occasionally interrupted.
Free Download Manager - Manage and speed up downloads
You can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Agisoft Metashape Professional 2.3.0 Build 21954</title><pubDate> Tue, 20 Jan 2026 16:50:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-agisoft-metashape-professional-1731.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-agisoft-metashape-professional-1731.html
</guid><description>
Agisoft Metashape (formerly PhotoScan) is a software product independently perform image processing and digital data creation, 3D space used in GIS applications, material cultural heritage and the production visual effects as well as the indirect measurement of the different subjects scale. Technical digital photography is deployed wisely is applied with the method of computer vision led to the system processor, smart auto, on the one hand, can be managed by a new person in the field of...
</description></item><item><title>Download MedCalc 23.4.8</title><pubDate> Tue, 20 Jan 2026 16:50:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-medcalc-1536.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-medcalc-1536.html
</guid><description>
MedCalc is a statistical software for biomedical research can analyze many performance curve system with a set of rich functionality, chart types and advanced module. MedCalc was designed to meet the needs and requirements of the study nature and aims to analyze the statistical calculations of the project. This software provides the tools and means essential to analyze the characteristic curve of the system (ROC), drawing data and perform the statistical calculations.
MedCalc -...
</description></item><item><title>Download Stardock Start11 2.6.0.2 Beta</title><pubDate> Tue, 20 Jan 2026 16:49:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stardock-start11-7029.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stardock-start11-7029.html
</guid><description>
Start11 is an application capable of customizing the Start Menu and Taskbar on Windows 11 and Windows 10. This is an application that allows users to customize Windows 11 to suit their preferences. his personal. Start11 will help you bring the new Start Menu of Windows 11 to Windows 10. And vice versa, Start11 also helps you to bring the Start Menu of Windows 10 to Windows 11.
Start11 also helps users bring some functions of Windows 10 to Windows 11 through customizing the Taskbar such...
</description></item><item><title>Download By Click Downloader 2.4.28</title><pubDate> Tue, 20 Jan 2026 16:49:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-by-click-premium-193.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-by-click-premium-193.html
</guid><description>
YouTube By Click Premium is a high quality powerful video downloader including YouTube downloader, YouTube Converter, YouTube Chrome Downloader, Facebook Video Downloader, Downloader Vimeo, Dailymotion Downloader and supports many other video sites.
YouTube By Click
YouTube By Click Features
	YouTube by Click can download and convert files to MP3, MP4, FLV, AVI, WMV, 3GP, WAV and WEBM formats.
	Download all supported qualities, including HD.
	YouTube By Click downloads entire YouTube...
</description></item><item><title>Download Chris-PC RAM Booster 7.26.0119</title><pubDate> Tue, 20 Jan 2026 16:48:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chris-pc-ram-booster-1181.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chris-pc-ram-booster-1181.html
</guid><description>
ChrisPC RAM Booster is software speed up your system by managing and acceleration of the RAM in the operating system. RAM Booster will monitor the RAM usage (memory random access) and upon reaching the threshold memory certain low, it will trigger the process of freeing up memory for the new program open while moving at the same time the old programs from the RAM memory into virtual memory on disk.
Chris-PC RAM Booster - speed up processing RAM
Certainly this is a slower process...
</description></item><item><title>Download Monkeys Audio 12.04</title><pubDate> Tue, 20 Jan 2026 16:48:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-monkeys-audio-949.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-monkeys-audio-949.html
</guid><description>
Monkey\'s Audio is software that compresses digital music without loss of quality. Supports high quality WAV files and CD ripping. Monkeys Audio will compress .wav tracks into .ape files to reduce their size without loss of sound quality, decompress .ape, convert files, check file integrity and manage tags.
Unlike traditional methods like MP3 and OGG, which permanently remove quality to save space, Monkey\'s Audio only creates perfect copies with the same sound quality as the originals....
</description></item><item><title>Download VidCoder 12.14 + Portable</title><pubDate> Tue, 20 Jan 2026 16:47:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vidcoder-534.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vidcoder-534.html
</guid><description>
VidCoder is software to convert movies to MKV and MP4, as well as extract video content from DVDS and Blu-ray. This is a software utility to help people extract the video content from the BD and DVD as well as convert the clips specific to MKV and MP4.
VidCoder has an interface that includes a clear design, including a menu bar, several buttons and a panel to display the queue. The file can be added with the help of the file browser or drag and drop-out.
Features VidCoder
	VidCoder...
</description></item><item><title>Download Filou NC Gorilla 2026.01.19</title><pubDate> Tue, 20 Jan 2026 16:47:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-filou-nc-gorilla-10211.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-filou-nc-gorilla-10211.html
</guid><description>
Experts estimate that 80-90% of all CNC parts are 2.5D parts. So there is no need to create complex 3D models, but 2.5D CNC codes can be quickly and easily obtained with the CAM module from easy-to-create 2D geometries. With Filou NC Gorilla, you create all your work in one software, from simple and fast 2D design to transfer to CNC machine/control to mill your workpiece.
Features of Filou NC Gorilla
	No complex 3D models
	Many CAM functions
	Create NC code easily
	Editor with 3D...
</description></item><item><title>Download WonderPen 3.0.6.8242</title><pubDate> Tue, 20 Jan 2026 16:46:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tominlab-wonderpen-7753.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tominlab-wonderpen-7753.html
</guid><description>
WonderPen is a writing app for both professional and amateur writers. WonderPen uses a tree directory to organize documents, supports unlimited levels, and can easily manage both short articles and long works. Documents can be exported to various formats such as images, PDF, Word, Epub and web pages. Multiple chapters can be exported as a book in batches.
WonderPen has a built-in full automatic backup function. By default, it will perform a full database backup every 15 minutes. It also...
</description></item><item><title>Download Code VBA 11.0.0.27</title><pubDate> Tue, 20 Jan 2026 16:46:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-code-vba-7207.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-code-vba-7207.html
</guid><description>
Code VBA allows professional software developers and MS Office users to write VBA code faster and take less time to search for online solutions. Find and insert VBA for Excel, Access and Word according to the application object model. The tool annotation explains what classes and procedures perform and grant direct access (F1) to the relevant documentation on Office MSDN online. In addition, the VBA code creator supports the writing of larger code blocks.
Features of Code VBA:
	The...
</description></item><item><title>Download Hallmark Card Studio Deluxe 23.0.1.4</title><pubDate> Tue, 20 Jan 2026 16:46:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hallmark-card-studio-delux-9807.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hallmark-card-studio-delux-9807.html
</guid><description>
Hallmark Card Studio Deluxe is a software application developed by Hallmark to help users create personalized greeting cards, invitations and other printable cards. It offers a wide range of templates, design tools, and features to assist in creating custom tags for different occasions.
Features of Hallmark Card Studio Deluxe
	Over 20,400 Customizable imprints and projects for every occasion
	Over 21,000 Breathtaking Graphics including Exclusive Hallmark Art
	Featured library of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Classroom Spy Professional 5.5.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 20 Jan 2026 16:45:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-classroom-spy-professional-916.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-classroom-spy-professional-916.html
</guid><description>
Classroom Spy Professional is a software classroom management effective. Manage and track activities of all the computers of students remotely. Plus, you can share your screen with the activity record of the student, the computer controls for performance, limit the use of the Internet, the application blocks and more.
Classroom Spy Professional - software classroom management
The main features of Classroom Spy Professional
	Display live images of the remote computer.
	You can control...
</description></item><item><title>Download WindowManager 10.24.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 20 Jan 2026 16:45:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desksoft-windowmanager-573.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desksoft-windowmanager-573.html
</guid><description>
WindowManager is a software by DeskSoft dedicated to providing software utilities for windows. DeskSoft WindowManager is the window manager window to ensure your windows are placed exactly where you want. Software will help you to help you improve your work flow by remembering and restoring the position and size of the program and your window. The processing window can completely customize and you can set the special rules for the windows favorite or used most often.
WindowManager send...
</description></item></channel></rss>