<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 11:34:56 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 11:34:56 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Argente System Repair 1.0.3.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 10 Oct 2025 14:34:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-argente-system-repair-13813.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-argente-system-repair-13813.html
</guid><description>
Argente System Repair is a lightweight utility designed to diagnose and fix common Windows system problems. It scans your system to identify errors in operating system components, file systems, installation files, and other system components, and then applies targeted fixes to resolve these problems. The tool provides different scan modes, including simple scan, recommended scan, and custom scan, allowing users to customize the repair process according to their needs.
System Repair...
</description></item><item><title>Download Opera GX (Gaming Browser) 122.0.5643.136</title><pubDate> Fri, 10 Oct 2025 14:34:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-gx-3170.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-gx-3170.html
</guid><description>
Opera GX is a special version of the Opera browser is built to complement gamers avid. Browser this game comes with the unique features to help users make maximum use of both the game and their browser. Opera GX is built specifically to support the game. This browser includes the unique features to help users have the best experience when gaming and surfing the web.
Opera GX - special browser for gamers
GX Control allows you to set a limit on the level of use RAM, CPU and network where...
</description></item><item><title>Download Brave Browser 1.83.112</title><pubDate> Fri, 10 Oct 2025 14:33:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-brave-browser-2874.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-brave-browser-2874.html
</guid><description>
Brave Browser is a browser based on Chromium, the basic principle is that operation fast and privacy of users. The program can block pop-up windows and other ads, plus it blocked the mechanism for monitoring the online activities of your. Therefore, you can purchase and safely browse the website you are interested in without having to worry about the fact that your activity will be monitored and then you will be shown the necessary advertising or service provider of parties...
</description></item><item><title>Download Smart Tools mini 1.3.3</title><pubDate> Fri, 10 Oct 2025 14:32:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-smart-tools-mini-9669.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-smart-tools-mini-9669.html
</guid><description>
Smart Tools mini is a new package optimized for devices without a magnetometer. Half of new Android devices do not have a compass sensor (Moto G4, Galaxy J, Galaxy Tab4...). Surely this application will work well on all Android devices.
It includes 5 professional sets with a total of 15 tools
	Set 1. Length, Angle, Slope, Level, Thread: Smart Ruler Pro
	Set 2. Sound meter, Vibration meter: Sound Meter Pro
	Set of 3. Flashlight, Magnifier, Mirror: Smart Light Pro
	Set 4. Unit,...
</description></item><item><title>Download WPS Office - PDF, Word, Excel, PPT 18.21.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 10 Oct 2025 14:31:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wps-office-pdf-word-excel-ppt-8244.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wps-office-pdf-word-excel-ppt-8244.html
</guid><description>
WPS Office is a mobile office suite app that allows users to view, edit and create documents, spreadsheets, and presentations on their Android device. The app is available for download from the Google Play Store and is compatible with a wide range of file formats, including Microsoft Office documents.
WPS Office - Free Office suite for Word, PDF, Excel, is an all-in-one office suite that integrates Word, PDF, Excel, PowerPoint, Forms, Cloud Storage, Online Editing, Template library and...
</description></item><item><title>Download PhotoDirector: AI Photo Editor 20.6.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 10 Oct 2025 14:31:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-photodirector-photo-editor-8144.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-photodirector-photo-editor-8144.html
</guid><description>
PhotoDirector is a photo editing app for Android devices that allows you to edit and enhance your photos with a variety of tools and effects. With PhotoDirector, you can adjust your photo's color and lighting, remove blemishes and other imperfections, and apply filters to give your photos a unique look. You can also use PhotoDirector to create photo collages and slideshows, add text and stickers to photos, and share your edited photos on social networks or through other sharing...
</description></item><item><title>Download All Document Reader and Viewer 3.0.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 10 Oct 2025 14:31:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-all-document-reader-and-viewer-8877.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-all-document-reader-and-viewer-8877.html
</guid><description>
All Document Reader: PDF, excel, word, Documents is a smart office application that helps you read all documents downloaded from the internet, supports reading PDF files, PDF Reader, doc, docx xls, ppt, txt, excel, xlxs files... fast, easy and convenient.. All Document Reader: PDF, excel, word, Documents are providing multiple Document reading features including PDF Reader, Docs Reader &amp;amp; Docx, ppt reader, xls reader, txt, excel &amp;amp; documents different from readers.
All Document...
</description></item><item><title>Download Avast Cleanup – Phone Cleaner 25.20.0 build 800011270</title><pubDate> Fri, 10 Oct 2025 14:30:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-avast-cleanup-phone-cleaner-8885.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-avast-cleanup-phone-cleaner-8885.html
</guid><description>
Avast Cleanup - Phone Cleaner is a mobile app for Android devices designed to help users optimize their phone's performance and free up storage space. This application provides many tools and features to clean and speed up your phone.
One of the main features of Avast Cleanup is the Junk Cleaner, which scans your phone for unnecessary files such as temporary files, app cache, and other junk data. The app will then provide a list of files that can be safely deleted to free up space on...
</description></item><item><title>Download Clime: NOAA Weather Radar Live 1.72.7 build 269</title><pubDate> Fri, 10 Oct 2025 14:30:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-clime-noaa-weather-radar-live-8743.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-clime-noaa-weather-radar-live-8743.html
</guid><description>
Get a powerful yet easy-to-use weather station right on your device with Weather Radar and Alerts. Real-time animated weather radar images on a highly interactive map enhanced with severe weather warnings provide accurate weather forecasts and don't let bad weather take you by surprise! This complex yet highly intuitive app reflects real-time weather conditions and gives you the detailed meteorological data you need to know: current temperature and "Feel Like", Heat Today's Min/Max...
</description></item><item><title>Download Money Lover - Spending Manager 8.47.1.36</title><pubDate> Fri, 10 Oct 2025 14:30:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-money-lover-spending-manager-8349.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-money-lover-spending-manager-8349.html
</guid><description>
Receive personal finance awards &amp;amp; Money management app to manage money now! Track your spending, monitor your transactions, create a monthly budget, motivate yourself to save money, and more. You can also link your Money Lover wallet to your bank account to automatically track your transaction history. Money Lover is a must-have app for personal finance management. Financial management becomes super easy and fast!
Managing personal finances can be difficult for many people. You need...
</description></item><item><title>Download Diseases Dictionary Offline 5.3</title><pubDate> Fri, 10 Oct 2025 14:29:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-diseases-dictionary-offline-14076.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-diseases-dictionary-offline-14076.html
</guid><description>
Diseases Dictionary Offline is a Medical Dictionary handbook, which can act as a clinical advisor for self-diagnosis and can also be used to look up symptoms, pathologies and treatments. Download free medical dictionary like a doctor for FREE at home, providing common diseases and treatment codes.
Features of the Medical App:
Offline – The app works offline, no internet connection required;
Detailed description of all major medical conditions and...
</description></item><item><title>Download SpeedChecker Speed Test 2.8.8</title><pubDate> Fri, 10 Oct 2025 14:29:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-speedchecker-speed-test-8162.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-speedchecker-speed-test-8162.html
</guid><description>
SpeedChecker Speed ​​Test is a mobile application that allows users to test the speed of their internet connection. To use the app, users simply download and install the app on their Android device, open the app, and then follow the on-screen instructions to run a speed test. The application will measure the download and upload speed of the user's internet connection and display the results in a clear and easy-to-read format.
It can also provide additional information such as...
</description></item><item><title>Download My Boy! - GBA Emulator 2.0.9</title><pubDate> Fri, 10 Oct 2025 14:29:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-my-boy-gba-emulator-9397.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-my-boy-gba-emulator-9397.html
</guid><description>
My Boy! is a super fast and full-featured emulator to run GameBoy Advance games on the widest range of Android devices, from low-end phones to modern tablets. It accurately emulates almost all aspects of the real hardware.
Features of My Boy! GBA Emulator
	Fastest emulation, thus saving your battery to the MAX.
	Very high game compatibility. Runs almost all games without any problems.
	Link cable emulation on the same device or between devices via Bluetooth or Wi-Fi.
	Gyro/tilt/sun...
</description></item><item><title>Download XAPK Installer 4.6.5</title><pubDate> Fri, 10 Oct 2025 11:27:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-xapk-installer-14218.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-xapk-installer-14218.html
</guid><description>
Is there an easier way to install apk apps on your device? This all-in-one xapk installer for Android will help you! Our app will help you download and install files seamlessly from apkpure and other sources. No need to search for folders, unzip packages, or use manual methods.
Although this is an apk installer for Android, it is also a full-fledged xapk installer to satisfy all users' requirements for an xapk file downloader. Our tool recognizes both .apk and .xapk files in just a few...
</description></item><item><title>Download KeyNote NF 2.1.1.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:49:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-keynote-nf-11953.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-keynote-nf-11953.html
</guid><description>
KeyNote NF is a tabbed notebook with a RichText editor, multi-level note taking, and powerful encryption. KeyNote NF was written to overcome significant limitations in other popular information managers, both freeware and shareware. KeyNote is the only information manager that offers a combination of simple notes and tree notes, a rich text editor, the ability to freely combine multiple notes of different types in one file unique and securely encrypted.
Main features:
Unicode...
</description></item><item><title>Download Abelssoft KeyDepot 2026 v12.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:48:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-abelssoft-keydepot-14052.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-abelssoft-keydepot-14052.html
</guid><description>
Abelssoft KeyDepot is a password manager software designed to securely store and manage passwords, logins, and other sensitive data. The software uses advanced encryption technology, specifically AES-256 encryption, to protect user data from unauthorized access. KeyDepot allows users to create a master password to secure access to their password vault, and this master password will never be stored on Abelssoft servers for added security.
Features of Abelssoft KeyDepot
	Secure password...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tenorshare 4DDiG File Repair 4.2.2.8</title><pubDate> Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:48:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tenorshare-4ddig-file-repair-5630.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tenorshare-4ddig-file-repair-5630.html
</guid><description>
Tenorshare 4DDiG File Repair is AI-powered software to repair damaged or damaged videos, photos, files and audios, improve their quality and add color to black media white. 4DDiG photo editing solves all photo problems like blurry photos, overexposed photos, etc. Powered by AI, it can dramatically improve image resolution and colorize black and white photos in seconds, not hours.
Features of Tenorshare 4DDiG File Repair
	Easily repair any blurry, overexposed and damaged videos, photos...
</description></item><item><title>Download AI Image Background Remover Pro 1.1.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:47:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ai-image-background-remover-pro-13963.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ai-image-background-remover-pro-13963.html
</guid><description>
Easily remove image backgrounds with pixel-perfect precision with AI Image Background Remover Pro. Designed for e-commerce sellers, graphic designers, photographers, and social media managers, this powerful desktop tool gives you complete control over your creative process. Unlike online tools, AI Image Background Remover Pro works 100% offline on your computer, keeping your images and projects completely private and secure. No uploads, no data collection, and no registration...
</description></item><item><title>Download GPU Caps Viewer 1.64.3.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:46:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gpu-caps-viewer-2926.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gpu-caps-viewer-2926.html
</guid><description>
GPU Caps Viewer is a software OpenCL and OpenGL is designed for Microsoft Windows, which allows you to view important information about the GPU, such as type, driver version, video memory, etc. The application can also display OpenCL, extensions, API support and the ability to OpenGL (texture size, version, number of texture units, etc.).
GPU Caps Viewer can also be used to view system configuration, provides information such as the amount of system memory, CPU type and speed, operating...
</description></item><item><title>Download Download Master 7.2.2.1739</title><pubDate> Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:45:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-download-master-2005.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-download-master-2005.html
</guid><description>
Download Master is a software to improve the speed of file download from the Internet. Download Master replace the standard module of the load in the popular browsers such as Google Chrome, Firefox, Safari, Yandex.Browser, Opera, Internet Explorer etc. The software support download the file from the current position after the break of the network connection. Download Master lets you download videos or music from various services and have the priority function of the load. The software...
</description></item><item><title>Download Intel Graphics Driver for Windows 10 / 11 32.0.101.8136</title><pubDate> Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:45:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intel-graphics-driver-for-windows-10-5954.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intel-graphics-driver-for-windows-10-5954.html
</guid><description>
Intel Graphics Driver for Windows 10 supports Intel ' s latest 8th-generation Core processor, introducing the Intel ® UHD graphics, with the ability to immerve in the top 4K UHD entertainment from your laptop for a maximum of 10 hours. Along with some security fixes, this driver also optimised the system's inactivity to reduce power consumption.
Look at the complete new interface of gameplay.intel.com, where you will find the proposed game settings for many of your favorite PC games....
</description></item><item><title>Download Prevent Restore Pro 2025 v114</title><pubDate> Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:44:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-prevent-restore-pro-1473.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-prevent-restore-pro-1473.html
</guid><description>
Prevent Restore Pro is software prevent restore files deleted in any drive: external hard drives and hard drives mounted in hard drive, SSD, Flash drives, except CD-ROM and CD-RW. The software uses many security algorithms can be used to get data.Our program includes some of the most reliable and accepted as standard.
Prevent Restore Pro - Prevent restore files deleted
The features of Prevent Restore Pro
Mode to clean up quickly
	In this mode, the program will not overwrite the free...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wireshark 4.6.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:44:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wireshark-56.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wireshark-56.html
</guid><description>
Wireshark (aka Ethereal) is a network protocol analyzer allows you to capture and examine data from a live network or from a snapshot file on disk.You can browse the captured data in an interactive way and view summary information and details for each package. Wireshark has several powerful features, including a language filter rich display and ability to view flow created back of the TCP.
Wireshark - network protocol analyzer
The program can read the capture file from tcpdump...
</description></item><item><title>Download Helium Music Manager Premium 17.4.535</title><pubDate> Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:39:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-helium-music-manager-premium-164.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-helium-music-manager-premium-164.html
</guid><description>
Helium Music Manager is a music manager that can rip, tag, play, browse, search, rename, burn and synchronize your music with the mobile. You can control your music collection with Helium Music Manager. Stop using time looking for the file on your computer or looking through CDS, vinyl records and tapes - instead, simply enjoy and explore your music! Helium Music Manager can replace the ripper, the player, tag editor and related software to audio your other.
Helium Music Manager...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ocenaudio 3.16.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:39:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ocenaudio-837.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ocenaudio-837.html
</guid><description>
Ocenaudio: software for windows, this is the sound editing easy, fast and powerful. ocenaudio is a program for audio editing multi-platform, easy to use, fast and functional. This is the ideal software for those who need to edit and analyze audio files.
Ocenaudio - editor powerful audio for windows
This software is based on Ocen Framework , a powerful library developed to simplify and standardize the development of application analysis and sound processing on many platforms.
Features...
</description></item></channel></rss>