<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 01:46:45 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 01:46:45 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download WiFi Network Monitor 9.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 11 Jan 2026 22:31:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wifi-network-monitor-14102.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wifi-network-monitor-14102.html
</guid><description>
WiFi Network Monitor is a useful tool to remotely scan and detect all the systems connected to your wireless network. It helps you monitor your Wi-Fi network and protect it from hackers and other unauthorized users.
The fast scanning capability powered by 'ARP-based Multi-Threading' technique allows you to scan the entire network in just a few seconds. It can detect all the systems connected to your Wi-Fi network, including desktops, laptops, mobile phones, home systems and other portable...
</description></item><item><title>Download Inno Setup Unpacker 2.2.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 11 Jan 2026 22:31:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-inno-setup-unpacker-12546.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-inno-setup-unpacker-12546.html
</guid><description>
Inno Setup is a popular and reliable application that creates program installers by helping you create scripts. Extracting the installation files from their container, resulting from compiling code with Inno Setup, can only be done through self-extracting files. In other words, you need to create a self-extracting executable to shell the installation documents.
Inno Setup Unpacker can help you avoid such actions, which is especially useful because some system security protocols block...
</description></item><item><title>Download Balabolka 2.15.0.911</title><pubDate> Sun, 11 Jan 2026 17:12:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-balaboka-142.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-balaboka-142.html
</guid><description>
Balabolka is a text-to-speech (TTS) program. It can read text on your screen in a human-like voice. You can use Balabolka to listen to text from a variety of file formats, convert text to spoken audio files, and adjust speech parameters such as speed and pitch. It is often used for accessibility purposes, helping people who have difficulty reading or multi-tasking by listening to text while doing other activities. Balabolka supports multiple languages and uses different TTS engines,...
</description></item><item><title>Download PrivaZer Pro Donors 4.0.116</title><pubDate> Sun, 11 Jan 2026 17:08:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-privazer-donors-198.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-privazer-donors-198.html
</guid><description>
PrivaZer Donors  cleans and removes filth traces from the system. Intensive cleaning of unwanted traces of what you've done, viewed, downloaded, deleted, etc. Take ownership of your security and freedom - Free up disk space. Keep your PC snug and secure !!!
With one click, PrivaZer can safely clean: Internet browsers, Index.dat, Cookies, Tor Cookies, Flash Cookies, Silverlight Cookies, DOM Storing, IndexedDB, AppCache Registry, RAM, Pagefile.sys and Hiberfil.sys files.  PrivaZer  can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Yamicsoft Windows 11/10 Manager 2.3.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 11 Jan 2026 17:07:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yamicsoft-windows-11-manager-6779.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yamicsoft-windows-11-manager-6779.html
</guid><description>
Windows 11 Manager is an all-in-one utility for Microsoft Windows 11 specially, it includes over forty different utilities to optimize, tweak, clean up, speed up and repair your Windows 11, helps make your system perform faster, eliminate system fault, increase stability and security, personalize your copy of Windows 11, and meet all of your expectations.
Features of Windows 11 Manager:
Information:
	Creates the system restore point manually;
	Gets detailed information about your...
</description></item><item><title>Download EmEditor Pro 25.4.5</title><pubDate> Sun, 11 Jan 2026 17:07:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-emeditor-pro-69.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-emeditor-pro-69.html
</guid><description>
EmEditor Pro - the professional version of editor text powerful for programmers, web developers and ordinary users with illumination of syntax and Unicode support. The features of the editor such as search and replace in files using regular expressions, automatic code detect, bookmark link and address email, block selection mode, configure the button bar, menu, font and elements color. With each language you can set separate configuration.
EmEditor Pro - text Editor professional
The...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cockos REAPER 7.59</title><pubDate> Sun, 11 Jan 2026 17:06:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cockos-reaper-889.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cockos-reaper-889.html
</guid><description>
Cockos REAPER is a powerful software for for windows, chp lets you record, arrange, edit, and display the audio waveform multi-track. Cockos REAPER offers an extensive feature set includes many effects and a sample project. REAPER supports ASIO, Kernel Streaming, WaveOut, and DirectSound for playback and recording. It reads the files in WAV, OGG and MP3 files and records WAV files. You can arrange any number of items in any number of tracks and use plug-in sound processing (DirectX and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Gilisoft Total Repair 11.6.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 11 Jan 2026 17:06:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-total-repair-12836.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-total-repair-12836.html
</guid><description>
Total Repair Toolkit is an all-in-one system maintenance tool that integrates smart diagnosis, in-depth repair, and performance optimization. It has a one-click smart repair engine that can automatically resolve over 500 common problems such as system lag, game crashes, and file corruption. Meanwhile, it provides a professional manual repair module to meet advanced requirements.
Gilisoft Total Repair Features
	Application error repair based on a large DLL library
	In-depth diagnosis...
</description></item><item><title>Download O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro 22.1.236 / Server</title><pubDate> Sun, 11 Jan 2026 17:05:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-diskimage-pro-218.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-diskimage-pro-218.html
</guid><description>
O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro is software backup data comprehensive and effective is provided to protect the data of the computer system, it creates images for individual drives or the entire system that still does not affect your system.
O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro allows the user to backup the entire computer or drive, the and files whenever you want even while the computer is being used. Or can use O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro to create a copy chinh sac of computer disk drives, can be used instead of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Zortam Mp3 Media Studio Pro 33.70</title><pubDate> Sun, 11 Jan 2026 17:01:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zortam-mp3-media-studio-pro-135.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zortam-mp3-media-studio-pro-135.html
</guid><description>
Zortam Mp3 Media Studio Pro brings you rich processing tools music includes extract and convert music from CD to Mp3 format, edit, music cards, music download....You can also create discs CD high-quality music, with Zortam Mp3 Media Studio search music files duplicated to remove them from the system, rename music files, switch back and forth between formats.
Zortam Mp3 Media Studio Pro is rated as perfect software in the processing of the MP3 files on the computer. First of all, you can...
</description></item><item><title>Download 4KSoftware 4K Downloader 6.1.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 11 Jan 2026 17:00:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-downloader-3858.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-downloader-3858.html
</guid><description>
4K Downloader is a Windows application small but powerful to download and convert video in 4K and 8K Ultra HD from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion and thousands of other video-based websites. It speeds up your download by up to 5 times. Consider that most smart phones, TVS, computers, and tablets all support the high definition format, don't be surprised when many users want to enjoy quality content on their device. 4K Downloader is a lightweight software designed to help you grab videos...
</description></item><item><title>Download GiliSoft MP3 CD Maker 9.7</title><pubDate> Sun, 11 Jan 2026 16:58:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-mp3-cd-maker-7400.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-mp3-cd-maker-7400.html
</guid><description>
GiliSoft MP3 CD Maker is software to create normal audio CDs from your favorite music. It supports you to create MP3 CD/DVD from popular music formats, burn WMA CD/DVD disc from popular audio and video format files. Enjoy sound in your portable CD player or car CD player. Support high speed recording. Easy to use with intuitive user interface.
GiliSoft MP3 CD Maker supports burning music CDs (Audio CDs) from all popular audio and video formats files including MP3, WMA, WAV, AAC, FLAC,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Any Video Downloader Pro 10.1.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 11 Jan 2026 16:58:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-video-downloader-pro-3731.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-video-downloader-pro-3731.html
</guid><description>
Any Video Downloader Pro is software support you can download video HD 720p, 1080p, 2K, 4K and 8K from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion, Vimeo, Metacafe and thousands of video sharing sites, other. It is a tool to speed up multi-threading can speed up your download faster up to 5 times. This helpful program support download at the same time. Any Video Downloader Pro lets you download multiple videos at the same time. Moreover, it allows you to pause and resume downloads if you need more...
</description></item><item><title>Download OneCommander Pro 3.106.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 11 Jan 2026 16:58:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-one-commander-4232.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-one-commander-4232.html
</guid><description>
One Commander is a file manager for Microsoft Windows with function improved user interface and navigation experience, system file and manipulating the files. Utilities use the tree view to sort the folder, subfolders, and files your, make sure that the current location of you always clear. It supports multiple tabs, allowing you to easily switch between them and access the folder you need.
One Commander - a filemanager for Windows
Depending on the format of the files, some files can...
</description></item><item><title>Download VovSoft - Vov Screen Recorder 4.6</title><pubDate> Sun, 11 Jan 2026 16:57:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-screen-recorder-5507.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-screen-recorder-5507.html
</guid><description>
VovSoft Screen Recorder is a handy tool for taking screenshots of your computer, ie recording the activities happening on the screen. Using Vov Screen Recorder, you can record your screen to create program videos, compile product demo videos for some customers, record gameplay to post on social networks or record any other screen activity to share with friends or stakeholders or to upload video streaming services such as YouTube. Vov Screen Recorder can capture a specific area or full...
</description></item><item><title>Download ProfiCAD 13.4.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 11 Jan 2026 16:57:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-proficad-1546.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-proficad-1546.html
</guid><description>
ProfiCAD is a software Program to draw diagram and circuit diagram of the electrical circuit and electronics with many features to support users. ProfiCAD will search the control circuit is different then help, you can design a variety of diagram techniques, such as diagrams, pneumatic and hydraulic. One of the obvious features of this product is the simplicity of it. Simple in the tool bar and the icons represent the parts. Simply arrange the menu, just put the items on the screen and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tomabo MP4 Downloader Pro 6.1.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 11 Jan 2026 16:56:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tomabo-mp4-downloader-pro-3602.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tomabo-mp4-downloader-pro-3602.html
</guid><description>
Tomabo MP4 Downloader Pro is the app designed exclusively for Windows users to help them download videos from the Internet. In addition, it also increase download speeds by up to 500%, or even more. Tomabo MP4 Downloader Pro, interface design, simple, well-organized, beautifully. Here, users can view a list of videos has download with gravatar, URL, quality, duration and size of them. Software allows download video series at the same time, at the same time, support create a list of clips...
</description></item><item><title>Download Universal Media Server 15.3.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 11 Jan 2026 16:50:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-universal-media-server-2364.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-universal-media-server-2364.html
</guid><description>
Universal Media Server is a media server UPnP compatible multi-platform DLNA. The purpose of this software is to give you a chance to stabilize to make the exchange quick and convenient files necessary. Server the device supports the different output and facilitate the process of exchanging information between a computer and necessary equipment. The development is based on PS3 Media Server, which means you can interact with the Playstation 3, Xbox 360, as well as TV Samsung or...
</description></item><item><title>Download Clean Media Player 2026.1.10.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 11 Jan 2026 16:49:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-clean-media-player-12416.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-clean-media-player-12416.html
</guid><description>
If you've ever been offended by profanity in a movie, chances are you'll want the censored version of the movie. However, until the director decides to release it, you still have the option of muting unwanted scenes or editing the subtitles manually, if you are able to do so. The application mutes and displays subtitles without offensive words and phrases. Customize the profanity filter to your preferences. Skip inappropriate scenes by selecting their start and end times.
Clean Media...
</description></item><item><title>Download Robin YouTube Video Downloader Pro 7.1.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 11 Jan 2026 16:49:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-video-downloader-pro-2828.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-video-downloader-pro-2828.html
</guid><description>
YouTube Video Downloader Pro is a Windows application professional to download and convert videos from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion and thousands of video sharing sites, other. It accelerates your download up to 5 times. YouTube Video Downloader Pro allows you to download multiple videos at the same time. It also allows you to pause, resume and cancel a download at any time.
YouTube Video Downloader Pro - Download online videos on social networks
Features of YouTube Video Downloader...
</description></item><item><title>Download DeskCalc Pro 10.0.6</title><pubDate> Sun, 11 Jan 2026 16:48:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-deskcalc-pro-1874.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-deskcalc-pro-1874.html
</guid><description>
DeskCalc Pro is a math tool can perform a variety of calculations, such as addition, subtraction, multiplication and division, as well as use trigonometric functions like sine, cosine, tangent and other functions. In addition, the program DeskCalc Pro also provides tools currency converter. Software DeskCalc Pro quite easy to perform many math operations, thanks to the support tab of it. Can export data created to Excel.
DeskCalc Pro - mathematical tools
Moreover, DeskCalc Pro allows...
</description></item><item><title>Download LuBan 3D 04.01.2026</title><pubDate> Sun, 11 Jan 2026 16:47:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-luban-3d-10427.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-luban-3d-10427.html
</guid><description>
LuBan 3D is creative design software that helps designers and manufacturers create their innovative products quickly. LuBan automatically creates 3D models in a variety of forms, such as lithophane, stacks, hashes, slabs, reliefs, modules, and wireframes. The resulting model can be fabricated by 3D printing, laser cutting and CNC milling. Model parts can be fabricated using laser cutting and 3D printing. LuBan does not depend on specific fabrication methods; instead, it can communicate...
</description></item><item><title>Download LINQPad Premium 9.5.10</title><pubDate> Sun, 11 Jan 2026 16:46:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-linqpad-premium-7181.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-linqpad-premium-7181.html
</guid><description>
LINQPad is a software utility targeting .NET Framework and .NET Core development. It is used to interactively query SQL databases using LINQ, as well as to write C# code interactively without an IDE. LINQPad will be where C# code can be rapidly prototyped outside of Visual Studio. It can also be used to code in VB.NET, SQL and F#.
With LINQPad, you can interactively query databases using a modern query language: LINQ. LINQPad includes a tool optimized for on-the-fly context creation of...
</description></item><item><title>Download TubeDownload Pro 7.1.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 11 Jan 2026 16:46:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubedownload-pro-12035.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubedownload-pro-12035.html
</guid><description>
TubeDownload Pro is a professional Windows application for downloading your favorite videos from YouTube and hundreds of other video sites. TubeDownload Pro can increase download speed up to 500% or even more.
Features of TubeDownload Pro
	Download your favorite videos from YouTube and hundreds of other video sites.
	Increase download speed up to 500% or even more.
	Download 720p, 1080p, 2K, 4K and 8K HD videos from YouTube.
	Download entire playlists in just a few clicks.
	Download...
</description></item><item><title>Download DesktopOK 12.26</title><pubDate> Sun, 11 Jan 2026 16:37:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopok-1635.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopok-1635.html
</guid><description>
DesktopOK is software save and restore the positions of icons. DesktopOK also offers a solution small but effective for the user to change the screen resolution often. DesktopOK is not installed and can be executed easily from the desktop, and can be carried on a small USB or memory device to another. Start of the program. The first time you use the program, the program will show you screen license. Free program and license info is only displayed the first time (on each PC).
DesktopOK -...
</description></item></channel></rss>