<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 19:58:44 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 19:58:44 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Universal Media Server 15.2.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 17:21:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-universal-media-server-2364.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-universal-media-server-2364.html
</guid><description>
Universal Media Server is a media server UPnP compatible multi-platform DLNA. The purpose of this software is to give you a chance to stabilize to make the exchange quick and convenient files necessary. Server the device supports the different output and facilitate the process of exchanging information between a computer and necessary equipment. The development is based on PS3 Media Server, which means you can interact with the Playstation 3, Xbox 360, as well as TV Samsung or...
</description></item><item><title>Download ImageGlass 9.4.0.1120</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 17:21:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-imageglass-4396.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-imageglass-4396.html
</guid><description>
ImageGlass is a software free image viewer open source. With a beautiful interface, simple and works in a gentle way is the advantages first thing that users notice in ImageGlass. Software ImageGlass is also a tool that helps users to view photos with support for many popular formats, including animations GIF, image transparent PNG. Imageglass allows users to view photos in zoom mode and zoom very flexible and easy. With this utility, you can browse the photo series with the same Zoom...
</description></item><item><title>Download HeidiSQL 12.14.0.7165</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 17:11:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-heidisql-3222.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-heidisql-3222.html
</guid><description>
HeidiSQL is a user interface, MySQL / MSSQL allows you to manage your database by yourself and browse table contents from Windows interface easy to use. In addition to the common tasks such as running SQL queries, creating, dropping and editing tables, you can also perform the maintenance operations covering various integrity checks, optimize database, repair, and more. Moreover, you can import data from text files, synchronize tables between two databases and export selected tables to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Win Screen Recorder 2025 v10.0.3.9</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 17:09:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-win-screen-recorder-7793.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-win-screen-recorder-7793.html
</guid><description>
Win Screen Recorder 2022 is a convenient and easy to use screen recording software that allows you to record any part of the screen, record HD video and audio, and capture screenshot any time you want.
Features of Win Screen Recorder
	Includes Filmmaker and Video Editor.
	It's easy to create your own movies from images and video clips.
	Add Music, Text, Animation, Effects and Mosaic to your videos.
	Cut, join, crop and rotate your video.
	Publish your video to the Internet or DVD.
</description></item><item><title>Download Windows 11 Pro 25H2 v26200.7462 NoTPM Multilingual Preactivated</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 17:09:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-11-6618.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-11-6618.html
</guid><description>
Windows 11 is officially leaked to a developer version. Previously, when Windows 10 was released, Microsoft once stated that Windows 10 would be the last version of Windows for users. Clearly, with the arrival of Windows 11, Microsoft needed a major reason to reverse its previous claims and still remove Windows 10 by introducing some new operating systems.
About the interface of Windows 11 is quite similar to Windows 10X (a version of Windows 10 has stopped growing). The logo image of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Monkeys Audio 11.90</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 17:08:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-monkeys-audio-949.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-monkeys-audio-949.html
</guid><description>
Monkey\'s Audio is software that compresses digital music without loss of quality. Supports high quality WAV files and CD ripping. Monkeys Audio will compress .wav tracks into .ape files to reduce their size without loss of sound quality, decompress .ape, convert files, check file integrity and manage tags.
Unlike traditional methods like MP3 and OGG, which permanently remove quality to save space, Monkey\'s Audio only creates perfect copies with the same sound quality as the originals....
</description></item><item><title>Download Axialis IconGenerator 2.10</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 17:08:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-axialis-icongenerator-14196.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-axialis-icongenerator-14196.html
</guid><description>
Axialis IconGenerator is a free icon generator for professional developers, UI designers, and illustrators. It allows you to create vector and bitmap icons in seconds from a database of available icon sets. It allows users to quickly create, customize, and generate vector and bitmap icons from a large database of available icon sets. The software supports many vector formats including SVG, XAML, PDF, EPS and PS, as well as bitmap formats such as PNG, BMP, JPEG, ICO and Mac...
</description></item><item><title>Download Windows 10 Pro (64-Bit) 22H2 v19045.6691 Multilingual Pre-activated</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 17:07:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-10-x64-bit-5460.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-10-x64-bit-5460.html
</guid><description>
Windows 10 is a Microsoft Windows operating system for PCs and workstations that is part of the Windows NT family of operating systems. This operating system was introduced on September 30, 2014 under the Build 2014 program and was officially released on July 29, 2015
Windows 10 x64 Bit is the most powerful version of windows that comes with Microsoft Edge, a brand new browser built to give you a better web experience. This is a version of Windows 10 Pro - Pre-activated providing the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Fotosizer Professional 3.21.0.594</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 17:06:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fotosizer-professional-2279.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fotosizer-professional-2279.html
</guid><description>
Fotosizer is a photo editing tool / photo series. It lets you resize hundreds of photos in few minutes quickly and easily. Increasingly, sharing photos on the internet is becoming increasingly popular. Image, is represented as JPEG files from digital cameras, taken at high resolution too big to send over the Internet, with some photos ending at 5 mega bytes. Upload photos to a website share photos is good, but 10, 20, or even more, this can last forever, especially on a dial-up...
</description></item><item><title>Download Allavsoft Video Downloader Converter 3.28.7.9473</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 17:06:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allavsoft-video-downloader-converter-248.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allavsoft-video-downloader-converter-248.html
</guid><description>
Allavsoft Video Downloader Converter software supports download movies, music videos, playlist, sport videos from video sharing website for free like Facebook, Youtube and over 100 video sharing sites.
Allavsoft is many users favorite thanks to the combined features simultaneous transmission of multiple videos and speed limit download video. Besides, the program also supports pause and resume data transmission, to help you interfere with the process of transmitting download data to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Antidote 12 v3</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 17:06:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-antidote-8032.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-antidote-8032.html
</guid><description>
Antidote is a multi-resource platform, very useful for anyone writing in English or French. Antidote's debugger flags a wide variety of errors: from capitalization and verb agreement to commas and unwanted redundancies. Once your spelling and grammar are correct, correct typographical and stylistic errors, including repetition of words and boring verbs. Never before has software given you such power to perfect your writing.
The error correction tool analyzes your text and highlights any...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mocha Pro for Adobe 2026.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 17:05:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mocha-pro-1029.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mocha-pro-1029.html
</guid><description>
Mocha Pro 2019 is the tool for visual effects and postproduction. Tool Tracking and VFX and is plugins for Adobe. Mocha is the artist and editor effects appreciate about the unique ability of his to reduce the time using keyframing related to VFX and premium finishing.
Mocha Pro 2019
Mocha Pro 2019 features track and remove objects that are GPU acceleratedtools, rotoscoping, advanced, stable, solved 3D camera, supports stereo 360 / VR, etc. Using Mocha AE CC in Adobe After Effects? See...
</description></item><item><title>Download Aidfile Recovery Software Professional 3.7.9.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 17:04:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aidfile-recovery-software-professional-4316.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aidfile-recovery-software-professional-4316.html
</guid><description>
Aidfile Recovery Software Professional is a software small but powerful will assist you to recover files lost, deleted or damaged. It is ideal to restore data such as videos, files, office, images, folders and many other things. Professional tool this will help you to perform full scan and in-depth hard drive and partition, USB drive, memory card or removable media , to fully restore your data. This software can restore the data file from the file system partition FAT32, NTFS and ExFAT,...
</description></item><item><title>Download MuPDF 1.27.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 17:04:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mupdf-4315.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mupdf-4315.html
</guid><description>
MuPDF is a utility compact, lightweight but effective, allowing you to open and view PDF documents and XPS. This application includes a tool to export advanced matching graphics anti-aliasing quality. The program can output text with the distance and figures correctly high. Although MuPDF is small in size, the app includes many useful features and powerful. The program can format support PDF 1.7 with the hyperlink, transparency, encryption, the ability to search, annotate and much more....
</description></item><item><title>Download Any MP3 Converter 2025 v10.0.3.9</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 17:03:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-mp3-converter-11983.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-mp3-converter-11983.html
</guid><description>
Any MP3 Converter is a user-friendly tool that supports many audio formats, including MP3. It allows you to convert audio files quickly and easily. It supports more than 1000 Video/Audio Formats. 30 times faster speed and no quality loss. Optimized for high quality HD Video and large Video files. Download and convert online videos like YouTube, Vimeo, etc. Trim/Join/Crop/Rotate, Add Text, Effects, Subtitles and more...
Main features of Any MP3 Converter
	MP3 converter allows you to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Hit'n'Mix RipX DeepAudio 8.0.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 17:03:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hitnmix-ripx-deepaudio-9448.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hitnmix-ripx-deepaudio-9448.html
</guid><description>
RipX DeepAudio includes the world's leading audio separation DeepRemix, along with DeepCreate MIDI/MPE, a sound and sample song creation system, and then adds processing tools advanced audio and original cleanup into the workflow, so you can create the highest quality extracted audio, and refine/create sounds with unprecedented levels of detail.
With RipX DeepAudio, users can isolate and extract specific parts of a song, remix tracks, or create entirely new compositions from existing...
</description></item><item><title>Download MusConv 4.10.439 Lifetime</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 17:02:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html
</guid><description>
MusConv transfers playlists, albums, followed artists and liked songs across a variety of services – Spotify, Apple Music, Amazon Music, YouTube, YouTube Music, iTunes, Deezer, Tidal, SoundCloud, Pandora and more 125 music services!
Features of MusConv Ultimate
	Transfer playlists, albums, followed artists and liked tracks between over 125 music servicesManage playlists (Delete, Merge, Split, Copy...)
	More than 125 music services supported
	Access DAILY updated music charts on...
</description></item><item><title>Download Privacy Eraser Free 6.25.0 Build 5456</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 17:02:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-privacy-eraser-free-9160.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-privacy-eraser-free-9160.html
</guid><description>
Privacy Eraser is a software tool that helps protect user privacy by securely erasing or deleting unwanted data from their computer or device. This tool is designed to delete browsing history, cookies, cache, temporary files and other sensitive information that may be stored on the computer.
Privacy Eraser can be used to clear browsing history of popular web browsers such as Google Chrome, Mozilla Firefox and Microsoft Edge. It can also clear the history and cache of other applications,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Jawset PostShot 1.0.116</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 17:02:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jawset-postshot-14329.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jawset-postshot-14329.html
</guid><description>
PostShot is designed and optimized for production. Easily create realistic 3D scenes and objects that look like photographs in minutes with any camera. This tool is geared towards workflows for visual effects, visualization, and 3D content creation, and currently runs on the Windows operating system with local processing mode for data security.
What PostShot does:
PostShot recreates a 3D radiation field from a sequence of input images or videos, allowing you to rotate the scene, change...
</description></item><item><title>Download QuickViewer 1.2.8</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 17:01:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quickviewer-3263.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quickviewer-3263.html
</guid><description>
QuickViewer is a image viewer, graphics to browse from the comfort multiple images. The software performs read image data first. And drawing the image data entered on the screen using OpenGL. You can browse picture with response smoother than ever.
QuickViewer - fast picture viewer
The features of the QuickViewer
To display images very quickly (using OpenGL)
Portable (no installation, registration, library, external)
Tablet ready
See page spread 2 pages (two photos, a times, for books...
</description></item><item><title>Download Kalmuri 4.1.6</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 17:01:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kalmuri-12521.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kalmuri-12521.html
</guid><description>
Kalmuri provides one of the simplest means of recording screen activity, working as both a snapshot utility and a screen recorder. It requires no installation and is ready to go at any time, waiting for your action quietly in the tray area, thus not disturbing your work.
Features of Kalmuri
	Supports video recording (specify entire screen and area)
	Entire screen, active program, window control, application area
	Supports PNG, JPG, BMP, GIF, MP4 file formats
	Supports saving documents...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mocha Pro for OFX 2026.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 16:59:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mocha-pro-for-ofx-4303.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mocha-pro-for-ofx-4303.html
</guid><description>
Mocha Pro for OFX is the tracking tool flat the world's most powerful for VFX and postproduction. With the tracking feature and remove objects that are GPU accelerated, mask advanced with snapshot feature edge, stable, corrective lens, the 3D camera, supports stereo 360 / VR, v. v. Mocha Pro for OFX is a plugin for Adobe Premiere Pro &amp;amp; After Effects, servers Avid Media Composer &amp;amp; OFX as Flame, Nuke, Fusion, HitFilm, and VEGAS Pro.
Mocha Pro for OFX 2020
New features in version...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wing FTP Server Corporate 8.0.9</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 16:58:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wing-ftp-server-corporate-2752.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wing-ftp-server-corporate-2752.html
</guid><description>
Wing FTP Server Corporate is a highly functional, easy and safe can be used in the operating system Windows, Linux, Mac and Solaris are used. The software supports a number of file transfer protocol such as FTP, HTTP, FTPS, HTTPS and SFTP. Wing FTP Server provides web-based interface to manage the server at any time. You can also get performance server and the online and even send email notifications about various events happening on the server.
Management server multi-function
Wing FTP...
</description></item><item><title>Download Syncovery Premium 11.11.7.137</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 16:58:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncovery-pro-enterprise-232.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncovery-pro-enterprise-232.html
</guid><description>
Syncovery Pro Enterprise is a great application used to back up data and to synchronize personal computers, servers, laptops, notepads and storage online. The software comes with support for FTP and secure FTP servers, SSH, WebDAV, Amazon S3, http, update the part file, ZIP compression, data encryption, and schedule automatic backups.
Syncovery Pro Enterprise have the ability to freely select files and folders across the whole folder hierarchy in tree view and supports email...
</description></item><item><title>Download Esri CityEngine 2025.1.11669</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 16:56:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-esri-cityengine-9985.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-esri-cityengine-9985.html
</guid><description>
Esri CityEngine is a powerful 3D urban planning and modeling software developed by Esri, a company known for geographic information systems technology ( GIS). CityEngine is designed to create, visualize, and analyze complex 3D urban environments, from entire cities to individual buildings. It is commonly used by urban planners, architects, game developers, and filmmakers to create realistic and detailed urban landscapes.
Esri CityEngine is widely used in various industries to create...
</description></item></channel></rss>