<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 14:34:33 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 14:34:33 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Defender Remover 13.0.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 10 Feb 2026 14:49:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-defender-remover-9034.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-defender-remover-9034.html
</guid><description>
Defender Remover is a free tool used to remove Windows Defender in Windows 8.x, Windows 10 (any version) and Windows 11. Also, it can also used to remove Windows Security App, Windows Smart-Screen, Windows Web-Threat Service, Microsoft Defender App Guard, Windows Virtualization-Based Security (VBS), Windows File Virtualization (UAC) and Windows Security Services.
Defender Remover has a simple interface and it requires no installation or configuration, so download and launch to get...
</description></item><item><title>Download Trillian 6.6 Build 12</title><pubDate> Tue, 10 Feb 2026 14:46:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-trillian-2638.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-trillian-2638.html
</guid><description>
Trillian is the chat help you sign in to more the registered name of a certain service or you can log on at the same time many services in a working window. It integrates multiple services such as Yahoo! MSN, IRC, AIM and ICQ. In addition, you can manage Email accounts, Facebook and Twitter friends - all in just one application.
Login is easy; just click on the network or the appropriate website and log in as normal. Trillian requires access your data (accepted) and post to friends...
</description></item><item><title>Download CyberLink PowerDirector Ultimate 2026 v24.2.1404.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 10 Feb 2026 14:45:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-powerdirector-ultimate-425.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-powerdirector-ultimate-425.html
</guid><description>
CyberLink PowerDirector Ultimate is software editor, edit video and make movies on the computer from a variety of templates are made available, complete with effects, transitions, animations, and music. CyberLink PowerDirector 17 is a combination of video editing software with advanced video editing features powerful. Cblowing need to add your clips into the time line and click on 'Production'!
The tool design video in CyberLink PowerDirector have the ability to customize helps you...
</description></item><item><title>Download QOwnNotes 26.2.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 10 Feb 2026 14:45:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qownnotes-3178.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qownnotes-3178.html
</guid><description>
QOwnNotes is notes bookmark file simple text (GPL) open source application for GNU / Linux , Mac OS X and Windows of Patrizio Bekerle ( pbek on GitHub and IRC) (optional) activity along with the notes application of ownCloud or Nextcloud. QOwnNote store your notes as plain text files and can be synchronized with synchronization function file of ownCloud / Nextcloud. You can also use other apps like Syncthing or Dropbox . Just write out your thoughts as they appear, and edit them if...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube Downloader 3.9.18 (0902)</title><pubDate> Tue, 10 Feb 2026 14:44:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube Downloader  is a dedicated software that helps users  downloading youtube videos  Favorites on PC for offline viewing. With MediaHuman YouTube  Downloader  you can download videos from youtube website to your computer with  fast speed , with special software development technology that automatically receives videos from Websites, in addition to the ability to download videos from software websites, can convert downloaded video formats to various formats for the purpose...
</description></item><item><title>Download Password Depot 19.0.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 10 Feb 2026 14:43:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-password-depot-1048.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-password-depot-1048.html
</guid><description>
Password Depot is a password manager powerful helps organize all your passwords, credit information or software licenses. Password Depot offers the ability to store your passwords in a secure way, ensuring you use the data safe and help you have secure passwords.
Password Depot does not only guarantee security: It also has the ability to convenient to use, customization ability, high flexibility, markedly when interacting with other devices and, last but not last long, flexibility is...
</description></item><item><title>Download Perfectly Clear WorkBench 5.0.2.3090</title><pubDate> Tue, 10 Feb 2026 14:43:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfectly-clear-workbench-6892.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfectly-clear-workbench-6892.html
</guid><description>
Perfectly Clear Workbench is an application that uses image editing libraries Perfectly Clear by Athentech and is provided to demonstrate the capabilities of the Perfectly Clear processing libraries, which recognize faces and allow quick export of processing settings for use.
One of the key features in Workbench is the ability to "export to API" when saving a Preset. This allows you to make image edits in Workbench and adjust the settings to suit your editing style and needs. You can...
</description></item><item><title>Download RAM Saver Professional 26.2.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 10 Feb 2026 14:42:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ram-saver-pro-565.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ram-saver-pro-565.html
</guid><description>
RAM Saver Pro is a professional software optimize RAM is for system stable operation with high performance. RAM Saver Pro aims to provide all the tools necessary to increase the amount of free memory, at any time, also monitor and check the RAM.
When using RAM Saver Pro, you will be allowed to access its main menu by right-clicking on the tray icon. Also, if you want to display the main panel of the program you just double-click the icon. In addition, from the main interface of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Active Password Changer Ultimate 26.1.4</title><pubDate> Tue, 10 Feb 2026 14:42:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-active-password-changer-ultimate-2827.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-active-password-changer-ultimate-2827.html
</guid><description>
Active Password Changer Ultimate tool is reset Windows password... is designed to reset administrator password and local user on the Windows in case the password is forgotten or lost. Unlock the locked account and change the properties of the account.
Easy to use app allows you to reset your password user account. It does exactly what it says, maybe even a bit more with the additional features of it, but the price tag may be too high for some people. But on this site you will download it...
</description></item><item><title>Download Trellix Stinger (McAfee Stinger) 13.0.0.604</title><pubDate> Tue, 10 Feb 2026 14:41:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mcafee-stinger-202.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mcafee-stinger-202.html
</guid><description>
McAfee Stinger is a free utility that functions to scan, check and remove the hazards and obstacles as virus or malware for Windows, whether they are hiding deep into the system.
In addition, due to the ability to search for the correct folder, or the data at risk contains viruses to scan instead you have to remove a long time waiting for antivirus software to scan all system on your computer. Thus speed of work of the McAfee Stinger faster and somewhat more accurate.
Themselves McAfee...
</description></item><item><title>Download Secure Eraser Pro 7.100</title><pubDate> Tue, 10 Feb 2026 14:41:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secure-eraser-1003.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secure-eraser-1003.html
</guid><description>
Secure Eraser is a software to delete data permanently on the folder of the hard drive to data can not be recovered by any software. Secure Eraser is software delete data completely best. The software has simple interface and very small capacity. In addition, the software Secure Eraser also helps to tidy and clean the system, prevent the fragmentation of the hard drive.
Secure Eraser - Tool To Delete Data Permanently
Secure Eraser supports 4 standard delete data (US DoD 5220,22-ME, US...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter 3.9.18 (0902)</title><pubDate> Tue, 10 Feb 2026 14:41:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-to-mp3-converter-1744.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-to-mp3-converter-1744.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter is the software support download youtube video and convert video to mp3 format fast and most simple. MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter allows you download and convert videos from YouTube and other websites to MP3 format by pasting the YouTube URL into the application. When you paste the URL, the program will display thumbnails for videos and you have the option to customize the title information, artist and album before you begin the process of...
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 7.9.8</title><pubDate> Tue, 10 Feb 2026 14:39:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-11-7760.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-11-7760.html
</guid><description>
TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 is a program that allows users to discover hidden settings in Windows 11. This application is specially designed for Windows 11, groups many registry settings and distribute them from the easy and secure user interface. With TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 you can move the Windows taskbar to the top and resize the taskbar by editing the registry value. With any application that modifies the registry, we recommend that you have a backup copy...
</description></item><item><title>Download Windows Backup &amp;amp; Restore Tool 2.0.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 10 Feb 2026 14:39:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-backup-restore-tool-14513.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-backup-restore-tool-14513.html
</guid><description>
Windows Backup &amp;amp; Restore Tool is a professional backup and restore utility designed for the Windows operating system. It works seamlessly in both standard Windows environments and WinPE (Windows Pre-installed Environment). Although primarily designed for backup and restore operations, it can also be used for fresh Windows installations when needed.
Key Features
	Full System Backup: Creates a complete backup of any drive or partition.
	VSS Support: Uses Volume Shadow Copy Service...
</description></item><item><title>Download Fan Control v257</title><pubDate> Tue, 10 Feb 2026 14:39:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fancontrol-5749.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fancontrol-5749.html
</guid><description>
FanControl is a highly customizable fan control software for Windows. Stay in control of every aspect of your PC's GPU and CPU fan with the help of this highly customizable fan control app.
Features of FanControl
	Save, edit and load multiple configurations
	Multiple temperature sources (CPU, GPU, motherboard, hard drive, ".sensor" files)
	Custom fan curve
	Fine tune fan control response with steps,% start,% stop, response time and delay
	Mix different curves and sensors...
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 7.9.8</title><pubDate> Tue, 10 Feb 2026 14:38:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-10-7759.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-10-7759.html
</guid><description>
TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 is a utility that allows users to discover hidden settings in Windows 10. This application is specially designed for Windows 10, groups many registry settings and provide them from an easy and secure user interface. With TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 you can move the Windows taskbar to the top and resize the taskbar by editing the registry value. With any application that modifies the registry, we recommend that you have a backup copy to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Power-user Premium 1.7.74.302</title><pubDate> Tue, 10 Feb 2026 14:37:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-power-user-premium-3149.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-power-user-premium-3149.html
</guid><description>
Power-user is a plugin for software, Microsoft Excel, PowerPoint and Word help you to provide more visual content so you can create the spreadsheet attractive. It contains templates, icons, tables, drawings and charts, modern, professional, allows you to build professional looking documents. You can add custom content to your project just by a click of the mouse and surprise clients and colleagues with your skills on Excel, PowerPoint and Word.
Power-user Premium - Plugin Excel,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Opera GX (Gaming Browser) 127.0.5778.41</title><pubDate> Tue, 10 Feb 2026 14:37:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-gx-3170.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-gx-3170.html
</guid><description>
Opera GX is a special version of the Opera browser is built to complement gamers avid. Browser this game comes with the unique features to help users make maximum use of both the game and their browser. Opera GX is built specifically to support the game. This browser includes the unique features to help users have the best experience when gaming and surfing the web.
Opera GX - special browser for gamers
GX Control allows you to set a limit on the level of use RAM, CPU and network where...
</description></item><item><title>Download AutoHotkey 2.0.21</title><pubDate> Tue, 10 Feb 2026 14:37:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-autohotkey-44.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-autohotkey-44.html
</guid><description>
AutoHotkey is a utility automation script allows you to automate almost any task on your PC by running applications or documents and / or sending keystrokes and mouse clicks. The program supports several advanced features allows you to create complex with flow control, the command math, variables and expressions, functions, file, message boxes, and more.
You can even create a form to enter data to customize the user interface and menu bar. AutoHotkey can learning curve initially and...
</description></item><item><title>Download ExtraMAME 26.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 10 Feb 2026 14:36:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-extramame-2608.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-extramame-2608.html
</guid><description>
ExtraMAME is a simple tool that allows simulation of the arcade game from the most popular platform but is long forgotten, thanks to which the game industry has reached the current level. After launch, you will get 11 games pre-installed, among which are: Super Mario Bros, Pac-Man Plus, Space Invaders II and other games.
The simulation of multiple machine arcade is authored by Nicola Salmoria and team MAME. MAME lets you play thousands of arcade game old school on your computer. ExtraMAME...
</description></item><item><title>Download Telegram for Desktop 6.5.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 10 Feb 2026 14:36:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-telegram-3376.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-telegram-3376.html
</guid><description>
Telegram is an instant messaging service and voice over IP services on the cloud platform. Client application Telegram is available for Android, iOS, Windows Phone, Windows NT, macOS, and Linux. Users can send messages and exchange photos, videos, stickers, audio and files of any kind.
Telegram - Messaging and free phone calls
Telegram seamless sync across all your devices and can be used on desktop, tablet and phone. You can send unlimited amount of messages, photos, videos and files...
</description></item><item><title>Download SimpleSoft Simple Invoice 3.25.2.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 10 Feb 2026 14:35:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-simplesoft-simple-invoice-3622.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-simplesoft-simple-invoice-3622.html
</guid><description>
SimpleSoft Simple Invoice is a useful tool for home sales. SimpleSoft Simple Invoice will help you quickly create the bill payment product to send bills to customers, from your phone or laptop by you. Save time, keep tidy and look professional!
SimpleSoft Simple Invoice - Create invoice products
Just select an invoice template and customize it with your logo. Add a signature, images, notes and much more. Always look professional and always tidy. Quickly create invoices and estimates...
</description></item><item><title>Download Power-user for PowerPoint and Excel 1.7.74.302</title><pubDate> Tue, 10 Feb 2026 14:35:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-power-user-for-powerpoint-and-excel-522.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-power-user-for-powerpoint-and-excel-522.html
</guid><description>
Power-user for PowerPoint and Excel is a utility providing you with a library of templates, icons, charts, maps and diagrams for spreadsheet and presentation. With Power-user for PowerPoint and Excel, you will attract the attention of your audience with stunning graphics will certainly impress.
Power-user comes with a collection of 2,000 icons to illustrate your slides. The icons are vector shapes so you can resize them without distortion and color back as you with. With Power-user, you...
</description></item><item><title>Download SSD Booster .NET 19.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 10 Feb 2026 14:34:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ssd-booster-net-7375.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ssd-booster-net-7375.html
</guid><description>
SSD Booster .NET is our perfect tool to optimize and adjust Windows for the SSD drive to increase performance and maintain the highest performance for your SSD. In addition, the app comes with the system information tab for information about the hardware and operating system of your machine. To check your specifications, move to the Introduction and find the System Information button.
Features of SSD Booster .NET
	The perfect tool to optimize and adjust Windows for the SSD drive to...
</description></item><item><title>Download MailWasher Pro 8.0.98</title><pubDate> Tue, 10 Feb 2026 14:33:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-firetrust-mailwasher-pro-825.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-firetrust-mailwasher-pro-825.html
</guid><description>
MailWasher Pro software is ready to filter all of your email accounts and blocked, remove the spam from the list of email. MailWasher allows you to preview all your email before to your computer or your mobile device, you allows you to read all your email securely, and instantly delete any unwanted emails or suspicious. Email good rest of you is download at PC or mobile devices, to help you not get any virus, spam or any email.
Firetrust MailWasher Pro - Blocker remove spam
The...
</description></item></channel></rss>