<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 21:34:17 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 21:34:17 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Google Drive (Backup and Sync) 113.0.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 27 Aug 2025 23:57:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-drive-6751.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-drive-6751.html
</guid><description>
Using Google Drive is a great way to store your files safely in secure data centers, where your files will not be lost. Even if your computer, phone or tablet is broken, the files you store in the Google Drive are safe. Download photos, videos, documents, and other files that are important to you up to Google Drive. Continue with the memory up to 15GB. Free. Google Drive helps you access your file faster by recognizing the objects in your image and text in the scanned documents.
Easy to...
</description></item><item><title>Download MikroTik Winbox 3.42</title><pubDate> Wed, 27 Aug 2025 23:55:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mikrotik-winbox-8411.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mikrotik-winbox-8411.html
</guid><description>
MikroTik Winbox is a software program that allows users to configure and manage MikroTik routers and wireless devices. It's a graphical user interface (GUI) that provides a simple and intuitive way to access and configure router settings and features.
This software allows users to monitor network performance, view traffic statistics, set up hotspots, configure wireless access points, create firewall rules, and more. In addition, the software allows users to access and manage the router...
</description></item><item><title>Download Intel Graphics Driver for Windows 10 / 11 32.0.101.7028</title><pubDate> Wed, 27 Aug 2025 23:52:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intel-graphics-driver-for-windows-10-5954.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intel-graphics-driver-for-windows-10-5954.html
</guid><description>
Intel Graphics Driver for Windows 10 supports Intel ' s latest 8th-generation Core processor, introducing the Intel ® UHD graphics, with the ability to immerve in the top 4K UHD entertainment from your laptop for a maximum of 10 hours. Along with some security fixes, this driver also optimised the system's inactivity to reduce power consumption.
Look at the complete new interface of gameplay.intel.com, where you will find the proposed game settings for many of your favorite PC games....
</description></item><item><title>Download Mozilla Firefox 142.0.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 27 Aug 2025 23:52:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-firefox-quantum-501.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-firefox-quantum-501.html
</guid><description>
Firefox Quantum is a web browser independently provide the tabbed browsing combined with numerous handy features like pop-up blocker, Bookmarks, direct (integrated RSS), password manager, and more. Functionality can be extended with dozens of plugins available for free (extensions).
Firefox Quantum are interface completely new, beautiful, neat, minimalistic and delicate, eats less RAM to 30% compared with the old version and solve the condition consuming capacity
Firefox can import all...
</description></item><item><title>Download InternetTest Pro 9.0.0.2508</title><pubDate> Wed, 27 Aug 2025 23:50:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-internettest-6718.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-internettest-6718.html
</guid><description>
InternetTest is a small multipurpose tool to check internet connection status and more, you can easily verify if a particular website is down or not. no and navigate to it via the Down Detector function. You can also check the IP location in the app via OpenStreetMap, Bing Maps or Google Maps. It will also give you the connection history displayed on the right side of the simple interface.
Features of InternetTest
	Check your Internet connection
	IP Localization
	Down Detector
	Dark...
</description></item><item><title>Download Topaz Video AI Pro 7.1.4</title><pubDate> Wed, 27 Aug 2025 23:49:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-video-enhance-ai-3733.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-video-enhance-ai-3733.html
</guid><description>
Topaz Video Enhance AI is a tool to increase video quality with this great technology ONE. Topaz Video Enhance WHO wide open your video to resolutions up to 8K with the details and consistency of motion. Until the present, there is no way to re-create a perfect high resolution video from the footage is low resolution. From the family film to SD low quality to DVD quality and more than that, Video Enhance WHO will convert your video into the footage is upgrade clear with resolutions up to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Acrobat Pro DC 2025.001.20643 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Wed, 27 Aug 2025 23:48:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-001en-adobe-acrobat-pro-458.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-001en-adobe-acrobat-pro-458.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Acrobat Pro DC is a comprehensive software that helps you create and edit the PDF&amp;nbsp;document, or create form, sign, protect PDF, connect, split PDF, export PDF to various formats. The Acrobat Pro DC is the latest version of Adobe with improvements in the interface with the polished ribbon bar and the ability to create and handle pdf files as well as its male versions.
The highlight of the Acrobat Pro DC is probably the ability to connect, store documents on the cloud, you can...
</description></item><item><title>Download HE - Hardware Read and Write Utility 1.25.08.27</title><pubDate> Wed, 27 Aug 2025 23:47:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-he-hardware-read-and-write-utility-4287.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-he-hardware-read-and-write-utility-4287.html
</guid><description>
HE - Hardware Read and Write Utility is a powerful utility intended for hardware engineer, engineer, BIOS developer, driver, engineer, QA engineers, performance test engineers, diagnostic, etc., this utility access almost all the computer hardware, including PCI (PCI Express), index / Data, PCI, memory, index memory / Data space I / O, Index I / O / Data, Super I / O, DIMM SPD, CPU The registers MSR, screen, SMART, physical area of the hard drive identification data, ATA, dump tables ACPI...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare Repairit 6.5.14.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 27 Aug 2025 23:47:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-recoverit-video-repair-3889.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-recoverit-video-repair-3889.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare Recoverit Video Repair is a reliable application that helps you fix the broken video, Wondershare Recoverit Video Repair supports file formats MP4, MOV, M4V, M2TS, MKV, MTS, 3GP, AVI and FLV is corrupt and broken. Great service we provide. It fixes the video that there is corruption in the process of shooting, when done, file transfer, while editing, convert.
Wondershare Recoverit Video Repair - video repair broken
Features of Wondershare Recoverit Video Repair
	Repair...
</description></item><item><title>Download NxFilter 4.7.3.4</title><pubDate> Wed, 27 Aug 2025 23:47:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nxfilter-50.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nxfilter-50.html
</guid><description>
NxFilter is a server filter DNS have the ability to filter Internet traffic based on domain names and content types. In addition, it can use check package DNS to protect your network from malware and botnet activity.
NxFilter is installed on a single computer, where it acts as a proxy server, DNS. To route Internet traffic through NxFilter, you will need to change the DNS settings on all the machines that you want to protect to use the IP address of the individual NxFilter (instead of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Bandicam 8.2.1.2529</title><pubDate> Wed, 27 Aug 2025 23:45:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bandicam-243.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bandicam-243.html
</guid><description>
Bandicam is the software screen recording powerful, helps users to record all activities happening on the computer such as video games, presentations,..
Software Bandicam uses graphics technology DirectX / OpenGL will help you carry out a video record with high compression ratio, while keeping the video quality closer to the original work and provide superior performance compared with other programs providing the same functionality.
Bandicam can create video with quality high but...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare Recoverit 13.6.1.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 27 Aug 2025 23:44:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-recoverits-374.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-recoverits-374.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare Recoverit is a data recovery software that is easily lost at a rapid rate and is used by many people. You will do what happens if one day your data is suddenly lost due to the virus or deleted it, .. Wondershare Recoverit will provide you with an environment to protect important data.
Wondershare Recoverit has all the scanning processes that are divided into multiple types, from the typical recovery of the deleted files that are deleted to the recovery of missing files due...
</description></item><item><title>Download DroidKit 2.3.7.20250827</title><pubDate> Wed, 27 Aug 2025 23:43:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-droidkit-6578.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-droidkit-6578.html
</guid><description>
DroidKit is data recovery software for your mobile device, it will quickly scan your phone memory and save photos, WhatsApp chats and files, messages Messages, contacts and more essential data up to 13 categories, covering almost everything you need every day. All Android phones and tablets are supported. Without rooting your device. No tech skills required. No need to wait many days. You can get back what you've lost with just a few simple clicks, instantly.
Besides, DroidKit also has...
</description></item><item><title>Download Systweak PDF Editor 1.0.0.8080</title><pubDate> Wed, 27 Aug 2025 23:36:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-systweak-pdf-editor-11484.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-systweak-pdf-editor-11484.html
</guid><description>
Systweak PDF Editor is a fast and simple solution to edit, convert, sign, protect, compress PDF files and make scanned PDF files searchable and can choose. With Systweak PDF Editor, quickly convert your PDF files into a variety of editable formats. Converting PDF files to and from any MS Office files, images, ebooks, web pages, and other formats just got easier.
For working and editing PDF files, Systweak PDF editor offers many features and tools. Using them, you can mark text for...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinMerge 2.16.50.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 27 Aug 2025 23:35:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winmerge-2028.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winmerge-2028.html
</guid><description>
WinMerge is a tool to merge and distinguish open source for Windows. WinMerge can compare and folders and files, presenting differences in a visual text easy to understand or manipulate. WinMerge is very useful for determining what has changed between the version of the project and merge the changes between the versions. WinMerge can be used as a tool to compare / merge, external or as a standalone application.
In addition, Winmerge has many helpful features helps to compare, synchronize...
</description></item><item><title>Download Coolmuster Android Assistant 6.0.76</title><pubDate> Wed, 27 Aug 2025 23:34:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-android-assistant-226.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-android-assistant-226.html
</guid><description>
Coolmuster Android Assistant is a lightweight application that allows you to export the data important from your mobile device to your computer for safekeeping just in few clicks.
Coolmuster Android Assistant allows you to browse a number of types of data on your mobile device, you, namely the apps, contacts, SMS, music, photos, videos , and books. In case you can't preview the contents of the desired part, then you can fix this minor inconvenience by access to the child folder of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Explzh 9.83</title><pubDate> Wed, 27 Aug 2025 23:33:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-explzh-2278.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-explzh-2278.html
</guid><description>
Explzh is software that originated from Japan. This program works with most formats, can extract the file directly to FTP server, split large files into multiple smaller size. I would like to note that the storage supports encryption of files compressed using AES algorithm, has a system of tabs in the main window, you can search for the information you need in the repository and work with files, batch mode is done.
Explzh - Compress and decompress file
The file is support work with the...
</description></item><item><title>Download All About PDF Advanced Edition 3.2034</title><pubDate> Wed, 27 Aug 2025 20:41:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-all-about-pdf-advanced-edition-14110.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-all-about-pdf-advanced-edition-14110.html
</guid><description>
All About PDF is a fast, beautifully designed, intuitive and portable PDF utility that you can use to merge, split, protect, compress, convert PDF files and more. We always strive to simplify pricing and deliver great value. Merge PDF, split PDF, convert PDF, protect PDF and more.
Features of All About PDF Advanced
Focus on privacy: As a desktop application, you don't need to upload your private PDF files to an unknown third-party remote server for processing. We also do not collect or...
</description></item><item><title>Download pdfFactory Pro 9.15</title><pubDate> Wed, 27 Aug 2025 18:07:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdffactory-pro-277.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdffactory-pro-277.html
</guid><description>
pdfFactory Pro is software to create PDF files according to standards in a simple and secure documents secure. pdfFactory Pro on taiwebs.com that support encryption (40 or 128bit) and control access to the PDF file.
pdfFactory Pro has all the features of pdfFactory and adds bookmarks, job order, title a letter and the email function automatically. Only pdfFactory allows printing to paper or PDF without printing twice. Acrobat is not needed for the printing. Increases the convenience of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare Filmora 14.9.3.14445</title><pubDate> Wed, 27 Aug 2025 18:07:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-filmora-2025-31.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-filmora-2025-31.html
</guid><description>
In early November 2020 Wondershare came up with a new version called Wondershare Filmora 13 with two new ways to edit: Action Cam Tool (Lens distortion correction, Clean up your audio, Control speed new) and Instant Cutter (Cut or merge clips quickly, Export instantly).
Wondershare Filmora 13  allows you to add your favorite tracks to your videos, creating a more stylish, romantic film reel, with a rich music library besides Users can manually add their favorite songs to the editing...
</description></item><item><title>Download IObit Uninstaller Pro 15.0.0.5</title><pubDate> Wed, 27 Aug 2025 18:06:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iobit-uninstaller-pro-339.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iobit-uninstaller-pro-339.html
</guid><description>
IObit Uninstaller Pro is software to delete programs not needed easily even when Windows "Remove Programs" operation not successful. IObit Uninstaller Pro will uninstall the app Windows, browser toolbars, software packages and plug-ins added. It comes with a scan function is powerful and a tool, Force Uninstall, both of which help to easily and completely remove the app stubborn, and the excess useless, to release more disk space.
With IObit Uninstaller Pro you will have peace of mind...
</description></item><item><title>Download Red Eye Pilot 3.14.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 27 Aug 2025 18:05:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-red-eye-pilot-6308.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-red-eye-pilot-6308.html
</guid><description>
Red Eye Pilot is this red eye removal program that allows you to adjust the field and brightness, and watch the results in real time. The program holds the structure of the students. With an automated mode of editing, which needs to adjust the brightness and contrast, you can adjust these parameters, you can use the editor with a tuning size to clear the editing effects, flip or rotate images at different angles, such as changing size or cutting files.
Red Eye Pilot can be used as a...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft Office 2021-2024 Professional Plus VL (64-bit) 2508 Build 19127.20154</title><pubDate> Wed, 27 Aug 2025 18:05:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-office-2021-6670.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-office-2021-6670.html
</guid><description>
Since the end of February 2021, Microsoft has announced two new versions of Office 2021 including: Office 2021 and Office LTSC. Reportedly, Office 2021 is the next version of Office 2019, promising to bring users a better experience in the new Word, Excel or PowerPoint tools.
With each office user, the Microsoft Office toolkit is essential and indispensable software in the job. Microsoft Office has undergone numerous editions from Office 2010, 2013, 2016, 2019 to Microsoft 365 developed...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Downloader 9.16.5</title><pubDate> Wed, 27 Aug 2025 18:04:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html
</guid><description>
YTD Youtube Downloader is an application that reliable and intuitive, allowing you to quickly download YouTube videos and save them to your computer. You can also convert the media files to the format desired video or extract audio streams and save separately. YTD Youtube Downloader lets you save your favorite clips of yourself from Youtube, Facebook, Vimeo and Dailymotion to your desktop. The software supports URLS from many web site hosting, multimedia and allows you to download desired...
</description></item><item><title>Download FinePrint 12.15</title><pubDate> Wed, 27 Aug 2025 18:04:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fineprint-276.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fineprint-276.html
</guid><description>
FinePrint is a software support you work in text saves paper and increases the lifespan of your printer. FinePrint is a software connected printer, you can print 4 or 8 pages file on the computer on a page of paper that still ensure the font is clear, easy to read.
With FinePrint works for you, the incidents of printing annoyances will disappear. Below are just some examples of incidents in which FinePrint can fix. Read more part of our Business for the benefit of the FinePrint in the...
</description></item></channel></rss>