<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 15:44:41 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 15:44:41 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Wondershare PDFelement Pro 12.1.4.3916</title><pubDate> Thu, 25 Dec 2025 16:11:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-pdfelement-pro-105.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-pdfelement-pro-105.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare PDFelement Pro support users to convert PDF to office documents for easier use, modify in every situation. Is one of the software conversion material is rated best today, integrated with many features. We recommend that you should use experience software many useful features this.
Wondershare PDFelement Pro - conversion Fie PDF more features, multi-language
Wondershare PDFelement Pro what?
Convert PDF into Word, Excel, PowerPoint...
• Convert PDF and protected PDF into...
</description></item><item><title>Download Topaz Photo Pro 1.1.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 25 Dec 2025 16:10:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-photo-ai-8105.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-photo-ai-8105.html
</guid><description>
What is Topaz Photo AI?
Topaz Photo AI is a professional software that automatically adjusts for your image quality needs. Simply import images into Topaz Photo AI and it will use specially trained AI models to first detect unique details, clarity, and resolution issues before applying the intelligently adjusts to maximize your image quality.
For users experienced with Topaz Labs image quality applications, it combines the functionality of DeNoise AI, Sharpen AI and Gigapixel AI into...
</description></item><item><title>Download iWatermark Pro 2 v4.0.34</title><pubDate> Thu, 25 Dec 2025 16:09:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iwatermark-pro-1908.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iwatermark-pro-1908.html
</guid><description>
iWatermark Pro is great tool to stamp copyright image, create own mark on the digital image to protect the image copyright. iWatermark Pro works as a digital app independently of the browser other photos, such as Lightroom, Picasa and ACDSee. iWatermark Pro is designed to save time photographers, it support stamped a series of images at a time to save your work.
iWatermark Pro - stamped images copyright
The features of iWatermark Pro
	Stamped copyright the entire images folder at the...
</description></item><item><title>Download ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro 15.25.1223</title><pubDate> Thu, 25 Dec 2025 16:08:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-videotube-downloader-pro-1276.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-videotube-downloader-pro-1276.html
</guid><description>
ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro is the professional version support download videos and playlists from YouTube, videos from Dailymotion, BBC iPlayer, ITV Player, ABC,  FOX,CBS.com Vimeo, Prosieben, Metacafe, Blip.tv CBC.ca many more video sites. After the video is downloaded, you can convert them to the formats compatible with iPad, iPhone, iPod, MPEG-4, H. 264, MP3, AC3.
ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro - Download videos on Youtube
This is one of the software download the most...
</description></item><item><title>Download Marvelous Designer Enterprise 2025.2.143</title><pubDate> Thu, 25 Dec 2025 16:08:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-marvelous-designer-1339.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-marvelous-designer-1339.html
</guid><description>
Marvelous Designer is one of the program best designed to help the 3D design and fashion design. A simulation system revolutionary use of physics. Now, you can create the correct clothes only using Marvelous Designer without help of the other CAD app. Marvelous Designer supports polylines, draw the curved lines connected for free. Any amendments and / or modifications will be displayed immediately on the model clothing 3D in real time.
Marvelous Designer - fashion design
The main...
</description></item><item><title>Download LostMyPassword 1.02</title><pubDate> Thu, 25 Dec 2025 16:07:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lostmypassword-14028.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lostmypassword-14028.html
</guid><description>
LostMyPassword is a tool for Windows that allows you to recover a lost password if it was stored by a software installed on your system. LostMyPassword can extract passwords from popular programs, including web browsers (Chrome, Firefox, Microsoft Edge, Brave, Internet Explorer, Opera, etc.), POP3/IMAP/SMTP passwords stored by email software (Microsoft Outlook, Thunderbird, Windows Mail), Dialup/VPN passwords stored by Windows operating system, remote computer login passwords stored by...
</description></item><item><title>Download 7+ Taskbar Tweaker 5.15.4 / 5.15.3.1 Beta</title><pubDate> Thu, 25 Dec 2025 16:07:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-7-taskbar-tweaker-1863.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-7-taskbar-tweaker-1863.html
</guid><description>
7+ Taskbar Tweaker is a software utility that helps Taskbar on Windows 7 and Windows 8 develop more features, allows users Taskbar more flexible. 7+ Taskbar Tweaker will help the user to completely hide the Start button, watch the hour of the clock displayed on the Taskbar, delete the gaps between the icons. 7+ Taskbar Tweaker allows to automatically hide the Taskbar on Windows to maximize screen space or hide menu Start Menu or Start Screen, turn off the sound on the system or adjust the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Total Uninstall Professional 7.6.2.367</title><pubDate> Thu, 25 Dec 2025 16:06:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-total-uninstall-professional-727.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-total-uninstall-professional-727.html
</guid><description>
Total Uninstall Professional  is an advanced software installation and removal aid that accurately analyzes existing installations. Total Uninstall creates a snapshot of your system before installing a new program. It will then take a snapshot once the installation is complete. It then compares the two snapshots and shows all changes in the graphical tree view, highlighting all registry values ​​and / or files added, changed, or deleted. Total Uninstall saves the changes and, if you...
</description></item><item><title>Download FastKeys Pro 6.05</title><pubDate> Thu, 25 Dec 2025 16:06:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fastkeys-219.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fastkeys-219.html
</guid><description>
FastKeys is a compact tool used to create the shortcut, assign a shortcut key to specify the string stands for the text often use and manage mouse gestures. Users can specify the mouse manipulation to increase the performance of the work or simply replace a string or use an acronym.
FastKeys trigger to allow for expansion of abbreviations for texts used frequently in any application and save time typing. Enter a few letters and automates the task of repeating in a professional manner....
</description></item><item><title>Download Avid Media Composer 25.12 Dongle BackUp</title><pubDate> Thu, 25 Dec 2025 16:05:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avid-media-composer-5432.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avid-media-composer-5432.html
</guid><description>
Avid Media Composer is the industry's most proven video editing software, trusted by professional editors in every segment of filmmaking, television, broadcast and online streaming. Designed for handling large volumes of various file-based media, Media Composer provides accelerated HD and high-resolution workflow, real-time collaboration, and powerful media management, Eliminate time-consuming tasks so you can concentrate on telling a great story.
Media Composer 2020 is packed with a lot...
</description></item><item><title>Download Full Discography 1.8.7</title><pubDate> Thu, 25 Dec 2025 16:04:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-full-discography-7509.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-full-discography-7509.html
</guid><description>
Full Discography is a program to discover all the releases of your favorite artists! Listen to every song your favorite artist ever made! Get to know all Albums &amp;amp; Single click by artist.
Features of Full Discography
	Discover all the releases by your favorite artists!
	Listen to every song your favorite artist ever made!
	Recognize All Albums &amp;amp; Single click by artist.
	Discover all the missing releases from your music collection.
	Get notified when your favorite artist...
</description></item><item><title>Download Gilisoft Total Repair 11.5.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 25 Dec 2025 16:04:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-total-repair-12836.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-total-repair-12836.html
</guid><description>
Total Repair Toolkit is an all-in-one system maintenance tool that integrates smart diagnosis, in-depth repair, and performance optimization. It has a one-click smart repair engine that can automatically resolve over 500 common problems such as system lag, game crashes, and file corruption. Meanwhile, it provides a professional manual repair module to meet advanced requirements.
Gilisoft Total Repair Features
	Application error repair based on a large DLL library
	In-depth diagnosis...
</description></item><item><title>Download Smart File Renamer 1.6.8</title><pubDate> Thu, 25 Dec 2025 16:04:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-smart-file-renamer-7510.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-smart-file-renamer-7510.html
</guid><description>
Smart File Renamer is software to rename multiple files easily! It supports hundreds of renaming scenarios and is loved by happy users aged 14 to 80. Rename 1000 files in less than a second!
Features of Smart File Renamer
	Quickly rename 1000 files in less than a second!
	Rename multiple files in one click!
	Rename photos by country, date, or EXIF ​​tag!
	Rename audio files by music tags easily!
	Rename preselected file categories with one click.
	Support Dark and Light...
</description></item><item><title>Download CLO Standalone OnlineAuth 2025.2.236</title><pubDate> Thu, 25 Dec 2025 16:03:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-clo-standalone-2806.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-clo-standalone-2806.html
</guid><description>
CLO Standalone is a powerful software to design 3D clothes and outfits. Nowadays, computer plays a prominent role in the industry and the different industries use a variety of techniques and computer techniques to increase the quality and quantity of their products. In the garment industry, it is important to design new templates for clothing to meet the needs of customers and diversify. Aware of this demand, programmers and software companies have launched many products to help the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Aseprite 1.3.16.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 25 Dec 2025 16:03:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aseprite-6901.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aseprite-6901.html
</guid><description>
Aseprite is a pixel art tool that allows you to create 2D animations for video games using a variety of tools. Animations and visual effects are used to enhance nearly any form of multimedia, including video games. They are created by combining many images and effects, with countless applications at your disposal.
Aseprite supports files and smart drawing tools, resulting in an enhanced image or short animation for use in your project. In addition, you can completely change or enhance...
</description></item><item><title>Download Large Files Finder 2.0.5</title><pubDate> Thu, 25 Dec 2025 16:02:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-large-files-finder-7511.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-large-files-finder-7511.html
</guid><description>
Large Files Finder is a program that instantly finds and deletes large files that occupy your hard drive. Removes the 5 largest files and saves 30% disk space. Multiple graphs for better representation of large files.
Features of Large Files Finder
	Instantly find and delete large files taking up your hard drive.
	Simple intuitive, easy to use.
	Discover all the missing releases from your music collection.
	Easily filter large files by Type, Extension, Date or Size.
	Multiple charts...
</description></item><item><title>Download C64 Forever Plus Edition 11.2.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 25 Dec 2025 16:02:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-c64-forever-plus-edition-2307.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-c64-forever-plus-edition-2307.html
</guid><description>
C64 Forever is the program is an emulator of Commodore strong, even comes with a set of rich game. Of course, video games have come a long way and so can you and you need more than a lifetime to undergo computer toys alone, not to mention game machines. If you, like me, are nostalgic and want to undergo these difficulties, neurological examination, patience and everything else, you need the emulator for this.
C64 Forever Plus Edition - The emulator game
External application suitable...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tray Weather 1.37.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 25 Dec 2025 16:01:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tray-weather-7091.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tray-weather-7091.html
</guid><description>
Tray Weather is a simple application to retrieve and display weather information for a given geographical location in a small dialog box and in the Windows OS system tray. Weather and map information is obtained from OpenWeatherMap. To get weather information from OpenWeatherMap you need to register on their website and enter the given API Key in Tray Weather configuration dialog.
when executed, the application will reside in the system tray, showing the current weather icon. Tooltip...
</description></item><item><title>Download Xreveal 2.8.9</title><pubDate> Thu, 25 Dec 2025 16:01:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xreveal-7252.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xreveal-7252.html
</guid><description>
Xreveal is an application similar to AnyDVD. This is an interactive research and purpose project. Xreveal does NOT contain any decryption key, it is based solely on the official public AACS specification. You need the decryption key or key database to make it work.
Features of Xreveal
	Remove Blu-ray AACS 1.0 protection
	Remove Blu-ray AACS 2.0 (UHD) protection
	Remove BD+ protection
	Remove BDAV Protection
	Remove DVD CSS protection
	Remove CPRM Protection
	Remove CPPM...
</description></item><item><title>Download dBpoweramp Music Converter Reference 2025.12.24</title><pubDate> Thu, 25 Dec 2025 16:01:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbpoweramp-music-converter-4222.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbpoweramp-music-converter-4222.html
</guid><description>
dBpoweramp Music Converter audio converter is perfect, easy to convert to mp3, FLAC, Apple lossless and more. dBpoweramp Music Converter has become the standard tool for audio conversion, more than 30 million users world trust their switch to dBpoweramp. dBpoweramp Music Converter integrates into Windows Explorer, an mp3 converter as simple as right-click on source files; convert into. Tip information Popup, edit tags ID are provided.
dBpoweramp Music Converter - audio converter...
</description></item><item><title>Download MusConv 4.10.444 Lifetime</title><pubDate> Thu, 25 Dec 2025 16:00:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html
</guid><description>
MusConv transfers playlists, albums, followed artists and liked songs across a variety of services – Spotify, Apple Music, Amazon Music, YouTube, YouTube Music, iTunes, Deezer, Tidal, SoundCloud, Pandora and more 125 music services!
Features of MusConv Ultimate
	Transfer playlists, albums, followed artists and liked tracks between over 125 music servicesManage playlists (Delete, Merge, Split, Copy...)
	More than 125 music services supported
	Access DAILY updated music charts on...
</description></item><item><title>Download KeyNote NF 2.1.4.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 25 Dec 2025 16:00:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-keynote-nf-11953.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-keynote-nf-11953.html
</guid><description>
KeyNote NF is a tabbed notebook with a RichText editor, multi-level note taking, and powerful encryption. KeyNote NF was written to overcome significant limitations in other popular information managers, both freeware and shareware. KeyNote is the only information manager that offers a combination of simple notes and tree notes, a rich text editor, the ability to freely combine multiple notes of different types in one file unique and securely encrypted.
Main features:
Unicode...
</description></item><item><title>Download Power-user Premium 1.7.70.245</title><pubDate> Thu, 25 Dec 2025 15:59:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-power-user-premium-3149.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-power-user-premium-3149.html
</guid><description>
Power-user is a plugin for software, Microsoft Excel, PowerPoint and Word help you to provide more visual content so you can create the spreadsheet attractive. It contains templates, icons, tables, drawings and charts, modern, professional, allows you to build professional looking documents. You can add custom content to your project just by a click of the mouse and surprise clients and colleagues with your skills on Excel, PowerPoint and Word.
Power-user Premium - Plugin Excel,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Power-user for PowerPoint and Excel 1.7.70.245</title><pubDate> Thu, 25 Dec 2025 15:59:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-power-user-for-powerpoint-and-excel-522.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-power-user-for-powerpoint-and-excel-522.html
</guid><description>
Power-user for PowerPoint and Excel is a utility providing you with a library of templates, icons, charts, maps and diagrams for spreadsheet and presentation. With Power-user for PowerPoint and Excel, you will attract the attention of your audience with stunning graphics will certainly impress.
Power-user comes with a collection of 2,000 icons to illustrate your slides. The icons are vector shapes so you can resize them without distortion and color back as you with. With Power-user, you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Qiplex Easy File Organizer 3.4.8</title><pubDate> Thu, 25 Dec 2025 15:58:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qiplex-easy-file-organizer-4780.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qiplex-easy-file-organizer-4780.html
</guid><description>
Qiplex Easy File Organizer is software that helps you arrange the files, folders and desktop easily! Computer to your desk can quickly become a crowded space even when not realized. Needless to say that the start cleaning your files becomes tedious, unless you rely on some dedicated application. In this regard, Qiplex Easy File Organizer to help you filter the files from any location by multiple options smart different.
The features of Qiplex Easy File Organizer
Quickly
Held 1000...
</description></item></channel></rss>