<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 17:37:25 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 17:37:25 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Alfa eBooks Manager Pro / Web 9.4.5.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 17:23:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-alfa-ebooks-manager-web-981.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-alfa-ebooks-manager-web-981.html
</guid><description>
Alfa eBooks Manager Web is a program that enables to arrange the electronic books and paper of you in a single electronic library. eBooks Manager Website will host the electronic books and print in an electronic library. Group, filter and sort books by multiple parameters. Find any book in just a second by title, author or ISBN.
Alfa eBooks Manager Web - ebook library
Alfa eBooks Manager Web provides comprehensive set of fields, including the author, category, publisher, series, ISBN,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Perfectly Clear WorkBench 4.8.0.2871</title><pubDate> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 17:22:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfectly-clear-workbench-6892.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfectly-clear-workbench-6892.html
</guid><description>
Perfectly Clear Workbench is an application that uses image editing libraries Perfectly Clear by Athentech and is provided to demonstrate the capabilities of the Perfectly Clear processing libraries, which recognize faces and allow quick export of processing settings for use.
One of the key features in Workbench is the ability to "export to API" when saving a Preset. This allows you to make image edits in Workbench and adjust the settings to suit your editing style and needs. You can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Any Video Downloader Pro 9.6.5</title><pubDate> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 17:22:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-video-downloader-pro-3731.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-video-downloader-pro-3731.html
</guid><description>
Any Video Downloader Pro is software support you can download video HD 720p, 1080p, 2K, 4K and 8K from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion, Vimeo, Metacafe and thousands of video sharing sites, other. It is a tool to speed up multi-threading can speed up your download faster up to 5 times. This helpful program support download at the same time. Any Video Downloader Pro lets you download multiple videos at the same time. Moreover, it allows you to pause and resume downloads if you need more...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare Repairit 6.5.16.10</title><pubDate> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 17:21:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-recoverit-video-repair-3889.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-recoverit-video-repair-3889.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare Recoverit Video Repair is a reliable application that helps you fix the broken video, Wondershare Recoverit Video Repair supports file formats MP4, MOV, M4V, M2TS, MKV, MTS, 3GP, AVI and FLV is corrupt and broken. Great service we provide. It fixes the video that there is corruption in the process of shooting, when done, file transfer, while editing, convert.
Wondershare Recoverit Video Repair - video repair broken
Features of Wondershare Recoverit Video Repair
	Repair...
</description></item><item><title>Download UniFab 3.0.3.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 17:21:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-unifab-10377.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-unifab-10377.html
</guid><description>
UniFab is software to efficiently convert, compress and edit more than 1000 video formats for playback on any device without losing quality. Enlarge video/audio to 1080p/DTS 7.1 and upgrade video to HDR10 or Dolby Vision with AI Enhancer. UniFab Pro provides the best AI-powered zoom tool that allows you to enlarge videos from low resolutions, such as 360p, 480p and 720p, to 1080p without losing any quality. Clearer and sharper image details will bring you an exceptional viewing...
</description></item><item><title>Download Astute Graphics Plug-ins Elite Bundle 4.3.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 17:19:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-astute-graphics-plug-ins-elite-bundle-5523.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-astute-graphics-plug-ins-elite-bundle-5523.html
</guid><description>
Astute Graphics Plug-ins Elite Bundle is a set of graphics editing tools for Adobe Illustrator. It includes many unique tools like Phantasm, VectorScribe, WidthScribe and many others. Get the complete set of plug-ins and transform your workflow in Illustrator. Add speed, ease, and precision with all our plug-ins and become the Astute Graphics Plug-in Elite Package!
Astute Graphics Plug-ins Elite Bundle Features:
	Correct alignment + selection
	Sketching visual vector
	Instantly...
</description></item><item><title>Download UltraSearch Professional 4.8.4.1184</title><pubDate> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 17:18:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ultrasearch-professional-10252.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ultrasearch-professional-10252.html
</guid><description>
UltraSearch Professional is the professional version that helps you find your files and documents on all connected hard drives and network drives. Search by file type, document content, or file properties. Take back your valuable time and let UltraSearch do the searching for you.
UltraSearch Professional does not maintain an index stored on your hard disk. It achieves speed by working directly on the Master File Table (MFT) of NTFS partitions. So it even identifies NTFS hardlinks. That...
</description></item><item><title>Download Draftable Desktop 25.10.100</title><pubDate> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 17:18:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-draftable-desktop-3749.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-draftable-desktop-3749.html
</guid><description>
Draftable Desktop is comparison tool documents the fastest. Compare over 300 pages in a few seconds. Draftable Desktop 2.0 is now available - faster and stronger than ever! See all the changes in your documents, locally and online. Take your work to the next level. Compare secret and private do not use the internet and your documents never leave your computer. Specifically, Draftable Desktop compatible with .xls, .xlsx, .xlsxm. With Office 2013, 2016 or 365, you can compare text in...
</description></item><item><title>Download EverNote 10.159.4.25257</title><pubDate> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 17:17:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-evernote-3261.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-evernote-3261.html
</guid><description>
EverNote is the all in one tool allows you to track notes, todo items, memos, outlines, excerpts, websites, ideas and other things and automatically synchronize them between multiple computers and mobile devices (iPhone, Android, etc.). You can choose to sort their notes into categories, password protect them, export them to XML and more. EverNote supports a number of pattern notes allow you to add to-do list, spreadsheet like Excel to calculate costs (automatic sum), notes, phone, contact...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter 3.9.17 (2110)</title><pubDate> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 17:16:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-to-mp3-converter-1744.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-to-mp3-converter-1744.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter is the software support download youtube video and convert video to mp3 format fast and most simple. MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter allows you download and convert videos from YouTube and other websites to MP3 format by pasting the YouTube URL into the application. When you paste the URL, the program will display thumbnails for videos and you have the option to customize the title information, artist and album before you begin the process of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Youtube Downloader HD 5.9.9.4</title><pubDate> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 17:16:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-downloader-hd-3122.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-downloader-hd-3122.html
</guid><description>
Youtube Downloader HD is the best application to download and save Youtube videos. And it's completely free :) You can also convert the downloaded video into various formats easily. Youtube Downloader HD is the download at video free. Download at your videos easily and convert to AVI video format or into MP4 video format (compatible with iPad, iPhone). You can download high quality videos, high definition videos and Full HD from YouTube.
Youtube Downloader HD - Download Youtube videos...
</description></item><item><title>Download Navicat for MariaDB 17.0.3</title><pubDate> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 17:15:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-navicat-for-mariadb-3804.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-navicat-for-mariadb-3804.html
</guid><description>
Navicat for MariaDB is a powerful and reliable allows you to easily develop and manage MariaDB databases. The app allows you to connect to the MariaDB server locally and remotely and provides support for Amazon RDS. The utility supports a variety of additional features, such as micro seconds, tool storage new column virtual and many other features. Navicat for MariaDB integrates the function of data synchronization, data transmission and synchronize the structure, will help you quickly and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Stardock Start11 2.5.6.3 Beta</title><pubDate> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 17:15:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stardock-start11-7029.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stardock-start11-7029.html
</guid><description>
Start11 is an application capable of customizing the Start Menu and Taskbar on Windows 11 and Windows 10. This is an application that allows users to customize Windows 11 to suit their preferences. his personal. Start11 will help you bring the new Start Menu of Windows 11 to Windows 10. And vice versa, Start11 also helps you to bring the Start Menu of Windows 10 to Windows 11.
Start11 also helps users bring some functions of Windows 10 to Windows 11 through customizing the Taskbar such...
</description></item><item><title>Download ThinkAutomation Studio Professional 5.1.1093.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 17:14:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thinkautomation-studio-professional-9635.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thinkautomation-studio-professional-9635.html
</guid><description>
ThinkAutomation Studio Professional is software that automates on-premises and cloud-based business processes to cut costs and save time. Automate incoming communication channels, monitor databases, react to incoming webhooks, web forms and chat bots. Handles documents, attachments, local files, and other message sources.
Parse and extract data from incoming messages and take actions in business processes, such as outbound communications, updating on-premises and cloud databases,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Muziza YouTube Downloader Converter 8.15.3</title><pubDate> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 17:14:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-muziza-youtube-downloader-converter-3972.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-muziza-youtube-downloader-converter-3972.html
</guid><description>
Muziza YouTube Downloader Converter is a tool to create conditions for an attractive interface and many features to help you to download video clips from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion, Instagram and other sites. Muziza YouTube Downloader Converter can also download the video UHD 8K, 5K, 4K, QHD 2K, HD 1080p and 720p from YouTube. The app allows you download only audio stream from YouTube and save as MP3. You don't need to download the entire video file.
Muziza YouTube Downloader...
</description></item><item><title>Download O&amp;amp;O Defrag Pro 30.0.1070</title><pubDate> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 17:14:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-o-o-defrag-pro-149.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-o-o-defrag-pro-149.html
</guid><description>
O&amp;amp;O Defrag Pro is the professional software has the ability to defragment the hard disk and can work with the file system different from FAT / 32 to NTFS / 5, and support for the different arrays Volume / Stripe Sets. You can also set the schedule which O &amp;amp; O Defrag will be booted and perform a number of manipulation certain. Regular defragmentation of the disk partition optimized performance of your computer. The user interface is very easy to use. It has a ribbon bar displays all...
</description></item><item><title>Download O&amp;amp;O Defrag Server 30.0.1070</title><pubDate> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 17:13:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-defrag-server-2521.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-defrag-server-2521.html
</guid><description>
O&amp;amp;O Defrag Server professional software has the ability to defragment the hard disk and can work with the file system different from FAT / 32 to NTFS / 5, and support for the different arrays Volume / Stripe Sets. You can also set the schedule which O &amp;amp; O Defrag will be booted and perform a number of manipulation certain. Regular defragmentation of the disk partition optimized performance of your computer. The user interface is very easy to use. It has a ribbon bar displays all the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Navicat for Oracle 17.0.3</title><pubDate> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 17:13:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-navicat-for-oracle-3805.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-navicat-for-oracle-3805.html
</guid><description>
Navicat for Oracle is an application database will provide a work environment that is reasonable for the developer and administrator of Oracle to increase efficiency and productivity of them. This app is compatible with any server database Oracle, starting from version 8i. The program also supports the latest features of the object Oracle including view materials, active directory, Oracle, table space, Type, synonyms, sequences, etc. Navicat for Oracle also provides a set of improved...
</description></item><item><title>Download RadioCaster 3.6.1.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 17:12:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-radiocaster-6516.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-radiocaster-6516.html
</guid><description>
RadioCaster is a program that takes any audio including the same signal that is connected to your computer or broadcast device and streaming the entire world. That means using seamless audio sources, existing radio programs and other materials while maintaining your own digital presence. The configuration is not difficult, while the detailed statistics help you track your subject.
Features of RadioCaster
	To any sound you have on your computer: support for audio recording from any...
</description></item><item><title>Download Print Conductor 11.0.2510.21180</title><pubDate> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 17:12:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-print-conductor-1559.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-print-conductor-1559.html
</guid><description>
Print Conductor is the software supports automatic printing of documents, text in different formats at the same time, all without opening each one. Print Conductor supports more than 75 kinds of different material and works with all types of printers. With Print Conductor, the printing of large volume of files as easy as 1-2-3. You no longer need to manually open each file, select printer, make settings to print, click "Print" and repeat. Instead, just drag and drop your documents into the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Secure Delete Professional 2025 v213</title><pubDate> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 17:12:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secure-delete-professional-4991.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secure-delete-professional-4991.html
</guid><description>
Secure Delete Professional is very simple tool but very effective to delete files and folders in a secure way. After using this tool, the files and folders selected will not be available for recovery. We have attached a number of security options so you can choose the security level that you need (this reflects the processing speed).
You can use this application in 3 ways. First, you can drag and drop the file or folder that you want to delete securely to the main window of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download 3D Youtube Downloader 1.23.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 17:11:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-3d-youtube-downloader-1631.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-3d-youtube-downloader-1631.html
</guid><description>
3D Youtube Downloader is application support users to download the videos from Youtube website with great quality. The advantage of this software is the ability to download the videos in 3D, make the download process is fully automated and the download speed is extremely fast. In addition to Youtube, this tool also allows to download videos from many other sites, so users can own any favorite videos yet. 3D Youtube Downloader is a downloads simple but powerful from Youtube, Vimeo,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Awesome Miner Ultimate 11.2.6</title><pubDate> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 17:10:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-awesome-miner-9041.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-awesome-miner-9041.html
</guid><description>
Awesome Miner is a software application designed to manage and monitor cryptocurrency mining operations. It supports a wide variety of mining hardware, including ASICs and GPUs, and can be used to manage mining for a variety of cryptocurrencies, including Bitcoin, Ethereum, and Litecoin.
Powerful tool to manage and monitor cryptocurrency mining activities. With support for a wide variety of mining hardware and cryptocurrencies, mobile apps, and customizable alerting and performance...
</description></item><item><title>Download AllMapSoft Offline Map Maker 8.360</title><pubDate> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 17:10:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-offline-map-maker-656.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-offline-map-maker-656.html
</guid><description>
AllMapSoft Offline Map Maker is software create, organize, offline map from Google Maps, Yahoo maps, Bing maps and Openstreetmap. You can view offline maps downloaded with map viewer offline. And you can zoom out or zoom in the offline map or export map under the file format .BMP with file world xxx.bpw, and can output files xxx.map for OziExplorer. If you want to make a offline map of your city by yourself, it is very useful for you.
Features AllMapSoft Offline Map Maker
	You can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Disk Sorter Ultimate 17.4.16 + Server + Pro</title><pubDate> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 17:09:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-disk-sorter-ultimate-1464.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-disk-sorter-ultimate-1464.html
</guid><description>
Disk Sorter Ultimate is the utility classification file lightweight and simple helps people detect files on most types of drives, as well as manage them according to many different criteria to create more capacity on the disc. This app allows you to search through the 500,000 files, have storage capacity of 2TB. To start sorting, all what you have to do is select a directory, drive or server and click the button "Classification". You should know that you can search for the type specific...
</description></item></channel></rss>