<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 20:14:13 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 20:14:13 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Monkeys Audio 12.35</title><pubDate> Sun, 22 Feb 2026 16:21:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-monkeys-audio-949.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-monkeys-audio-949.html
</guid><description>
Monkey\'s Audio is software that compresses digital music without loss of quality. Supports high quality WAV files and CD ripping. Monkeys Audio will compress .wav tracks into .ape files to reduce their size without loss of sound quality, decompress .ape, convert files, check file integrity and manage tags.
Unlike traditional methods like MP3 and OGG, which permanently remove quality to save space, Monkey\'s Audio only creates perfect copies with the same sound quality as the originals....
</description></item><item><title>Download Screenpresso Pro 2.2.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 22 Feb 2026 16:18:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-screenpresso-pro-1362.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-screenpresso-pro-1362.html
</guid><description>
Screenpresso Pro is a program easy to take great photos on your screen! Screenpresso blocked Print Screen key and screen capture the best in a few seconds. Allows you to capture windows and screen area, roll the part of the screen, edit the images obtained, add effects, resize a group of images, send screenshots by email and post them to Web resources.
Screenpresso Pro - Shooting the computer screen
Features of Screenpresso Pro
	Take the window and screen area. Take a partial screen...
</description></item><item><title>Download Secure Delete Professional 2026 v217</title><pubDate> Sun, 22 Feb 2026 16:18:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secure-delete-professional-4991.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secure-delete-professional-4991.html
</guid><description>
Secure Delete Professional is very simple tool but very effective to delete files and folders in a secure way. After using this tool, the files and folders selected will not be available for recovery. We have attached a number of security options so you can choose the security level that you need (this reflects the processing speed).
You can use this application in 3 ways. First, you can drag and drop the file or folder that you want to delete securely to the main window of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Photoshop 2026 v27.4.0.15 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Sun, 22 Feb 2026 16:17:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-0010-adobe-photoshop-737.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-0010-adobe-photoshop-737.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Photoshop is a powerful raster graphics editor developed by Adobe Systems, primarily used for image editing, photo editing, and graphic design. Currently,&amp;nbsp;Adobe Photoshop 2025 is considered a graphic design software, creating and enhancing images, illustrations, and 3D artwork. In addition, it also supports website and mobile app design, video editing, real-life painting simulation, and more.
Adobe Photoshop 2025 - Graphic design
When it comes to Adobe Photoshop, it is...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDF Architect Pro + OCR 9.1.88.23120</title><pubDate> Sun, 22 Feb 2026 16:16:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-architect-pro-ocr-6381.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-architect-pro-ocr-6381.html
</guid><description>
PDF Architect  is professional software that provides PDF creation and editing features according to your needs. Our PDF editor keeps you up to date with forward-looking features. Take complete control of your PDF files with our PDF editor. Modify text, images, and pages, and convert PDF to Word and Excel and more.
It has many advanced options and features for customizing, securing, and collaborating PDF files. All necessary features are included in this for better user experience. This...
</description></item><item><title>Download DiskDigger Pro 2.0.13.4177</title><pubDate> Sun, 22 Feb 2026 16:15:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-diskdigger-pro-435.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-diskdigger-pro-435.html
</guid><description>
DiskDigger Pro is software restore data files, videos, pictures, sounds, media files, from a USB Flash drive, memory card.  DiskDigger can recover all the deleted files from your means, can help even when files or folders lost due to virus attack. It gives users the ability to restore various types of data including: pictures, video, audio, text.
DiskDigger Pro support in multiple files with different formats: JPG, PNG, GIF, BMP, TIFF, ICO, ANI, DOC, DOCX, XLS, PPT, PDF, VSD, PPTX,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Balabolka 2.15.0.913</title><pubDate> Sun, 22 Feb 2026 16:06:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-balaboka-142.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-balaboka-142.html
</guid><description>
Balabolka is a text-to-speech (TTS) program. It can read text on your screen in a human-like voice. You can use Balabolka to listen to text from a variety of file formats, convert text to spoken audio files, and adjust speech parameters such as speed and pitch. It is often used for accessibility purposes, helping people who have difficulty reading or multi-tasking by listening to text while doing other activities. Balabolka supports multiple languages and uses different TTS engines,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Spencer 1.37</title><pubDate> Sun, 22 Feb 2026 15:56:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-spencer-1881.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-spencer-1881.html
</guid><description>
Spencer provide an easy way to bring start Menu Windows XP classic for Windows 8 your. This program is a standalone application and requires no installation. Just copy the file spencer.exe to desktop your and click that file to display a menu with all Menu items, start your current.
Spencer - Create Menu Windows XP classic
If you want to integrate it into your taskbar to make it look like the start Button is actually more, you can choose the option "Pin to taskbar" from right click...
</description></item><item><title>Download Homedale 2.23</title><pubDate> Sun, 22 Feb 2026 15:55:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-homedale-1914.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-homedale-1914.html
</guid><description>
Homedale is a screen wireless network simple allows you to view the status and signal strength of nearby access points. In addition to displaying technical information like infrastructure, channels and bitrate are supported, the program also includes a chart signals allows you to monitor signal strength of multiple access points in real time.
Because this is a mobile program, it is important to mention that it does not leave any traces in the Windows Registry. You can copy it on any USB...
</description></item><item><title>Download VovSoft Text Edit Plus 15.7</title><pubDate> Sun, 22 Feb 2026 15:54:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-text-edit-plus-2872.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-text-edit-plus-2872.html
</guid><description>
VovSoft Text Edit Plus is app designed replacement for Notepad by offering a feature set wider. Text Edit Plus is a lightweight tool that allows users to easily create new text document or edit the existing document. This app is designed replacement for Notepad by offering a feature set wider.
VovSoft Text Edit Plus - text editing
A number of features: dark Mode. Add date and time. The change of the background color and the font. Encrypt and decrypt text. Combine the lines. System...
</description></item><item><title>Download Apisonic Audio Speedrum 2.3.4</title><pubDate> Sun, 22 Feb 2026 15:51:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-apisonic-labs-speedrum-6993.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-apisonic-labs-speedrum-6993.html
</guid><description>
Speedrum is an MPC style drum sampler. Designed for easy startup and fast workflow, but with powerful features if you need them. 32 pads with essential effects, and with 8 sample layers per pad. 16 pads layout A/B with view to all pad FX or 32 pads layout with one FX view at a time.
Features of Speedrum:
	Speedrum is an MPC style drum sampler.
	Designed for easy startup and fast workflow, but with powerful features if you need them.
	32 pads with essential effects, and with 8 sample...
</description></item><item><title>Download GeoGebra 6.0.916</title><pubDate> Sun, 22 Feb 2026 15:51:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-geogebra-992.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-geogebra-992.html
</guid><description>
GeoGebra is software the mathematics on the computer for you to solve problems more quickly and accurately data problem given. GeoGebra supports connect geometry, algebra and elements of mathematics other in an interactive way and tight. Besides, GeoGebra also allows users to directly enter and manipulate mathematical equations and coordinates, and make use of the points, vector, lines, triangles, cones..
GeoGebra - graph the function
GeoGebra is designed for math classes in junior...
</description></item><item><title>Download lessmsi 2.12.5</title><pubDate> Sun, 22 Feb 2026 15:50:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lessmsi-12392.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lessmsi-12392.html
</guid><description>
Lessmsi (Less MSIerables) is a free and portable application that allows users to view and extract the contents of MSI files.
How does it work? Files with the .msi extension are not as widely used as their .exe cousins, but both contain programs for Windows. The main difference between them is that the latter does not always come with an installer, while it comes standard with the former. However, there will be cases where you just need to view or want to extract specific content from...
</description></item><item><title>Download Prepros 7.39.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 22 Feb 2026 15:49:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-prepros-4471.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-prepros-4471.html
</guid><description>
Prepros is a tool simple to use display interface is minimalistic and allows users to load, view and preprocess images, CSS and JS. Prepros available in a bright and dark themes, the user interface has a sleek style and is optimized to show all the highlights the potential that you encountered in the process of compiling highlights. You can start by adding the project you are implementing, an action you can complete in a convenient way by dragging and dropping.
Prepros - Learn to write...
</description></item><item><title>Download MiniMeters 1.0.24.172</title><pubDate> Sun, 22 Feb 2026 15:48:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minimeters-9410.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minimeters-9410.html
</guid><description>
MiniMeters is a simple standalone sound meter application for Windows. Monitor your System Audio*, Any Input, or insert the MiniMeter Server Plug-in (VST3/AU/CLAP) at the end of your main channel in the DAW of your choice. Customize the layout in a horizontal bar (perfect for above or below the audio engine of your choice) or pop out into modules to create custom layouts.
Features of MiniMeters
	6 modules to choose from to build your perfect metering setup: Spectrogram, Waveform,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Jailer 16.11.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 22 Feb 2026 15:45:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jailer-3196.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jailer-3196.html
</guid><description>
Jailer is a tool to reset the database, schema and browse data. It the sets of continuous, intact reference from the database relations. It removes outdated data without violating integrity. Theory is that force majeure DBMS (using JDBC), platform-independent and tạobộ data DbUnit , XML has hierarchical structure and SQL-DML is arranged in the link structure.
Jailer - Installed back to the database
Database Jailer is growing both in scale and complexity to meet the growing needs of...
</description></item><item><title>Download NetSpeedTray 1.2.6 + Portable</title><pubDate> Sun, 22 Feb 2026 15:45:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-netspeedtray-14068.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-netspeedtray-14068.html
</guid><description>
NetSpeedTray is a lightweight, open source network monitor for Windows that displays upload/download speeds directly on the Taskbar with a native look and feel.
Designed to blend seamlessly with Windows 10/11 user interface. Includes intelligent detection of light and dark themes on the taskbar to ensure text is always visible. Sits quietly in the system tray without hogging resources. Features "Dynamic Update Rate" that automatically reduces update frequency when the network is idle to...
</description></item><item><title>Download MaximizeToVirtualDesktop 0.0.6</title><pubDate> Sun, 22 Feb 2026 13:12:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-maximizetovirtualdesktop-14577.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-maximizetovirtualdesktop-14577.html
</guid><description>
MaximizeToVirtualDesktop is a free, open-source utility that brings the full-screen zoom feature of macOS's virtual desktop to Windows 11. When activated, the window in the foreground will be moved to a completely new virtual desktop and zoomed in. Closing, minimizing, or re-enabling the shortcut will restore everything — the window returns to its original screen and size, and the temporary virtual desktop will be removed.
The application runs in the system tray. Right-click the icon...
</description></item><item><title>Download Voice Creator Pro 1.1.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 22 Feb 2026 13:03:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-voice-creator-pro-14576.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-voice-creator-pro-14576.html
</guid><description>
A versatile local AI voice creator software that sounds like a real person. Voice copying, voice design, text-to-speech, and speech-to-text conversion, with full REST API access.
Features of Voice Creator Pro
	Voice Copying — Copy any voice with just 3 seconds of audio. Create voices that sound indistinguishable from the original.
	Voice Design — Create custom voices from text descriptions. No audio samples needed — just describe the voice you want.
	Text-to-Speech — Convert...
</description></item><item><title>Download Perfectly Clear WorkBench 5.0.2.3107</title><pubDate> Sun, 22 Feb 2026 00:21:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfectly-clear-workbench-6892.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfectly-clear-workbench-6892.html
</guid><description>
Perfectly Clear Workbench is an application that uses image editing libraries Perfectly Clear by Athentech and is provided to demonstrate the capabilities of the Perfectly Clear processing libraries, which recognize faces and allow quick export of processing settings for use.
One of the key features in Workbench is the ability to "export to API" when saving a Preset. This allows you to make image edits in Workbench and adjust the settings to suit your editing style and needs. You can...
</description></item><item><title>Download StartAllBack 3.9.21.5360</title><pubDate> Sun, 22 Feb 2026 00:20:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-startallback-6857.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-startallback-6857.html
</guid><description>
With the official release of Windows 11, chances are that most of you want to try it out. As the name suggests, StartAllBack is a small, lightweight tool that can help you enjoy the power of the new operating system while keeping the look and feel, especially because main work area, desktop of Windows 7, Windows 10 as taskbars and start menu styles.
StartAllBack is specially designed for Windows 11 and will not work on any older operating systems. If you want to get the start menu back...
</description></item><item><title>Download Soda PDF Desktop Pro 15.0.08.24416</title><pubDate> Sun, 22 Feb 2026 00:20:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-soda-pdf-home-808.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-soda-pdf-home-808.html
</guid><description>
Soda PDF Pro  is intuitive PDF software that helps you to easily process and create PDF files from more than 300 different formats. Soda PDF is built to help you power through any PDF task. Convert to a wide range of file types. Edit the content of your document. Create custom forms. Annotate your files. Send and track contracts for electronic signatures.
Soda PDF Pro: Create PDF file
Features of Soda PDF Pro
	Read your PDFs and digital publications in 3D with unique page-turning...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube Downloader 3.9.18 (2102)</title><pubDate> Sun, 22 Feb 2026 00:18:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube Downloader  is a dedicated software that helps users  downloading youtube videos  Favorites on PC for offline viewing. With MediaHuman YouTube  Downloader  you can download videos from youtube website to your computer with  fast speed , with special software development technology that automatically receives videos from Websites, in addition to the ability to download videos from software websites, can convert downloaded video formats to various formats for the purpose...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft OneDrive 26.017.0126.0002</title><pubDate> Sun, 22 Feb 2026 00:18:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-onedrive-48.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-onedrive-48.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft OneDrive is a client application file transmission to the service cloud storage of Microsoft. If you are familiar with Dropbox, you will find that OneDrive works in a similar way. It creates a OneDrive folder and any files you copy into the folder will automatically be synced and uploaded to the cloud service OneDrive.
Microsoft OneDrive
You can access your files from the client application other on PC. Mac or mobile devices as well as web interface. OneDrive also allows you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tiny11 25H2 Build 26200.7840 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Sun, 22 Feb 2026 00:01:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tiny11-8649.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tiny11-8649.html
</guid><description>
Tiny11 is a compact Windows operating system based on Windows 11 Pro 22H2, Tiny11 has everything you need for a comfortable, hassle-free computing experience. cumbersome and messy like a standard Windows installation. The operating system requires only 8GB of disk space and 2GB of RAM, and requires no TPM (Trusted Platform Module) and Secure Boot support.
The main goal of Tiny11 is to extend the reach of systems that can access Windows 11. The custom edition can run on any system...
</description></item></channel></rss>