<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 13:46:16 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 13:46:16 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Digital Compass 18.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 16:37:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-digital-compass-13590.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-digital-compass-13590.html
</guid><description>
This app is a smart compass with high accuracy and a great tool for outdoor activities. This compass app allows you to easily determine the direction you are facing. This app is built using the device's gyroscope, accelerometer, magnetometer, gravity sensor to determine the direction. Make sure your device has an accelerometer and magnetometer sensor or it will not work.
Features
	Show current location (longitude, latitude, address)
	Show altitude
	Show magnetic field strength
	Show...
</description></item><item><title>Download All PDF Editor &amp;amp; Reader | Xodo 10.10.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 16:37:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-xodo-pdf-reader-editor-8451.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-xodo-pdf-reader-editor-8451.html
</guid><description>
Xodo PDF Reader &amp;amp; Editor is a mobile application for reading and editing PDF documents on Android and iOS devices. The app allows users to view, annotate, and edit PDF files using a variety of tools, including highlighting, underlining, and adding notes. With Xodo, you can read, annotate, sign, and share PDFs and fill out PDF forms, all while syncing with Google Drive, Dropbox, and OneDrive.
Xodo PDF Reader &amp;amp; Editor Features
	PDF Viewer: Application that allows users to view...
</description></item><item><title>Download radio.net PRIME 5.18.1.0-app build 100116</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 16:37:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-radionet-prime-8335.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-radionet-prime-8335.html
</guid><description>
radio.net PRIME is a mobile application that allows users to listen to a variety of radio stations on their Android devices. This app provides access to more than 30,000 radio stations around the world, including local and international stations in a variety of genres and formats.
Features of radio.net PRIME
	Access to more than 30,000 radio stations around the world
	Supports multiple genres and formats, including news, music, sports, and chat
	Option to create a list of favorite...
</description></item><item><title>Download Power VPN: Fast &amp;amp; Secure VPN 2.2.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 16:37:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-power-vpn-fast-secure-vpn-10109.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-power-vpn-fast-secure-vpn-10109.html
</guid><description>
Power VPN - Free Unlimited VPN Master for Android. Now you can easily access blocked Internet Content with just one click with PowerVPN's Fast and Secure VPN Tunnel. Power VPN Free VPN is the fastest VPN with a secure server network worldwide.
Power VPN Features: Fast and Secure VPN
	This is the best VPN (free VPN) ever created. Create your IPVanish
	Simple interface. Just click to connect
	Over 30 different server locations worldwide to connect to.
	Allows torrenting, P2P, and file...
</description></item><item><title>Download mcpro24fps manual video camera v043cw</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 16:36:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-mcpro24fps-manual-video-camera-8325.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-mcpro24fps-manual-video-camera-8325.html
</guid><description>
Probably the most advanced and powerful professional video camera app on Android! McPro24FPS opens up incredible video recording possibilities on your phone, something previously only available on professional camcorders.
Features of mcpro24fps manual video camera
	Capture in 10 bits for a large number of devices. HLG / HDR10 HDR Video
	record video to log without turning on the GPU, just like on Big Big's big camera
	Huge number of log modes for every situation. Post-production...
</description></item><item><title>Download Solid Explorer File Manager 3.2.9</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 16:36:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-solid-explorer-file-manager-8924.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-solid-explorer-file-manager-8924.html
</guid><description>
Solid Explorer is a file management application inspired by old file management applications. Solid Explorer is a popular file management app for Android devices that allows users to manage and organize their files and folders in an intuitive and user-friendly interface. It offers many features that make it stand out from other file management apps.
Solid Explorer allows you to navigate to files stored on your device and automatically organize them into collections. You can view,...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDF Converter AI Convert files v254</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 16:36:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pdf-converter-convert-file-11089.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pdf-converter-convert-file-11089.html
</guid><description>
PDF Converter Convert files and images to PDF, DOC, PPT, XLS, RTF, ODT, JPG, PNG. Convert documents, images and files to PDF, DOC, PPT, XLS, RTF, ODT, JPG, PNG.
PDF Converter Convert files and images to PDF by Offiwiz is a document converter to convert files to other extensions: you can convert PDF to Word, TXT, PPT, DOC, JPG, PNG, XLS and more. This PDF Converter app is also a PDF Reader and PDF Editor. Choose the extension, output format and convert any document, perfect for creating...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDF Scanner app - TapScanner 3.0.92</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 16:35:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pdf-scanner-app-tapscanner-12104.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pdf-scanner-app-tapscanner-12104.html
</guid><description>
TapScanner is a mobile application that allows you to scan documents with your smartphone camera and convert them into PDF files or image formats. It essentially turns your device into a portable scanner, making capturing and digitizing physical documents convenient on the go.
TapScanner Features
	Scan documents, receipts, QRs and business cards
	Document Scanner App - Automatic Border Detection
	Tweak your images with multiple filters to achieve perfection
	Easily manage your...
</description></item><item><title>Download Silent Camera [High Quality] 8.16.7</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 16:35:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-silent-camera-10536.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-silent-camera-10536.html
</guid><description>
Introducing the best silent camera! Without the shutter sound, photos can be taken in complete silence! It also ranks number 1 among many silent cameras thanks to its high image quality! Take high-quality photos with the silent camera! You won't disturb anyone around you because the shutter sound can't be heard. You can take high-quality photos of any situation, such as your baby's cute sleeping face, your pet's natural behaviors, and words written on a blackboard!
Silent Camera...
</description></item><item><title>Download Zero Cleaner: clear cache 25.12.1 build 39</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 16:34:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-zero-cleaner-clear-cache-10667.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-zero-cleaner-clear-cache-10667.html
</guid><description>
Zero Cleaner is a mobile application that specializes in removing cache files from your device. Cache files are temporary data stored by applications and websites to improve their performance and load times. Over time, cache files can accumulate and take up valuable storage space on your device.
Some key features of Zero Cleaner include:
	Cache Cleaner: The app will scan your device for cache files created by apps and web browsers, allowing you to clear them with just a tap. This...
</description></item><item><title>Download Flat Equalizer - Bass Booster 6.3.5.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 16:34:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-flat-equalizer-bass-booster-10055.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-flat-equalizer-bass-booster-10055.html
</guid><description>
Equalizer, Bass Booster, Volume Booster and Virtualizer for your phone follow Google's Material Design. You can control Equalizer FX, Bass Boost, Sound Boost and Virtualizer independently, which means you don't need to turn on EQ to enable Bass Boost. For best results, pair this app with your best headphones. If you don't have a pair of headphones or if you want to use speakers, you can still enjoy good music with our app. This is also a great speaker booster if you use a Bluetooth...
</description></item><item><title>Download Listen Audiobook Player 5.4.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 16:34:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-listen-audiobook-player-8511.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-listen-audiobook-player-8511.html
</guid><description>
Listen Audiobook Player is a mobile app for playing audiobooks on your phone or tablet. It lets you play, pause, rewind, and fast-forward audiobooks with ease, while also providing a convenient way to track your listening progress.
Some key features of Listen Audiobook Player include:
	Library Management: Allows you to store and organize your audiobooks in a virtual library for easy access.
	Bookmark: Automatically saves your listening position so you can pick up where you left...
</description></item><item><title>Download Dev Tools Pro (Developer Tools) 9.1.2-gp</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 16:33:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-dev-tools-pro-developer-tools-12197.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-dev-tools-pro-developer-tools-12197.html
</guid><description>
Android Dev Tools Pro is an essential, efficient, powerful, automation Android Development Assistant, It can improve your development productivity. It can be used to decompile another app, view other app's layout details, view screen colors (color sampler or eyedropper), view latest open source projects, view activity history, view manifest of any app, view recently used or installed apps, extract apk or more, debug apps, view hardware and firmware related information phone software,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Bluetooth Codec Changer 1.7.4 build 1093</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 16:33:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-bluetooth-codec-changer-8542.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-bluetooth-codec-changer-8542.html
</guid><description>
Bluetooth Codec Changer is a technology used to encode and decode audio data transmitted over a Bluetooth connection. Improve audio quality and latency by controlling the Bluetooth device decoder. You have complete control over the A2DP Profile Decoder for your Bluetooth headset.
Features of Bluetooth Codec Changer
	Automatically switch codecs when you connect a Bluetooth device.
	Manage your different devices with different codec profiles and swap between them without any...
</description></item><item><title>Download Shazam: Find Music &amp;amp; Concerts 16.22.1-251209</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 16:33:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-shazam-music-discovery-10763.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-shazam-music-discovery-10763.html
</guid><description>
Shazam will identify any song in seconds. Discover, artists, lyrics, videos &amp;amp; playlists, all for free. Over 1 billion installs and counting. Use Pop-up Shazam to identify music in any app - Instagram, YouTube, TikTok... No connection? No problem! Shazam while offline.
Features of Shazam: Music Discovery
	Find the name of any song in seconds.
	Listen and add to Apple Music playlists.
	Follow along with time-synced lyrics.
	Watch music videos from Apple Music or YouTube.
	Enable...
</description></item><item><title>Download QR Code &amp;amp; Barcode Scanner Plus 1.9.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 16:32:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-qr-code-barcode-scanner-plus-13406.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-qr-code-barcode-scanner-plus-13406.html
</guid><description>
QR Code &amp;amp; Barcode Scanner Plus is your go-to app for seamless barcode and QR code scanning, designed for Android users. This powerful free QR code scanner and free barcode scanner app quickly decodes QR codes and barcodes, ensuring fast and accurate results. With this free QR code reader and barcode reader, scanning becomes easy.
Discover how QR Code &amp;amp; Barcode Scanner Plus enhances your daily activities:
	Instantly scan QR codes to access Wi-Fi without manually entering...
</description></item><item><title>Download Weather &amp;amp; Radar USA - Pro 2025.25</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 16:32:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-weather-radar-usa-pro-8391.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-weather-radar-usa-pro-8391.html
</guid><description>
Weather &amp;amp; Radar USA is a mobile application that provides users with real-time weather information and forecasts for locations in the United States. The app includes many features such as current weather conditions, hourly and daily forecasts, radar and satellite images, and severe weather alerts. It also includes many customizable settings, such as the ability to set up multiple locations and receive notifications about specific weather conditions.
Features of Weather &amp;amp; Radar...
</description></item><item><title>Download ACR Phone 0.380</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 16:32:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-acr-phone-10805.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-acr-phone-10805.html
</guid><description>
ACR Phone &amp;amp; Dialer Spam call blocker is a phone app that can replace your default dialer. This is a completely new application and we are constantly improving it.
Features of ACR Phone
	Blacklist/Block spam
	Call person to notify
	Call notes
	Backup
	Outgoing call blocker
	Call log
	Supports dual SIM
	Contacts
	Video call and photo call screen
	SIP client (on supported devices)
	Call recording (on supported devices)
	Cloud Upload
	Auto Dialer
	Visual voicemail
</description></item><item><title>Download SnapTube for Android 7.51.1.75172601</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 16:31:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-snaptube-youtube-downloader-hd-video-8351.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-snaptube-youtube-downloader-hd-video-8351.html
</guid><description>
SnapTube is a mobile application that allows users to download videos from various platforms, such as YouTube, Vimeo, and Dailymotion. It provides video resolution in multiple formats 144p, 720p, 1080p HD, 2K HD, 4K HD and audio formats MP3 and M4A. With Snaptube, users can search for content across all their platforms without using multiple apps.
Features of SnapTube for Android
Download in multiple resolutions
	MP4 videos are available in resolutions: choose small 360 pixels or...
</description></item><item><title>Download Fraction Calculator Plus 6.1.4</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 16:31:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-fraction-calculator-plus-8354.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-fraction-calculator-plus-8354.html
</guid><description>
Fraction Calculator Plus is a mobile application that provides a user interface to perform basic mathematical operations such as addition, subtraction, multiplication and division. Many calculator apps also have advanced features such as scientific calculations, unit conversions, and graphing.
Features of Fraction Calculator Plus
	It displays your calculations in sharp, clear, elegant text that you can quickly read from a distance.
	My innovative three-keyboard display lets you type...
</description></item><item><title>Download IMDb: Movies &amp;amp; TV Shows 9.2.4.109240300</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 16:31:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-imdb-movies-tv-shows-8258.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-imdb-movies-tv-shows-8258.html
</guid><description>
IMDb (Internet Movie Database) is a popular application that provides information about movies, TV shows, and other video content. This app allows users to search and browse information about a variety of movies and TV shows, including cast and crew information, user ratings and reviews, trailers, and more. Users can also create watchlists and rate the movies and shows they've watched.
Some key features of the IMDb application include:
	Browse movies and TV shows by popularity,...
</description></item><item><title>Download KillApps: Close Running Apps 1.56.6 build 968</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 16:30:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-killapps-close-running-apps-10803.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-killapps-close-running-apps-10803.html
</guid><description>
KillApps allows you to automatically close background apps with a simple tap. You can choose to close all apps at once, or you can select specific apps to close. This app requires access to accessibility services to be able to close other apps. This application will be able to observe interface-related actions to guide the process of automating the task of closing the application, by monitoring the transitions between windows during simulation of interaction with interface.
Features of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Chat AI - AI Chatbot Assistant 229.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 16:30:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-chat-ai-ai-chatbot-assistant-11260.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-chat-ai-ai-chatbot-assistant-11260.html
</guid><description>
AI Chatbot is a smart artificial intelligence interactive application that brings a unique and convenient experience to users. With AI Chatbot, you can communicate and ask questions directly with a powerful AI system that helps you find information, answer questions, and even provide solutions to complex problems.
Main features of Chatbot AI include
	Natural conversation: Chatbot AI uses advanced natural language technology to understand and respond to your questions and requests...
</description></item><item><title>Download Audiomack: Music Downloader 7.9.0 build 31102</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 16:30:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-audiomack-music-downloader-11192.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-audiomack-music-downloader-11192.html
</guid><description>
Stream and download the best new trending music (full tracks offline data-free) and listen to your local MP3s!&amp;nbsp;Browse music from the best artists in top categories like Hip-Hop, Rap, R&amp;amp;B, EDM, Afropop, and Reggae on the Audiomack music app. Download songs and listen offline, without using your data, or listen to your personal MP3 collection! Audiomack provides download access and unlimited streaming to the newest and hottest tracks, right at your fingertips. Our music download...
</description></item><item><title>Download Castro Premium - system info 4.8.3 build 369</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 16:29:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-castro-premium-system-info-10230.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-castro-premium-system-info-10230.html
</guid><description>
Castro is an information utility for your tablets and smartphones. It displays various diagnostic information about the device. Castro processes and displays a huge amount of information, namely
	Detailed processor statistics (CPU and GPU);
	Battery monitoring;
	Consumes all types of memory;
	Data usage over Wi-Fi and mobile networks;
	Real-time sensor data with helpful graphs;
	Detailed information about the device's camera;
	Full list of available audio and video codecs;
	Monitor the...
</description></item></channel></rss>