<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 17:46:51 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 17:46:51 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download AnyDesk 9.6.9</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 18:20:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anydesk-1321.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anydesk-1321.html
</guid><description>
AnyDesk is software computer control remote, easy connection with remote computer management and manipulation on the computer. After installing the AnyDesk up 2 the computer then you can easily use the software to provide technical support for a friend or family member or you have access to your computer while you away from home or office.
AnyDesk - control your computer remotely
The process of using very simple software, want to allow access to his computer, only need to provide for...
</description></item><item><title>Download PrivaZer Pro Donors 4.0.117</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 18:19:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-privazer-donors-198.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-privazer-donors-198.html
</guid><description>
PrivaZer Donors  cleans and removes filth traces from the system. Intensive cleaning of unwanted traces of what you've done, viewed, downloaded, deleted, etc. Take ownership of your security and freedom - Free up disk space. Keep your PC snug and secure !!!
With one click, PrivaZer can safely clean: Internet browsers, Index.dat, Cookies, Tor Cookies, Flash Cookies, Silverlight Cookies, DOM Storing, IndexedDB, AppCache Registry, RAM, Pagefile.sys and Hiberfil.sys files.  PrivaZer  can...
</description></item><item><title>Download EndNote 2025.3.1 Build 19926</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 18:18:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-endnote-4237.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-endnote-4237.html
</guid><description>
EndNote X9 as a researcher, you constantly carry the different roles, addressing the competing demands on your time and coordinate not only the activities of the own in study published that all your collaborators on the whole and on the whole world. EndNote X9 is software management reference not only frees you from the tedious work in collecting and managing research material and format folder manually but also help you easy and more controlled in coordination with colleagues.
EndNote...
</description></item><item><title>Download AI FaceSwap 2.6.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 18:18:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ai-faceswap-11511.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ai-faceswap-11511.html
</guid><description>
AI FaceSwap uses artificial intelligence (AI) algorithms to swap faces between two or more people in an image or camera. This technology leverages deep learning techniques, especially convolutional neural networks (CNN), to accurately detect and manipulate facial features.
The algorithm identifies important facial landmarks such as eyes, nose, mouth, etc. to understand the structure and orientation of each face. The faces are then aligned to ensure that the corresponding facial features...
</description></item><item><title>Download JRiver Media Center 35.0.40</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 18:16:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jriver-media-center-110.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jriver-media-center-110.html
</guid><description>
JRiver Media Center can help you strictly manage all your files media and enjoy them in a completely new way. Launching the application for the first time, users will be immediately impressed with the intuitive and eye-catching interface with many interesting features to explore. Most people who have used JRiver Media Center evaluate that the software interface design is youthful and modern.
The software for arranging cover art of music files is also extremely neat, especially Insert...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tiny11 25H2 Build 26200.7627 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 18:15:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tiny11-8649.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tiny11-8649.html
</guid><description>
Tiny11 is a compact Windows operating system based on Windows 11 Pro 22H2, Tiny11 has everything you need for a comfortable, hassle-free computing experience. cumbersome and messy like a standard Windows installation. The operating system requires only 8GB of disk space and 2GB of RAM, and requires no TPM (Trusted Platform Module) and Secure Boot support.
The main goal of Tiny11 is to extend the reach of systems that can access Windows 11. The custom edition can run on any system...
</description></item><item><title>Download By Click Downloader 2.4.29</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 18:15:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-by-click-premium-193.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-by-click-premium-193.html
</guid><description>
YouTube By Click Premium is a high quality powerful video downloader including YouTube downloader, YouTube Converter, YouTube Chrome Downloader, Facebook Video Downloader, Downloader Vimeo, Dailymotion Downloader and supports many other video sites.
YouTube By Click
YouTube By Click Features
	YouTube by Click can download and convert files to MP3, MP4, FLV, AVI, WMV, 3GP, WAV and WEBM formats.
	Download all supported qualities, including HD.
	YouTube By Click downloads entire YouTube...
</description></item><item><title>Download Revive Faces 2.0.12</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 18:14:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-revive-faces-13762.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-revive-faces-13762.html
</guid><description>
Have you ever looked at an old photo or video and wished you could see those faces clearly again? Time, blurriness, and pixels shouldn't steal the smiles, glances, or stories of the people you love. With Revive Faces, our breakthrough AI-powered restoration software, blurry, smudged, and pixelated faces can now shine with stunning clarity—as if they were taken yesterday.
Why Restore Faces?
	See the unseen again – Our advanced AI not only sharpens images, but also recreates lost...
</description></item><item><title>Download Active UNDELETE Ultimate 26.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 18:14:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-active-undelete-ultimate-2716.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-active-undelete-ultimate-2716.html
</guid><description>
Active Undelete is recovery software powerful data to help you recover the deleted files and restore partitions deleted. The Pro version of the software Active Undelete has the advanced features like recovery volume / partition has been deleted, the editing part volume boot and the possibility to modify the partition rollback. Package contains the files ISO image that you can use to create CD / DVD / USB that can boot to launch the computer can't execute. If your system does not boot and...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube Downloader 3.9.18 (3001)</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 18:14:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube Downloader  is a dedicated software that helps users  downloading youtube videos  Favorites on PC for offline viewing. With MediaHuman YouTube  Downloader  you can download videos from youtube website to your computer with  fast speed , with special software development technology that automatically receives videos from Websites, in addition to the ability to download videos from software websites, can convert downloaded video formats to various formats for the purpose...
</description></item><item><title>Download Let It Be Light 2.0.12</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 18:13:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-let-it-be-light-13761.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-let-it-be-light-13761.html
</guid><description>
Let It Be Light – Illuminate the Invisible, Unleash Infinite Content! Tired of dark, underexposed footage that could be your next viral hit? Say hello to Let It Be Light – revolutionary AI image and video processing software that turns dull clips into beautiful, well-lit masterpieces!
Why Let It Be Light?
	Unlock Hidden Content – ​​Turn dark, grainy, or underexposed footage from film, old archives, or social media into crisp, bright, and useful content. No more discarding...
</description></item><item><title>Download Scale Photo Up 2.0.12</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 18:13:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-scale-photo-up-13763.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-scale-photo-up-13763.html
</guid><description>
Are you tired of low-resolution, pixelated footage that stifles your creativity? Say goodbye to grainy memories and say hello to Scale Photo Up – groundbreaking AI software that doubles resolution, enhances detail, and smooths out imperfections in your photos and videos with stunning clarity!
Why Scale Photo Up?
	Upscale 2x – No loss of quality! – Turn blurry, low-resolution photos and videos into sharp, high-resolution masterpieces. Perfect for breathing new life into old...
</description></item><item><title>Download dBpoweramp Music Converter Reference 2026.01.31</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 18:12:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbpoweramp-music-converter-4222.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbpoweramp-music-converter-4222.html
</guid><description>
dBpoweramp Music Converter audio converter is perfect, easy to convert to mp3, FLAC, Apple lossless and more. dBpoweramp Music Converter has become the standard tool for audio conversion, more than 30 million users world trust their switch to dBpoweramp. dBpoweramp Music Converter integrates into Windows Explorer, an mp3 converter as simple as right-click on source files; convert into. Tip information Popup, edit tags ID are provided.
dBpoweramp Music Converter - audio converter...
</description></item><item><title>Download ChessBase 26.5</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 18:12:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chessbase-13889.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chessbase-13889.html
</guid><description>
ChessBase is the personal, independent chess database that has become the world standard. Everyone uses ChessBase, from World Champions to the amateur player next door. It is the program of choice for anyone who loves the game and wants to learn more about it. Start your personal success story with ChessBase and enjoy the game even more.
Whether it's preparing for an individual opponent or tournament, managing and analyzing your own games, developing training materials for self-study or...
</description></item><item><title>Download Social Media Downloader 8.1.6</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 18:11:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-socialmediaapps-facebook-video-downloader-3742.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-socialmediaapps-facebook-video-downloader-3742.html
</guid><description>
SocialVideo Downloader (formerly SocialMediaApps Facebook Video Downloader) is a Windows application to download and convert your favorite videos from Facebook and hundreds of other video sharing sites. It increases your loading speed by up to 500%, or even more! The application has a simple and intuitive user interface, its main functions and features are quite obvious to anyone. , regardless of prior experience with similar purpose tools.
&amp;nbsp;
SocialVideo Downloader
The main...
</description></item><item><title>Download FRITZ 20.11</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 18:11:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fritz-14060.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fritz-14060.html
</guid><description>
FRITZ 20 is more than just a chess engine – it’s a training revolution for aspiring players and professionals. Whether you’re taking your first steps into the world of professional chess training, or are already playing at tournament level, FRITZ 20 will help you train more efficiently, intelligently and personally than ever before.
Simulate playing styles at the highest level
FRITZ 20 analyzes your next opponent – and plays just like them!
Use the style analysis feature in...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sante PACS Server PG 4.4.4</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 18:10:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sante-pacs-server-pg-7540.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sante-pacs-server-pg-7540.html
</guid><description>
Sante PACS Server PG is an HTTP server (web) for DICOM files and a recorder and In CD/DVD with high performance and reliability. It provides connectivity with all the DICOM (CT, MR, US, CR, NM, XA, MG, DX, etc.). The review of the DICOM image can be done with the Sante PACS Viewer.
Integrated web servers can be used as a free cloud server for DICOM files!
</description></item><item><title>Download GibbsCAM 2026 v26.0.55</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 18:10:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gibbscam-001-732.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gibbscam-001-732.html
</guid><description>
GibbsCAM is a full-featured CAM system that provides powerful CNC programming capabilities to optimize manufacturing production.GibbsCAM 12 introduces a modern, updated system Updated interface designed to increase efficiency and improve overall user experience.
GibbsCAM
GibbsCAM updates with a new interface that gives users the ability to customize, along with the ease-of-use features users expect, while still maintaining character, personality and traditional workflows. by...
</description></item><item><title>Download Filmworkz Phoenix 2025.4.004</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 18:10:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-digital-vision-phoenix-6617.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-digital-vision-phoenix-6617.html
</guid><description>
The Phoenix Ministry of products provides world-class restoration tools for the most demanding jobs. With the DVO technology that has won many of our awards, Phoenix is designed to produce great results quickly with fewer handicrave interventions. With a familiar time-based interface, artists and storage houses can easily review and edit things according to the context if required. Each product has been designed around a set of features for specific work and budget.
Features of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Abelssoft EasyFirewall 2025 v3.02.69764</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 18:09:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-abelssoft-easyfirewall-7855.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-abelssoft-easyfirewall-7855.html
</guid><description>
Abelssoft EasyFirewall is software that provides Windows firewall rules to make it easy to set which applications are allowed to communicate with the internet and which are not. It has a firewall wizard that helps you create rules and gives you tips on what's behind the technical jargon.
With real-time protection, you will be notified immediately when the application grants permission to send data to the Internet. Use the different modes to switch between maximum security or comfort -...
</description></item><item><title>Download Pepakura Designer 6.1.5</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 18:09:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pepakura-designer-748.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pepakura-designer-748.html
</guid><description>
Pepakura Designer is software to create 2D models, 3D quick, easy and developed in Japan. Pepakura Designer helps easily design the template paper craft by importing data 3D model. No special knowledge is required to model papercraft. All you have to do is prepare the 3D model. You can use some software 3DCG released from other developers to make the 3D models for unfolding.
Pepakura Designer - Create model 2D 3D
Pepakura Designer to create the form of 2D images that you can share it...
</description></item><item><title>Download Scientific Toolworks Understand 7.2 Build 1244</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 18:08:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-scientific-toolworks-understand-1532.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-scientific-toolworks-understand-1532.html
</guid><description>
Scientific Toolworks Understand is a tool of static analysis to management, measurement and analysis, ability to program. This tool can measure multiple metrics and give you the clear chart about the indicator code different. For example: number of layers, number of project files, number of methods, number of lines, blank lines, comments, dead code, rate, comment on code, complexity in the cycle and the level of trouble of the code, the level of dependence of code together, the rate of...
</description></item><item><title>Download OneCommander Pro 3.107.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 18:07:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-one-commander-4232.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-one-commander-4232.html
</guid><description>
One Commander is a file manager for Microsoft Windows with function improved user interface and navigation experience, system file and manipulating the files. Utilities use the tree view to sort the folder, subfolders, and files your, make sure that the current location of you always clear. It supports multiple tabs, allowing you to easily switch between them and access the folder you need.
One Commander - a filemanager for Windows
Depending on the format of the files, some files can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sure Cuts A Lot Pro 6.080</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 18:07:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sure-cuts-a-lot-pro-2614.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sure-cuts-a-lot-pro-2614.html
</guid><description>
Sure Cuts A Lot Pro is this program offers you a set of drawing tools and you get a work environment, comprehensive, where you can create interesting shapes and cut them by a special electronic. The intelligent combination of fonts OpenType and TrueType in your system, in conjunction with the library program rich text, photos, and other input, will help you create everything you can imagine.
This app is compatible with hundreds of font style and provide support for various cutting...
</description></item><item><title>Download Imaginando VS 2.0.6</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 18:06:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-imaginando-vs-11117.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-imaginando-vs-11117.html
</guid><description>
Take your music to another dimension with a captivating visual world. VS - Visual Synthesizer makes it easy to represent your sounds optically in a highly customizable way. At the core of Imaginando VS is a set of graphics shaders called materials, which render procedurally generated geometry in real time, based on each material's unique set of parameters. VS comes equipped with 50 beautifully hypnotic materials for you to customize and combine to create mesmerizing performances.
Visual...
</description></item></channel></rss>