<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 20:00:14 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 20:00:14 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Internet Download Manager (IDM) 6.42 Build 50</title><pubDate> Wed, 08 Oct 2025 15:52:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-inetnet-download-manager-161.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-inetnet-download-manager-161.html
</guid><description>
Internet Download Manager is the download acceleration software, the best download support now, it can help you speed up the download up to five times, continue and schedule downloads. The latest version of IDM adds the compatibility of Windows 10 and Windows 11, it has supported all current popular browsers such as Internet Explorer, Mozilla Firefox, Opera, Google Chrome, ..
Download IDM with the latest version on taiwebs.com making it easy to download and manage your downloaded files...
</description></item><item><title>Download Google Chrome 141.0.7390.66</title><pubDate> Wed, 08 Oct 2025 15:52:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-chrome-1012.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-chrome-1012.html
</guid><description>
Google Chrome web browser is the most used today. Support surf the web, listen to music, watch movies, play web game effective no jerky lag with the internet connection stable. When you are surfing the web or performing an important task, whether it is operation big or small, work or entertainment, then Chrome has the smart features and the speed you need to make, create and explore on the net.
The latest version of Google Chrome is the third 114. But we are providing for users Google...
</description></item><item><title>Download FastStone Capture 11.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 08 Oct 2025 15:51:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-faststone-capture-2044.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-faststone-capture-2044.html
</guid><description>
FastStone Capture is a screen capture tool and screen video recording, powerful, lightweight, yet full-featured. FastStone Capture that allows you to easily capture and annotate anything on the screen including windows, objects, menus, full screen, rectangular area / freedom / fixed as well as scrolling the window / web page. It also allows you to record all the activity on the screen, including changes on the screen, speech from microphone, mouse movement and click on the video file is...
</description></item><item><title>Download Perfectly Clear WorkBench 4.8.0.2858</title><pubDate> Wed, 08 Oct 2025 15:50:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfectly-clear-workbench-6892.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfectly-clear-workbench-6892.html
</guid><description>
Perfectly Clear Workbench is an application that uses image editing libraries Perfectly Clear by Athentech and is provided to demonstrate the capabilities of the Perfectly Clear processing libraries, which recognize faces and allow quick export of processing settings for use.
One of the key features in Workbench is the ability to "export to API" when saving a Preset. This allows you to make image edits in Workbench and adjust the settings to suit your editing style and needs. You can...
</description></item><item><title>Download IDM Retail 6.42 Build 50</title><pubDate> Wed, 08 Oct 2025 15:50:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-internet-download-manager-retail-3609.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-internet-download-manager-retail-3609.html
</guid><description>
IDM - Internet Download Manager Retail is a reliable utility and high efficiency will help you to increase your download speed and manage download at better. The program allows you to easily schedule, pause and resume downloads with a single click. Moreover, the application provides error resilience robust and can restart the download at the interrupted or broken. You can restore the download is interrupted due to network problems, lost connections, unexpected power outages, computer...
</description></item><item><title>Download Notepad++ 8.8.6 + Portable</title><pubDate> Wed, 08 Oct 2025 15:49:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-notepad-1062.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-notepad-1062.html
</guid><description>
Notepad++ is software editor programming editor and edit source code support on Windows platform, working with many other programming languages like ASP, PHP, Java, C#, Python, Jsp... Notepad++ is a source code editor is many programmers choice with many functions than men of it is Notepad.
Notepad++ - tool editor programming
Notepad++ has many features, simple interface, and can combine with many programming languages different. Notepad++ supports you to automatically perform various...
</description></item><item><title>Download Marmoset Toolbag 5.02 (5022)</title><pubDate> Wed, 08 Oct 2025 15:48:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-marmoset-toolbag-1352.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-marmoset-toolbag-1352.html
</guid><description>
Marmoset Toolbag is a real-time rendering strong providing editing documents, editing, animation and the rendered graphics. The program brings a necessary tool for 3D rendering, editing, animation, providing all the tools you need to create images / videos not nearly as practical and display the artwork of your best light.
Marmoset Toolbag - rendering and graphics editing
The features of Marmoset Toolbag
	Tools build professional
	Enjoy the whole new system to enter and collage,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tor Browser 14.5.8</title><pubDate> Wed, 08 Oct 2025 15:48:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tor-browser-1833.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tor-browser-1833.html
</guid><description>
Tor Browser also has full name is Tor Browser Bundle is a web browser give you ability to access the internet safety and security your personal information as well as sensitive documents absolutely. By Tor Browser Bundle will automatically change the IP address on the machine to hide the identity when surfing the web. Tor Browser is free web browser full-featured basic and advanced allows you to leverage the Tor network anonymously without need to make any configuration changes or install...
</description></item><item><title>Download Dropbox 234.4.5591</title><pubDate> Wed, 08 Oct 2025 15:47:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dropbox-1313.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dropbox-1313.html
</guid><description>
Dropbox on taiwebs.com is free tool, the data synchronization across multiple PC become easier than never before: after installation, all what you have to do is enter your name, email address and password before opening the folder My Dropbox. If you install the software on a different computer, Dropbox will reflect the content of the online storage. So you exchange any data between the different computer is connected to Dropbox account. In addition the client is installed on the computer,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Blue Iris 5.9.9.72</title><pubDate> Wed, 08 Oct 2025 15:46:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blue-iris-5656.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blue-iris-5656.html
</guid><description>
Blue Iris is professional surveillance software that allows you to view and record up to 64 cameras (IP cameras, web cameras, DVR / CCTV based cameras) simultaneously and is compatible with the vast majority of IP camera brands. and DVR. Besides. It takes advantage of H.264 video compression that allows you to save hard drive space and reduce bandwidth consumption. Use Blue Iris to turn your existing Windows PC into a full featured professional video surveillance system. Additional...
</description></item><item><title>Download FastCopy Pro 5.11.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 08 Oct 2025 15:46:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fastcopy-pro-9404.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fastcopy-pro-9404.html
</guid><description>
FastCopy Pro is file copying and synchronization software designed to provide faster and more efficient file transfer operations than native file copying tools in operating system. It provides various features and optimizations to enhance the speed and reliability of file copying.
It can copy/delete unicode and more than MAX_PATH(260byte) pathname files. Automatically, after copy source and copy destination are HDD under the same physical HDD or evaluated, it will work as follows. Diff...
</description></item><item><title>Download TunnelBear 4.15.0.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 08 Oct 2025 15:45:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tunnelbear-4601.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tunnelbear-4601.html
</guid><description>
TunnelBear is a VPN app for the Internet connection to help you protect your identity, allow you to select the IP address that author for you to easily access other Internet services. The purpose of TunnelBear is to help you add an additional layer of security to the data communication occurs between the PC and a remote server by using the service anonymous to encrypt information. With the help of it you can navigate on the Internet without having to worry that your data can be blocked by...
</description></item><item><title>Download Shutter Encoder 19.5</title><pubDate> Wed, 08 Oct 2025 15:45:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-shutter-encoder-6837.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-shutter-encoder-6837.html
</guid><description>
Shutter Encoder is an easy-to-use program to convert, edit and encode images, videos, audio files and more. Shutter Encoder is a video, audio and image converter based on FFmpeg and other great tools. It has been designed by video editors to be as accessible and effective as possible.
Features of Shutter Encoder:
	Cut without re-encoding, Replace Audio, Rewind, Edit, Merge, Extract, Subtitle, Insert Video
	Audio Converter: WAV, AIFF, FLAC, MP3, AAC, AC3, OPUS, OGG
	Edit codecs: DNxHD,...
</description></item><item><title>Download StartAllBack 3.9.16.5322</title><pubDate> Wed, 08 Oct 2025 15:45:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-startallback-6857.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-startallback-6857.html
</guid><description>
With the official release of Windows 11, chances are that most of you want to try it out. As the name suggests, StartAllBack is a small, lightweight tool that can help you enjoy the power of the new operating system while keeping the look and feel, especially because main work area, desktop of Windows 7, Windows 10 as taskbars and start menu styles.
StartAllBack is specially designed for Windows 11 and will not work on any older operating systems. If you want to get the start menu back...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cloudflare WARP 2025.8.779.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 08 Oct 2025 15:44:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cloudflare-warp-12256.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cloudflare-warp-12256.html
</guid><description>
Cloudflare WARP is a free application developed by Cloudflare that provides a secure and private connection to the internet. The app acts as a Virtual Private Network (VPN) service, encrypting users' internet traffic and routing it through Flare's global network. Cloudflare Zero Trust replaces legacy security perimeters with Cloudflare's global network, making the Internet faster and more secure for teams around the world. Consult our reference architecture to learn how to evolve your...
</description></item><item><title>Download Monkeys Audio 11.56</title><pubDate> Wed, 08 Oct 2025 15:44:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-monkeys-audio-949.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-monkeys-audio-949.html
</guid><description>
Monkey\'s Audio is software that compresses digital music without loss of quality. Supports high quality WAV files and CD ripping. Monkeys Audio will compress .wav tracks into .ape files to reduce their size without loss of sound quality, decompress .ape, convert files, check file integrity and manage tags.
Unlike traditional methods like MP3 and OGG, which permanently remove quality to save space, Monkey\'s Audio only creates perfect copies with the same sound quality as the originals....
</description></item><item><title>Download Software Companions GerbView 11.30.0.630</title><pubDate> Wed, 08 Oct 2025 15:44:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-software-companions-gerbview-1484.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-software-companions-gerbview-1484.html
</guid><description>
GerbView is a file, advanced, but easy to use, convert, print, and view files HPGL, HPGL / 2, Excellon and raster. It supports both RS274D and RS274X. You can use this software to convert the old format and RS274D standard to the new RS274X have default data. Gerbview is used to represent and illustrate the intricate design of you.
Software Companions GerbView - conversion, printing, and viewing HPGL, HPGL / 2, Excellon
You don't need to wait for rendered images to see the picture of...
</description></item><item><title>Download XYplorer (32 Bit) 27.20.0100</title><pubDate> Wed, 08 Oct 2025 15:43:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-portable-12066.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-portable-12066.html
</guid><description>
XYplorer Portable is a file management software application that provides a comprehensive set of features for organizing and managing files and folders on your computer. This is a portable version of XYplorer that you can run directly from a portable storage device, such as a USB drive, without installation.
XYplorer Portable Features
	File Management: XYplorer Portable provides a two-window interface, allowing you to view and work with two folders at the same time. It provides easy...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wing IDE Pro 11.0.6</title><pubDate> Wed, 08 Oct 2025 15:42:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wing-ide-pro-2080.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wing-ide-pro-2080.html
</guid><description>
Wing IDE Pro is a integrated development environment to create applications using the Python language. Wing IDE Pro provides a code editor professional, in which you can use the keyboard shortcuts vi and emacs, auto-complete code re-structure, follow up calls, reminders, contextual. A code debugger graphics to debug locally and remotely, an interface to version control system, a test unit, a search tool flexibility available.
Wing IDE Pro - programming language Python
Features of Wing...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tray Weather 1.36.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 08 Oct 2025 15:42:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tray-weather-7091.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tray-weather-7091.html
</guid><description>
Tray Weather is a simple application to retrieve and display weather information for a given geographical location in a small dialog box and in the Windows OS system tray. Weather and map information is obtained from OpenWeatherMap. To get weather information from OpenWeatherMap you need to register on their website and enter the given API Key in Tray Weather configuration dialog.
when executed, the application will reside in the system tray, showing the current weather icon. Tooltip...
</description></item><item><title>Download FastCopy 5.11.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 08 Oct 2025 15:41:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fastcopy-2525.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fastcopy-2525.html
</guid><description>
FastCopy - application copy data super fast, is a tool perfect replacement for copy default of windows. FastCopy is a tool that gives you the great utility with the ability to increase speed copy data files up to 4MB/sec. In particular, FastCopy perform copy data without interruption by ignoring the file error.
After launch, you will see a small window with the necessary parameters, if you go to settings, then there is a list of options impressive.To start the copy, you just need to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Room Arranger 10.2.1.733 Beta</title><pubDate> Wed, 08 Oct 2025 15:41:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-room-arranger-3779.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-room-arranger-3779.html
</guid><description>
Room Arranger is a 3D application lets you easily plan for the room, office or his apartment just a few mouse clicks. The application comes with a simple interface will significantly simplify your work. You can draw many kinds of objects and items to create furniture of your own. This app also includes a library of object rich.
Software Room Arranger enables you to view your project in 3D form. You can also upload the 3D scene interact on your blog or your website. The application uses...
</description></item><item><title>Download XenoDream Jux 4.700</title><pubDate> Wed, 08 Oct 2025 15:40:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xenodream-jux-3953.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xenodream-jux-3953.html
</guid><description>
XenoDream Jux is a tool fractal for the 2D Julia and Mandelbrot. It includes a variety of recipes. It has color effects and beautiful lighting. It is very easy to use. No recipe editor or script. There are many possible ways to color fractals Mandelbrot / Julia. XenoDream Jux has the integration method is selected because of the simplicity, flexibility and aesthetics of them. You can use color alone, or modify it with lighting effects market height. XenoDream Jux can add the light effect...
</description></item><item><title>Download KS DB Merge Tools for MySQL 1.23.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 08 Oct 2025 15:40:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ks-db-merge-tools-for-mysql-12756.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ks-db-merge-tools-for-mysql-12756.html
</guid><description>
KS DB Merge Tools for MySQL is a distinct and incorporated search engine that is easy to use for the MySQL and MariaDB database.
Main features
	Comparison of both schema and data
	Quick filter to display all/new/changed
	Unity of changes in both directions
	Light GUI for Windows, command line for Windows and Linux
	Free version with basic features, available for commercial use. No credit cards, no registration, no advertisements, no hidden telemetry.
The supported DBMS, MySQL...
</description></item><item><title>Download Clean Media Player 2025.10.7.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 08 Oct 2025 15:39:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-clean-media-player-12416.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-clean-media-player-12416.html
</guid><description>
If you've ever been offended by profanity in a movie, chances are you'll want the censored version of the movie. However, until the director decides to release it, you still have the option of muting unwanted scenes or editing the subtitles manually, if you are able to do so. The application mutes and displays subtitles without offensive words and phrases. Customize the profanity filter to your preferences. Skip inappropriate scenes by selecting their start and end times.
Clean Media...
</description></item></channel></rss>