<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 03:35:15 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 03:35:15 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Blender 4.5.4</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 00:16:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blender-3017.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blender-3017.html
</guid><description>
Blender has a tool that new and very powerful, whose name is Ciking provides the ability to display extremely impressive and extremely realistic.
Features of Blender
	- Feature button support complete
	- The ball exactly on the physical side, SSS and translucency
	- Support languages open for coding the ball unique
Blender - The software-rendered optical
Tool output integration provides:
	- The GPU and CPU
	- Preview options view real-time
	- Support light HDR
	- The license...
</description></item><item><title>Download FurMark 2.10.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 23:41:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-furmark-1718.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-furmark-1718.html
</guid><description>
FurMark is free software to help check the operation of the computer graphics card at the same time can emulator the situation, unplanned incidents of the CPU, the video card to you have how to handle best. FurMark allows you to set resolutions that card check will pass directly, you can perform both in full-screen mode and window, there are many parameters smoothing, in general, have enough parameters, you just need to artfully place them and you can immediately proceed to check out. If...
</description></item><item><title>Download NVIDIA App 11.0.5.420</title><pubDate> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 23:35:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nvidia-app-12646.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nvidia-app-12646.html
</guid><description>
NVIDIA App is an indispensable companion for PC gamers and creators. Make sure your PC is always updated with the latest NVIDIA drivers and technology. Optimize your games and apps with the new unified GPU control center, capture your favorite moments with powerful recording tools through in-game overlays, and explore new tools and features. Latest NVIDIA software.
The program consists of two main parts
	Game Ready Drivers: GeForce Game Ready Drivers are fine-tuned in collaboration...
</description></item><item><title>Download W10Privacy 5.3.0.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 23:34:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-w10privacy-2956.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-w10privacy-2956.html
</guid><description>
W10Privacy is a program lightweight and simple application that allows you to easily and quickly configure the privacy settings in system Windows its 10. Typically these options can be configured directly from the operating system, but they are hidden in some menu that the user can not normally access easily.
W10Privacy - Configure the options the right to privacy in Windows
The application will display the settings available clear, allowing you to configure the desired options...
</description></item><item><title>Download Revo Registry Cleaner Pro 2.0.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 23:30:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-revo-registry-cleaner-pro-12750.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-revo-registry-cleaner-pro-12750.html
</guid><description>
Revo Registry Cleaner Pro provides complete solutions to advanced Registry cleaning. It uses more than 15 separate scanning categories to identify and completely delete invaluable and redundant registry items that can slow down your system performance. You can customize the cleaning process by specifying the items including and the main exclusion, allowing a more appropriate approach to maintain the integrity of the registration book. In addition, Revo Registry Cleaner has four flexible...
</description></item><item><title>Download Fast Video Downloader 4.0.0.77</title><pubDate> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 23:29:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fast-video-downloader-2619.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fast-video-downloader-2619.html
</guid><description>
Fast Video Downloader is a support program download quick video of genuine FastPcTools. ast Video Downloader is an easy to use program that allows you to download desired videos from a number of sites online storage. I think that I will not reveal secret if they write that most of the sites have video archives do not contain the ability to download videos and sometimes that's very necessary. This is when the same program is rescue, this allows you to save videos from the archive page as...
</description></item><item><title>Download reaConverter Pro 8.0.150</title><pubDate> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 23:28:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html
</guid><description>
reaConverter Pro is software image processing feature with batch conversion and image editing periodically becomes simple. eaConverter also provide command line utilities allow you to process images automatically, thus helping you shorten the time for other work.
reaConverter Pro integrated powerful tool of Uber with many great features. It provides advanced solutions to process and adjust images. Management of the conversion process the base image with the latest version of...
</description></item><item><title>Download O&amp;amp;O ShutUp10++ 2.1.1015</title><pubDate> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 23:28:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-shutup10-1535.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-shutup10-1535.html
</guid><description>
O&amp;amp;O ShutUp10 is software that puts you in full control of today's latest Windows 10 and Windows 11 features, it's up to you to decide what information to pass on Windows 10 or Windows 11. Using a simple user interface, this program disables the parts of Windows 10 and Windows 11 that don't want to receive and send your data. The program is completely free and requires no installation, and once downloaded, you can run it immediately. The program does not install adware and spam software...
</description></item><item><title>Download DroidKit 2.3.7.20251028</title><pubDate> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 23:27:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-droidkit-6578.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-droidkit-6578.html
</guid><description>
DroidKit is data recovery software for your mobile device, it will quickly scan your phone memory and save photos, WhatsApp chats and files, messages Messages, contacts and more essential data up to 13 categories, covering almost everything you need every day. All Android phones and tablets are supported. Without rooting your device. No tech skills required. No need to wait many days. You can get back what you've lost with just a few simple clicks, instantly.
Besides, DroidKit also has...
</description></item><item><title>Download TeamViewer 15.71.4 + Portable</title><pubDate> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 23:26:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-teamviewer-528.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-teamviewer-528.html
</guid><description>
TeamViewer is software that functions to connect and control the remote computer, the ability to connect with any system anywhere from all over the place. This is a support tool users is very convenient. TeamViewer to help users control remote computer becomes much more simple, help you interact and collaborate with others in the exchange and share of information, instruction manual, application software or fix the computer.
TeamViewer as a revolution of computer science. when you have...
</description></item><item><title>Download Draftable Desktop 25.10.300</title><pubDate> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 23:25:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-draftable-desktop-3749.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-draftable-desktop-3749.html
</guid><description>
Draftable Desktop is comparison tool documents the fastest. Compare over 300 pages in a few seconds. Draftable Desktop 2.0 is now available - faster and stronger than ever! See all the changes in your documents, locally and online. Take your work to the next level. Compare secret and private do not use the internet and your documents never leave your computer. Specifically, Draftable Desktop compatible with .xls, .xlsx, .xlsxm. With Office 2013, 2016 or 365, you can compare text in...
</description></item><item><title>Download AskAdmin 2.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 23:25:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-askadmin-743.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-askadmin-743.html
</guid><description>
AskAdmin is also known with the name is to appadmin. Software support user application blocking on your computer to prevent others can access, such as Microsoft Store, windows, Google Chrome, App integration (UWP), Skype or File as bat, cmd, reg, data. The program has a password to prevent blocked programs are blocked can easily unlock the user.
AskAdmin - Block program on the computer
The features of AskAdmin
	Blocked software on the computer to prevent unauthorized access.
	Use a...
</description></item><item><title>Download Flyby11 1.41.581</title><pubDate> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 23:24:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-flyby11-12467.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-flyby11-12467.html
</guid><description>
Flyby11 is a simple patcher that removes annoying restrictions that prevent you from installing Windows 11 (24H2) on unsupported hardware. Do you have an old PC? No TPM, Secure Boot or your processor is not supported? Flyby11 allows you to install Windows 11 24H2. There are no complicated steps. Just run the tool and you'll be running Windows 11 on your outdated machine in no time.
Technical overview
Flyby11 takes advantage of a feature of the Windows 11 setup process that uses the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Flyoobe 1.41.581</title><pubDate> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 23:24:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oobelux-13956.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oobelux-13956.html
</guid><description>
Flyoobe was born out of the frustration many users felt with the Windows 11 setup experience. Whether it was the mandatory online account, the endless "Next, next, next..." screens, or the incomplete configuration options when you finally reached the desktop, the current setup lacked focus on what users really wanted.
Why choose Flyoobe?
	Simplifies the Windows 11 setup process right out of the box.
	Allows easy local account creation without need to hunt for hidden options.
	Includes...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ashampoo Photo Converter 3.0.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 23:23:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-photo-converter-14004.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-photo-converter-14004.html
</guid><description>
Ashampoo Photo Converter is a Windows software tool designed for efficient image conversion and editing. The software supports more than 18 image formats and includes popular formats such as BMP, GIF, JPG, PNG, PDF and many more. The software can process individual photos or entire folders in batch mode, suitable for processing large photo collections.
Ashampoo Photo Converter Features
	Extensive format support allows conversion between multiple file types.
	Batch processing for...
</description></item><item><title>Download AMS SmartSHOW 3D 26.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 23:23:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ams-software-smartshow-3d-deluxe-6471.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ams-software-smartshow-3d-deluxe-6471.html
</guid><description>
SmartSHOW 3D Deluxe  is a smart photo presentation software with professional ability. Revolutionary 3D tools inside this program make professional animation tools available to all types of users. This program is ideal for both novices with no experience in creating slideshows or taking photos and for experienced enthusiasts looking for new ways to express themselves.
With SmartSHOW 3D Deluxe, you'll easily create and edit slides to create your own animations, including amazing 3D...
</description></item><item><title>Download Revo Uninstaller 2.6.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 23:22:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-revo-uninstaller-free-6752.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-revo-uninstaller-free-6752.html
</guid><description>
Revo Uninstaller is a freeware that helps you to uninstall software and remove unwanted programs easily. Revo Uninstaller acts as a replacement and complement to the built-in functionality of Windows by running the built-in uninstaller for the program first and then scanning for leftover data, making it obsolete. become your best option when it comes to removing stubborn pieces completely. Programs, temporary files, and other unnecessary program data are left behind after the standard...
</description></item><item><title>Download HTMLPad 2025 v18.4.0.270</title><pubDate> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 23:21:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-htmlpad-2997.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-htmlpad-2997.html
</guid><description>
HTMLPad is a HTML editor, JavaScript, and CSS smart, be so many experts and learners in over 50 countries trust. Full of features and comprehensive options, HTMLPad allows you to make, edit, re-use, verify, navigate and use the HTML code, CSS and JavaScript faster and simpler than ever. HTMLPad include CSS studio and editor JavaScript strong bring you the best value.
HTMLPad - editor, HTML, CSS, JavaScript
Features of HTMLPad
	Quick and lightweight loads much faster than any other...
</description></item><item><title>Download 2BrightSparks SyncBackPro 11.3.124</title><pubDate> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 23:20:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-2brightsparks-syncbackpro-812.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-2brightsparks-syncbackpro-812.html
</guid><description>
SyncBackPro is a backup utility, restore and synchronize professional and enhanced with many advanced features. With SyncBackPro you can copy any file whether it is locked or is open, which usually isn't possible to copy in these conditions. But this feature works only on window XP or higher version of window. Backup with SyncBackPro is a process that is very fast and it can handle the number of files is not limited.
2BrightSparks SyncBackPro - backup, restore data
The main features of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Blumentals Rapid PHP 2025 v18.4.0.270</title><pubDate> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 23:19:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blumentals-rapid-php-2996.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blumentals-rapid-php-2996.html
</guid><description>
Blumentals Rapid PHP is an editor PHP powerful and fast mixing function of the Environment integrated development PHP complete along with the speed of the Notepad. This is a comprehensive software that will support you coding CSS, HTML, PHP, JavaScript and other programming languages. Rapid PHP provides a set of advanced tools to validate, reuse, debugging, navigate and format your code. This software allows you to save valuable time and increase productivity by writing code in a way...
</description></item><item><title>Download Opera GX (Gaming Browser) 122.0.5643.178</title><pubDate> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 23:19:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-gx-3170.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-gx-3170.html
</guid><description>
Opera GX is a special version of the Opera browser is built to complement gamers avid. Browser this game comes with the unique features to help users make maximum use of both the game and their browser. Opera GX is built specifically to support the game. This browser includes the unique features to help users have the best experience when gaming and surfing the web.
Opera GX - special browser for gamers
GX Control allows you to set a limit on the level of use RAM, CPU and network where...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sante PACS Server 4.3.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 23:18:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sante-pacs-server-7541.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sante-pacs-server-7541.html
</guid><description>
Sante PACS Server is an HTTP (web) server for DICOM files and a CD/DVD Burn and Print server that offers high performance and reliability at an affordable price. It provides connectivity to all DICOM methods (CT, MR, US, CR, NM, XA, MG, DX, etc.). Reviewing of DICOM images can be done using the Sante PACS Viewer (the system's built-in, full-featured DICOM Viewer). The built-in web server can be used as a free cloud server for DICOM files!
Tools of Sante PACS Server
	The Migration Tool...
</description></item><item><title>Download DBF Converter 7.65</title><pubDate> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 23:18:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbf-converter-6362.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbf-converter-6362.html
</guid><description>
DBF Converter is a common solution for all your DBF format conversion needs. Whenever you need to extract data from the DBF file to CSV, XLS, XLSX, SQL or pure text, the software will provide a simple way to do this with minimal effort.
Features of DBF Converter
	Work with DBF Converter is easy. You specify a DBF file or a directory with DBF files that you want to convert, select the fields and filter out the records you need. Then, just a click to DBF Converter to turn the source...
</description></item><item><title>Download ToDoList 9.1.5.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 23:18:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-todolist-1637.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-todolist-1637.html
</guid><description>
ToDoList is an application note and task management with multiple options, set up help you to easily split and track the progress of the work. Todolist helps millions of people feel in control of their lives more and be the leader in a number of organizations inspired the world to believe. Todolist keep all to-dos of I in one place and perfectly integrated with the other tools that I use. It helps me turn everything faster.
ToDoList - management software job
Every day you have to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Blumentals WeBuilder 2025 v18.4.0.270</title><pubDate> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 23:17:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blumentals-webuilder-1572.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blumentals-webuilder-1572.html
</guid><description>
Blumentals WeBuilder is a powerful app to edit the HTML code, CSS, JavaScript, PHP and ASP in an environment simple and user friendly. WeBuilder is a versatile application for web developers to edit code.
The application Blumentals WeBuilder this supports the programming languages HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, Ruby, Python, ASP, SSI and Perl. The integrated tool of this software allows you to verify, re-use and redirect your code and expand them according to how efficient and complex....
</description></item></channel></rss>