<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 20:00:21 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 20:00:21 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download FBackup 9.9.994</title><pubDate> Mon, 20 Oct 2025 22:54:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fbackup-1834.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fbackup-1834.html
</guid><description>
FBackup enables you to backup files and important folders on the hard drive locally or outside (not memory card, USB drive) or network drive. You can create multiple backup sets and schedule them to run automatically at the times defined in advance. The backups can be compressed into a ZIP file to be stored or reproduced in copy form files standard.
Modern interface
The program interface is quite easy to use, FBackup supports multi-language and provided the free utility, can also be...
</description></item><item><title>Download Kaspersky Lab Products Remover 1.0.5562.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 20 Oct 2025 22:54:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kaspersky-lab-products-remover-2207.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kaspersky-lab-products-remover-2207.html
</guid><description>
Kaspersky Lab Products Remover is a mobile gadget from a famous developer will allow you to completely remove all products of Kaspersky Lab. Working with the program as simple as possible, we started, enter code from image, then you can choose the product with the pen or selecting them about what the program found.
Kaspersky Lab Products Remover - Uninstall the software of Kaspersky Lab
I think won't mean anything when writing any program is support, look carefully at the screenshot...
</description></item><item><title>Download PrivaZer Pro Donors 4.0.113.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 20 Oct 2025 19:07:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-privazer-donors-198.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-privazer-donors-198.html
</guid><description>
PrivaZer Donors  cleans and removes filth traces from the system. Intensive cleaning of unwanted traces of what you've done, viewed, downloaded, deleted, etc. Take ownership of your security and freedom - Free up disk space. Keep your PC snug and secure !!!
With one click, PrivaZer can safely clean: Internet browsers, Index.dat, Cookies, Tor Cookies, Flash Cookies, Silverlight Cookies, DOM Storing, IndexedDB, AppCache Registry, RAM, Pagefile.sys and Hiberfil.sys files.  PrivaZer  can...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDF Suite Pro + OCR 20.0.23.21526</title><pubDate> Mon, 20 Oct 2025 19:06:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-suite-ocr-6691.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-suite-ocr-6691.html
</guid><description>
PDF Suite is the software that provides the most necessary functions such as reading, creating and editing basic PDF. You will be able to open, save, print and mark any PDF files using PDF Suite. You can see the presentation, CV, the Book of Electronics and many other electronic documents. PDF Suite has a modern conversion tool that can transfer any files that can be printed into a fully readable PDF document 100%. Convert Word, Excel, PowerPoint and other MS Office documents to PDF...
</description></item><item><title>Download Renee PDF Aide 2025.10.19.185</title><pubDate> Mon, 20 Oct 2025 19:05:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-renee-pdf-aide-2042.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-renee-pdf-aide-2042.html
</guid><description>
Renee PDF Aide is versatile software support to convert and edit PDF like you are edit Word, Excel, Power Point (PPT), Image, HTML,. PDF is the file format most popular commercial but difficult to edit. That's how Renee PDF support: it helps users to convert PDF documents into files that can edit like Word, Excel, Power Point (PPT), Image, HTML, EPUB and txt document. In addition, Renee PDF Aide is equipped with cutting-edge OCR technology can recognize the characters in image PDF or...
</description></item><item><title>Download Advanced Renamer Commercial 4.18</title><pubDate> Mon, 20 Oct 2025 19:04:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-renamer-2647.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-renamer-2647.html
</guid><description>
Advanced Renamer is a program to rename multiple files and folders at the same time. By configuring the method name change, the name can be manipulated in many different ways. It's easy to set up a batch job using multiple methods on a large number of files. 14 different modes allow you to change the name, attributes and timestamp of the file in once. The file can also be copied or moved to new location based on information in the file.
The program can rename files in many different ways,...
</description></item><item><title>Download AB Download Manager 1.7.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 20 Oct 2025 19:04:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ab-download-manager-12399.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ab-download-manager-12399.html
</guid><description>
With this application, you can easily download files from anywhere. Enjoy fast, free downloads with seamless browser extension support. It is built to be a desktop application that allows you to manage and organize your downloads better than before.
AB Download Manager features
	Simple and modern UI: Simple UI and dark mode by default
	Faster download speeds: Download files using multiple connections to increase your download speed by up to 500%
	Download Queue: Create and manage your...
</description></item><item><title>Download BleachBit 5.0.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 20 Oct 2025 19:03:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bleachbit-1219.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bleachbit-1219.html
</guid><description>
BleachBit is software system cleanup frees hard disk space and speed up your computer performance. BleachBit quickly frees disk space. When your information is only your business, BleachBit protects your privacy. With BleachBit you can free cache, delete cookies, clear Internet history, delete temporary files, delete logs, and remove the garbage that you don't even know were there. Designed for Linux systems and Windows, it wipe thousands of apps including Firefox, Internet Explorer, Adobe...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinTools.net Professional / Premium / Classic 25.11.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 20 Oct 2025 19:03:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wintoolsnet-304.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wintoolsnet-304.html
</guid><description>
WinTools.net is an optimal tool working performance of the operating system and delete the unnecessary program from the hard drive and control the start-up process of Windows.
WinTools.net integrates many useful tools, to support increased processing speed and ability, stable operation for the computer include: Clean Uninstaller, Scan Files, Scan Registry, Start Up, Tweak UI, Net Tweaker, The Privacy. Scan Files are often used to scan the hard drive periodically, search for junk files or...
</description></item><item><title>Download Balabolka 2.15.0.908</title><pubDate> Mon, 20 Oct 2025 19:02:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-balaboka-142.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-balaboka-142.html
</guid><description>
Balabolka is a text-to-speech (TTS) program. It can read text on your screen in a human-like voice. You can use Balabolka to listen to text from a variety of file formats, convert text to spoken audio files, and adjust speech parameters such as speed and pitch. It is often used for accessibility purposes, helping people who have difficulty reading or multi-tasking by listening to text while doing other activities. Balabolka supports multiple languages and uses different TTS engines,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Drive SnapShot 1.50.0.1748</title><pubDate> Mon, 20 Oct 2025 19:02:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-drive-snapshot-701.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-drive-snapshot-701.html
</guid><description>
Drive SnapShot is a backup software, Restore disk, including operating system, installed programs, your data and all security attributes - while windows is running and you continue to work. With Drive SnapShot you backup partition or hard drive and it can also create disk image of your system. If a disaster occurs (a virus, trojan or the fixed hard disk), the recover complete and accurate your system will be able to accomplish after only a few minutes. The image file can be mounted as...
</description></item><item><title>Download Directory Opus Pro 13.19</title><pubDate> Mon, 20 Oct 2025 19:01:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-opus-pro-779.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-opus-pro-779.html
</guid><description>
Directory Opus Pro is a software replacement for Explorer with traditional strength and function more than any manager other files. Directory Opus Pro full support for high DPI screen (for example 4K and 5K) with the rename dialog is redesigned, with new features. Besides being a recording macro only allows you to perform mass renaming complex that don't need regular expressions. In addition, Directory Opus Pro also enhances the ability to script.Better handling of renaming recursive and...
</description></item><item><title>Download EditPlus 6.0 Build 779</title><pubDate> Mon, 20 Oct 2025 19:01:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-editplus-338.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-editplus-338.html
</guid><description>
EditPlus is editor text, editor, HTML and editor program for Windows. EditPlus works as a text editor as well as editor, PHP editor, HTML, editor, Java viewer and Hex. It supports syntax highlighting for many languages, such as HTML, CSS, Java, PHP, C / C ++, Perl, and Python, and can act as a web browser to preview the HTML page. EditPlus also provides some other useful features, such as auto completion, code folding, spell checking, search and replace, keyboard shortcuts, custom and HTML...
</description></item><item><title>Download Zortam Mp3 Media Studio Pro 33.40</title><pubDate> Mon, 20 Oct 2025 19:00:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zortam-mp3-media-studio-pro-135.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zortam-mp3-media-studio-pro-135.html
</guid><description>
Zortam Mp3 Media Studio Pro brings you rich processing tools music includes extract and convert music from CD to Mp3 format, edit, music cards, music download....You can also create discs CD high-quality music, with Zortam Mp3 Media Studio search music files duplicated to remove them from the system, rename music files, switch back and forth between formats.
Zortam Mp3 Media Studio Pro is rated as perfect software in the processing of the MP3 files on the computer. First of all, you can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Balsamiq Wireframes 4.8.6</title><pubDate> Mon, 20 Oct 2025 19:00:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-balsamiq-wireframes-3918.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-balsamiq-wireframes-3918.html
</guid><description>
Balsamiq Wireframes is a tool to create frame user interface fidelity low quickly, reproduces experience sketching on a notepad or white board, but use the computer. Balsamiq Wireframes really force you to focus on structure and content, avoid long discussions about color and detail will come later in the process. Wireframes is FAST: you will create more ideas, so you can throw away the bad ones and discover the best solution.
Balsamiq Wireframes - Create frame app and Website
The...
</description></item><item><title>Download Text Editor Pro 34.2.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 20 Oct 2025 18:59:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-text-editor-pro-800.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-text-editor-pro-800.html
</guid><description>
Text Editor Pro is software to handle text, HTML, Perl, Ruby, or Fortran with features syntax highlighting, professional. Text Editor provides syntax highlighting for over 50 scripts and has a simple interface and easy access. In addition, the Text Editor Pro also supports more than 50 programming languages like C ++, COBOL, graph DOT, DSP, DWScript, Fortran, Foxpro, Java, Perl, Python, Ruby, SQL and many other languages.
Text Editor Pro - text Processing professional
The software can...
</description></item><item><title>Download XMedia Recode 3.6.1.9</title><pubDate> Mon, 20 Oct 2025 18:59:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xmedia-recode-919.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xmedia-recode-919.html
</guid><description>
XMedia Recode is software to change the quality for video files on windows operating system, it has the ability to change quality, video format. XMedia Recode supports the format conversion such as 3GP, 3GPP, 3GPP2, AAC, AC3, AIFF, AMR, ASF, AU, AVI, DIVX, DTS, DVR-MS, FLV, H. 261, H. 263, H. 264, M4A, M1V, M2V, M4V, MKV.
Parameters advanced
The user can step into the more advanced and modify bitrate, frame interval the frame rate, modes, speed control and many other settings regarding...
</description></item><item><title>Download Security Task Manager 3.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 20 Oct 2025 18:59:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-security-task-manager-493.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-security-task-manager-493.html
</guid><description>
Security Task Manager is management software task program window for you to know the performance is the use of the software. Security Task Manager provides ratings, risk, security, process description, file path, chart, CPU usage, start time, hidden functions embedded. The software also lets you know the ability to the process is the spyware potential malware, Trojan or keylogger.
Security Task Manager also delete traces of Internet activity and your computer, stop monitoring keyboard...
</description></item><item><title>Download 3DCoat 2025.11</title><pubDate> Mon, 20 Oct 2025 18:58:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-3d-coat-1269.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-3d-coat-1269.html
</guid><description>
3D Coat is a computer program that trade for modeling objects of different organic and 3D models low-poly. The app provides a variety of tools allow users to create sculptures, adding topology, create UV maps, texture surface interactions of the model, showing the static and animated round of the pattern.
3D Coat - 3D modeling
The content in the software 3D Coat:
Texture simple and PBR:
	Support drawing drawings top en model, draw the pixel and Ptex
	Rendered physics-based (PBR)...
</description></item><item><title>Download JoyToKey 7.3.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 20 Oct 2025 18:57:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-joytokey-1983.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-joytokey-1983.html
</guid><description>
JoyToKey (or Joy2Key) enables game controller PC simulation input keyboard and mouse for Windows applications and web games can be controlled by the joystick of your favorite! Whenever the buttons and sticks are pressed on the controller, JoyToKey will convert them into keyboard strokes and / or mouse movement to the destination application will act as able to use the keyboard and mouse real. JoyToKey lets create some configuration file, which supports up to 16 joysticks, compatible with...
</description></item><item><title>Download EarthTime 6.30.12</title><pubDate> Mon, 20 Oct 2025 18:57:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-earthtime-185.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-earthtime-185.html
</guid><description>
EarthTime is software that displays the time and date local time of any place in the world. This application has database integration good for 3000 city, users can manually add, download at EarthTime if you want to. EarthTime allows you to install for the time zone and current local time.EarthTime displays the Earth according to the view night and day, you can view the map in full screen mode.
EarthTime
The feature on EarthTime
	EarthTime allows users to interact with visualization...
</description></item><item><title>Download PortScan &amp;amp; Stuff 2.03</title><pubDate> Mon, 20 Oct 2025 18:56:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-portscan-stuff-2430.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-portscan-stuff-2430.html
</guid><description>
PortScan &amp;amp; Stuff is a small utility does not require installation, will help you to easily find all active devices on your network. After the scanning process gateway is started, the utility will display all the open ports for you. In addition, you can get a lot of other useful information. For example: host name, MAC address, FTP, SMTP and other services. PortScan can search the device is connected, can ping your personal computer.
PortScan &amp;amp; Stuff - Scan devices are using the...
</description></item><item><title>Download PrivaZer 4.0.113.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 20 Oct 2025 18:56:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-privazer-66.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-privazer-66.html
</guid><description>
PrivaZer : the program performs the scan is very thorough not only includes the trace downloads like registration, Internet history, cookies, etc but also find the traces of potential in the field of free disk space of you. PrivaZer can permanently delete all traces by using the method of secure erase and also re-establish the sector disk free to 0 to remove all traces from the delete operation earlier. The process of scanning and cleaning the original can spend less time (20-30 minutes),...
</description></item><item><title>Download Typing Instructor Gold 5.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 20 Oct 2025 18:56:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-typing-instructor-gold-8168.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-typing-instructor-gold-8168.html
</guid><description>
Typing Instructor Gold is the most advanced Typing Program available (first released in 2019). Typing Instructor Gold is presented in full screen size and rich colors to provide the ultimate Typing Instructor experience for typists. No other typing guide is more entertaining and educational than it.
Every typing adventure is filled with so much fun and motivation, typists forget that they are learning to type. They will progress in the Adventure by taking lessons, quizzes, typing...
</description></item><item><title>Download Typing Instructor for Kids Gold 3.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 20 Oct 2025 18:51:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-typing-instructor-for-kids-gold-8167.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-typing-instructor-for-kids-gold-8167.html
</guid><description>
Typing Instructor for Kids Gold is a software used for typing training for children to learn to type or improve typing skills. Teach keyboard basics in one of over 10 age- and skill-appropriate typing plans. It is available in 2 world languages, English or Spanish.
Features of Typing Instructor for Kids Gold
	Updated to latest version to work on Windows 11, 10 and 8
	Basic typing instructor adventure for kids in fullscreen size and rich colors
	The Island Adventure theme motivates...
</description></item></channel></rss>