<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 20:05:46 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 20:05:46 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Wifi Password: Wifi Hotspot 1.1.7</title><pubDate> Thu, 31 Jul 2025 19:19:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wifi-hotspot-speed-test-11513.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wifi-hotspot-speed-test-11513.html
</guid><description>
Wifi Hotspot - Wifi Hotspot helps you share internet with other mobile devices and create your own free hotspot. This is a simple and free Wifi Hotspot app for Android that you can use to share Internet with other devices. Instantly turn your phone into a wi fi hotspot with this Wifi Hotspot - Wifi Hotspot application without root. Simple to use and easy to install, this hotspot proxy app will turn your phone into a powerful wifi for mobile monitor transmitter!
Amazing Wifi Hotspot -...
</description></item><item><title>Download Unit Converter Pro 2.6.4</title><pubDate> Thu, 31 Jul 2025 19:19:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-unit-converter-pro-9060.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-unit-converter-pro-9060.html
</guid><description>
Pro Unit Converter is the 6th set of the Smart Tools® collection. This app includes currency exchange rates (money, bitcoin). It has no ads and ads are replaced with useful texts. There are many unit conversion applications on the market. However, most are inconvenient and difficult to use because of poor and complicated user interfaces.
Features of Unit Converter Pro
	Basic: length (distance), area, weight (mass), volume (capacity)
	Life: exchange rates, temperature, time, speed,...
</description></item><item><title>Download EOBD Facile: OBD2 Car Scanner 3.77.1112</title><pubDate> Thu, 31 Jul 2025 19:19:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-eobd-facile-obd2-car-scanner-8698.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-eobd-facile-obd2-car-scanner-8698.html
</guid><description>
Run diagnostics on your car with your Android Smartphone or tablet and discover why the engine light is on... no need to check the manufacturer's manual! Connect the ELM 327 interface to your car's OBD2 port and run the app: you will be able to read engine and transmission error codes and view data from your vehicle in real time.
EOBD Facile features for Android
	View engine and transmission fault codes (also known as DTCs) and see what they mean (over 11,000 definitions...
</description></item><item><title>Download Weather Live 7.8.6 build 393</title><pubDate> Thu, 31 Jul 2025 19:18:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-weather-live-8465.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-weather-live-8465.html
</guid><description>
Weather Live is a weather forecast app for Android devices that provides users with current weather conditions, hourly and daily forecasts, and severe weather warnings. The app has a user-friendly interface that displays weather information in an easy-to-read format. Get live weather forecast, storm radar, current temperature, rain intensity, wind speed, severe weather alerts, rain and snow warnings – all in one with Weather Live.
Live Weather Features
	Weather forecast for many...
</description></item><item><title>Download Reverso Translate and Learn 14.4.0 build 120056</title><pubDate> Thu, 31 Jul 2025 19:18:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-reverso-translate-and-learn-8356.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-reverso-translate-and-learn-8356.html
</guid><description>
Reverso is a comprehensive tool that helps you get high-quality translations and continuously improve your language skills. The best part about the Reverso app? It is available for free. Teachers or translators, students or business professionals, beginners or advanced learners use Reverso to enrich their vocabulary and read, write and speak more accurately and confidently.
Download the Reverso app and you'll have millions of words and expressions at your fingertips, with their...
</description></item><item><title>Download 365Scores: Live Scores &amp;amp; News 14.2.7</title><pubDate> Thu, 31 Jul 2025 19:17:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-365scores-live-scores-news-8220.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-365scores-live-scores-news-8220.html
</guid><description>
365Scores is a sports app that provides users with real-time scores, statistics, and news for many sports including football, basketball, soccer, and more. Some features of the application include:
	Live scores and notifications: 365Scores provides live scores and push notifications for many sports, including football, soccer, basketball, baseball, etc.
	Match statistics: The app includes detailed match statistics such as ball control, number of shots on goal, etc.
	Latest News:...
</description></item><item><title>Download Meteo Weather Widget - Donate 2.8.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 31 Jul 2025 19:17:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-meteo-weather-widget-donate-8623.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-meteo-weather-widget-donate-8623.html
</guid><description>
Meteogram Weather Widget is a weather app that displays the weather in a very detailed way right on your home screen. While many weather apps display the weather forecast in a rather basic way, this app does it by visualizing the forecast in what is called a meteogram. Doing so gives you a much better overview of exactly when it will rain, when the sun will shine, when it will be cloudy.
Meteogram displays the expected temperature and precipitation for the entire forecast period....
</description></item><item><title>Download Handy GPS 43.8</title><pubDate> Thu, 31 Jul 2025 19:17:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-handy-gps-8741.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-handy-gps-8741.html
</guid><description>
The perfect companion for your next outdoor adventure. Search, find, record and return home with handy GPS. This app is a powerful navigation tool designed for outdoor sports such as hiking, backpacking, mountain biking, kayaking, canoeing and horseback riding. It is also useful for surveying, mining, archeology and forestry applications.
This application is simple and works even in the most remote countries because it does not require a network connection. It allows you to work in UTM...
</description></item><item><title>Download WiFi Analyzer 6.0 build 99</title><pubDate> Thu, 31 Jul 2025 19:17:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wifi-analyzer-10225.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wifi-analyzer-10225.html
</guid><description>
Introducing a new way to analyze and optimize your WiFi, Turn your Android device into a WiFi Analyzer! WiFi Analyzer Recommends the best channels and locations for your network. WiFi Analyzer gives you the most useful optimization information to help reduce interference and increase connection speed and stability.
WiFi Analyzer Features
	WiFi optimizer for interference issues
	Channel analyzer for neighboring APs
	Real-time data and distance calculation.
	Signal strength...
</description></item><item><title>Download BetterSleep: Sleep tracker 25.13.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 31 Jul 2025 19:16:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-bettersleep-sleep-tracker-8274.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-bettersleep-sleep-tracker-8274.html
</guid><description>
BetterSleep is a sleep tracking app that helps users track and improve their sleeping habits. The app uses the phone's sensors to track movement and sounds during sleep, then provides users with detailed sleep reports and analysis. It also includes features such as a sleep log, smart alarm, and white noise generation to help users fall asleep and wake up more refreshed. Additionally, BetterSleep allows users to set sleep goals, track their progress, and receive personalized...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ad Blocker Pro 6.5.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 31 Jul 2025 19:15:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ad-blocker-9269.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ad-blocker-9269.html
</guid><description>
Ad Blocker Pro is an ad blocking application with unique features, Helps you surf the web faster, safer and more comfortably with Ad Blocker Pro! With these unique features, you can switch between when you want to use ad blocking and when you don't want to use it smoothly.
	Equipped with unique features not found in other ad blockers!
	One-touch ON/OFF switching function
	You can turn ON/OFF ad block with just one tap from quick panel, widget, notification bar.
Features of Ad Blocker...
</description></item><item><title>Download Music Folder Player Full 3.1.36</title><pubDate> Thu, 31 Jul 2025 19:15:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-music-folder-player-full-10481.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-music-folder-player-full-10481.html
</guid><description>
Music folder player created for people who don't like to see music displayed based on artist, album, track or playlist. If you like to organize your audio tracks in folders, this might be the right player for you.
Full features of Music Folder Player
	Material Design
	Three different home screen widgets (full version only)
	Continue where you left off. Archive for each folder where you left off
	Show folders as a 'flat' list if you have a small collection
	Show folder hierarchy like...
</description></item><item><title>Download Multi Timer StopWatch 2.13.18 build 483</title><pubDate> Thu, 31 Jul 2025 19:15:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-multi-timer-stopwatch-8914.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-multi-timer-stopwatch-8914.html
</guid><description>
Multi Timer is a beautifully designed time management app. Multiple timers can be set, started and run independently at the same time. Stopwatch results can be stored. Use Multi Timer for cooking, sports, machine washing, studying, working, gaming - whatever you like.
Features of Multi Timer StopWatch
	Multiple timers at once: Store the timers you often use for cooking, sports, studying, working, gaming, whatever you want. Start them with just one tap, anytime you need.
	Timer in...
</description></item><item><title>Download AVG Cleaner - Storage Cleaner 25.15.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 31 Jul 2025 19:14:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-avg-cleaner-storage-cleaner-9005.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-avg-cleaner-storage-cleaner-9005.html
</guid><description>
AVG Cleaner is a memory cleaning and optimization application developed by AVG Technologies. It is designed to help users reclaim space on their Android devices by deleting unnecessary files and optimizing system performance.
The app can scan your device for junk files, including temporary files, cache files, and outdated APK files, and help you delete them safely. Additionally, AVG Cleaner can analyze your device's battery consumption and provide suggestions on how to improve your...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mirror Plus - HD Mirror app 4.4.7</title><pubDate> Thu, 31 Jul 2025 19:14:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-mirror-plus-mirror-with-light-8703.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-mirror-plus-mirror-with-light-8703.html
</guid><description>
Mirror Plus is a unique experience. With great camera quality, a beautiful classic design, and easy gesture controls, you'll have the ability to share your best images right in the app. Check your appearance after a few seconds, then freeze the screen and save the photo.
Or go one step further and use our special features:
	The 3D feature captures your appearance from left to right or top to bottom, so you can show off your amazing outfit or hairstyle to your friends!
	Create a...
</description></item><item><title>Download PeakFinder 4.8.46</title><pubDate> Thu, 31 Jul 2025 19:14:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-peakfinder-10050.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-peakfinder-10050.html
</guid><description>
Explore more mountains than any other climber! PeakFinder AR makes it possible… and shows the names of all the mountains and peaks with a 360° panoramic display. This functionality is completely offline - and worldwide! PeakFinder knows more than 650,000 mountain peaks - from Mount Everest to that little hill on the corner.
PeakFinder Features
	Works offline and worldwide
	Includes more than 650,000 peak names
	Install the camera image using a panoramic drawing *
	Display real-time...
</description></item><item><title>Download Smart Launcher 6 ‧ Home Screen 6.5 build 0363</title><pubDate> Thu, 31 Jul 2025 19:13:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-smart-launcher-8412.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-smart-launcher-8412.html
</guid><description>
Smart Launcher is a mobile app that provides users with a customized home screen and app launcher on their Android devices. It includes features like minimalist interface, automatic app sorting, and gesture controls. The app also includes many customizable settings, such as the ability to change the theme, icon size, and screen layout, as well as the ability to create custom categories for the app.
Smart Launcher Features
	Ambient theme: Smart launcher automatically changes theme...
</description></item><item><title>Download Business Calendar 2 Pro 2.53.0 build 253000</title><pubDate> Thu, 31 Jul 2025 19:13:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-business-calendar-8433.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-business-calendar-8433.html
</guid><description>
Business Calendar 2 Pro is the premium version of our popular calendar app. It provides a great overview of your appointments, is easy to use, and gives you powerful tools to plan and schedule your events and tasks.
Features of Business Calendar
Your personal organizer
	calendar, planner and tasks in one app
	6 clearly designed main views: month, week, day, agenda, year and tasks
	popup with live event details in month view
	flexible daily and weekly planning that can be adjusted...
</description></item><item><title>Download 7Fon: Wallpapers &amp;amp; Backgrounds 6.0.79</title><pubDate> Thu, 31 Jul 2025 19:13:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-7fon-wallpapers-4k-pro-11673.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-7fon-wallpapers-4k-pro-11673.html
</guid><description>
7Fon Wallpapers 4K (PRO) Android is a great application for people who love beauty and art. With thousands of high-quality wallpapers, users can find the perfect photos for their phone screen.
This app offers a huge collection of 4K wallpapers from different categories like nature, animals, art, landscapes and more. Users can easily search for wallpapers by topic or keyword, helping them quickly find their favorite photos.
Outstanding features of the application include:
	More than...
</description></item><item><title>Download Koala Sampler 1.4124</title><pubDate> Thu, 31 Jul 2025 19:12:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-koala-sampler-9322.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-koala-sampler-9322.html
</guid><description>
Koala is the ultimate pocket sampler. Record everything with your phone's mic or upload your own audio. Use Koala to create beats with those samples, add effects and create tracks! Koala's super-intuitive interface helps you hit the tracks in a flash, without the need for a brake pedal. You can also resample the application's output to input through effects so the audio possibilities are endless.
Koala's design is focused entirely on keeping the music moving quickly, keeping you in the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Automatic Scroll 3.0.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 31 Jul 2025 19:12:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-automatic-scroll-13673.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-automatic-scroll-13673.html
</guid><description>
Are you tired of swiping or scrolling through long pages while reading or browsing on your phone? With Auto Scroller: Auto Scrolling Text, you can finally relax and let the screen scroll for you. This one-of-a-kind solution aims to automate all your scrolling experience and make viewing and reading seamless on Android devices.
The auto scroller app for Android allows you to work without trying to physically interact with the device to scroll. While reading an e-book or watching...
</description></item><item><title>Download Icon Pack Studio 2.3 build 002 GP</title><pubDate> Thu, 31 Jul 2025 19:11:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-icon-pack-studio-11209.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-icon-pack-studio-11209.html
</guid><description>
IPS was created with the idea that no icon pack can fit your home screen better than an icon pack you create yourself. With IPS, you can create an icon pack from scratch, or you can download and apply one of the thousands of icons uploaded by our community every day. The advanced editor allows you to resize and move any element in your custom icon. Use special filters like lights, shadows, textures and borders, and when you're satisfied with the results, apply the new icon pack to your...
</description></item><item><title>Download My Earthquake Alerts Pro 25.0.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 31 Jul 2025 19:11:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-my-earthquake-alerts-pro-11974.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-my-earthquake-alerts-pro-11974.html
</guid><description>
My Earthquake Alerts Pro is a powerful earthquake monitoring app that provides all the information you need, with push notifications included. It also includes a beautifully simple design optimized for the latest Android versions.
FEATURES AND CHARACTERISTICS
	Live Earthquake Map can detect and track earthquakes from around the world.
	Earthquake alerts are customized for you, without restrictions.
	Powerful search feature to find earthquake history dating back to 1970!
	Beautiful and...
</description></item><item><title>Download WillyWeather 4.1.4</title><pubDate> Thu, 31 Jul 2025 19:11:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-willyweather-10929.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-willyweather-10929.html
</guid><description>
WillyWeather is a feature-packed weather app that includes radar and NOAA satellites, detailed forecasts for wind, rain, tides, ocean waves and UV, as well as moon phases as well like sunrise and sunset times. In addition to our regular weather service, we process and refine coordinate-specific forecast data for more than 175,000 locations across the United States, including all towns, cities, beaches, rivers, parks, lakes and islands.
Weather data
	Weather - Six-day NOAA weather...
</description></item><item><title>Download The Guardian - Live World News 6.185.21826</title><pubDate> Thu, 31 Jul 2025 19:10:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-the-guardian-news-sport-8572.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-the-guardian-news-sport-8572.html
</guid><description>
Read the best news stories, hot news &amp;amp; comments along the way. The Guardian app gives you access to the latest politics, business and sports news through award-winning journalism.
World news, live updates &amp;amp; opinion - take your news feed with you wherever you go. Explore US stories, headlines, content and media on a variety of topics; from business to music, politics, sports, culture &amp;amp; more.
5 reasons to download The Guardian App
	Breaking news alerts, sent straight to...
</description></item></channel></rss>