<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 13:56:05 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 13:56:05 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download ClevNote - Notepad, Checklist 2.24.11</title><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 16:10:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-clevnote-notepad-checklist-8746.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-clevnote-notepad-checklist-8746.html
</guid><description>
ClevNote is a note-taking and checklist app for Android devices. It allows users to create and manage various types of notes, such as to-do lists, grocery lists, reminders, and more. ClevNote is a memo application that helps users write necessary daily memos
Features of ClevNote for Android
	Simple and easy-to-use interface
	Supports creating and managing multiple notes and checklists
	Ability to set reminders for specific notes or tasks
	Built-in templates for common note types, such...
</description></item><item><title>Download PrintHand Mobile Print 14.8.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 16:09:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-printhand-mobile-print-11658.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-printhand-mobile-print-11658.html
</guid><description>
PrintHand Mobile Print is a convenient and multifunctional mobile printing application that allows users to print photos, documents and other files from mobile phones or tablets. This application supports direct printing from mobile devices via Wi-Fi or Bluetooth connection to the printer for printing without using an intermediary computer.
With PrintHand Mobile Print, users can easily print from any application on their mobile device, including Email, Dropbox, Google Drive and more....
</description></item><item><title>Download Busuu: Learn &amp;amp; Speak Languages 32.28.0(1547155)</title><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 16:09:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-busuu-learn-languages-8400.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-busuu-learn-languages-8400.html
</guid><description>
Busuu: Learn Languages is a mobile application that allows users to learn and practice various languages ​​on their Android devices. It includes various features such as interactive lessons, flashcards, quizzes, and exercises designed to help users learn and practice vocabulary, grammar, and conversation skills. The app also includes many customizable settings, such as the ability to choose between different languages ​​and set learning goals.
Busuu Features: Learn...
</description></item><item><title>Download Moviebase: Movies &amp;amp; TV Guide 5.6.3</title><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 16:09:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-moviebase-track-tv-shows-8175.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-moviebase-track-tv-shows-8175.html
</guid><description>
Are you looking for a useful movie finder and movie tracker app to help you find movie ratings, movie reviews, movie recommendations, movie trailers and more? Try Moviebase – Movie Manager. Moviebase is the most popular movie finder and movie tracker app where you can find movies, series, seasons, episodes. Movie reviews, movie trailers, movie descriptions and actors from the largest community database TMDB.
Explore the world of movies and series from Movie Tracker
	Explore a huge...
</description></item><item><title>Download Shazam: Find Music &amp;amp; Concerts 16.25.0-260115</title><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 16:08:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-shazam-music-discovery-10763.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-shazam-music-discovery-10763.html
</guid><description>
Shazam will identify any song in seconds. Discover, artists, lyrics, videos &amp;amp; playlists, all for free. Over 1 billion installs and counting. Use Pop-up Shazam to identify music in any app - Instagram, YouTube, TikTok... No connection? No problem! Shazam while offline.
Features of Shazam: Music Discovery
	Find the name of any song in seconds.
	Listen and add to Apple Music playlists.
	Follow along with time-synced lyrics.
	Watch music videos from Apple Music or YouTube.
	Enable...
</description></item><item><title>Download Magnifying Glass 4.1.8</title><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 16:08:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-magnifying-glass-9389.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-magnifying-glass-9389.html
</guid><description>
Magnifier is a simple app for Android devices used to magnify the appearance of objects or text that are small and difficult to see with the naked eye.
Features of Magnifier for Android
	Zoom: from 1x to 10x.
	Flashlight: Use a flashlight in dark places or at night.
	Freeze: After freezing, you can view a more detailed enlarged image.
	Take a photo: Save an enlarged photo on your phone.
	Completely free.
</description></item><item><title>Download Windy.app - Enhanced forecast 87.1.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 16:08:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-windyapp-windy-weather-map-10522.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-windyapp-windy-weather-map-10522.html
</guid><description>
WINDY - wind, wave and weather forecast app for surfers, kitesurfers, windsurfers and sailors.
Features
	Wind reports, forecasts and statistics: wind compass, wind map, wind speed meter, wind gusts and wind direction. It is very useful for extreme wind sports.
	Weather history (archived) 2012-2016: view wind data, temperature (day and night) and atmospheric pressure. The weather archive will help you choose the best month to go to that location.
	Local forecast from NOAA: temperature...
</description></item><item><title>Download NYTimes: US and Global News 11.57.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 16:08:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-the-new-york-times-8235.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-the-new-york-times-8235.html
</guid><description>
Understand the world around you with original reporting from The New York Times. Free to download, The Times app gives you access to expert news from 1700 journalists in 160 countries worldwide. From breaking news to opinion, business, technology and the arts, subscribers get unlimited access to groundbreaking reporting, analysis and commentary.
Features of The New York Times
	Wake up with The Morning, your morning guide to what's happening and why it matters. It's the news you need...
</description></item><item><title>Download FotMob - Soccer Live Scores 222.15577.20260119.rc</title><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 16:07:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-fotmob-soccer-live-scores-8241.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-fotmob-soccer-live-scores-8241.html
</guid><description>
FotMob gives you all the live scores, stats and storylines to help you keep up with the world of football. Personalized news and notifications make it easy to follow your favorite teams and players. And lightning-fast match updates ensure you never miss a goal, no matter where you are.
Features of FotMob - Live soccer scores
	Live match score
	Results, schedule, standings and lineup
	Detailed statistics, including expected goals (xG) and expected assists (xA)
	Capture map
	Player...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wakey Alarm Clock 3.7 - Aether - Build 30736</title><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 16:07:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wakey-alarm-clock-13454.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wakey-alarm-clock-13454.html
</guid><description>
Wakey Alarm Clock is a cute and gentle wake-up companion with a spectacular design and immersive animations, aiming to make waking up a fun experience. It includes features such as bedtime reminders, sleep sounds, wake-up challenges (e.g. math problems or typing sequences), nap options, customizable snooze mode, and snooze alarm mode. The app is ad-free and optimized for modern Android devices, designed to transform your morning routine with a friendly interface and engaging...
</description></item><item><title>Download 365Scores: Live Scores &amp;amp; News 14.5.4</title><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 16:06:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-365scores-live-scores-news-8220.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-365scores-live-scores-news-8220.html
</guid><description>
365Scores is a sports app that provides users with real-time scores, statistics, and news for many sports including football, basketball, soccer, and more. Some features of the application include:
	Live scores and notifications: 365Scores provides live scores and push notifications for many sports, including football, soccer, basketball, baseball, etc.
	Match statistics: The app includes detailed match statistics such as ball control, number of shots on goal, etc.
	Latest News:...
</description></item><item><title>Download New Scientist 4.20</title><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 16:06:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-new-scientist-13829.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-new-scientist-13829.html
</guid><description>
Discover award-winning journalism and stay up to date with science news and breakthroughs that will change your world in the New Scientist app. In a world where the real truth is scarce, there's never been a greater need for a trustworthy, unbiased source of information about what's going on in the world - or for inspiration through great ideas.
From artificial intelligence to climate change, from the latest health innovations to the mysteries of quantum physics and the human mind, New...
</description></item><item><title>Download 9GAG: Funny GIF, Meme &amp;amp; Video 8.17.4</title><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 16:06:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-9gag-funny-gif-meme-video-11500.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-9gag-funny-gif-meme-video-11500.html
</guid><description>
9GAG has the best funny, cute, weird, wacky, cosplay photos, GIFs, videos, memes, photos on the web. We are your greatest and happiest source. With millions of visitors every day, 9GAG is an application that helps you play LOL, kill time and make new friends around the world.
9GAG features
	The 9GAG app loads quickly and allows for easy scrolling. Don't waste time picking me up or just having a good laugh.
	Carry unlimited fun in your pocket. Enjoy 9GAG anytime, anywhere and...
</description></item><item><title>Download TidyWindow 3.9.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 01:34:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tidywindow-14454.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tidywindow-14454.html
</guid><description>
TidyWindow is a Windows desktop assistant that automates developer PC setup, cleanup, diagnostics, software package installation, registry tweaking, and driver updates—powered by a WPF interface and robust PowerShell 7 automation capabilities in the background.
Key Features
	Essentials Repair Center (docs/essentials.md): Queues selected automation tasks Filter for network, Defender, printing, and Windows Update issues. Each task supports preview run, sequential execution, restore...
</description></item><item><title>Download AnyDesk 9.6.8</title><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 01:33:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anydesk-1321.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anydesk-1321.html
</guid><description>
AnyDesk is software computer control remote, easy connection with remote computer management and manipulation on the computer. After installing the AnyDesk up 2 the computer then you can easily use the software to provide technical support for a friend or family member or you have access to your computer while you away from home or office.
AnyDesk - control your computer remotely
The process of using very simple software, want to allow access to his computer, only need to provide for...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Acrobat Pro DC 2025.001.21111 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jan 2026 22:19:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-001en-adobe-acrobat-pro-458.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-001en-adobe-acrobat-pro-458.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Acrobat Pro DC is a comprehensive software that helps you create and edit the PDF&amp;nbsp;document, or create form, sign, protect PDF, connect, split PDF, export PDF to various formats. The Acrobat Pro DC is the latest version of Adobe with improvements in the interface with the polished ribbon bar and the ability to create and handle pdf files as well as its male versions.
The highlight of the Acrobat Pro DC is probably the ability to connect, store documents on the cloud, you can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Drive SnapShot 1.50.0.1830</title><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jan 2026 22:18:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-drive-snapshot-701.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-drive-snapshot-701.html
</guid><description>
Drive SnapShot is a backup software, Restore disk, including operating system, installed programs, your data and all security attributes - while windows is running and you continue to work. With Drive SnapShot you backup partition or hard drive and it can also create disk image of your system. If a disaster occurs (a virus, trojan or the fixed hard disk), the recover complete and accurate your system will be able to accomplish after only a few minutes. The image file can be mounted as...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Substance 3D Designer 15.1.1 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jan 2026 22:17:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-substancee-designer-adobe-908.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-substancee-designer-adobe-908.html
</guid><description>
Substance Designer is the tool aggregated structure to help design, create 3D material. Create the file Quality or texture bitmap. Substance Designer helps users to create materials with full control and infinite variations. Edit the texture complete immediately and create texture, Quality and material of MDL will be handled directly in the renderer or game engine of you.
Substance Designer - design, create 3D material
The main features of Substance Designer
	Substance Designer...
</description></item><item><title>Download PhotoPad Image Editor Pro 15.00 Beta</title><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jan 2026 22:16:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photopad-image-editor-572.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photopad-image-editor-572.html
</guid><description>
PhotoPad Image Editor is a software to help edit photos and supports lots of features like edit, cut, rotate, resize and flip digital photos. With PhotoPad Image Editor, you can freely perform the basic editing for their images and also can add some neat effect. It has the option to create a photo collage and mosaic images from your photos, and you can also add text and captions. If you prefer, you can complete your masterpiece by adding the frame or contour is simple.
The main features...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sante DICOM Worklist Server 2.4.5</title><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jan 2026 22:15:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sante-dicom-worklist-server-12615.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sante-dicom-worklist-server-12615.html
</guid><description>
Sante DICOM Worklist Server (MWL Server) is an automated program that can receive via HL7 communication messages the patient's demographic information and examination schedules stored in the HIS/RIS system. Hospital Information System/Radiology Information System) and transfer them to any modality/medical scanner via DICOM communication protocol (C-FIND). The program provides automatic, error-free and reliable transfer of HL7 information (HIS/RIS) nodes to DICOM (medical scanner) nodes...
</description></item><item><title>Download Advanced SystemCare Ultimate 18.1.0.87</title><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jan 2026 20:53:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-systemcare-ultimate-132.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-systemcare-ultimate-132.html
</guid><description>
Advanced SystemCare Ultimate 17: Antivirus software that also helps protect, repair, clean and optimize your PC. Based on BitDefender antivirus technology and IObit anti-malware engine, it is part of IObit antivirus project devoted to providing better and value-added services to our users.
With real-time protection against viruses, spyware and phishing attacks, powerful tuning and cleaning functions, Advanced SystemCare Ultimate provides always-on protection, Automatic and all-in-one...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Lightroom Classic 2026 v15.1.1 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jan 2026 20:52:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-photoshop-lightroom-classic-0004-734.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-photoshop-lightroom-classic-0004-734.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Photoshop Lightroom Classic is a desktop-optimized photo editing and organizing software. Lightroom Classic gives you powerful one-click tools and advanced controls to make your photos look great. Easily organize all your photos on your desktop and share them in a variety of ways.
In addition, Lightroom Classic has a powerful import process that allows users to preview images before importing. It supports many camera raw formats and includes a database system for efficient photo...
</description></item><item><title>Download Perfectly Clear WorkBench 5.0.1.3052</title><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jan 2026 20:51:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfectly-clear-workbench-6892.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfectly-clear-workbench-6892.html
</guid><description>
Perfectly Clear Workbench is an application that uses image editing libraries Perfectly Clear by Athentech and is provided to demonstrate the capabilities of the Perfectly Clear processing libraries, which recognize faces and allow quick export of processing settings for use.
One of the key features in Workbench is the ability to "export to API" when saving a Preset. This allows you to make image edits in Workbench and adjust the settings to suit your editing style and needs. You can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Donemax Disk Clone Enterprise 3.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jan 2026 20:51:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-donemax-disk-clone-enterprise-9076.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-donemax-disk-clone-enterprise-9076.html
</guid><description>
Donemax Disk Clone Enterprise is a software tool designed for Windows computers that allows users to create a complete backup of their hard drive or partition. The software can be used to clone an entire hard drive, including the operating system, applications, and data to another hard drive or SSD, making it a useful tool for administrators. systems and IT professionals who need to manage multiple computers.
This software provides users with several options for creating backups,...
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 7.9.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jan 2026 20:51:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-10-7759.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-10-7759.html
</guid><description>
TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 is a utility that allows users to discover hidden settings in Windows 10. This application is specially designed for Windows 10, groups many registry settings and provide them from an easy and secure user interface. With TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 you can move the Windows taskbar to the top and resize the taskbar by editing the registry value. With any application that modifies the registry, we recommend that you have a backup copy to...
</description></item></channel></rss>