<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 15:47:53 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 15:47:53 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Text Editor Pro 35.2.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:43:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-text-editor-pro-800.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-text-editor-pro-800.html
</guid><description>
Text Editor Pro is software to handle text, HTML, Perl, Ruby, or Fortran with features syntax highlighting, professional. Text Editor provides syntax highlighting for over 50 scripts and has a simple interface and easy access. In addition, the Text Editor Pro also supports more than 50 programming languages like C ++, COBOL, graph DOT, DSP, DWScript, Fortran, Foxpro, Java, Perl, Python, Ruby, SQL and many other languages.
Text Editor Pro - text Processing professional
The software can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Lyric Video Studio 1.4.12</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:40:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lyric-video-studio-13581.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lyric-video-studio-13581.html
</guid><description>
Lyric Video Studio is a powerful, feature-rich video editor specifically designed to create lyric videos, music videos, and visualizers with ease. It integrates simple and effective text tools along with generative AI capabilities to streamline the video creation process. Whether you're a musician launching a killer new track, a content creator, or just love playing with visuals, this app lets you sync your lyrics to your music in just a few clicks. Enter lyrics, drag to sync and you're...
</description></item><item><title>Download PC Assist Software PDF Assist 3.0.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:40:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pc-assist-software-pdf-assist-12798.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pc-assist-software-pdf-assist-12798.html
</guid><description>
One of the most widely used file formats today is PDF, due to its many advantages. Not only because it is cross-platform, but also because it is compact, secure and ensures the integrity of graphics, displaying identical content regardless of the device it is viewed on. PDF Assist is a full-featured PDF processing tool that not only acts as a PDF viewer but also comes with options to annotate documents, sort pages, hide sensitive content or completely encrypt a file, convert, merge and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Executor 2.2.2.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:39:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-executor-271.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-executor-271.html
</guid><description>
Executor for windows is a software alternative premium customization features for the Windows "Run" and "Search Programs". When you press WIN + Z and provides the search results instant, as-you-type for any keywords you enter. By default, Executor will index all the Desktop and Start Menu and you can easily expand the search range by adding the folder location additional.
Executor for windows
The program comes with a list of commands built in which you can use to quickly access many...
</description></item><item><title>Download Inno Setup Unpacker 2.1.4</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:39:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-inno-setup-unpacker-12546.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-inno-setup-unpacker-12546.html
</guid><description>
Inno Setup is a popular and reliable application that creates program installers by helping you create scripts. Extracting the installation files from their container, resulting from compiling code with Inno Setup, can only be done through self-extracting files. In other words, you need to create a self-extracting executable to shell the installation documents.
Inno Setup Unpacker can help you avoid such actions, which is especially useful because some system security protocols block...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter 3.9.18 (0401)</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:39:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-to-mp3-converter-1744.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-to-mp3-converter-1744.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter is the software support download youtube video and convert video to mp3 format fast and most simple. MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter allows you download and convert videos from YouTube and other websites to MP3 format by pasting the YouTube URL into the application. When you paste the URL, the program will display thumbnails for videos and you have the option to customize the title information, artist and album before you begin the process of...
</description></item><item><title>Download IObit Smart Defrag Pro 11.2.0.472</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:38:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iobit-smart-defrag-pro-319.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iobit-smart-defrag-pro-319.html
</guid><description>
IObit Smart Defrag Pro is software that defragment the disk to help speed up the whole system to prevent the technical errors not desired. Based on the technology of disk defragmentation latest of IObit, and technology “boot Time disk defrag” Smart Defrag 5 is created with the ability to defragment in the world. It not only provides defragmentation, but also smart sorting your files based on using frequency, thus increasing the disk speed and the whole system for highest...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mass Image Compressor 4.2.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:37:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mass-image-compressor-12571.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mass-image-compressor-12571.html
</guid><description>
Mass Image Compressor is easy to use - a point-and-shoot mass image compression and conversion tool for Web page optimization, photographers, HTML game creators, and regular Windows users.
MassImageCompressor reduces image size significantly (&amp;gt;90%) according to user-selected size and quality parameters. Reduce large numbers of images in a folder (and optional subfolders) with just one click. Batch compressing images for websites, emails or mobile storage has never been easier! Most...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinScript 1.4.4</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:37:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winscript-12800.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winscript-12800.html
</guid><description>
WinScript is an open source tool built to help you build custom scripts for Windows 10 and 11. It includes scripts for debugging, privacy, performance, and more, along with the ability to install all your favorite apps with just one click.
Features
	Debloat: Remove Windows bloatware, CoPilot, Edge, OneDrive, and other pre-installed features preset.
	Privacy: Disable Windows and 3rd party data collection, tracking, app access, and telemetry.
	Performance: Set background services to...
</description></item><item><title>Download VovSoft Search Text in Files 5.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:28:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-search-text-in-files-5417.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-search-text-in-files-5417.html
</guid><description>
VovSoft Search Text in Files is an application that searches through text files with simple queries, and the application will quickly find the file. Select the folder, enter the search text and filename filter, then click the Start button. All files including the search text will be listed. You can export the list to text or a CSV file. You can open, copy or delete files by right clicking. You can also display file sizes and file icons by using checkboxes.
VovSoft Features Search Text...
</description></item><item><title>Download PLEdit 7.4.0.742</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:23:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pledit-5224.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pledit-5224.html
</guid><description>
PLEdit is the application that allows to edit and compile the module code PL / SQL (the stored procedure.) It is optimized for fast and friendly resource. Thanks to the user interface according to the card of the program, you can open and edit multiple modules at the same time. In addition, you have the option to save the workspace current and complete his mission at a later date.
PLEdit supports marked syntax, help you write the code and detect errors more easily, also can turn on or...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wing FTP Server Corporate 8.1.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:23:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wing-ftp-server-corporate-2752.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wing-ftp-server-corporate-2752.html
</guid><description>
Wing FTP Server Corporate is a highly functional, easy and safe can be used in the operating system Windows, Linux, Mac and Solaris are used. The software supports a number of file transfer protocol such as FTP, HTTP, FTPS, HTTPS and SFTP. Wing FTP Server provides web-based interface to manage the server at any time. You can also get performance server and the online and even send email notifications about various events happening on the server.
Management server multi-function
Wing FTP...
</description></item><item><title>Download Malwarebytes Support Tool 1.9.17.1158</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:22:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-malwarebytes-support-tool-4901.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-malwarebytes-support-tool-4901.html
</guid><description>
Malwarebytes Support Tool is designed to help you fix the problem with Malwarebytes for Windows. Tool support Malwarebytes combines many utilities, such as utilities cleanup Malwarebytes and scan tool recover Farbar. Tool support Malwarebytes collect information from your computer and create a new support ticket or update a ticket out there with the information collected.
Tool support Malwarebytes can do?
	Provides the option of self-help to troubleshoot
	Create a support ticket...
</description></item><item><title>Download AndroidDrive 2.4.14</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:22:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-androiddrive-10400.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-androiddrive-10400.html
</guid><description>
AndroidDrive is a program that allows mounting Android smartphones/tablets as drives on Windows. When AndroidDrive is running and you connect an Android device, AndroidDrive automatically mounts the drive containing that device's internal storage (files, folders).
Once you have started AndroidDrive, the connected Android smartphone/tablet will be recognized as a new drive in Windows Explorer. This way, any files, photos, or other media can be moved back and forth between your Windows...
</description></item><item><title>Download Synchredible Professional 9.101</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:16:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-synchredible-professional-1923.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-synchredible-professional-1923.html
</guid><description>
Synchredible Professional is the most advanced version help synchronize the folder and your drive quickly and easily. Whether it is a single file or an entire drive - Synchredible Professional will synchronize, copy and save them for you. The software guide will assist you to identify the work that is scheduled in advance or be done through the USB connection. This way, you can keep your files in sync - automatically.
In the past years, the advanced technology of the us in Synchredible...
</description></item><item><title>Download Synchredible 9.101</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:16:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-synchredible-53.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-synchredible-53.html
</guid><description>
Synchredible is an easy to use tool to synchronize folders and files. It provides a wizard interface lets you set up the sync job, select files to exclude, schedule the job to execute automatically, and more.Additional features include support for network and external drives, check CRC32, and more.
Synchredible - synchronization of folders and files
Among other things, you can use the filter for the file type specific data synchronization according to the time or routine deletion of...
</description></item><item><title>Download NTFS Permissions Auditor Pro 26.1.4</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:15:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-albusbit-ntfs-permissions-auditor-pro-7539.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-albusbit-ntfs-permissions-auditor-pro-7539.html
</guid><description>
NTFS Permissions Auditor Pro is a software to quickly and easily audit directory permissions in your Windows system. It allows you to quickly analyze, verify and review any NTFS folder permissions and provides additional features like powerful, customizable filtering, exporting to different formats, etc.
Features of NTFS Permissions Auditor Pro
	Get up and running with just one install.
	Instant and accurate details about NTFS permissions for all target folders.
	Filters combine many...
</description></item><item><title>Download HttpMaster Pro 6.2.6</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:10:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-httpmaster-pro-1925.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-httpmaster-pro-1925.html
</guid><description>
A useful application for web developers who need to automate the test the web application by requesting multiple resources from a specified site web-based application. The professional version httpMaster in order to meet the requirements of many people when related to the test application. When working with HttpMaster Pro, most of the time you will manage the attributes and properties of the project HttpMaster of the items required in project. Project properties provides the global options...
</description></item><item><title>Download VirtualDJ Home 2026 Build 8985</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:09:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-virtual-dj-home-4801.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-virtual-dj-home-4801.html
</guid><description>
Virtual DJ Home is software compiled and mix of tracks with many music formats various. It has the features as there are 2 installation mode for the program is automatically or manually transformed the structure of music has to arrange after the claim theft of Remix music, record your mixes, burn a CD, rip DVD, vinyl rip, create radio on the Internet.
Although VirtualDJ is integrated with many features but still very easy to learn. You can start with the basics and advance as you learn...
</description></item><item><title>Download PingTool 5.0.0.98</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:01:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pingtool-11816.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pingtool-11816.html
</guid><description>
PingTool is a powerful utility for administrators. It's more than just a simple ping tool: PingTool can also wake up computers using Wake-on-Lan, to check the availability of TCP ports, scan networks, and more.
PingTool Features
	Permanent display of network device status (red/green)
	Scan IP range - with MAC address and vendor
	Check that the remote device responds on specific TCP ports
	Wake up your computer using Wake-on-Lan
	Direct access to the device via Telnet, SSH and...
</description></item><item><title>Download PentaLogix ViewMate Pro 11.24.73</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:01:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pentalogix-viewmate-pro-1008.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pentalogix-viewmate-pro-1008.html
</guid><description>
PentaLogix ViewMate Pro is software to view, edit and convert files from DXF to other formats such as Gerber. When using ViewMate Pro, with the DFM smart, you can check the data view there are mass violations or not. And not just a class once! Many violations, laminated with results quickly and accurately. The system provides an error report in ASCII, and in addition, create a file Gerber to help edit the file plot quickly.
PentaLogix ViewMate Pro - View and convert DXF
ViewMate Pro,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Calcpad 7.5.8</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:00:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-calcpad-12576.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-calcpad-12576.html
</guid><description>
Calcpad is free software for mathematical and engineering calculations. It is a flexible and modern programmable calculator with Html report generator. Calcpad uses a simple programming language that is fast and easy to learn. It does not require any special programming skills, which makes it suitable for engineers without any computer programming background. You can create calculation notes simply by writing your formula and text, enclosed in 'quotation marks'.
The program includes...
</description></item><item><title>Download Shutter Encoder 19.8</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:00:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-shutter-encoder-6837.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-shutter-encoder-6837.html
</guid><description>
Shutter Encoder is an easy-to-use program to convert, edit and encode images, videos, audio files and more. Shutter Encoder is a video, audio and image converter based on FFmpeg and other great tools. It has been designed by video editors to be as accessible and effective as possible.
Features of Shutter Encoder:
	Cut without re-encoding, Replace Audio, Rewind, Edit, Merge, Extract, Subtitle, Insert Video
	Audio Converter: WAV, AIFF, FLAC, MP3, AAC, AC3, OPUS, OGG
	Edit codecs: DNxHD,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Telegram for Desktop 6.4.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:59:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-telegram-3376.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-telegram-3376.html
</guid><description>
Telegram is an instant messaging service and voice over IP services on the cloud platform. Client application Telegram is available for Android, iOS, Windows Phone, Windows NT, macOS, and Linux. Users can send messages and exchange photos, videos, stickers, audio and files of any kind.
Telegram - Messaging and free phone calls
Telegram seamless sync across all your devices and can be used on desktop, tablet and phone. You can send unlimited amount of messages, photos, videos and files...
</description></item><item><title>Download Fluke TruTest 1.1.0.255</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:59:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fluke-trutest-12626.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fluke-trutest-12626.html
</guid><description>
Fluke TruTest software is designed to eliminate the hassle associated with traditional power system data management and reporting. Whether you are testing fixed wiring systems or equipment in the office, verifying repairs in the workshop or carrying out annual inspections, proper data management is critical to creating Produce easy-to-understand reports for customers. Compatible with a growing list of Fluke and Beha-Amprobe test and measurement devices TruTest software allows you to...
</description></item></channel></rss>