<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 21:34:46 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 21:34:46 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Adobe Audition 2025 v25.6.0 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Fri, 14 Nov 2025 19:01:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-0010-adobe-audition-1246.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-0010-adobe-audition-1246.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Autdition 2024 is a professional tool for professionals active in the field of audio processing and video, offering them the ability to almost unlimited. Ease of use combined with flexibility of work, allows you to create the main copy of the highest class, edit, mix, handle, impose more sound effects especially. In fact, users have to be on my computer a recording studio powerful full with the tool easy to use at the same time, the tool is quite professional.
Adobe autdition CC -...
</description></item><item><title>Download Chaos Corona 14 for 3ds Max 2018 - 2026</title><pubDate> Fri, 14 Nov 2025 19:00:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chaos-corona-2986.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chaos-corona-2986.html
</guid><description>
Corona Renderer is the name of the plug-in technique and dedicated powerful, but have high functionality for Autodesk software 3ds Max. Plug before you is a standalone application known to the CLI. In addition, users can use this tool to promote their business on software Maxon Cinema 4D is also used. The manufacturers of this product believe that working with this tool is very simple and in fact you only need to press the activities rendered. With this tool easier than ever can do the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Chaos Corona 14 for Cinema 4D R17 - 2026</title><pubDate> Fri, 14 Nov 2025 19:00:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-corona-renderer-for-cinema-4d-6499.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-corona-renderer-for-cinema-4d-6499.html
</guid><description>
Corona Renderer  is the name of a powerful, but highly functional engineering and dedicated plug-in for Autodesk 3ds Max software. Plug in before you are a known CLI standalone application. In addition, users can use this tool to advertise their business on Maxon Cinema 4D software which is also used. The manufacturers of this product firmly believe that working with this tool is very simple, and in fact you just need to hit render the rendering operations. With this tool it's easier...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Acrobat Reader DC 2025.001.20918</title><pubDate> Fri, 14 Nov 2025 18:57:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-acrobat-reader-3707.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-acrobat-reader-3707.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Acrobat Reader DC is a system of application software and Web services developed by Adobe Systems to view, create, manipulate, print and manage PDF files. With Adobe Acrobat Reader DC, you can create, export, edit, and track PDF files from anywhere - and maintain connection with the recent set of files on all your devices.
Adobe Acrobat Reader current DC is connected with Adobe Document Cloud - help working on the computers and mobile devices becomes easier than ever before. This is...
</description></item><item><title>Download Chaos Envision 1.3.1.588412</title><pubDate> Fri, 14 Nov 2025 18:57:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chaos-envision-14167.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chaos-envision-14167.html
</guid><description>
Chaos Envision is a standalone 3D visualization software designed for realistic real-time rendering combined with fast animation capabilities. The software is primarily aimed at architects, visualization professionals, and designers, providing a tool for creating professional, immersive presentations with animations, realistic crowds, and object manipulation.
Envision supports very large and complex scenes without compromising performance and integrates seamlessly with other Chaos tools...
</description></item><item><title>Download Equalizer &amp;amp; Bass Booster - XEQ 31.10.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 14 Nov 2025 18:03:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-equalizer-bass-booster-xeq-10095.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-equalizer-bass-booster-xeq-10095.html
</guid><description>
This XEQ app is a powerful yet easy-to-use Music Equalizer with Bass Boost, Volume Boost, Auto Volume Boost and 3D Virtualizer effects, which can improve the sound quality of your device. your Android device.
This is the only equalizer fx app you will ever need for your smartphone. With this feature, you can not only equalize the bass boost, but also increase the normal sound volume of your Android phone, add virtual 3D effects, save custom presets, automatically recall presets of audio...
</description></item><item><title>Download RAR for Android 7.20 build 129</title><pubDate> Fri, 14 Nov 2025 18:03:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-rar-for-android-8780.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-rar-for-android-8780.html
</guid><description>
RAR for Android is an application that allows users to create, manage and extract compressed files in RAR and ZIP formats on their Android devices. This application is developed by RARLAB, the same company that created the popular WinRAR software for Windows.
RAR can create RAR and ZIP and decompress RAR, ZIP, TAR, GZ, BZ2, XX, 7z, ISO, ARJ archives. List of functions includes command to repair damaged ZIP and RAR files, benchmarking function compatible with RARLAB's WinRAR benchmark,...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaMonkey 2.1.1.1188</title><pubDate> Fri, 14 Nov 2025 18:02:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-mediamonkey-8211.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-mediamonkey-8211.html
</guid><description>
MediaMonkey APK is a media player and management application for Android devices. MediaMonkey lets you organize and play music, podcasts, and audiobooks on your device. It supports multiple audio formats and has a built-in equalizer, sleep timer, and customizable interface.
MediaMonkey can also sync your music library with other devices, including Windows and Mac computers, and allows you to create playlists and play music on a variety of devices. This app is a great way to organize and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Speedtest by Ookla 6.5.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 14 Nov 2025 18:02:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-speedtest-by-ookla-for-android-8605.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-speedtest-by-ookla-for-android-8605.html
</guid><description>
Speedtest by Ookla is a popular online service that allows users to measure the speed of their internet connection. The service works by sending small amounts of data to a user's device and measuring the time it takes for that data to return to the server. Based on this measurement, the service provides reports on the user's download and upload speeds as well as connection latency.
Features of Ookla Speedtest
	Explore your downloads, uploads, and pings
	The only Internet connection...
</description></item><item><title>Download MacroDroid - Device Automation 5.58.13</title><pubDate> Fri, 14 Nov 2025 18:02:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-macrodroid-device-automation-9863.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-macrodroid-device-automation-9863.html
</guid><description>
MacroDroid is the easiest way to automate everyday tasks on your Android smartphone or tablet. Through its smart user interface, MacroDroid provides a simple solution to perform automated tasks on your device in just a few taps. Developed by ArloSoft, MacroDroid simplifies repetitive tasks by automating various actions and processes on your Android device. It offers a user-friendly interface and a variety of triggers, actions, and constraints to create personalized...
</description></item><item><title>Download Computer Science Calculations 4.2.7</title><pubDate> Fri, 14 Nov 2025 18:01:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-computer-science-calculations-11750.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-computer-science-calculations-11750.html
</guid><description>
Computer Science Calculations is the best application in the IT field, it has many calculations that can help you in your work. It can't miss in your smartphone!
Features:
All available tools:
	Byte conversion - Conversion of December, bin, October, hexadecimal - Signed number representation: Signed magnitude, One's complement, Two's complement - Bitwise operations - Bit shifting and rotation - Password generation - Random number generation - Base 64 encoding/decoding - URL...
</description></item><item><title>Download Shazam: Find Music &amp;amp; Concerts 16.18.0-251106</title><pubDate> Fri, 14 Nov 2025 18:01:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-shazam-music-discovery-10763.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-shazam-music-discovery-10763.html
</guid><description>
Shazam will identify any song in seconds. Discover, artists, lyrics, videos &amp;amp; playlists, all for free. Over 1 billion installs and counting. Use Pop-up Shazam to identify music in any app - Instagram, YouTube, TikTok... No connection? No problem! Shazam while offline.
Features of Shazam: Music Discovery
	Find the name of any song in seconds.
	Listen and add to Apple Music playlists.
	Follow along with time-synced lyrics.
	Watch music videos from Apple Music or YouTube.
	Enable...
</description></item><item><title>Download My dictionary - WordTheme Pro 13.4.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 14 Nov 2025 18:00:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-my-dictionary-wordtheme-pro-9328.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-my-dictionary-wordtheme-pro-9328.html
</guid><description>
You want to learn a foreign language or study a specific topic, and you're looking for an app that helps you organize and study your vocabulary list?
You can also use this app as a vocabulary or glossary, according to the topic you want (math, physics, chemistry, biology, cooking, psychology, philosophy, justice, etc.). This application is also very useful if you want to create a construction language (or conlang).
Features of My Dictionary - WordTheme Pro
	add/modify words or...
</description></item><item><title>Download APKMirror Installer (Official) 1.11.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 14 Nov 2025 18:00:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-apkmirror-installer-official-13332.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-apkmirror-installer-official-13332.html
</guid><description>
APKMirror Installer is a helper application that allows you to install .apkm, .xapk, and .apks application package files as well as regular APK files. We've also added a highly requested bonus feature for regular APK files: if an APK fails to load and you want to know why, you can now see the exact reason by initiating the installation from APKMirror Installer.
This app solves the challenge posed by Google's App Bundles, which splits the app into multiple parts to optimize delivery....
</description></item><item><title>Download Intel Graphics Driver for Windows 10 / 11 32.0.101.8250</title><pubDate> Fri, 14 Nov 2025 17:33:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intel-graphics-driver-for-windows-10-5954.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intel-graphics-driver-for-windows-10-5954.html
</guid><description>
Intel Graphics Driver for Windows 10 supports Intel ' s latest 8th-generation Core processor, introducing the Intel ® UHD graphics, with the ability to immerve in the top 4K UHD entertainment from your laptop for a maximum of 10 hours. Along with some security fixes, this driver also optimised the system's inactivity to reduce power consumption.
Look at the complete new interface of gameplay.intel.com, where you will find the proposed game settings for many of your favorite PC games....
</description></item><item><title>Download PhraseExpress 17.0.133</title><pubDate> Fri, 14 Nov 2025 17:27:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-phraseexpress-41.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-phraseexpress-41.html
</guid><description>
PhraseExpress is a useful application that helps users save time when typing frequently used text or commands. This application allows users to create shortcuts to automatically insert text quickly and conveniently.
With PhraseExpress, users can create "templates" for common commands, regular emails, chat messages, or any text they have to retype frequently. Users only need to set up shortcuts for each template and when needed, just type that shortcut and the text will automatically...
</description></item><item><title>Download Disk Drill Enterprise 6.1.1159.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 14 Nov 2025 17:27:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-disk-drill-enterprise-6875.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-disk-drill-enterprise-6875.html
</guid><description>
Disk Drill Enterprise is software that allows you to recover files from hard drives and USB devices, external hard drives, memory cards, iPhone and iPad, drive formats like NTFS, FAT, exFAT, HFS + Mac drive, EXT2/3/4. The software provides fast scan and deep scan mode, depending on the user's needs, to save time and achieve the highest efficiency.
Features of Disk Drill Enterprise
	Users simply need one click to activate Disk Drill.
	Support to scan the entire drive and rejoin lost...
</description></item><item><title>Download Modbus Slave 10.0.0.2493</title><pubDate> Fri, 14 Nov 2025 17:26:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-modbus-slave-4327.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-modbus-slave-4327.html
</guid><description>
Modbus Slave user to simulate up to 32 devices in 32 Windows!. Accelerated programming your PLC with the simulation tool this. Start programming and test before you get the device depends from his supplier. Data contained in any document, open any can gain access to the main application. Same user interface as Modbus Poll. Support functions 01, 02, 03, 04, 05, 06, 15, 16, 22 and 23. Automation OLE to communicate with Excel. To interpret and display data Modbus according to the specific...
</description></item><item><title>Download Seamless3d 3.38.5</title><pubDate> Fri, 14 Nov 2025 17:26:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-seamless3d-10257.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-seamless3d-10257.html
</guid><description>
Seamless3d is one of the easiest 3D modeling and animation programs that offers artistic freedom. It is designed to be a powerful and practical way to create 3D models that will appeal to anyone who wants to create quality 3D animated content for the web. A versatile NURBS-based 3D Modeler/Animator designed for ease of use without compromising artistic freedom, allowing you to create unique models.
Features of Seamless3d
	WYSIWYG
	Undo/Redo
	Export clean, efficient files
	Dedicated...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Downloader 9.18.5</title><pubDate> Fri, 14 Nov 2025 17:25:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html
</guid><description>
YTD Youtube Downloader is an application that reliable and intuitive, allowing you to quickly download YouTube videos and save them to your computer. You can also convert the media files to the format desired video or extract audio streams and save separately. YTD Youtube Downloader lets you save your favorite clips of yourself from Youtube, Facebook, Vimeo and Dailymotion to your desktop. The software supports URLS from many web site hosting, multimedia and allows you to download desired...
</description></item><item><title>Download Chaos V-Ray 7.2.1 Build 7.20.01 for SketchUp 2021 - 2026</title><pubDate> Fri, 14 Nov 2025 17:24:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chao-vray-for-sketchup-3936.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chao-vray-for-sketchup-3936.html
</guid><description>
V-Ray Next for SketchUp is the tool of Chaos Group for Windows PC, this is a lighting tool and as a professional for architects &amp;amp; designers.V-Ray Next for SketchUp allows you to export everything and everything - from the design models to the 3D scene details most of you. Use V-Ray for SketchUp, you can also have access to over 600 documents actual photo, drag and drop. V-Ray Next for SketchUp is very easy to use and brings great results. You can use it to create everything - from 3D...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sysinternals Suite 2025.11.13</title><pubDate> Fri, 14 Nov 2025 17:23:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sysinternals-suite-1447.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sysinternals-suite-1447.html
</guid><description>
Sysinternals Suite is a software monitoring and control system helps to find and fix errors most impressive. The software includes more than seventy utilities aimed at overcoming the problem related to managing files and disks, network problems and security, as well as information about processes and systems. Because of this very rich, the analysis of each ministry will take a significant period of time and therefore, we decided to focus on the most popular.
Sysinternals Suite - Set of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Chaos V-Ray 7.2.1 Build 7.20.01 for Rhinoceros 7-9</title><pubDate> Fri, 14 Nov 2025 17:23:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-v-ray-next-for-rhino-1285.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-v-ray-next-for-rhino-1285.html
</guid><description>
V-Ray Next For Rhino is an extension a very powerful and handy for Rhino can be used to improve the process output. V-Ray Next allows you to achieve much achievement in Rhino than ever. It's faster to showcase your designs in the best light of them. And a variety of new tools to help manage and display the sight of you much easier.
V-Ray Next For Rhino
V-Ray Next in for Rhino comes with some speed on the table. Optimize performance, speed up the production up to 50% off. The shader...
</description></item><item><title>Download Edge Remover 18.38</title><pubDate> Fri, 14 Nov 2025 17:21:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-edge-remover-7689.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-edge-remover-7689.html
</guid><description>
Edge Remover is our mini user interfaceless tool to permanently remove Microsoft Edge from your system. Easily remove Microsoft Edge browser from your system, with just one click, with this simple, no UI app.
Features of Edge Remover
	Remove MSEdge and its components
	Prevent reinstalling MSEdge on your system
Requirements:
Operating System: Microsoft Windows 7 or later
Framework: Microsoft .NET Framework 4.0
</description></item><item><title>Download SSD Booster .NET 18.38</title><pubDate> Fri, 14 Nov 2025 17:21:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ssd-booster-net-7375.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ssd-booster-net-7375.html
</guid><description>
SSD Booster .NET is our perfect tool to optimize and adjust Windows for the SSD drive to increase performance and maintain the highest performance for your SSD. In addition, the app comes with the system information tab for information about the hardware and operating system of your machine. To check your specifications, move to the Introduction and find the System Information button.
Features of SSD Booster .NET
	The perfect tool to optimize and adjust Windows for the SSD drive to...
</description></item></channel></rss>