<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 17:32:21 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 17:32:21 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download AI Chat - Chatbot AI Assistant 1.66</title><pubDate> Sun, 31 Aug 2025 19:19:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ai-chat-chatbot-ai-assistant-13721.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ai-chat-chatbot-ai-assistant-13721.html
</guid><description>
Welcome to AI Chat: AI ChatBot Assistant, built on GPT-4o &amp;amp; GPT-4. This chat AI tool also acts as a personal AI writer, ready to assist with any task from casual chatting to essay writing.
With GPT Chat Assistant, you can:
Creative Content: Let our character AI act as your dedicated essay writer, creating a variety of written content. Need a heartfelt poem, a memorable verse or a unique congratulatory message? GPT-4o is ready to compose for you. Struggling with a book or an...
</description></item><item><title>Download KMPlayer Plus (Divx Codec) 35.08.261</title><pubDate> Sun, 31 Aug 2025 19:18:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-kmplayer-plus-divx-codec-8720.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-kmplayer-plus-divx-codec-8720.html
</guid><description>
KMPlayer Plus with DivX codec is also available for Android devices, providing a powerful media player that supports many video and audio formats. These features include ad-free playback, cloud storage support, and high-resolution video playback support.
With support for DivX, KMPlayer Plus for Android allows users to watch high-quality DivX encoded videos on their mobile devices without the need for additional codecs or software. This is a convenient feature for users who want to watch...
</description></item><item><title>Download CALCU Stylish Basic Calculator 4.7.9</title><pubDate> Sun, 31 Aug 2025 19:18:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-stylish-calculator-calcu-8716.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-stylish-calculator-calcu-8716.html
</guid><description>
Express your style with a computer made just for you. Choose a stylish, colorful theme to brighten your day while you calculate with ease. CALCU™ is easy to use for everyday calculations, with all the scientific capabilities you need for work and school at a swipe. And for your most demanding needs, CALCU™ lets you add or remove the functions and constants you need to create the perfect calculator you designed for you.
Features of Fashion Calculator - CALCU
	Try our new Material...
</description></item><item><title>Download Weather Live Wallpapers 2.15.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 31 Aug 2025 19:18:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-weather-live-wallpapers-11506.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-weather-live-wallpapers-11506.html
</guid><description>
The movement of the sun, rainfall and phases of the moon are realistic animations on the screen with beautifully crafted details. The picturesque landscape reflects the weather with astonishing accuracy. Enjoy the sunrise, the rainbow, the birds singing and all the bright sunshine!
You can use real weather apps as wallpaper on your screen, they will reflect the current weather and you will always know the weather conditions. You can also launch the weather app in a window or install a...
</description></item><item><title>Download WiFi Speed Test Pro 6.6</title><pubDate> Sun, 31 Aug 2025 19:17:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wifi-speed-test-pro-11765.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wifi-speed-test-pro-11765.html
</guid><description>
WiFi Speed ​​Test Pro is a wifi and local network (LAN) speed meter. Check the best speed for your Ethernet network!
Main features
	Test the speed of wireless and wired networks
	Test download and upload speed
	Automatically saves previous Wifi speed test results, including download and upload speed, ping, signal strength, network name, IP address
	Display IP address, network information, latency, signal strength, channel information
	Share speed test results easily
	Test Windows...
</description></item><item><title>Download Rain Alarm 6.0.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 31 Aug 2025 19:17:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-rain-alarm-8639.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-rain-alarm-8639.html
</guid><description>
This weather app alerts you when rain is approaching. Alerts are a reliable short-term forecast based on near real-time data. This app is more accurate and reliable than a traditional forecast. It is useful for all outdoor activities - including cycling, motorcycling, hiking, gardening, BBQs, picnics, dog walking and DIY.
Features of Rain Alarm for Android
	Alerts for all types of precipitation, whether rain, snow or hail
	Alerts as a notification with vibration and/or sound
	Simple...
</description></item><item><title>Download Gaia GPS: Offroad Hiking Maps 2025.6 build 10116</title><pubDate> Sun, 31 Aug 2025 19:16:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-gaia-gps-offroad-hiking-maps-8610.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-gaia-gps-offroad-hiking-maps-8610.html
</guid><description>
Gaia GPS is a navigation app that provides hiking maps, topographic maps, and satellite images for outdoor enthusiasts. It allows users to plan trips, navigate the wilderness, and track their progress. The app is available for both iOS and Android devices, and offers a premium subscription for offline maps, aerial imagery, and advanced features.
Features of Gaia GPS for Android
	Offline maps: Ability to download maps for offline use, ideal for use in areas with limited or no Internet...
</description></item><item><title>Download Pear Launcher 3.8.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 31 Aug 2025 19:16:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pear-launcher-11126.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pear-launcher-11126.html
</guid><description>
PEAR Launcher is a highly functional and feature-rich personalization app for Android devices. Developed by Yajat Kumar, the app offers a wide range of options to customize the look and feel of your device. With Pear Launcher, you can choose from different drawer styles, including vertical, page, and section styles, and customize your home screen with indicator styles, grid sizes, icon labels, etc. Again.
Features of Pear Launcher
	Folders in the app drawer.
	Choose your drawer style...
</description></item><item><title>Download Music for Meditation 9.6</title><pubDate> Sun, 31 Aug 2025 19:15:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-music-for-meditation-9803.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-music-for-meditation-9803.html
</guid><description>
With mindfulness meditation music, people are more focused, sleep better and are less stressed. Practicing meditation affects: stress, anxiety, sleepiness, concentration, depression, happiness, self-motivation, creativity, anger, pregnancy and more. Listening to music suitable for meditation will greatly facilitate the achievement of deep meditation, relaxation and concentration. Improve mental and physical health.
Science proves that people who meditate better fight stress, depression...
</description></item><item><title>Download Video Converter: Compress Video 2.35</title><pubDate> Sun, 31 Aug 2025 19:15:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-video-converter-compress-video-13666.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-video-converter-compress-video-13666.html
</guid><description>
Explore the power of ConverterBlack, the ultimate Video Converter app designed to optimize your video files efficiently and easily. Enjoy the convenience of converting your videos while maintaining high quality output. This app is a multi-purpose tool that provides comprehensive functions such as video compression, format conversion, audio extraction, etc.
Features
	Convert Video to MP3: Turn your videos into stunning MP3 background music with MP4 to MP3 Converter today. Convert video...
</description></item><item><title>Download SMS Backup &amp;amp; Restore Pro 10.23.001</title><pubDate> Sun, 31 Aug 2025 19:15:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sms-backup-restore-pro-8277.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sms-backup-restore-pro-8277.html
</guid><description>
SMS Backup &amp;amp; Restore Pro is an Android application that allows users to backup and restore text messages (SMS) and multimedia messages (MMS). This application can be useful for those who want to keep their text messages safe or for those who want to transfer text messages from one device to another.
Features of SMS Backup &amp;amp; Restore Pro Restore Pro
	Backup SMS (Text) Messages, MMS and Call Logs in XML format.
	Local device backup with options to automatically upload to Google...
</description></item><item><title>Download Noteshelf 3: Digital Notes 2.0.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 31 Aug 2025 19:14:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-noteshelf-3-digital-notes-13087.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-noteshelf-3-digital-notes-13087.html
</guid><description>
Introducing the all-new Noteshelf 3 the perfect note-taking app for students, teachers, professionals, artists, and bullet journal enthusiasts to create and organize digital notes. Download for free and start your journey of seamless organization, productivity, and creativity.
PERSONALIZE YOUR NOTE-TAKING EXPERIENCE
	Create beautiful handwritten notes with a variety of realistic pens and highlighters. Try our fountain pens to add a touch of elegance to your handwriting.
	Take notes on...
</description></item><item><title>Download Lighting Calculations 6.1.7</title><pubDate> Sun, 31 Aug 2025 19:14:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-lighting-calculations-8927.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-lighting-calculations-8927.html
</guid><description>
Lighting calculation is the best application in the field of lighting, it has many calculations that can help you in your work. Lighting calculations are used to determine the amount of light needed in a given space or area to achieve the desired lighting level. These calculations take into account a number of factors, including the size and shape of the space, the type and placement of lighting fixtures, and the brightness of the light source.
Calculate total luminous flux, Indoor...
</description></item><item><title>Download Conversations (Jabber / XMPP) 2.19.3 build 4215604</title><pubDate> Sun, 31 Aug 2025 19:13:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-conversations-jabber-xmpp-11493.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-conversations-jabber-xmpp-11493.html
</guid><description>
Free and open source Jabber/XMPP client for Android. Easy to use, reliable, battery friendly. With built-in support for images, group chats and e2e encryption.
Main features
	End-to-end encryption with OMEMO or OpenPGP
	Encrypted audio and video calls (DLTS-SRTP)
	Send and receive images
	Intuitive user interface follows Android Design guidelines
	Image / Avatar for your Contacts
	Sync with desktop client
	Conference (with bookmark support)
	Address book integration
	Multiple accounts...
</description></item><item><title>Download CastReceiver 1.6.13</title><pubDate> Sun, 31 Aug 2025 19:13:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-castreceiver-10098.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-castreceiver-10098.html
</guid><description>
Castreceiver is a screen casting receiver. It allows you to mirror your Android phone or Chrome tab to any Android box running Castreceiver. By Castreceiver, you can easily share your phone/Chromebook screen for friendly or meeting presentation.
Features of Castreceiver
	1, supports both tab casting and desktop casting built into all Chromebook platforms and all desktop platforms with Google Chrome Browser.
	2, works with all Google Cast enabled Android devices without installing...
</description></item><item><title>Download Pacer Pedometer &amp;amp; Step Tracker 12.9.1 build 2025082900</title><pubDate> Sun, 31 Aug 2025 19:12:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pacer-pedometer-step-tracker-11194.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pacer-pedometer-step-tracker-11194.html
</guid><description>
Pacer App: “Pedometer, Pedometer, and Weight Loss Tracker App” that syncs steps and calories with MyFitnessPal and Fitbit! Track your steps, walking and weight loss with this free health counter. Lose weight and track distance walked and calories burned using 24/7 step counting from our pedometer, pedometer and health tracker app.
Main features:
	Best pedometer for any phone
	Accurate activity and step tracking
	Lose weight, track BMI and count calories burned
	Daily exercise...
</description></item><item><title>Download 9GAG: Funny GIF, Meme &amp;amp; Video 8.13.8</title><pubDate> Sun, 31 Aug 2025 19:12:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-9gag-funny-gif-meme-video-11500.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-9gag-funny-gif-meme-video-11500.html
</guid><description>
9GAG has the best funny, cute, weird, wacky, cosplay photos, GIFs, videos, memes, photos on the web. We are your greatest and happiest source. With millions of visitors every day, 9GAG is an application that helps you play LOL, kill time and make new friends around the world.
9GAG features
	The 9GAG app loads quickly and allows for easy scrolling. Don't waste time picking me up or just having a good laugh.
	Carry unlimited fun in your pocket. Enjoy 9GAG anytime, anywhere and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Currency Converter Plus 3.1.3</title><pubDate> Sun, 31 Aug 2025 19:12:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-currency-converter-plus-8174.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-currency-converter-plus-8174.html
</guid><description>
Advanced currency converter - With multiple currency fields, historical rate charts, and a built-in calculator for convenience, compare prices wherever you travel abroad to ensure Make sure you get the best deal at today's price. All conversions use live exchange rates from AccuRate™, providing the most accurate rates available in the world. Plus, it still works offline for moves when exchange rate data isn't available. This app even supports Bitcoin!
Features of Currency Converter...
</description></item><item><title>Download IgeBlock - Tube ad blocker 2.0.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 31 Aug 2025 19:11:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-igeblock-tube-ad-blocker-11113.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-igeblock-tube-ad-blocker-11113.html
</guid><description>
IgeBlock is an app that allows you to watch videos without ads, watch videos with sound, and watch videos in pop-up player while using other apps.
IgeBlock Features
Block ads
	Automatically skip annoying video ads.
	Automatically skip ads even in sound and pop-up player mode.
Pop-up player (PIP)
	You can play videos in floating mode without additional permissions.
Can be added
	Full screen touch lock function
	looped video
	Bookmark function without logging in
	Timer to turn...
</description></item><item><title>Download Bluetooth Commander Pro 9.8</title><pubDate> Sun, 31 Aug 2025 19:11:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-bluetooth-commander-pro-10162.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-bluetooth-commander-pro-10162.html
</guid><description>
Bluetooth Commander is a Bluetooth terminal application to manage low-level communication between Android smartphones and Bluetooth devices (one or more) such as microcontrollers, Arduino, processor boards or other Bluetooth terminals. The application allows simultaneous connections to multiple devices with traffic diagnostics and contains an interface for creating a database of user-defined commands.
Features of Bluetooth Commander Pro
	Connect and communicate with multiple Bluetooth...
</description></item><item><title>Download Twilight: Blue light filter 14.9 build 570</title><pubDate> Sun, 31 Aug 2025 19:10:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-twilight-blue-light-filter-12193.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-twilight-blue-light-filter-12193.html
</guid><description>
Are you having trouble falling asleep? Is your child hyperactive when playing with the tablet before going to bed? The Twilight app helps your device's screen adapt to the time of day. It filters the blue light emitted from your phone or tablet after sunset and protects your eyes with a soft and pleasant red filter. Filter intensity is smoothly adjusted to the solar cycle based on your local sunset and sunrise times.
Get more from Twilight
	- Reading in bed: Twilight is more...
</description></item><item><title>Download aCalendar+ Calendar &amp;amp; Tasks 2.9.4 build 2009400</title><pubDate> Sun, 31 Aug 2025 19:10:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-acalendar-calendar-tasks-9857.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-acalendar-calendar-tasks-9857.html
</guid><description>
aCalendar+ Calendar &amp;amp; Tasks is a popular calendar and task manager app for Android devices. It is developed by Tapir Apps GmbH and acts as an enhanced version of the free aCalendar app. aCalendar+ offers a variety of features and customization options to help users stay organized and manage their schedules and tasks effectively.
Features of aCalendar+ Calendar &amp;amp; Tasks Tasks
	intuitive navigation with smooth transitions
	day, week, month and year views
	full screen...
</description></item><item><title>Download FotMob - Soccer Live Scores 215.14433.20250820.rc</title><pubDate> Sun, 31 Aug 2025 19:10:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-fotmob-soccer-live-scores-8241.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-fotmob-soccer-live-scores-8241.html
</guid><description>
FotMob gives you all the live scores, stats and storylines to help you keep up with the world of football. Personalized news and notifications make it easy to follow your favorite teams and players. And lightning-fast match updates ensure you never miss a goal, no matter where you are.
Features of FotMob - Live soccer scores
	Live match score
	Results, schedule, standings and lineup
	Detailed statistics, including expected goals (xG) and expected assists (xA)
	Capture map
	Player...
</description></item><item><title>Download Today Weather: Radar &amp;amp; Widgets 2.4.0-3</title><pubDate> Sun, 31 Aug 2025 19:09:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-today-weather-alerts-widgets-8915.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-today-weather-alerts-widgets-8915.html
</guid><description>
Weather Today is a beautiful and easy-to-use weather app that provides the world's most accurate local weather forecasts.
Features of Weather Today for Android
	Displays clear, easy-to-understand weather forecasts.
	Enjoy every moment you open the app with thousands of beautiful photos corresponding to the weather and day.
	Prepare for any situation with 24/7 weather forecasts and chance of rain.
	Protect your health with air quality, UV index and pollen count.
	Capture beautiful...
</description></item><item><title>Download Chomp SMS 9.25 build 9092563</title><pubDate> Sun, 31 Aug 2025 19:09:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-chomp-sms-8403.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-chomp-sms-8403.html
</guid><description>
Comes with many great features, especially passcode app lock, privacy options, scheduled SMS sender (reminders, birthday wishes), stopping messages while sending , pin favorites to top, backup, SMS blacklist/blocker, signature, excerpt text, quick reply popup (even on lock screen), multi-select photo gallery, dual sim, better MMS and GROUP messaging, etc...
Plus unlimited customization options for LED color, ringtone, vibration pattern, screen color, font type, font size and wallpaper....
</description></item></channel></rss>