<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 22:12:17 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 22:12:17 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Perfectly Clear WorkBench 5.0.2.3110</title><pubDate> Tue, 24 Feb 2026 22:52:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfectly-clear-workbench-6892.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfectly-clear-workbench-6892.html
</guid><description>
Perfectly Clear Workbench is an application that uses image editing libraries Perfectly Clear by Athentech and is provided to demonstrate the capabilities of the Perfectly Clear processing libraries, which recognize faces and allow quick export of processing settings for use.
One of the key features in Workbench is the ability to "export to API" when saving a Preset. This allows you to make image edits in Workbench and adjust the settings to suit your editing style and needs. You can...
</description></item><item><title>Download MiniTool Partition Wizard Technician 13.6</title><pubDate> Tue, 24 Feb 2026 22:52:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minitool-partition-wizard-pro-604.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minitool-partition-wizard-pro-604.html
</guid><description>
MiniTool Partition Wizard Technician is the best partition manager for Windows, MiniTool Partition Wizard aims to maximize disk performance. It helps to create/change the size/format of the flexible partition, the disk conversion between the MBR and GPT disks, the partition conversion between NTFS and FAT32 and converting the disk into a basic without losing data.
Recovery of data quickly, effective: MiniTool partition management software provides two perfect solutions for data recovery....
</description></item><item><title>Download XnViewMP 1.10.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 24 Feb 2026 22:52:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xnview-mp-1074.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xnview-mp-1074.html
</guid><description>
XnViewMP "XnView MP" is the enhanced version of XnView Classic. This is the view and convert images multi-platform powerful, compatible with more than 500 image formats, different today. XnView MP easily export images to about 70 file format is different. Similar to XnConvert, XnView MP also features integrated switch at the same time batch file to help you process photos faster. XnView is another version of the photo viewer but with the ability to support formats more limited.
XnView...
</description></item><item><title>Download MiniTool Partition Wizard Pro Ultimate 13.6 + Pro Version</title><pubDate> Tue, 24 Feb 2026 22:51:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minitool-partition-wizard-pro-ultimate-6012.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minitool-partition-wizard-pro-ultimate-6012.html
</guid><description>
MiniTool Partition Wizard Pro Ultimate is a feature-wide multiplicity algorithm, designed to optimize your disk usage and data protection. It comes with a lot of powerful features that you can completely control your hard disk and partition. With a user-friendly interface and simple guidance, you can change the size of the partition, copy the disk, scan the lost partition and move the operating system to the SSD easily and safely.
Software support software Linux Ext2, Ext3, Ext4,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Agisoft Metashape Professional 2.3.1 Build 22145</title><pubDate> Tue, 24 Feb 2026 22:51:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-agisoft-metashape-professional-1731.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-agisoft-metashape-professional-1731.html
</guid><description>
Agisoft Metashape (formerly PhotoScan) is a software product independently perform image processing and digital data creation, 3D space used in GIS applications, material cultural heritage and the production visual effects as well as the indirect measurement of the different subjects scale. Technical digital photography is deployed wisely is applied with the method of computer vision led to the system processor, smart auto, on the one hand, can be managed by a new person in the field of...
</description></item><item><title>Download HWiNFO 8.42 Build 5930</title><pubDate> Tue, 24 Feb 2026 22:50:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hwinfo-1828.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hwinfo-1828.html
</guid><description>
HWiNFO (HWiNFO32) is a diagnostic tool and hardware information, recognizes and displays detailed information about all the hardware components of you. HWiNFO will hold the component in the tree view and provide the report easy to read for each category.
HWiNFO - Hardware Diagnostics
HWiNFO is especially useful so you don't have to install it on each computer and completely for free. Just run the direct program and you will have full information of the computer that you need. The...
</description></item><item><title>Download MSI Center 2.0.67.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 24 Feb 2026 22:46:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-msi-center-12314.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-msi-center-12314.html
</guid><description>
The AI ​​era of computing: MSI laptops are equipped with MSI's exclusive AI technology capable of providing completely new smart features. The AI ​​revolution has arrived on MSI laptops. MSI AI Engine automatically recognizes various user situations, triggering appropriate adjustments in performance, sound effects, display modes and keyboard backlighting. Users do not need to make manual adjustments to achieve optimal situations.
MSI Center combines all of MSI's exclusive...
</description></item><item><title>Download Disk Drill Enterprise 6.2.1278.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 24 Feb 2026 22:45:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-disk-drill-enterprise-6875.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-disk-drill-enterprise-6875.html
</guid><description>
Disk Drill Enterprise is software that allows you to recover files from hard drives and USB devices, external hard drives, memory cards, iPhone and iPad, drive formats like NTFS, FAT, exFAT, HFS + Mac drive, EXT2/3/4. The software provides fast scan and deep scan mode, depending on the user's needs, to save time and achieve the highest efficiency.
Features of Disk Drill Enterprise
	Users simply need one click to activate Disk Drill.
	Support to scan the entire drive and rejoin lost...
</description></item><item><title>Download OkMap Desktop 19.5.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 24 Feb 2026 22:45:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-okmap-desktop-581.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-okmap-desktop-581.html
</guid><description>
OkMap Desktop is interactive software working on the computer with web maps or digital maps bought or scanned. OkMap can also import a data vector from the most common formats and data DEM related to information height.
Through the map you can organize your path by creating waypoints , routesand tracks on the screen your computer, and upload this data to your GPS . OkMap set data high speedautomatic and estimated moving time . Furthermore OkMap provides you also have autorouting and...
</description></item><item><title>Download HWiNFO Portable 8.42</title><pubDate> Tue, 24 Feb 2026 22:44:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hwinfo-portable-11340.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hwinfo-portable-11340.html
</guid><description>
HWiNFO Portable is a professional hardware information and diagnostic tool that supports the latest components, technologies and industry standards. These tools are designed to collect and present the maximum amount of information possible about computer hardware, making them suitable for users looking for driver updates, computer manufacturers, system integrators as well as technical experts. Retrieved information is presented in a logical, easy-to-understand format and can be exported...
</description></item><item><title>Download Aidfile Recovery Software Professional 3.7.9.6</title><pubDate> Tue, 24 Feb 2026 22:43:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aidfile-recovery-software-professional-4316.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aidfile-recovery-software-professional-4316.html
</guid><description>
Aidfile Recovery Software Professional is a software small but powerful will assist you to recover files lost, deleted or damaged. It is ideal to restore data such as videos, files, office, images, folders and many other things. Professional tool this will help you to perform full scan and in-depth hard drive and partition, USB drive, memory card or removable media , to fully restore your data. This software can restore the data file from the file system partition FAT32, NTFS and ExFAT,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Dr. Hardware 2026 v26.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 24 Feb 2026 22:42:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dr-hardware-12023.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dr-hardware-12023.html
</guid><description>
Dr Hardware is a computer hardware diagnostic and information tool designed to provide detailed information about the hardware components of a computer system. This is a software program that helps users analyze and troubleshoot computer hardware for you, identify potential problems, and gather comprehensive information about system configuration.
Dr Hardware can detect and identify various hardware components installed in a computer, including processor, memory, hard drive, graphics...
</description></item><item><title>Download VovSoft OCR Reader 4.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 24 Feb 2026 22:41:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-ocr-reader-7875.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-ocr-reader-7875.html
</guid><description>
VovSoft OCR Reader is an image-based text recognition program that converts images of typed, handwritten or printed text into machine-encoded text. , whether from a scanned document or an image of a document. VovSoft OCR Reader can easily digitize scanned image files and documents on your laptop or desktop computer. This application uses the Tesseract OCR engine, which supports more than 100 languages. It uses a neural network-based OCR (LSTM) engine that focuses on line recognition, but...
</description></item><item><title>Download MiniTool Partition Wizard Pro Deluxe 13.5 + Pro Platinum</title><pubDate> Tue, 24 Feb 2026 19:49:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minitool-partition-wizard-pro-deluxe-6013.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minitool-partition-wizard-pro-deluxe-6013.html
</guid><description>
MiniTool Partition Wizard Pro Deluxe is one of the best partition managers. It does not only include all of the functions of Free, but also embedded some of the advanced partition technologies such as partition merger, NTFS conversion to FAT32, changing the size of the cluster size and conversion of the disk to basic users.
The software helps you convert partition format such as FAT MBR Disk, GPT Disk, copy and convert Dynamic Disk, change the size of the cluster, change the label,...
</description></item><item><title>Download MiniTool Partition Wizard Enterprise 13.6 + Server</title><pubDate> Tue, 24 Feb 2026 19:48:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minitool-partition-wizard-enterprise-3338.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minitool-partition-wizard-enterprise-3338.html
</guid><description>
MiniTool Partition Wizard Enterprise is a rich feature partition tool, designed to optimize the use of disk and to protect your data. It comes with a lot of powerful features that you can completely control your hard disk and partition. With a user-friendly interface and simple guidance, you can change the size of the partition, copy the disk, scan the lost parties and move the OS to the SSD easily and safely.
The features of MiniTool Partition Wizard Enterprise
	All-in-One Disk...
</description></item><item><title>Download IDM 6.4x by Ali.Dbg v20.6</title><pubDate> Tue, 24 Feb 2026 17:27:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-64x-by-alidbg-13003.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-64x-by-alidbg-13003.html
</guid><description>
IDM 6.4x by Ali.Dbg is a compact program (only 0.1 MB) used to activate Internet Download Manager, Windows 7, 8, 10, 11 operating systems and Office suite from 2016 - 2024.
Previously, it was simply a patch for the regular IDM (Internet Download Manager) software. But with recent updates, the author Ali.Dbg has added tools for WinRAR/Windows/Office (inspired by MAS:Massgravel).
In addition, with the addition of the new WinToolBox toolkit (from ChrisTitusTech) users can use it to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Google Earth Pro 7.3.7.1094</title><pubDate> Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:49:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-earth-pro-1118.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-earth-pro-1118.html
</guid><description>
Google Earth Pro is the upgraded version of Google Earth helps track earth map and share the information with others. Google has released the new version of the software package called Google Earth. The application is designed to operate with the same service, which allows you to view satellite images of planet earth in 3D mode using OpenGL technology. There is a search function by address, by subject. The seventh version has a simple interface as well as the ability to display a number of...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDF-XChange Editor Plus 10.8.3.408</title><pubDate> Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:48:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-xchange-editor-plus-645.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-xchange-editor-plus-645.html
</guid><description>
PDF-XChange Editor Plus is the editor, PDF viewer, compact, fast with many features, add-ons, professional. When using the PDF-XChange Editor Plus, easy for users to create, view, edit, annotate, OCR and digital signing PDF files, plus much more.
PDF-XChange Editor is a PDF editing full-featured. With the help of it, you can edit, fix, add, or delete text easily. Graphics can also be moved, resized or removed.
Features PDF-XChange Editor Plus
Edit documents
	Use a variety of editing...
</description></item><item><title>Download EmEditor Pro 26.0.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:47:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-emeditor-pro-69.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-emeditor-pro-69.html
</guid><description>
EmEditor Pro - the professional version of editor text powerful for programmers, web developers and ordinary users with illumination of syntax and Unicode support. The features of the editor such as search and replace in files using regular expressions, automatic code detect, bookmark link and address email, block selection mode, configure the button bar, menu, font and elements color. With each language you can set separate configuration.
EmEditor Pro - text Editor professional
The...
</description></item><item><title>Download Scooter Beyond Compare 5.2.0.31950</title><pubDate> Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:46:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-scooter-beyond-compare-2649.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-scooter-beyond-compare-2649.html
</guid><description>
Scooter Beyond Compare is a powerful tool to compare quickly and easily the files and folders. This program provides you with a full report on work done so you can compare the complete data on the file, folder, folder with speed and file size, very fast and incredible, time changes on the file as well as the compared bytes Do byte this information. With the strong command of this program, you can merge the changes, synchronize files, create a report to record.
Scooter Beyond Compare -...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDF-XChange Pro 10.8.3.408</title><pubDate> Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:45:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-xchange-editor-pro-3422.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-xchange-editor-pro-3422.html
</guid><description>
PDF-XChange Editor Pro is an application to manipulate and create PDF versatile, offering a wide range of useful features and powerful will help you to easily work with PDF files. This application is very flexible and allows you to easily create and modify PDF files. PDF-XChange Editor Pro provides a powerful set of tools and flexibility to work with PDF files, such as editor PDF-XChange new, utilities series, OFFice2PDF and the Addin tool Bar allows you to easily convert multiple file...
</description></item><item><title>Download PIDKey Lite 1.64.4 b54</title><pubDate> Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:44:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pidkey-lite-2693.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pidkey-lite-2693.html
</guid><description>
PIDKey Lite is a program intended to show the renovation and preservation in the database of the product information to check "validity" of the key Microsoft from the famous program we or is Ratiborus and VAMT. Program PIDKey LiteIt is the successor of the PIDKey. and I got out of it the idea the best program (allows you To add new keyboard with two methods additional mode key).
The program has a number of configuration integration, but you can also create custom profiles by themselves....
</description></item><item><title>Download reaConverter Pro 8.0.200</title><pubDate> Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:43:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html
</guid><description>
reaConverter Pro is software image processing feature with batch conversion and image editing periodically becomes simple. eaConverter also provide command line utilities allow you to process images automatically, thus helping you shorten the time for other work.
reaConverter Pro integrated powerful tool of Uber with many great features. It provides advanced solutions to process and adjust images. Management of the conversion process the base image with the latest version of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Google Chrome 145.0.7632.117</title><pubDate> Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:43:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-chrome-1012.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-chrome-1012.html
</guid><description>
Google Chrome web browser is the most used today. Support surf the web, listen to music, watch movies, play web game effective no jerky lag with the internet connection stable. When you are surfing the web or performing an important task, whether it is operation big or small, work or entertainment, then Chrome has the smart features and the speed you need to make, create and explore on the net.
The latest version of Google Chrome is the third 114. But we are providing for users Google...
</description></item><item><title>Download DisplayFusion Pro 12.0.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:41:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-displayfusion-pro-1576.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-displayfusion-pro-1576.html
</guid><description>
DisplayFusion Pro is software that support open computer dual screen with good performance and smooth operation the most. With DisplayFusion Pro, you can add a taskbar to every monitor acts and looks just like the Windows taskbar. Or take advantage of background image support multi-screen, advanced Integrated Flickr to search for images and the hot key manager window can be fully customized. Here are just a few of the many things that DisplayFusion can do.
DisplayFusion Pro - open...
</description></item></channel></rss>