<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 14:10:12 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 14:10:12 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Syncovery Premium 11.12.8.162</title><pubDate> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 17:09:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncovery-pro-enterprise-232.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncovery-pro-enterprise-232.html
</guid><description>
Syncovery Pro Enterprise is a great application used to back up data and to synchronize personal computers, servers, laptops, notepads and storage online. The software comes with support for FTP and secure FTP servers, SSH, WebDAV, Amazon S3, http, update the part file, ZIP compression, data encryption, and schedule automatic backups.
Syncovery Pro Enterprise have the ability to freely select files and folders across the whole folder hierarchy in tree view and supports email...
</description></item><item><title>Download PeaZip 10.9.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 17:09:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-peazip-1800.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-peazip-1800.html
</guid><description>
PeaZip is an Archive Utility And Compressed open-source, support multiple compression formats. It lets you create 7Z, ARC, BZ2, GZ, PAQ / ZPAQ, PEA, QUAD / BALZ, TAR, UPX, and ZIP, and enables you to open and extract 133 format additional storage, including RAR. PeaZip has the ability to open and extract over 150 file formats compressed downloads, have the ability to create and switch between multiple file formats, different background on an interface intuitive and easy to use. In...
</description></item><item><title>Download iDownerGo 10.14.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 17:08:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idownergo-12439.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idownergo-12439.html
</guid><description>
iDownerGo is the best tool that allows users to download videos, music and playlists from more than 10,000 streaming sites. It can easily convert videos to MP4, MOV, MKV, 3GP, AAC, WAV, FLAC and other formats on PC and Mac. With this amazing program, users can enjoy their favorite media content without restrictions.
iDownerGo Features
	Download any video up to 8K resolution
	Download 1080p videos online from over 10,000 popular streaming sites easily.
	Save any video in various...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Saver Pro 10.14.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 16:57:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-saver-6830.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-saver-6830.html
</guid><description>
YT Saver is a software that supports downloading Video, Audio, Playlist from 10,000+ websites, Convert Video to MP4, MOV, AAC, WAV and more. YT Saver is a powerful downloader that allows you to save video and audio for free. The output format of the high-speed converter is high-quality MP4, MP3. Fully compatible with iPhone, iPad, iTunes, iMovie, Android Phone and more.
Supported Input Formats:
	Video: MP4, M4V, 3GP, MPEG, DAT, AVI, ASF, WMV, VOB, MKV, FLV, 3GS, 3G2, F4V, WEBM, TS,...
</description></item><item><title>Download VideoPad Video Editor Pro 18.10 Beta</title><pubDate> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 16:56:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-videopad-video-editor-pro-268.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-videopad-video-editor-pro-268.html
</guid><description>
VideoPad Video Editor Pro is software edit video from any camcorder, DV camcorder, VHS player or webcam for best quality. The interface of this utility is divided into several parts (for example: list of multi-media, Effects, transitions, Files, Clips, video track, audio track, overlay), which makes everything seem difficult to operate. You can capture videos from camcorder or other devices like webcam or capture card TV and after you have added files and sequence clips to the queue, you...
</description></item><item><title>Download TeXstudio 4.9.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 16:56:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-texstudio-7399.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-texstudio-7399.html
</guid><description>
TeXstudio is an integrated writing environment for creating LaTeX documents. The goal of TeXstudio is to make writing LaTeX as easy and comfortable as possible. Therefore TeXstudio has many features such as syntax highlighting, built-in viewer, reference checking and various assistants.
Features of TeXstudio
	Advanced Syntax Highlighting
	Checking direct references
	Built-in PDF viewer
	Live Preview
	Complete Latex Command and Check Syntax
	Live grammar check
	Local and global...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDF Suite Pro + OCR 20.0.37.21544</title><pubDate> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 16:55:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-suite-ocr-6691.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-suite-ocr-6691.html
</guid><description>
PDF Suite is the software that provides the most necessary functions such as reading, creating and editing basic PDF. You will be able to open, save, print and mark any PDF files using PDF Suite. You can see the presentation, CV, the Book of Electronics and many other electronic documents. PDF Suite has a modern conversion tool that can transfer any files that can be printed into a fully readable PDF document 100%. Convert Word, Excel, PowerPoint and other MS Office documents to PDF...
</description></item><item><title>Download Exportizer Enterprise 10.3.0.880</title><pubDate> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 16:55:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-exportizer-pro-470.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-exportizer-pro-470.html
</guid><description>
Exportizer Pro is software export base, robust data that allows view, edit and export the database to a data file, text, clipboard. Exportizer Pro is a software tool effective and simple, can be used to help individuals view, filter and copy an entire database to clipboard or convert it to another format.
Simple interface and no complex also indicates that Exportizer Pro meet the system requirements, the application can run on most operating systems.
The main window of Exportizer Pro...
</description></item><item><title>Download Telegram for Desktop 6.5.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 16:54:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-telegram-3376.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-telegram-3376.html
</guid><description>
Telegram is an instant messaging service and voice over IP services on the cloud platform. Client application Telegram is available for Android, iOS, Windows Phone, Windows NT, macOS, and Linux. Users can send messages and exchange photos, videos, stickers, audio and files of any kind.
Telegram - Messaging and free phone calls
Telegram seamless sync across all your devices and can be used on desktop, tablet and phone. You can send unlimited amount of messages, photos, videos and files...
</description></item><item><title>Download XL-Connector 3.6.45.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 16:54:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xl-connector-12415.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xl-connector-12415.html
</guid><description>
XL-Connector is a popular plugin that securely integrates Excel and Salesforce to export, import, refresh and transform data seamlessly with ultra-fast api connection. It provides Salesforce administrators with a comprehensive toolbox that easily performs data and metadata management activities in a familiar Excel environment.
Features
Export from Salesforce to Excel
	Get data from existing Salesforce reports or build your own SOQL queries directly into Excel.
Import data into...
</description></item><item><title>Download AllmapSoft Google Satellite Maps Downloader 8.416</title><pubDate> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 16:54:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-google-satellite-maps-downloader-687.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-google-satellite-maps-downloader-687.html
</guid><description>
AllmapSoft Google Satellite Maps Downloader is software help download map images from google maps on computer for you to get the satellite images from google map. All the downloaded photos will be saved on disk. You can see the map is downloaded by viewer Or you can combine them into the map BMP, big. It supports proxy server. And you can easily get the longitude and latitude of each image tile small download.
You can use offline maps in GIS software such as Global Mapper, QGIS,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Whatsapp - WS Tool Pro 8.6.6</title><pubDate> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 16:53:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-whatsapp-ws-tool-pro-13751.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-whatsapp-ws-tool-pro-13751.html
</guid><description>
Introducing WSTool Pro, easy-to-use bulk marketing software that takes your personal or professional WhatsApp to the next level. It helps you engage with your audience efficiently and effectively, all from a PC running Windows 7 Service Pack 1 or higher.
WSTool Pro is the ultimate WhatsApp bulk marketing software, offering a wide range of features to optimize your campaigns and enhance communication with your audience. From unlimited messages to personalized content and advanced...
</description></item><item><title>Download CrawlRhino SEO Crawler PRO 1.1.15</title><pubDate> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 16:53:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-crawlrhino-seo-crawler-pro-14273.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-crawlrhino-seo-crawler-pro-14273.html
</guid><description>
Ensuring your website is properly indexed and has optimal SEO aspects can be more difficult than you think, but luckily, web crawlers like CrawlRhino SEO Crawler can professionally assist you. This application allows you to perform website crawls to analyze site structure, find broken links, duplicate entries, as well as perform in-depth SEO audits and generate reports that can be used to improve performance and resolve upcoming issues.
How CrawlRhino SEO Crawler Works
CrawlRhino SEO...
</description></item><item><title>Download Retail Barcode 5.7</title><pubDate> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 16:52:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-retail-barcode-2586.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-retail-barcode-2586.html
</guid><description>
Retail Barcode a product of genuine VovSoft, is a cashier app can help users track product sales. This tool allows a person to identify customers, as well as affiliate sales of credit products to individual customers. This utility has value to any who are trading in the management of small shops. It is an ideal solution for the small shop faced with many types of products to be processed. Stores that don't stock items with barcodes can avoid this problem by simply creating a custom code...
</description></item><item><title>Download Calcpad 7.6.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 16:52:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-calcpad-12576.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-calcpad-12576.html
</guid><description>
Calcpad is free software for mathematical and engineering calculations. It is a flexible and modern programmable calculator with Html report generator. Calcpad uses a simple programming language that is fast and easy to learn. It does not require any special programming skills, which makes it suitable for engineers without any computer programming background. You can create calculation notes simply by writing your formula and text, enclosed in 'quotation marks'.
The program includes...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft OneDrive 25.243.1211.0001</title><pubDate> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 16:51:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-onedrive-48.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-onedrive-48.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft OneDrive is a client application file transmission to the service cloud storage of Microsoft. If you are familiar with Dropbox, you will find that OneDrive works in a similar way. It creates a OneDrive folder and any files you copy into the folder will automatically be synced and uploaded to the cloud service OneDrive.
Microsoft OneDrive
You can access your files from the client application other on PC. Mac or mobile devices as well as web interface. OneDrive also allows you...
</description></item><item><title>Download PPTube 10.14.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 16:51:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pptube-12556.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pptube-12556.html
</guid><description>
PPTube Video Downloader allows you to download HD videos easily, from 720p, 1080p, 2K, 4K and 8K. You can save multiple videos at the same time. Just copy multiple video URLs from various websites and paste them into PPTube Downloader, then you can download multiple videos in seconds.
In addition, you can download HD videos from Instagram, TikTok, Facebook, Apple Music, Vimeo, adult websites, etc. and convert them to MP4, MP3, MOV, AAC and more than 20 other output formats. PPTube...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sure Cuts A Lot Pro 6.081</title><pubDate> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 16:50:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sure-cuts-a-lot-pro-2614.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sure-cuts-a-lot-pro-2614.html
</guid><description>
Sure Cuts A Lot Pro is this program offers you a set of drawing tools and you get a work environment, comprehensive, where you can create interesting shapes and cut them by a special electronic. The intelligent combination of fonts OpenType and TrueType in your system, in conjunction with the library program rich text, photos, and other input, will help you create everything you can imagine.
This app is compatible with hundreds of font style and provide support for various cutting...
</description></item><item><title>Download AllMapSoft Offline Map Maker 8.366</title><pubDate> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 16:50:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-offline-map-maker-656.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-offline-map-maker-656.html
</guid><description>
AllMapSoft Offline Map Maker is software create, organize, offline map from Google Maps, Yahoo maps, Bing maps and Openstreetmap. You can view offline maps downloaded with map viewer offline. And you can zoom out or zoom in the offline map or export map under the file format .BMP with file world xxx.bpw, and can output files xxx.map for OziExplorer. If you want to make a offline map of your city by yourself, it is very useful for you.
Features AllMapSoft Offline Map Maker
	You can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Muziza YouTube Downloader Converter 9.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 16:49:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-muziza-youtube-downloader-converter-3972.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-muziza-youtube-downloader-converter-3972.html
</guid><description>
Muziza YouTube Downloader Converter is a tool to create conditions for an attractive interface and many features to help you to download video clips from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion, Instagram and other sites. Muziza YouTube Downloader Converter can also download the video UHD 8K, 5K, 4K, QHD 2K, HD 1080p and 720p from YouTube. The app allows you download only audio stream from YouTube and save as MP3. You don't need to download the entire video file.
Muziza YouTube Downloader...
</description></item><item><title>Download QueueExplorer Professional 5.0.69</title><pubDate> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 16:49:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-queueexplorer-professional-4823.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-queueexplorer-professional-4823.html
</guid><description>
QueueExplorer is a tool indispensable to work with queues and messages: understand and manage your system, find the error and fix it. Or you can use QueueExplorer to sort them by any field available. Because of the sort display the messages in another order with them will be handled, QueueExplorer more columns of Ms Ms # # so you can still see what is processed first.
The features of QueueExplorer
Move, copy or delete messages
	Messages can be handled the same as in process explorer,...
</description></item><item><title>Download vMail OST to PST Converter 15.0.0.3</title><pubDate> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 16:48:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vmail-ost-to-pst-converter-13620.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vmail-ost-to-pst-converter-13620.html
</guid><description>
vMail OST to PST Converter is the best email recovery and conversion tool for Outlook offline data files. This software can easily convert corrupted and inaccessible OST to easily accessible PST file and recover all mailboxes, contacts, calendars, etc. without losing any data.
Features
	Import into IMAP, Gmail, Yahoo! Mail, Yandex, Rediff Mail Accounts
	Ability to repair corrupted or damaged OST files.
	Recover all mailbox components including Inbox, Outbox, Sent Items and Deleted...
</description></item><item><title>Download SEO Checker 10.6</title><pubDate> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 16:48:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-seo-checker-2514.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-seo-checker-2514.html
</guid><description>
SEO Checker (A product of genuine VOVSoft) is a tool to analyze all type of web site or personal web page. The software works in many different ways, it can help you discover the content that you have specifically chosen to analyze from suitable site. As the authors write, the program, as this program allows you to plan for your SEO strategy by providing information about the function of it, you will get a set of keyword analysis and tracking the reverse link.
SEO Checker - Support SEO...
</description></item><item><title>Download Robin YouTube Video Downloader Pro 7.2.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 16:47:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-video-downloader-pro-2828.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-video-downloader-pro-2828.html
</guid><description>
YouTube Video Downloader Pro is a Windows application professional to download and convert videos from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion and thousands of video sharing sites, other. It accelerates your download up to 5 times. YouTube Video Downloader Pro allows you to download multiple videos at the same time. It also allows you to pause, resume and cancel a download at any time.
YouTube Video Downloader Pro - Download online videos on social networks
Features of YouTube Video Downloader...
</description></item><item><title>Download CrawlRhino SEO Monitor 1.0.9</title><pubDate> Sun, 08 Feb 2026 16:47:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-crawlrhino-seo-monitor-14292.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-crawlrhino-seo-monitor-14292.html
</guid><description>
CrawlRhino SEO Monitor is a professional desktop monitoring solution designed for digital agencies, SEO consultants, and businesses that depend on stable website performance.
It continuously tracks your site's uptime, downtime, and important SEO tag changes — including titles, meta descriptions, H1 headings, robots directives, and canonicals — so you can immediately identify any issues that could impact rankings or user experience.
Core Features of CrawlRhino SEO...
</description></item></channel></rss>