<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 15:41:53 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 15:41:53 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download FakeDriveCheck 4.68</title><pubDate> Mon, 08 Sep 2025 18:38:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fakedrivecheck-11322.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fakedrivecheck-11322.html
</guid><description>
FakeDriveCheck is a simple utility you can run to verify if your USB stick or MicroSD card is fake. It's easy to get and use, making it a good choice for anyone skeptical about the authenticity of their external storage.
FakeDriveCheck Features
	Existing files will not be destroyed while the USB drive is verified.
	Super fast verification.
	No need to unplug and plug in.
	Hot Plug: FakeDriveCheck detects USB drives
	inserted after FakeDriveCheck is started.
</description></item><item><title>Download 12-Ants 6.77</title><pubDate> Mon, 08 Sep 2025 18:38:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-12-ants-2727.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-12-ants-2727.html
</guid><description>
12-Ants is a free software created little ants crawling on the computer screen, making your computer back up is more fun when work. You peace of mind because this app is free software and mobile, so perfect if you want to take it on a USB memory stick and want to play trick your friends.
12-Ants - Ants crawling on screen
The features of 12-Ants
	Software very small
	5 algorithm for motion
	3-50 desktop-Ants
	Adjust the speed
	Color comments can adjust (Red, Black, blue, Green,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Duplicate File Finder Professional 2025 v406</title><pubDate> Mon, 08 Sep 2025 18:32:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-duplicate-file-finder-professional-4425.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-duplicate-file-finder-professional-4425.html
</guid><description>
Duplicate File Finder Professional is a compact application helps you quickly find and remove files duplicate on the computer. With Duplicate File Finder Professional you can choose any folder on the hard drive or use the folder standard user and our app will analyze the deep content of the selected folder to copy. It will take only a few seconds. The files will be compared by the hash algorithm MD5, which means they will be compared by content, not by name. Then, use our convenient...
</description></item><item><title>Download IsMyTouchScreenOK 3.01</title><pubDate> Mon, 08 Sep 2025 18:31:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ismytouchscreenok-11229.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ismytouchscreenok-11229.html
</guid><description>
With IsMyTouchScreenOK you can simply but very quickly check if there are any bad contacts on your touch screen. It can be used to test the functionality of a new touch screen before purchasing or to test a purchased touch screen during the warranty period. You may receive a replacement product after the manufacturer reports a contact failure.
By touching and testing all areas of the touchscreen with one or more fingers, you can ensure that the touchscreen is...
</description></item><item><title>Download Chief Architect Premier X17 v27.2.1.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 08 Sep 2025 18:31:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chief-architect-premier-1243.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chief-architect-premier-1243.html
</guid><description>
Chief Architect Premier is a program that is almost ideal for interior design, successfully combined interface, user friendly, easy to use and library cliparts rich. After download at on taiwebs.com you will not need to draw each line in a long time and tedious, and is a master in the mouse only exact - thanks to the option to connect the walls, foundation and frame of home appear in just a few seconds.
Chief Architect Premier - interior design
The program Chief Architect Premier...
</description></item><item><title>Download ClassicMenu by Reuschtools 4.68</title><pubDate> Mon, 08 Sep 2025 18:30:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-classicmenu-by-reuschtools-13987.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-classicmenu-by-reuschtools-13987.html
</guid><description>
ClassicMenu by Reuschtools is a software tool designed for Windows that allows users to switch between the classic and the new context menu introduced in Windows 11. The tool allows the classic context menu to be enabled or disabled, which is useful for users who prefer the traditional full context menu over the newer compact version with fewer items. ClassicMenu is free, requires no installation (click to run), and is accessible from the Start Menu after installing Reuschtools.
When...
</description></item><item><title>Download YouTube Music Desktop App 2.0.10</title><pubDate> Mon, 08 Sep 2025 18:30:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-music-desktop-app-3913.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-music-desktop-app-3913.html
</guid><description>
YouTube Music Desktop App is an application based on the Electron provides the user an alternative solution, allowing them to access services directly from an app to the desktop. It is a process wrapped simply around the user interface site, so nothing too spectacular, but it performs work. YouTube Music Desktop App nearly identical to the version based on the browser of the player, with a few additions, such as lyrics, key media and media controls on the task bar.
YouTube Music Desktop...
</description></item><item><title>Download IntraWEB Ultimate 16.1.5</title><pubDate> Mon, 08 Sep 2025 18:30:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intraweb-ultimate-2007.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intraweb-ultimate-2007.html
</guid><description>
IntraWEB Ultimate is a tool to build the website. With this tool, the developer can create the page using the same method used to build the Windows program. Because the HTML page directly from the concept design to the user's computer does not download a bit more complicated and in fact is required from web server. So, the template IntraWeb on the server and download server and displays them to the user. Things technology direction of the IntraWEB Ultimate provides part flexibility and...
</description></item><item><title>Download AnyRail 7.111</title><pubDate> Mon, 08 Sep 2025 18:29:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anyrail-7570.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anyrail-7570.html
</guid><description>
AnyRail is probably the easiest to use model railway design tool available today. It's also completely standalone, so you can build with almost any track. Love your layout design with AnyRail to make sure everything fits. AnyRail lets you get through the planning or editing phase of your content and you don't need to be a geek to create successful designs.
Designing with AnyRail is like operating an ultimate model railway store. We've included every train set component you can find, so...
</description></item><item><title>Download Top Process Monitor 11.4</title><pubDate> Mon, 08 Sep 2025 18:29:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-top-process-monitor-2753.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-top-process-monitor-2753.html
</guid><description>
Top Process Monitor is a small utility that allows you to view the processes are using most CPU, memory and other important components in your system. It can be easily installed and configured, even by inexperienced users. The interface of the application is based on a small frame that you can move to any location on the screen. So, you can check the current CPU, along with the application and the total stream is included.
Top Process Monitor - View operation, the CPU, computer...
</description></item><item><title>Download ArchiWIZARD 2026.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 08 Sep 2025 18:28:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-archiwizard-3d-4362.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-archiwizard-3d-4362.html
</guid><description>
ArchiWIZARD is software that analyzes real-time 3D model-based BIM is directly connected with the solution of architectural CAD. ArchiWIZARD provides analysis of heat, light, solar and shadow, accurate simulation of renewable energy (photovoltaic system &amp;amp; solar thermal). It embed the simulation program building energy EnergyPlus v8.1 (STD) to combine performance analysis building more accurate with the ability to use advanced user interface ArchiWIZARD and interactive capabilities....
</description></item><item><title>Download FeelYourSound House Engine Pro 2.1.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 08 Sep 2025 18:27:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-feelyoursound-house-engine-pro-9248.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-feelyoursound-house-engine-pro-9248.html
</guid><description>
FeelYourSound House Engine Pro is a software plugin designed for electronic music producers and DJs. The plugin offers a wide range of tools for creating and editing music at home, including chord progressions, basses, and drum samples. HouseEngine turns your chord progressions into expressive piano beats, deep bass, catchy melodies, and sparkling arpeggios. Give HouseEngine your chords, and this plug-in creates authentic and professional MIDI samples for you.
Features of FeelYourSound...
</description></item><item><title>Download YouTube Music Desktop App (Unofficial) 3.11.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 08 Sep 2025 18:26:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-music-desktop-app-unofficial-12770.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-music-desktop-app-unofficial-12770.html
</guid><description>
YouTube Music is an unofficial, cross-platform, open-source YouTube Music Desktop application with a built-in ad blocker and downloader. It has a native interface, aiming to keep the original interface combined with a framework for custom plugins: change YouTube Music to your needs (style, content, features), enable/disable plugins with just one click.
Available plugins:
	Ad Blocker: Block all ads and tracks instantly
	Album Actions: Add Dislike, Dislike, Like and Dislike buttons to...
</description></item><item><title>Download HOFA IQ-Limiter 2.0.7</title><pubDate> Mon, 08 Sep 2025 18:26:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hofa-iq-limiter-10269.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hofa-iq-limiter-10269.html
</guid><description>
HOFA IQ-Limiter is a truly next-generation mastering limiter. At its core is an extremely flexible set of modes. You'll find the right limit for every application and every genre. Additionally, you will find V1 Fast, Med &amp;amp; Award-winning slow. This makes the IQ-Series Limiter V2 fully downward compatible.
Features of HOFA IQ-Limiter
	Next generation true peak mastering limiter
	6 impressive modes for a variety of sounds
	Innovative and user-friendly interface
	Highly accurate LUFS...
</description></item><item><title>Download UJAM Usynth 1.4.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 08 Sep 2025 18:24:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ujam-usynth-9386.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ujam-usynth-9386.html
</guid><description>
UJAM Usynth is designed to provide musicians and producers with a flexible and user-friendly synthesizer for creating electronic sounds. It provides a wide range of parameters and controls that allow you to shape and control the sound to suit your musical needs.
Features of UJAM Usynth
	UJAM Usynth typically uses a powerful audio engine capable of producing various types of electronic sounds, including lead, bass, accompaniment, and more.
	It comes with a library of presets, providing...
</description></item><item><title>Download Password Tech (PwTech) 3.5.8</title><pubDate> Mon, 08 Sep 2025 18:24:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-password-tech-5036.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-password-tech-5036.html
</guid><description>
Password Tech is a program to create strong passwords have the ability to create a large number of passwords is secured by a password, the password can pronounce is, password-based form, the passphrase including of from and password written in the script. The password can be stored in the database is encrypted along with the user name, URL, notes, etc. Password Tech offers many options to customize the password according to the different needs of users, and individual commands with Lua...
</description></item><item><title>Download FeelYourSound Trance Engine Pro 2.1.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 08 Sep 2025 18:23:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-feelyoursound-trance-engine-pro-9259.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-feelyoursound-trance-engine-pro-9259.html
</guid><description>
FeelYourSound Trance Engine Pro is a software plugin designed to create Trance music. It offers a wide range of features and tools that can be used to create dynamic and complex tracks, including step sequencers, chord progressions, arpeggio generators, and more. It also includes a chord progressions feature that allows users to create and experiment with different chord progressions. The plugin includes various preset processes and users can also create their own custom ones.
Features...
</description></item><item><title>Download Explzh 9.84</title><pubDate> Mon, 08 Sep 2025 18:23:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-explzh-2278.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-explzh-2278.html
</guid><description>
Explzh is software that originated from Japan. This program works with most formats, can extract the file directly to FTP server, split large files into multiple smaller size. I would like to note that the storage supports encryption of files compressed using AES algorithm, has a system of tabs in the main window, you can search for the information you need in the repository and work with files, batch mode is done.
Explzh - Compress and decompress file
The file is support work with the...
</description></item><item><title>Download VovSoft Http Requester 6.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 08 Sep 2025 18:22:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-http-requester-6570.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-http-requester-6570.html
</guid><description>
VovSoft Http Requester is a simple tool for asking POST and GET queries. The POST and GET are the two basic requirements in HTTP, each with its own role, but both are based on the demand-feedback protocol. A list of URLs that can be filled in manually or glued to a private school, while the input name and corresponding values also have a reserved area.
The user can add new input data in a manual manner, but there is also an option to import that data from the CSV file. Right next to,...
</description></item><item><title>Download SmartSystemMenu 2.32.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 08 Sep 2025 18:18:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-smartsystemmenu-6018.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-smartsystemmenu-6018.html
</guid><description>
SmartSystemMenu will help to work with more windows becoming a more efficient process with many useful functions to arrange your work. It can be attached to the title bar menu for easy access. The fact that it can be portable is just another bonus because you can quickly upload it to the flash drive to use on any machine you might be using.
SmartSystemMenu will be a significant upgrade to the default Windows installation with the ability to be added to help with window management...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tier1App yCrash 3.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 08 Sep 2025 18:17:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tier1app-ycrash-13868.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tier1app-ycrash-13868.html
</guid><description>
yCrash is a root cause analysis tool developed by Tier1App that helps identify the source of complex manufacturing issues. The tool is designed to quickly determine why issues like CPU spikes, memory degradation, or increased response times occur, rather than simply identifying what the problem is.
Key features and functionality of yCrash include:
	Automatic data collection and analysis The tool collects and analyzes over 18 different artifacts, including GC logs, stream backups, and...
</description></item><item><title>Download FeelYourSound ChordPotion 2.5.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 08 Sep 2025 18:17:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-feelyoursound-chordpotion-9853.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-feelyoursound-chordpotion-9853.html
</guid><description>
Create powerful and impressive harmonic phrases within seconds. ChordPotion is a MIDI plug-in that turns any chord progression into new riffs and tunes in real time. The MIDI ChordPotion (VST + AU) audio sequencer and effects plug-in is the fastest way to create powerful and impressive mixes within seconds.
Features of FeelYourSound ChordPotion
	Speed up your workflow. Make more great music.
	Create complex MIDI in minutes. Say goodbye to the annoying pencil tool session.
	Become a...
</description></item><item><title>Download Telegram for Desktop 6.1.3</title><pubDate> Mon, 08 Sep 2025 18:17:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-telegram-3376.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-telegram-3376.html
</guid><description>
Telegram is an instant messaging service and voice over IP services on the cloud platform. Client application Telegram is available for Android, iOS, Windows Phone, Windows NT, macOS, and Linux. Users can send messages and exchange photos, videos, stickers, audio and files of any kind.
Telegram - Messaging and free phone calls
Telegram seamless sync across all your devices and can be used on desktop, tablet and phone. You can send unlimited amount of messages, photos, videos and files...
</description></item><item><title>Download HOFA SYSTEM All Bundle 11.0.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 08 Sep 2025 15:20:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hofa-system-all-bundle-14143.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hofa-system-all-bundle-14143.html
</guid><description>
HOFA SYSTEM provides you with 32 premium plugins, which you can use in your DAW or connect them together in the advanced SYSTEM environment.
	For mixing, mastering and sound design
	With advanced dynamics, EQ, reverb, FX, modulation and saturation effects and more
	Intuitive and fast workflow for multi-band, mid/side, parallel and dual mono routing
	All Plugins can be used as inserts and in HOFA SYSTEM
</description></item><item><title>Download HE - Hardware Read and Write Utility 1.25.09.05</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Sep 2025 17:46:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-he-hardware-read-and-write-utility-4287.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-he-hardware-read-and-write-utility-4287.html
</guid><description>
HE - Hardware Read and Write Utility is a powerful utility intended for hardware engineer, engineer, BIOS developer, driver, engineer, QA engineers, performance test engineers, diagnostic, etc., this utility access almost all the computer hardware, including PCI (PCI Express), index / Data, PCI, memory, index memory / Data space I / O, Index I / O / Data, Super I / O, DIMM SPD, CPU The registers MSR, screen, SMART, physical area of the hard drive identification data, ATA, dump tables ACPI...
</description></item></channel></rss>