<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 13:50:17 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 13:50:17 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Danil Pristupov Fork 2.15</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 16:49:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fork-6879.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fork-6879.html
</guid><description>
Fork is a great Git client app that allows you to keep tabs on every file line so you can know who is the last person to make changes. The simple and intuitive design of this app helps the management of all of your warehouses much easier. The Fork interface is extremely friendly to users. There is a long list of repositories, branches, origins, tags and archives on the left side of the screen.
With Fork, you can also search and open any of the repositories quickly, from the top of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Executor 2.1.12</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 16:49:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-executor-271.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-executor-271.html
</guid><description>
Executor for windows is a software alternative premium customization features for the Windows "Run" and "Search Programs". When you press WIN + Z and provides the search results instant, as-you-type for any keywords you enter. By default, Executor will index all the Desktop and Start Menu and you can easily expand the search range by adding the folder location additional.
Executor for windows
The program comes with a list of commands built in which you can use to quickly access many...
</description></item><item><title>Download ProtonVPN 4.3.9</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 16:48:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-protonvpn-10433.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-protonvpn-10433.html
</guid><description>
ProtonVPN app for Windows is the best way to stay safe and private while surfing the internet. It is open source, easy to use, and packed with useful security features. ProtonVPN will secure your connection by routing your traffic through multiple servers to protect you against advanced network-based attacks.
It helps keep your IP address safe if something goes wrong with your VPN connection. If your VPN connection fails, the kill switch feature will prevent your device from connecting...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sygic GPS Navigation &amp;amp; Maps 25.7.0-2494</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 16:22:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sygic-gps-navigation-maps-8606.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sygic-gps-navigation-maps-8606.html
</guid><description>
Sygic GPS Navigation &amp;amp; Maps is the most downloaded GPS navigation app in the world, trusted by more than 200 million drivers. Offline 3D maps stored on your phone for GPS navigation without an internet connection. We update our maps for free multiple times each year so you can always rely on Sygic GPS Navigation.
Navigate anywhere, even without an Internet connection
	Offline maps of all the countries in the world, from TomTom and other providers
	Free map updates several times...
</description></item><item><title>Download Shazam: Find Music &amp;amp; Concerts 16.22.0-251204</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 16:21:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-shazam-music-discovery-10763.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-shazam-music-discovery-10763.html
</guid><description>
Shazam will identify any song in seconds. Discover, artists, lyrics, videos &amp;amp; playlists, all for free. Over 1 billion installs and counting. Use Pop-up Shazam to identify music in any app - Instagram, YouTube, TikTok... No connection? No problem! Shazam while offline.
Features of Shazam: Music Discovery
	Find the name of any song in seconds.
	Listen and add to Apple Music playlists.
	Follow along with time-synced lyrics.
	Watch music videos from Apple Music or YouTube.
	Enable...
</description></item><item><title>Download FolderSync Pro FolderSync Pro</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 16:21:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-foldersync-pro-8221.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-foldersync-pro-8221.html
</guid><description>
FolderSync Pro allows users to synchronize files and folders between their mobile devices and various cloud storage services, such as Dropbox, Google Drive and OneDrive. Back up music, pictures, and other important files from your phone to your cloud storage, or vice versa. It has never been easier. Automation support with Tasker and similar programs allows granular control over your synchronization process.
FolderSync contains a full file manager, allowing you to manage your files...
</description></item><item><title>Download Speedtest by Ookla 6.5.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 16:20:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-speedtest-by-ookla-for-android-8605.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-speedtest-by-ookla-for-android-8605.html
</guid><description>
Speedtest by Ookla is a popular online service that allows users to measure the speed of their internet connection. The service works by sending small amounts of data to a user's device and measuring the time it takes for that data to return to the server. Based on this measurement, the service provides reports on the user's download and upload speeds as well as connection latency.
Features of Ookla Speedtest
	Explore your downloads, uploads, and pings
	The only Internet connection...
</description></item><item><title>Download Gaia GPS: Offroad Hiking Maps 2025.8 build 10267</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 16:20:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-gaia-gps-offroad-hiking-maps-8610.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-gaia-gps-offroad-hiking-maps-8610.html
</guid><description>
Gaia GPS is a navigation app that provides hiking maps, topographic maps, and satellite images for outdoor enthusiasts. It allows users to plan trips, navigate the wilderness, and track their progress. The app is available for both iOS and Android devices, and offers a premium subscription for offline maps, aerial imagery, and advanced features.
Features of Gaia GPS for Android
	Offline maps: Ability to download maps for offline use, ideal for use in areas with limited or no Internet...
</description></item><item><title>Download Fluids Particle Simulation LWP 12.1.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 16:20:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-fluids-particle-simulation-lwp-12083.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-fluids-particle-simulation-lwp-12083.html
</guid><description>
This is a quick and relaxing app that helps calm down and relieve stress. Be creative, create satisfying and calming digital art! Our sandbox game &amp;amp; fluid flow simulation creates beautiful liquids, particles and slimes. You can also create live wallpapers (LWP)! Are you anxious or looking for a stress relief game? This game is here to help!
Features:
	Experience stress relief while simulating fluid physics, with multiple settings (color intensity, vortex, visuals, flow...
</description></item><item><title>Download Clear Wave - Water Eject Pro 1.17</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 16:19:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-clear-wave-water-eject-pro-11088.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-clear-wave-water-eject-pro-11088.html
</guid><description>
Clear Wave app removes water from both speakers on your Phone by playing extremely low, high frequency sounds. We have developed an algorithm that includes various sounds and vibrations that intelligently expel water and dust.
Decibel meter - calculates the noise level near the phone. This may help you buy a quieter washing machine or avoid noisy rooms to avoid earaches.
Volume booster - improves speaker sound after cleaning it from water.
Sound recorder - when you measure noise with...
</description></item><item><title>Download Librera PRO - Book reader 9.1.35</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 16:19:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-librera-pro-all-my-books-9008.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-librera-pro-all-my-books-9008.html
</guid><description>
PRO Librera Reader is an easy-to-use and highly configurable reading application that supports most popular document formats, including: PDF, EPUB, EPUB3, MOBI, DjVu, FB2, FB2.zip, TXT, RTF, AZW, AZW3, CBR, CBZ, HTML, XPS, MHT and more. With a simple yet powerful interface, Librera Reader makes reading documents a real pleasure. Librera even has a unique hands-free, auto-scrolling music mode.
Some key features of Librera reader include:
Easily explore documents with optional and...
</description></item><item><title>Download MacroDroid - Device Automation 5.59.12</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 16:19:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-macrodroid-device-automation-9863.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-macrodroid-device-automation-9863.html
</guid><description>
MacroDroid is the easiest way to automate everyday tasks on your Android smartphone or tablet. Through its smart user interface, MacroDroid provides a simple solution to perform automated tasks on your device in just a few taps. Developed by ArloSoft, MacroDroid simplifies repetitive tasks by automating various actions and processes on your Android device. It offers a user-friendly interface and a variety of triggers, actions, and constraints to create personalized...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tails 7.3.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 01:07:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tails-3241.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tails-3241.html
</guid><description>
Tails is a live operating system that you can boot on almost any computer from a USB memory stick or DVD. Tails does this by using the distribution classic Gnome of Linux. The top navigation bar allows you quick access to "Applications" and "Places" so you can easily access what you need quickly and easily and not lost.
Tails - independent operating System for security
Menu "apps" provide shortcuts for bundled software, including graphics, audio and video, office, system tools, and...
</description></item><item><title>Download CyberLink PowerDirector Ultimate 2026 v24.0.1209.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 01:04:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-powerdirector-ultimate-425.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-powerdirector-ultimate-425.html
</guid><description>
CyberLink PowerDirector Ultimate is software editor, edit video and make movies on the computer from a variety of templates are made available, complete with effects, transitions, animations, and music. CyberLink PowerDirector 17 is a combination of video editing software with advanced video editing features powerful. Cblowing need to add your clips into the time line and click on 'Production'!
The tool design video in CyberLink PowerDirector have the ability to customize helps you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Macro Expert Enterprise 4.9.8.7</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 01:04:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-macro-expert-enterprise-3558.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-macro-expert-enterprise-3558.html
</guid><description>
Macro Expert Enterprise is a powerful tool that will help you save time and money by empowering you to automate fully the work repetitive and regular. Macro Expert Enterprise can simplify a lot of work your computer, providing more than 260 action will meet most all your needs, automate your task. To keep they have the ability to access and organize high Macro Expert Enterprise split these actions into separate groups: Email, Excel document, database, Text, window, FTP, Internet, File,...
</description></item><item><title>Download ManicTime Pro 2025.3.5.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 01:02:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-manictime-18.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-manictime-18.html
</guid><description>
ManicTime is a software automatically collect information about how to use your computer. It records the time of operation of the machine, see the change data in the machine, how much data you share, received on or moved away, what software you use, use at any time
ManicTime allows you to keep up the work of the staff, send progress reports accurately and manage your time better than ever. This type of software can help your business more efficient when it comes to the internal problems...
</description></item><item><title>Download NetSpeedTray 1.1.8 + Portable</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 01:02:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-netspeedtray-14068.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-netspeedtray-14068.html
</guid><description>
NetSpeedTray is a lightweight, open source network monitor for Windows that displays upload/download speeds directly on the Taskbar with a native look and feel.
Designed to blend seamlessly with Windows 10/11 user interface. Includes intelligent detection of light and dark themes on the taskbar to ensure text is always visible. Sits quietly in the system tray without hogging resources. Features "Dynamic Update Rate" that automatically reduces update frequency when the network is idle to...
</description></item><item><title>Download ASCOMP F-Rename Professional 2.112</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 00:55:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ascomp-f-rename-6327.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ascomp-f-rename-6327.html
</guid><description>
ASCOMP F-Rename allows you to rename the number of files at the same time. With it, you can assign the file names that mean a large amount of data that does n' t cost much work. Besides, it allows you to find all the files on your hard drive after this without having to send a search group.
Features of ASCOMP F-Rename
	The numbering or date for the entire file collection and name of your MP3 file is only a few clicks based on the ID3 card.
	The function of renaming the individual...
</description></item><item><title>Download Avast Clear 25.12.10659</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 00:55:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avast-clear-4437.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avast-clear-4437.html
</guid><description>
Avast Clear is a utility to remove accurately and completely line product anti-virus AVAST. Avast to leave a lot of garbage behind the computer and in the register. In particular, the registry hassle can, for example, can be an obstacle to install a program anti-virus Avast other then. In such cases, you can use a special utility Avast!
Avast Clear - Uninstall program Avast
Recommended avoid any inconvenience, should always engage the help of a dedicated tool to know where to search...
</description></item><item><title>Download AVG Clear 25.12.10659</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 00:54:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avg-clear-4945.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avg-clear-4945.html
</guid><description>
AVG Clear is free program help completely erase everything from installing AVG current your including the registry entries, file, settings, files, users, etc. AVG Clear is provided by AVG and is the last measure to use if you encounter a problem when deleting AVG current whether it is error repair, reinstall, or delete altogether.
Please note that all user settings AVG will be removed after the uninstall process is complete. The items should be deleted to include content from Virus...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cutting Optimization Pro 5.18.16.30</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 00:46:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cutting-optimization-pro-6573.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cutting-optimization-pro-6573.html
</guid><description>
Cutting Optimization Pro is a cutting software used to obtain the optimal cut layout for one-dimensional (1D) and two-dimensional (2D) pieces. The software also allows you to define and process complex products, such as desks, tables, cabinets, cabinets, bookshelves... Cutting Optimization Pro can be used to cut rectangular panels made of glass, wood, metal, plastic or any other material used in industrial applications.
Features of Cutting Optimization Pro
	Optimize 1D and 2D in the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Opera GX (Gaming Browser) 125.0.5729.22</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 00:45:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-gx-3170.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-gx-3170.html
</guid><description>
Opera GX is a special version of the Opera browser is built to complement gamers avid. Browser this game comes with the unique features to help users make maximum use of both the game and their browser. Opera GX is built specifically to support the game. This browser includes the unique features to help users have the best experience when gaming and surfing the web.
Opera GX - special browser for gamers
GX Control allows you to set a limit on the level of use RAM, CPU and network where...
</description></item><item><title>Download Opera One 125.0.5729.21</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 00:44:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-972.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-972.html
</guid><description>
Opera is a fast, safe, configurable and compliant intranet web browser, which includes both the reader and the application. The Opera browser supports web browsing, listening to music, watching high speed movies, you can open many tabs on the Opera without affecting your browsing speed. Opera now supports almost all devices and operating systems such as windows, IOS, Android, linux, MacOS ...
Opera is a beautiful interface and many interesting features, operating on both PCs and mobile,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Quick Clipboard Editor 3.1.2.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 00:43:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quick-clipboard-editor-9421.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quick-clipboard-editor-9421.html
</guid><description>
Quick Clipboard Editor is free software that provides direct access to the text stored in your clipboard, allowing you to quickly modify it to meet your needs. meet your needs before pasting the text into the app you want. It allows you to quickly retrieve previous clips from your clipboard history, find and replace specific words or phrases, insert new content into each line, trim unwanted pieces of text, keep or remove lines or characters based on different criteria, arrange text using...
</description></item><item><title>Download Drives Monitor 18.7</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 00:43:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-drives-monitor-6969.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-drives-monitor-6969.html
</guid><description>
Drives Monitor is a Windows 10 utility that provides a lot of useful information about the activity of each physical disk, and a real-time graph is also provided. With Drives Monitor, you can view detailed information about the physical drive type, capacity, type, number of partitions and more. If the free space is running low, the disk space usage bar will turn red, so let you know about the problem and take appropriate measures.
If you run CrystalDiskInfo in the background, the...
</description></item></channel></rss>