<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 10:33:06 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 10:33:06 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download MediBang Paint Pro 32.4</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 02:20:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-medibang-paint-pro-610.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-medibang-paint-pro-610.html
</guid><description>
MediBang Paint Pro is the professional version to draw comics with great tools to help you create the products comics perfect. MediBang Paint Pro offers more than 50 pen drawing for you to use as GPen Pen and draw a map to pour the ink and water color brush to color. Each brush has different settings so they can be customized to your liking. You can also create brushes of your own!
Although all the features of it is MediBang Paint Pro is sleek and lightweight. It is made to run smoothly...
</description></item><item><title>Download Winxvideo AI 4.6.0.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 02:20:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winxvideo-ai-10981.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winxvideo-ai-10981.html
</guid><description>
Winxvideo AI is an innovative video editing app that leverages the power of artificial intelligence to provide users with advanced video editing capabilities. With advanced features and a user-friendly interface, Winxvideo AI is designed to streamline the video editing process and empower creators to create professional-quality videos.
Winxvideo AI meets all your audio/video conversion needs and compresses your 4K/8K footage from GB to MB without compromising on quality, powered by...
</description></item><item><title>Download R-Wipe &amp;amp; Clean 20.0 Build 2539</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 02:19:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-wipe-clean-891.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-wipe-clean-891.html
</guid><description>
R-Wipe &amp;amp; Clean is software to delete junk files, unnecessary files from your computer to release the storage space and speed up your computer. In addition, R-Wipe &amp;amp; Clean also unleash the capacity of your drive and delete information invasion of privacy on different operations online and offline including your internet history and cookies, the list of downloaded files and documents were open, buffer different data, temporary files and many other items, created by the operating...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ashampoo Backup Pro 27.5.27</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 02:18:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-backup-pro-716.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-backup-pro-716.html
</guid><description>
Ashampoo Backup Pro is software to backup and restore data professional to save the file, the important data for your computer. Ashampoo Backup Pro will remove the fear of viruses, ransomware, or hardware errors. Ashampoo® Backup Pro offers you various options to backup individual files or entire disk partitions on any storage media or on the cloud. User friendly, intuitive, fast. Even in case an error occurs the entire system, application integrated emergency can bring your...
</description></item><item><title>Download Office Timeline Plus 13.15.01.00 Expert / Pro / Pro+ Edition</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 02:18:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-timeline-2106.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-timeline-2106.html
</guid><description>
Office Timeline is an add-on very useful and powerful software for Microsoft PowerPoint. With add-ons, you can create PowerPoint documents look more beautiful. With add-ons, you can add the time Line on the project by yourself. Application time for the composition and different segments of the document, your PowerPoint will not only increase the beauty for your work, but also for customers and your manager. The people who created this product is also believe that add-ons this is the only...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Illustrator 2026 v30.1.0.136 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 02:17:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-illustrator-0022-749.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-illustrator-0022-749.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Illustrator is a powerful vector graphics editor developed by Adobe Inc., first released in 1987. It is primarily used by graphic designers, illustrators, and artists to create high-quality illustrations, logos, icons, and digital artwork. Unlike raster graphics editors like Adobe Photoshop, which manipulate images pixel by pixel, Illustrator uses mathematical formulas to create vector graphics. This allows designs to be scaled infinitely without losing quality, making it ideal for...
</description></item><item><title>Download Windows Video Converter 2025 v10.0.3.9</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 02:16:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-video-converter-6371.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-video-converter-6371.html
</guid><description>
Windows Video Converter is a comprehensive software with many features such as Transaction, Download and Rapid Video Editing. Windows Video Converter supports video conversion to 1000 formats at a rate of 30 times faster without reducing the quality. Download and convert video online. Cut, Cut, Add Text, Effect, Appendix, And More.
Features of Windows Video Converter
	The conversion of video to over 1000 formats.
	The speed is 30 times faster.
	The quality is not reduced.
	Download...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Substance 3D Designer 15.1.0.10084 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 02:15:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-substancee-designer-adobe-908.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-substancee-designer-adobe-908.html
</guid><description>
Substance Designer is the tool aggregated structure to help design, create 3D material. Create the file Quality or texture bitmap. Substance Designer helps users to create materials with full control and infinite variations. Edit the texture complete immediately and create texture, Quality and material of MDL will be handled directly in the renderer or game engine of you.
Substance Designer - design, create 3D material
The main features of Substance Designer
	Substance Designer...
</description></item><item><title>Download GoodSync Enterprise 12.9.19.9</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 02:14:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-goodsync-enterprise-163.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-goodsync-enterprise-163.html
</guid><description>
GoodSync Enterprise is a software that saves files and files easily and is reliable. It automatically analyts, synchronize and backup your email, family photos, contacts, MP3, financial documentation and other important files-between desktop computers, laptops, servers, external drives and Windows Mobile devices as well as remotely via FTP , SFTP, WebDAV and more. The GoodSync synchronized software combines bulletproof reliability with an extremely easy interface to compare, synchronize...
</description></item><item><title>Download Drive SnapShot 1.50.0.1803</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 02:14:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-drive-snapshot-701.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-drive-snapshot-701.html
</guid><description>
Drive SnapShot is a backup software, Restore disk, including operating system, installed programs, your data and all security attributes - while windows is running and you continue to work. With Drive SnapShot you backup partition or hard drive and it can also create disk image of your system. If a disaster occurs (a virus, trojan or the fixed hard disk), the recover complete and accurate your system will be able to accomplish after only a few minutes. The image file can be mounted as...
</description></item><item><title>Download UPDF 2.1.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 02:13:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-updf-14160.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-updf-14160.html
</guid><description>
UPDF for Windows is easy-to-use PDF software for Windows! Enjoy powerful editing tools for text, images, links, and more in your PDFs. Customize backgrounds, watermarks, and page sizes as easily as in Word. AI-powered PDF editor and manager that offers a wide range of features including editing, annotating, converting, OCR (Optical Character Recognition), organizing, protecting, sharing, printing, summarizing, translating, and interpreting PDF files.
Features of UPDF
Analyze PDFs with...
</description></item><item><title>Download VirtualDub2 2.5.1.1095</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 02:13:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-virtualdub2-12584.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-virtualdub2-12584.html
</guid><description>
VirtualDub2 (formerly VirtualDub FilterMod) has all the features of the original VirtualDub, plus built-in encoding/decoding functionality of H264 and other formats; Open and save MOV, MP4, MKV, etc. Improved navigation, display (full screen display when zoomed in, ...) and other UI bits (color format selection...); improve performance; and supports high bit depth color formats.
Features of VirtualDub2
	Just like the original VirtualDub, this application requires no installation. You...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ventoy 1.1.09 + LiveCD</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 02:12:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ventoy-4578.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ventoy-4578.html
</guid><description>
Ventoy is an open source tool for creating bootable USB drives for ISO files. With ventoy, you don't need to format the disk multiple times, you just need to copy the iso file to the USB drive and boot it. You can copy multiple iso files at once and ventoy will give you a boot menu to select them.
Features of Ventoy
100% Open Source
Simple to Use
Fast (limited only by iso file copy speed)
Boot directly from iso file, no extraction required
Legacy + UEFI supported in the same...
</description></item><item><title>Download eM Client Pro 10.4.4195</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 02:12:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-em-client-pro-953.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-em-client-pro-953.html
</guid><description>
eM Client Pro is an email app full features with modern interface. eM Client offers calendar, tasks, contacts and chat. Software is best Email app for windows today. eM Client supports all major services including Gmail, Exchange, iCloud and Outlook.com. You can find more information in the server part on our website.
eM Client Pro - the best email App for windows
eM Client is very simple , can automatically set everything up for most of the services. It is also effective to import...
</description></item><item><title>Download WindowTop Pro 5.29.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 02:11:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windowtop-6955.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windowtop-6955.html
</guid><description>
WindowTop is a program that pins windows on Desktop, in other words it sets the window to float above all other program windows, creating transparency for the windows. that window via a dedicated slider, which supports adjusting transparency, changing the color of application windows or similar programs with the dark theme of the Windows 10 operating system, creating contrast and reducing tension straight, painful for the eyes.
Features of WindowTop
	Put window on top
	Set window to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Zortam Mp3 Media Studio Pro 33.60</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 02:11:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zortam-mp3-media-studio-pro-135.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zortam-mp3-media-studio-pro-135.html
</guid><description>
Zortam Mp3 Media Studio Pro brings you rich processing tools music includes extract and convert music from CD to Mp3 format, edit, music cards, music download....You can also create discs CD high-quality music, with Zortam Mp3 Media Studio search music files duplicated to remove them from the system, rename music files, switch back and forth between formats.
Zortam Mp3 Media Studio Pro is rated as perfect software in the processing of the MP3 files on the computer. First of all, you can...
</description></item><item><title>Download AnyMP4 Android Data Recovery 2.1.56</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 02:10:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anymp4-android-data-recovery-1256.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anymp4-android-data-recovery-1256.html
</guid><description>
AnyMP4 Android Data Recovery is software restore data Android provides the feature to restore data powerful for mobile and tablet Android. AnyMP4 Android Data Recovery can recover text content has been removed and lost, such as contacts, SMS, text messages, call history, notes, WhatsApp chat and more from your Android device. And the contact exported will be saved as VCF, CSV or HTML for you to use. Whether you've accidentally deleted Android data or lost data after restore factory, os...
</description></item><item><title>Download Coolutils Total Movie Converter 4.1.0.74</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 02:03:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-total-movie-converter-915.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-total-movie-converter-915.html
</guid><description>
Coolutils Total Movie Converter is software to convert video files in any popular formats such as AVI, MPG, WMV, MPEG, FLV. At the same time, the program can prepare video for a variety of devices - iPod, iPhone, Zune, Apple TV, Archos, Creative Zen Vision, XBox and many other devices. Provides the ability to batch convert a group of files.
Coolutils Total Movie Converter 4 - convert video formats
Total Movie Converter supports 3GP format this is suitable for those who are still using...
</description></item><item><title>Download iSunshare BitLocker Genius 3.0.4.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 02:02:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-isunshare-bitlocker-genius-5867.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-isunshare-bitlocker-genius-5867.html
</guid><description>
Regardless of whether you are using Windows 7 or Windows 10 to encrypt the USB drive or external hard drive to protect the data, there is no direct way to open the encrypted BitLocker drive on macOS and Mac OSX. When you connect the drive protected by BitLocker with your Mac computer, you ' ll see that drive that the computer ca n' t read. However, with iSunshare BitLocker Genius, you can open, read and write BitLocker on Mac for a few minutes.
The features of iSunshare BitLocker...
</description></item><item><title>Download FoneLab Android Data Recovery 3.1.52</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 02:02:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fonelab-android-data-recovery-3984.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fonelab-android-data-recovery-3984.html
</guid><description>
FoneLab Android Data Recovery is a software that helps you to recover data allows you to recover your Android phone or SD card contacts, messages, videos, photos and more without loss of data. FoneLab Android Data Recovery can get back lost data whether your Android device is broken water, virus attacks, or broken part as it can be FoneLab detection for Android. With Android data recovery this you can get back all files lost his within a few minutes. Mobile phone sometimes as a replacement...
</description></item><item><title>Download EarthTime 6.31</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 02:02:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-earthtime-185.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-earthtime-185.html
</guid><description>
EarthTime is software that displays the time and date local time of any place in the world. This application has database integration good for 3000 city, users can manually add, download at EarthTime if you want to. EarthTime allows you to install for the time zone and current local time.EarthTime displays the Earth according to the view night and day, you can view the map in full screen mode.
EarthTime
The feature on EarthTime
	EarthTime allows users to interact with visualization...
</description></item><item><title>Download Blank And Secure 8.24</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 01:51:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blank-and-secure-2934.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blank-and-secure-2934.html
</guid><description>
Blank And Secure is a application lightweight and portable allows you to completely erase your sensitive data without possibility to restore. This add-on accomplish this by overwriting your files with zeros (0) before you delete them. This method is also called "zeroing data / drives". You should know that once completed, the complete data can't be recovered, so you should only use this tool if you want to permanently delete your files.
Blank And Secure - Delete data permanently
Blank...
</description></item><item><title>Download iSumsoft BitLocker Reader 3.2.2.8</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 01:51:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-isumsoft-bitlocker-reader-5869.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-isumsoft-bitlocker-reader-5869.html
</guid><description>
iSumsoft BitLocker Reader is a handy and practical BitLocker management tool for Windows. It offers you an easy and quicker way to manage BitLocker coding for the PC ' s hard drive or mobile drive. iSumsoft BitLocker Reader allows you to encrypt the hard drive and mobile drives of the PC using BitLocker to prevent the curious eyes from looking for your sensitive data.
iSumsoft BitLocker Reader provides robust data coding capabilities to ensure high security for your data. By turning on...
</description></item><item><title>Download Bitvise SSH Client 9.51</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 01:01:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bitvise-ssh-client-2845.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bitvise-ssh-client-2845.html
</guid><description>
Bitvise SSH Client is a SSH terminal, tunneling and file transfer application SFTP for free with the command line interface and graphics. It supports all versions desktop and server of Windows! Bitvise SSH Client for free use! Bitvise SSH Client is an application multipurpose, fast and powerful in the transmission of the advanced file helps users control and manage the terminal remotely in a flexible manner. Bitvise SSH Client intensive support for establishing the secure connection...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Bridge 2026 v16.0.1.18 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 00:57:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-bridge-0003-1338.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-bridge-0003-1338.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Bridge is a versatile digital asset management application developed by Adobe Inc., first released in 2005 as part of the Adobe Creative Suite. It acts as a powerful tool for organizing, previewing, and managing creative assets across various Adobe applications. By downloading the program on taiwebs.com, you can easily edit elements in batch mode, add watermarks and even set color options centrally - Adobe Bridge CC will simplify your work and help maintain order.
Adobe Bridge...
</description></item></channel></rss>