<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 18:10:00 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 18:10:00 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Free Download Manager 6.33.1.6644</title><pubDate> Thu, 19 Feb 2026 16:31:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-download-manager-3105.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-download-manager-3105.html
</guid><description>
Free Download Manager is free application download manager, Free Download Manager will significantly increase downloads by splitting the files into several smaller parts and then downloads at the same time. Speed your download will be significantly increased. Manager download free can also continue to download at broken or not responding, so you don't need start downloading from the beginning after occasionally interrupted.
Free Download Manager - Manage and speed up downloads
You can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Text Editor Pro 35.4.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 19 Feb 2026 16:29:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-text-editor-pro-800.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-text-editor-pro-800.html
</guid><description>
Text Editor Pro is software to handle text, HTML, Perl, Ruby, or Fortran with features syntax highlighting, professional. Text Editor provides syntax highlighting for over 50 scripts and has a simple interface and easy access. In addition, the Text Editor Pro also supports more than 50 programming languages like C ++, COBOL, graph DOT, DSP, DWScript, Fortran, Foxpro, Java, Perl, Python, Ruby, SQL and many other languages.
Text Editor Pro - text Processing professional
The software can...
</description></item><item><title>Download ALLPlayer 9.6.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 19 Feb 2026 16:28:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allplayer-2522.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allplayer-2522.html
</guid><description>
ALLPlayer is perhaps the most popular program for watching movies with subtitles matching . It play all media formats know files, RAR and more can LiveUpdate function is implemented to update the latest codecs if there is a problem with opening a movie file. The program also automatically searches for matching subtitles in all languages . Subtitles smart to keep subtitles on the screen for the period of time required for you to read them. AVI Doctor helps when you are downloading a torrent...
</description></item><item><title>Download ACDSee Luxea Video Editor Pro 8.0.2.3533</title><pubDate> Thu, 19 Feb 2026 16:27:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-acdsee-luxea-video-editor-5312.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-acdsee-luxea-video-editor-5312.html
</guid><description>
ACDSee Luxea Video Editor is a software simple and effective to edit and edit all types of video files (with the ability to record video from the screen), unlike the video editing software professional and heavy the other, with the environment simple and easy, the task video editing for non-professional users he's doing that. Using software ACDSee Luxea Video Editor, you can edit or mixed film and do things like quickly edit audio and video of the video file, set video effects, simple to...
</description></item><item><title>Download CoolUtils Total Doc Converter 5.1.0.376/148</title><pubDate> Thu, 19 Feb 2026 16:26:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-total-doc-converter-84.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-total-doc-converter-84.html
</guid><description>
CoolUtils Total Doc Converter Program that will allow you to document conversion DOC to others, the list can be viewed on the official website or you can watch carefully the screenshot, I think the question would no longer can download CoolUtils Total Doc Converter below. There is batch processing,in general, everything is convenient, I hope you like it.
Total Doc Converter is conversion tools text comprehensive and multi-featured, very necessary when storing or printing the text. It also...
</description></item><item><title>Download ExpanDrive 2026.02.09</title><pubDate> Thu, 19 Feb 2026 16:25:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-expandrive-609.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-expandrive-609.html
</guid><description>
ExpanDrive is software sync cloud storage strong support BackBlaze B2, Google Team Drive, SMB / CIFS and new interface and easy user search file version, share links and much more.  ExpanDrive mapped network drives for macOS and Micosoft Windows connect with all the provide major cloud storage such as Dropbox, Google Drive, Google Team Drive, Amazon Drive, Box, OneDrive, OneDrive for Business, Sharepoint, Openstack Swift , BackBlaze B2, Amazon S3 or SFTP servers, FTP or WebDAV on your own...
</description></item><item><title>Download Advanced Driver Updater 4.6.1086.8640</title><pubDate> Thu, 19 Feb 2026 16:24:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-driver-updater-1170.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-driver-updater-1170.html
</guid><description>
Advanced Driver Updater is software that automatically check, download and install the Driver for the fastest computer with the software always be updated with the latest. Advanced Driver Updater will help your system will always have the latest drivers and you will no longer have to make search for driver updates manually. Outdated drivers can slow your PC or even cause errors. Drivers for video cards are particularly prone to this. A program is clearly structured to provide access to...
</description></item><item><title>Download foobar2000 2.25.7</title><pubDate> Thu, 19 Feb 2026 16:23:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-foobar2000-1812.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-foobar2000-1812.html
</guid><description>
foobar2000 is the media player for media formats MP3, WAV, OGG and other formats multimedia other. It has no bells and whistles, however, under the hood, the program offers quite many features, including format, title and layout of the interface can be customized, convert WAV, Equalizer, Resampler, note cards, MP3, playlists, music album, CD, drag / drop and more. It also includes all the standard features like shuffle, random play, etc.
foobar2000 - The media player
foobar2000 running...
</description></item><item><title>Download Chess King 2026 v26.0.0.2610</title><pubDate> Thu, 19 Feb 2026 16:22:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chess-king-13917.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chess-king-13917.html
</guid><description>
Chess King 2025 is the latest version of the Chess King software suite, designed for chess players of all levels to play, practice, analyze and improve their games with advanced tools and rich resources.
Chess King Analysis 25 is a new and versatile tool for chess players, an ideal software for beginners, a challenging opponent for amateurs and an invaluable trainer for aspiring players. Chess King Analysis 25 emphasizes simplicity of use in training players. However, it is more than just...
</description></item><item><title>Download MiniMeters 1.0.23.160</title><pubDate> Thu, 19 Feb 2026 16:21:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minimeters-9410.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minimeters-9410.html
</guid><description>
MiniMeters is a simple standalone sound meter application for Windows. Monitor your System Audio*, Any Input, or insert the MiniMeter Server Plug-in (VST3/AU/CLAP) at the end of your main channel in the DAW of your choice. Customize the layout in a horizontal bar (perfect for above or below the audio engine of your choice) or pop out into modules to create custom layouts.
Features of MiniMeters
	6 modules to choose from to build your perfect metering setup: Spectrogram, Waveform,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Avast Ransomware Decryption Tools 1.0.0.821</title><pubDate> Thu, 19 Feb 2026 16:21:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avast-ransomware-decryption-tools-5371.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avast-ransomware-decryption-tools-5371.html
</guid><description>
Avast Ransomware Decryption Tools is a package of ransomware decryption tools to help you get back files from 20 different ransomware encrypted. Avast Ransomware Decryption Tools supports decryption AES_NI, Alcatraz Locker, Apocalypse, BadBlock, Bart, BTCWare, Crypt888, CryptoMix (Offline), CrySiS, EncrypTile, FindZip, Globe HiddenTear, Jigsaw, Legion NoobCrypt, Stampado, SZFLocker, TeslaCrypt, XData.
Features of Avast Ransomware Decryption Tools
	Easily remove ransomware
	Decrypt and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Coolutils Total Excel Converter 7.1.0.110</title><pubDate> Thu, 19 Feb 2026 16:20:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-total-excel-converter-849.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-total-excel-converter-849.html
</guid><description>
Coolutils Total Excel Converter is software that converts Excel documents to other formats like ODS, XML, SQL, WK2, WKS WAB, DBF, TEX and DIF for you to use. In addition, the software also supports converting Excel files into file DOC, DOCX, PDF, HTML, Access, TXT, ODT, ODS, XML, SQL, CSV, Lotus, DBF, TEX, DIFF, SYLK and LaTeX.
Coolutils Total Excel Converter - batch convert Excel
Total Excel Converter has a perfect layout and tight. When the conversion is finished you will get an...
</description></item><item><title>Download SysTools PST Converter 10.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 19 Feb 2026 16:19:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-systools-pst-converter-8287.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-systools-pst-converter-8287.html
</guid><description>
SysTools PST Converter is a software tool that allows users to convert PST (Personal Archives Table) files to various file formats like EML, MSG, HTML, MBOX , PDF and other formats. This can be useful for individuals or organizations that need to access their email data from a PST file and import it into various email clients like Thunderbird, Apple Mail, and others. The software also allows users to export PST files to different platforms like Office 365, Live Exchange and G Suite. It...
</description></item><item><title>Download SysTools OST Converter 11.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 19 Feb 2026 16:18:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-systools-ost-converter-8643.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-systools-ost-converter-8643.html
</guid><description>
SysTools OST Converter is a software tool that helps users to convert OST (Offline Archive Table) files to various file formats like PST (Personal Archive Table) , EML, MSG, MBOX, etc. This software is commonly used to recover data from inaccessible or corrupted OST files and convert the data to a format that can be imported into email clients such as Microsoft Outlook, Mozilla Thunderbird and others. other. This tool supports OST files created in Microsoft Exchange and Office 365, and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Syncovery Premium 11.12.12.166</title><pubDate> Thu, 19 Feb 2026 16:16:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncovery-pro-enterprise-232.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncovery-pro-enterprise-232.html
</guid><description>
Syncovery Pro Enterprise is a great application used to back up data and to synchronize personal computers, servers, laptops, notepads and storage online. The software comes with support for FTP and secure FTP servers, SSH, WebDAV, Amazon S3, http, update the part file, ZIP compression, data encryption, and schedule automatic backups.
Syncovery Pro Enterprise have the ability to freely select files and folders across the whole folder hierarchy in tree view and supports email...
</description></item><item><title>Download Argente System Repair 1.0.5.4</title><pubDate> Thu, 19 Feb 2026 16:15:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-argente-system-repair-13813.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-argente-system-repair-13813.html
</guid><description>
Argente System Repair is a lightweight utility designed to diagnose and fix common Windows system problems. It scans your system to identify errors in operating system components, file systems, installation files, and other system components, and then applies targeted fixes to resolve these problems. The tool provides different scan modes, including simple scan, recommended scan, and custom scan, allowing users to customize the repair process according to their needs.
System Repair...
</description></item><item><title>Download Opera One 127.0.5778.76</title><pubDate> Thu, 19 Feb 2026 00:45:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-972.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-972.html
</guid><description>
Opera is a fast, safe, configurable and compliant intranet web browser, which includes both the reader and the application. The Opera browser supports web browsing, listening to music, watching high speed movies, you can open many tabs on the Opera without affecting your browsing speed. Opera now supports almost all devices and operating systems such as windows, IOS, Android, linux, MacOS ...
Opera is a beautiful interface and many interesting features, operating on both PCs and mobile,...
</description></item><item><title>Download UltraSearch Professional 4.9.0.1201</title><pubDate> Thu, 19 Feb 2026 00:44:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ultrasearch-professional-10252.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ultrasearch-professional-10252.html
</guid><description>
UltraSearch Professional is the professional version that helps you find your files and documents on all connected hard drives and network drives. Search by file type, document content, or file properties. Take back your valuable time and let UltraSearch do the searching for you.
UltraSearch Professional does not maintain an index stored on your hard disk. It achieves speed by working directly on the Master File Table (MFT) of NTFS partitions. So it even identifies NTFS hardlinks. That...
</description></item><item><title>Download Batch Image Combiner PRO 1.3.2.4</title><pubDate> Thu, 19 Feb 2026 00:43:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-batch-image-combiner-pro-11123.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-batch-image-combiner-pro-11123.html
</guid><description>
Are you looking for a quick and effective way to combine multiple images vertically and horizontally? Look no further than this utility: Batch Image Combiner PRO is an easy-to-use Windows application that allows you to quickly join two or more images into one both vertically and horizontally in just 1-2 seconds.
With the help of Batch Image Combiner, a powerful program that allows users to combine images into one image, this task can be done quickly and automatically. No more tedious...
</description></item><item><title>Download AI Video to SRT 1.1.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 19 Feb 2026 00:43:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ai-video-to-srt-14564.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ai-video-to-srt-14564.html
</guid><description>
VideoToSRT uses advanced on-premise artificial intelligence (AI) to convert video and audio files into SRT, VTT, and TXT formats. No cloud upload required, no registration needed, and absolute privacy guaranteed for your content.
Features of AI Video to SRT
	Offline speech-to-text conversion using AI technology.
	Batch processing queue for multiple files in sequence.
	NVIDIA GPU acceleration for ultra-fast speeds.
	Supports input formats MP4, MOV, MKV, MP3, WAV, and M4A.
	Export to...
</description></item><item><title>Download dBpoweramp Image Converter Premier 2026-02-16</title><pubDate> Thu, 19 Feb 2026 00:42:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbpoweramp-image-converter-7007.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbpoweramp-image-converter-7007.html
</guid><description>
dBpoweramp Image Converter is a simple visual transformation application that aims to make the transition as simple as possible. dBpoweramp Image Converter will switch between all popular formats, Bitmap, PNG, JPEG, TIFF and many other formats. It also has the ability to make mass transformation for multiple files and folders with only one click and filter on the png or other types of files.
dBpoweramp Image Converter is capable of switching high speed by using simultaneously all CPU...
</description></item><item><title>Download Bitvise SSH Client 9.59</title><pubDate> Thu, 19 Feb 2026 00:41:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bitvise-ssh-client-2845.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bitvise-ssh-client-2845.html
</guid><description>
Bitvise SSH Client is a SSH terminal, tunneling and file transfer application SFTP for free with the command line interface and graphics. It supports all versions desktop and server of Windows! Bitvise SSH Client for free use! Bitvise SSH Client is an application multipurpose, fast and powerful in the transmission of the advanced file helps users control and manage the terminal remotely in a flexible manner. Bitvise SSH Client intensive support for establishing the secure connection...
</description></item><item><title>Download Freemake Video Converter Gold 5.0.0.36</title><pubDate> Thu, 19 Feb 2026 00:39:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-freemake-video-converter-gold-167.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-freemake-video-converter-gold-167.html
</guid><description>
Freemake Video Converter Gold is a software to help convert tail high quality videos with many different formats on many devices. Freemake Video Converter - convert video to AVI, MP4, WMV, MKV, 3GP, DVD, MP3, iPad, iPhone, PSP, Android phone. Video to MP3 just with one click! Rip and burn DVD. Convert YouTube to MP4, AVI, etc. with Freemake! Results guaranteed. Freemake Video Converter has fast conversion speed, guarantee the output quality,support create HTML5 videos have the embed code...
</description></item><item><title>Download TreeSize Professional 9.7.1.2201</title><pubDate> Thu, 19 Feb 2026 00:39:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-treesize-professional-390.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-treesize-professional-390.html
</guid><description>
TreeSize Pro is a software to manage hard disk space powerfully and flexibly for Windows 2003/2008 / XP / Vista / 7/8/10. TreeSize will find out which directory the largest on your drives and recover megabytes on disk. TreeSize Professional shows you the size, allocated and wasted space, number of files, 3D charts, last accessed date, file owner and permissions, the speed NTFS compression and much more information for several folders or drives you choose. It also lets you search drives,...
</description></item><item><title>Download FormulaDesk FormulaSpy 1.39</title><pubDate> Thu, 19 Feb 2026 00:38:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-formuladesk-formulaspy-12266.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-formuladesk-formulaspy-12266.html
</guid><description>
FormulaDesk FormulaSpy is an Excel add-on that makes Excel formulas easy to understand, easy to test, easy to troubleshoot, and easy to repair. It provides a horizontal view that shows the results of each part of the formula to see how the results are calculated. You can also expand and collapse formula sections by clicking the green results bar. Additionally, you can use FormulaSpy to discover the cells the formula uses, access those cells and view their formulas, then dig deeper into...
</description></item></channel></rss>