<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:16:13 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:16:13 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download AndreaMosaic 3.54.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 01:05:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-andreamosaic-1684.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-andreamosaic-1684.html
</guid><description>
AndreaMosaic is a other tool allows you to transform photos into mosaics created from collection of photos of you. The manner of operation of the program is very simple, but it does not always give you the results you are looking for. The user must choose the image collection you want to use to create the mosaic and the photo will be converted on AndreaMosaic.
&amp;nbsp;
AndreaMosaic allows you to configure a number of options, such as width the last of the mosaic, the number of images on...
</description></item><item><title>Download NetSpeedTray 1.1.7 + Portable</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 01:05:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-netspeedtray-14068.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-netspeedtray-14068.html
</guid><description>
NetSpeedTray is a lightweight, open source network monitor for Windows that displays upload/download speeds directly on the Taskbar with a native look and feel.
Designed to blend seamlessly with Windows 10/11 user interface. Includes intelligent detection of light and dark themes on the taskbar to ensure text is always visible. Sits quietly in the system tray without hogging resources. Features "Dynamic Update Rate" that automatically reduces update frequency when the network is idle to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Balabolka 2.15.0.906</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 01:03:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-balaboka-142.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-balaboka-142.html
</guid><description>
Balabolka is a text-to-speech (TTS) program. It can read text on your screen in a human-like voice. You can use Balabolka to listen to text from a variety of file formats, convert text to spoken audio files, and adjust speech parameters such as speed and pitch. It is often used for accessibility purposes, helping people who have difficulty reading or multi-tasking by listening to text while doing other activities. Balabolka supports multiple languages and uses different TTS engines,...
</description></item><item><title>Download MiniTool Partition Wizard Technician 13.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 01:03:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minitool-partition-wizard-pro-604.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minitool-partition-wizard-pro-604.html
</guid><description>
MiniTool Partition Wizard Technician is the best partition manager for Windows, MiniTool Partition Wizard aims to maximize disk performance. It helps to create/change the size/format of the flexible partition, the disk conversion between the MBR and GPT disks, the partition conversion between NTFS and FAT32 and converting the disk into a basic without losing data.
Recovery of data quickly, effective: MiniTool partition management software provides two perfect solutions for data recovery....
</description></item><item><title>Download UniGetUI 3.3.5</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 01:01:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-unigetui-12209.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-unigetui-12209.html
</guid><description>
UniGetUI (formerly WingetUI) is a graphical user interface for WinGet (and other package managers), a command-line package manager for Windows 10 and Windows 11 such as Winget, Scoop, Chocolatey, Pip, NPM, .NET Tool and PowerShell Gallery. It allows users to install, update and uninstall software from the package manager easily. Additionally, it provides features like backup, restore, group and update your packages and receive notifications about new updates.
With this program, you can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Freemake Video Converter Gold 5.0.0.14</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 01:01:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-freemake-video-converter-gold-167.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-freemake-video-converter-gold-167.html
</guid><description>
Freemake Video Converter Gold is a software to help convert tail high quality videos with many different formats on many devices. Freemake Video Converter - convert video to AVI, MP4, WMV, MKV, 3GP, DVD, MP3, iPad, iPhone, PSP, Android phone. Video to MP3 just with one click! Rip and burn DVD. Convert YouTube to MP4, AVI, etc. with Freemake! Results guaranteed. Freemake Video Converter has fast conversion speed, guarantee the output quality,support create HTML5 videos have the embed code...
</description></item><item><title>Download System Mechanic Pro 25.7.0.4 + Standard</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:59:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-system-mechanic-434.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-system-mechanic-434.html
</guid><description>
System Mechanic Pro is tool cleanup and repair errors on the system and restore hard drive and operating speed window.  System Mechanic helps you to clean your entire computer system, delete the unnecessary files, detect and repair the incident occurred due to virus attack or due to mistakenly deleted system files.
System Mechanic offers many useful features such as Registry cleaning, defragmenting computer memory, protect your privacy while accessing the Internet. With programs this...
</description></item><item><title>Download System Mechanic Ultimate Defense 25.7.0.4</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:59:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-system-mechanic-ultimate-defense-1974.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-system-mechanic-ultimate-defense-1974.html
</guid><description>
System Mechanic Ultimate Defense is software provides tracking features anti browser and protect your online privacy, management, encryption and secure password protection, anti-virus certified, VB100, detect and remove malware on demand, technology, erase hard drive military grade, award-winning optimize PC, software, file recovery advanced.
Malware threats is growing fast now because of almost a million new viruses, worms, trojan horses, rootkits and other types of spyware, and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Animate 2024 v24.0.11 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:58:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-animate-05en-1221.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-animate-05en-1221.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Animate 2024 is an application to develop vector animation and raster interactive for games, applications, and websites. Vector animation design and bitmap interact for games, applications, and web. Making cartoons and banner ads became lively. And add the action to the instructions and the information. With the Adobe Animate CC, you can quickly publish on a variety of platforms and approach viewers on desktop computers, mobile devices and TVs.
Start your game. Developing...
</description></item><item><title>Download Aseprite 1.3.15.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:57:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aseprite-6901.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aseprite-6901.html
</guid><description>
Aseprite is a pixel art tool that allows you to create 2D animations for video games using a variety of tools. Animations and visual effects are used to enhance nearly any form of multimedia, including video games. They are created by combining many images and effects, with countless applications at your disposal.
Aseprite supports files and smart drawing tools, resulting in an enhanced image or short animation for use in your project. In addition, you can completely change or enhance...
</description></item><item><title>Download AllMapSoft Google Maps Downloader 8.880</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:57:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-google-maps-downloader-2796.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-google-maps-downloader-2796.html
</guid><description>
AllMapSoft Google Maps Downloader is a reliable application aimed at downloading maps from Google at high speed. The result is a set of small images can be combined in a larger map. This can serve in a large variety of projects, from creating a tile map to presentations and tutorials.
Google Maps Downloader successfully fulfills both of those conditions, providing simple means to quickly grab maps at the resolution satisfactory. In addition, it is extremely easy to use and integrated a...
</description></item><item><title>Download SIV System Information Viewer 5.83</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:56:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-siv-system-information-viewer-1803.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-siv-system-information-viewer-1803.html
</guid><description>
SIV System Information Viewer is advanced tool that provides in depth information for many components, Windows, hardware and different networks, including information for CPU info, PCI info, PCMCIA info, USB SMBus information SPD, the method ACPI, information , machine, hardware sensors, and more.
SIV System Information Viewer - viewer system information advanced
The original interface can be somewhat overwhelming and perhaps you will have to take a bit of effort to familiarize...
</description></item><item><title>Download Screencapt Professional 2.004</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:54:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-screencapt-professional-12260.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-screencapt-professional-12260.html
</guid><description>
Screencapt Professional is powerful Windows software for screen recording that allows you to accurately and easily record any on-screen activity. Whether you want to create tutorials, record webinars, or simply record your favorite games, Screencapt gives you all the tools you need.
With Screencapt, you can record the entire screen, a selected area, or a specific window. This flexibility makes Screencapt the perfect screen recorder for any type of application. Thanks to the built-in...
</description></item><item><title>Download iZotope Ozone Advanced 12 v12.0.2.1331</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:54:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ozone-advanced-2580.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ozone-advanced-2580.html
</guid><description>
iZotope Ozone Advanced is the overall most comprehensive in the industry, Ozone 8 additional to his legacy by introducing signal processing clever new shape the spectral balance control loudness, v. v. master your audio with more than the first fifteen years of the audio industry at your fingertips. Improved with new features, future, smart, Ozone 8 is your stop for a professional master, balanced with ten processors, the necessary. That is version smart most of the Ozone is...
</description></item><item><title>Download Argente System Repair 1.0.2.5</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:53:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-argente-system-repair-13813.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-argente-system-repair-13813.html
</guid><description>
Argente System Repair is a lightweight utility designed to diagnose and fix common Windows system problems. It scans your system to identify errors in operating system components, file systems, installation files, and other system components, and then applies targeted fixes to resolve these problems. The tool provides different scan modes, including simple scan, recommended scan, and custom scan, allowing users to customize the repair process according to their needs.
System Repair...
</description></item><item><title>Download AllMapSoft Offline Map Maker 8.352</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:53:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-offline-map-maker-656.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-offline-map-maker-656.html
</guid><description>
AllMapSoft Offline Map Maker is software create, organize, offline map from Google Maps, Yahoo maps, Bing maps and Openstreetmap. You can view offline maps downloaded with map viewer offline. And you can zoom out or zoom in the offline map or export map under the file format .BMP with file world xxx.bpw, and can output files xxx.map for OziExplorer. If you want to make a offline map of your city by yourself, it is very useful for you.
Features AllMapSoft Offline Map Maker
	You can...
</description></item><item><title>Download MiniTool Partition Wizard Technician WinPE ISO 13.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:52:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minitool-partition-wizard-technician-winpe-iso-5115.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minitool-partition-wizard-technician-winpe-iso-5115.html
</guid><description>
MiniTool Partition Wizard Technician WinPE ISO is a magic partition have feature-rich, designed to optimize disk usage and to protect your data. It comes with many powerful features that you can completely control the hard disk and partitions by yourself. With interface, user friendly, and simple instructions, you can resize partition, copy disk, scan the lost partition and move OS to SSD easily and safely.
Features of MiniTool Partition Wizard Technician WinPE ISO
	Is manager best...
</description></item><item><title>Download StarUML 7.0.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:51:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-staruml-3172.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-staruml-3172.html
</guid><description>
StarUML is a software modeling powerful software, which is integrated with many features and useful functions. The application supports standard UML 2.x and allows you to create and use 11 kinds of UML diagrams are different, including Ca use, composition, sequence, Communication, diagram, record, Class, object, deployment, composite structure, Statechart and Activity.
StarUML allows you to easily create diagrams entity relationship. Here is the diagram that are widely used for the...
</description></item><item><title>Download MKVToolnix 95.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:50:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mkvtoolnix-1129.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mkvtoolnix-1129.html
</guid><description>
MKVToolnix is software that supports video editing, such as cutting or splicing the videos together to create a complete video and unique. MKVToolnix to help you cut the interesting scenes in the video to create the short clips impress others. In addition, you can also stitch multiple videos together to create a single video quality, get big interest from viewers.
MKVToolnix - Cut and connect video
MKVToolnix allows you to customize and manage up the MKV file had to be cut or connect...
</description></item><item><title>Download ASCOMP Easy Slideshow Professional 1.003</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:50:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ascomp-easy-slideshow-professional-13811.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ascomp-easy-slideshow-professional-13811.html
</guid><description>
ASCOMP Easy Slideshow Professional is a user-friendly Windows software designed to quickly create stunning slideshow videos from your photos. Ideal for both beginners and professionals, the software offers an intuitive drag-and-drop interface for arranging images, setting display durations, and adding individual subtitles or captions for personalization.
Key features include:
	Over 200 built-in transition effects such as soft fades, dynamic zooms, and creative animations for changing...
</description></item><item><title>Download AllmapSoft Google Satellite Maps Downloader 8.409</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:49:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-google-satellite-maps-downloader-687.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-google-satellite-maps-downloader-687.html
</guid><description>
AllmapSoft Google Satellite Maps Downloader is software help download map images from google maps on computer for you to get the satellite images from google map. All the downloaded photos will be saved on disk. You can see the map is downloaded by viewer Or you can combine them into the map BMP, big. It supports proxy server. And you can easily get the longitude and latitude of each image tile small download.
You can use offline maps in GIS software such as Global Mapper, QGIS,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Psiphon 186.20250913</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:49:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-psiphon-7347.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-psiphon-7347.html
</guid><description>
Psiphon is a firewall bypass tool by Psiphon Inc. Uses VPN, SSH and HTTP Proxy technology to give you uncensored access to Internet content. Your Psiphon app automatically learns about new hotspots to maximize your chances of bypassing censorship.
The way the software works is that Psiphon constantly changes the proxy, so the user's IP address is also constantly changing, the server will not detect the user's real address, so you can feel free. roof. access to websites and software...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cerberus FTP Server Enterprise 2025.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:49:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cerberus-ftp-server-enterprise-317.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cerberus-ftp-server-enterprise-317.html
</guid><description>
Cerberus FTP Server Enterprise is software that provides encrypted SSL / TLS industrial safety and server performance FTP most powerful. The special point is Cerberus FTP Server Enterprise uses very little CPU and memory, Cerberus has friendly interface, users can easily hidden or accessed from the system tray.
Server can listen to connections on multiple interfaces (PC users), integrated with the user database Windows NT or Active Directory, run as NT service, resume transfer not...
</description></item><item><title>Download AnyMP4 Blu-ray Player 6.5.80</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:48:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anymp4-blu-ray-player-1113.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anymp4-blu-ray-player-1113.html
</guid><description>
AnyMP4 Blu-ray Player software is a Blu-ray Player wonderful and this unique ability to play any Blu-ray which are released in different regions, all folder Blu-ray files and ISO image backup on your hard drive. It also features the function of HD software Video Player, can play 1080p HD video and AVCHD video in picture effect, video quality, fluent and high.
AnyMP4 Blu-ray Player - The video player Blu-ray
In addition, software Blu-ray Player works as a software Universal Media...
</description></item><item><title>Download YUMI exFAT 1.0.3.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:47:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yumi-exfat-7423.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yumi-exfat-7423.html
</guid><description>
YUMI exFAT is a Multiboot USB creator that supports exFAT format and files larger than 4GB. BIOS and USB UEFI boot. YUMI exFAT is compatible with Ventoy. It supports both modern UEFI and Legacy BIOS boot modes. Included is a separate USB Boot creation tool derived from Ventoy/Ventoy2Disk. This variant is also backward compatible with Ventoy. If desired, you can even copy YUMI-exFAT-xxx.exe to the same location as Ventoy2Disk.exe and use the YUMI-exFAT-xxx.exe user interface with...
</description></item></channel></rss>