<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 01:45:00 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 01:45:00 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Realtek High Definition Audio Drivers 6.0.9918.1 WHQL</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Dec 2025 23:37:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-realtek-high-definition-audio-drivers-r282-32bit-64bit-442.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-realtek-high-definition-audio-drivers-r282-32bit-64bit-442.html
</guid><description>
Realtek High Definition Audio Drivers is audio drivers Realtek high-quality latest for windows operating systems, virgin audio controller is based on Realtek for Windows 7/8/8.1/10. When the window is integrated this Driver will make the sound of computer, laptop, your back up crisp, and the sound output for the highest quality possible.
Realtek High Definition Audio Drivers and devices are supported :
ALC880, ALC882, ALC883, ALC885, ALC888, ALC889, ALC861VC, ALC861VD, ALC892, ALC663,...
</description></item><item><title>Download MiniTool Partition Wizard Technician 13.5</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Dec 2025 23:36:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minitool-partition-wizard-pro-604.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minitool-partition-wizard-pro-604.html
</guid><description>
MiniTool Partition Wizard Technician is the best partition manager for Windows, MiniTool Partition Wizard aims to maximize disk performance. It helps to create/change the size/format of the flexible partition, the disk conversion between the MBR and GPT disks, the partition conversion between NTFS and FAT32 and converting the disk into a basic without losing data.
Recovery of data quickly, effective: MiniTool partition management software provides two perfect solutions for data recovery....
</description></item><item><title>Download Aiseesoft Burnova 1.5.52</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Dec 2025 23:36:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aiseesoft-burnova-512.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aiseesoft-burnova-512.html
</guid><description>
Aiseesoft Burnova is software to create a DVD with the video customized by downloading them from the web, add effects. Aiseesoft Burnova is the kind of app to create DVD interesting videos, including the custom menu. The interface is quite intuitive, with modern structure and the menu delete allows you to quickly understand and easily perform all actions. A slider capacity estimates for you know if you have enough or too much data to record.
No need to say that you can include the clip...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ashampoo Burning Studio 27.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Dec 2025 23:35:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-burning-studio-266.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-burning-studio-266.html
</guid><description>
Ashampoo Burning Studio 19 recording files, movies and music to any disc CD, DVD, or Blu-ray any. It's easy, fast and secure! Record data, create audio CDS, create backups, or create your own movie - the possibilities are endless! Even the senior project as a DVD video with the menu and the scene selection screen is only a few minutes. Get the total solution for the drive recorder of you!
Ashampoo Burning Studio
Features Ashampoo Burning Studio
	Fast, clear and powerful - now with...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ableton Live Suite 12.3.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Dec 2025 23:34:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ableton-live-suite-663.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ableton-live-suite-663.html
</guid><description>
Ableton Live Suite is professional software to create, edit, music with effects, instruments, audio and all creative. Ableton Live Suite is the software fast, flexible and flexibility to create and perform music. Move freely between the musical elements and play with ideas, that don't stop the music and do not break the flow of your sound.
Features, Ableton Live Suite
	Meet Wavetable, Echo, Drum Buss and Pedal: the new equipment means new sounds, colorful can with the instruments and...
</description></item><item><title>Download MiniTool Partition Wizard Pro Deluxe 13.5 + Pro Platinum</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Dec 2025 23:34:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minitool-partition-wizard-pro-deluxe-6013.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minitool-partition-wizard-pro-deluxe-6013.html
</guid><description>
MiniTool Partition Wizard Pro Deluxe is one of the best partition managers. It does not only include all of the functions of Free, but also embedded some of the advanced partition technologies such as partition merger, NTFS conversion to FAT32, changing the size of the cluster size and conversion of the disk to basic users.
The software helps you convert partition format such as FAT MBR Disk, GPT Disk, copy and convert Dynamic Disk, change the size of the cluster, change the label,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tor Browser 15.0.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Dec 2025 23:33:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tor-browser-1833.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tor-browser-1833.html
</guid><description>
Tor Browser also has full name is Tor Browser Bundle is a web browser give you ability to access the internet safety and security your personal information as well as sensitive documents absolutely. By Tor Browser Bundle will automatically change the IP address on the machine to hide the identity when surfing the web. Tor Browser is free web browser full-featured basic and advanced allows you to leverage the Tor network anonymously without need to make any configuration changes or install...
</description></item><item><title>Download priPrinter Professional 7.0.0.2615 Beta</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Dec 2025 23:33:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-priprinter-professional-633.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-priprinter-professional-633.html
</guid><description>
priPrinter Professional is the printer driver allows you to manipulate the output of the printer before being printed. PriPrinter is installed and select the same as the printer driver other. After printing it automatically displays the preview in where you can preview his print, change the layout, page position back, cut them, and much more. Then, you print it to printer or save your document for later use. With PriPrinter you will always be sure his prints will look like. You can measure...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tenorshare 4DDiG File Repair 4.3.3.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Dec 2025 23:33:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tenorshare-4ddig-file-repair-5630.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tenorshare-4ddig-file-repair-5630.html
</guid><description>
Tenorshare 4DDiG File Repair is AI-powered software to repair damaged or damaged videos, photos, files and audios, improve their quality and add color to black media white. 4DDiG photo editing solves all photo problems like blurry photos, overexposed photos, etc. Powered by AI, it can dramatically improve image resolution and colorize black and white photos in seconds, not hours.
Features of Tenorshare 4DDiG File Repair
	Easily repair any blurry, overexposed and damaged videos, photos...
</description></item><item><title>Download Robin YouTube Video Downloader Pro 7.0.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Dec 2025 23:32:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-video-downloader-pro-2828.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-video-downloader-pro-2828.html
</guid><description>
YouTube Video Downloader Pro is a Windows application professional to download and convert videos from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion and thousands of video sharing sites, other. It accelerates your download up to 5 times. YouTube Video Downloader Pro allows you to download multiple videos at the same time. It also allows you to pause, resume and cancel a download at any time.
YouTube Video Downloader Pro - Download online videos on social networks
Features of YouTube Video Downloader...
</description></item><item><title>Download MiniTool Partition Wizard Pro Ultimate 13.5 + Pro Version</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Dec 2025 23:31:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minitool-partition-wizard-pro-ultimate-6012.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minitool-partition-wizard-pro-ultimate-6012.html
</guid><description>
MiniTool Partition Wizard Pro Ultimate is a feature-wide multiplicity algorithm, designed to optimize your disk usage and data protection. It comes with a lot of powerful features that you can completely control your hard disk and partition. With a user-friendly interface and simple guidance, you can change the size of the partition, copy the disk, scan the lost partition and move the operating system to the SSD easily and safely.
Software support software Linux Ext2, Ext3, Ext4,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Psiphon 186.20251209</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Dec 2025 23:31:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-psiphon-7347.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-psiphon-7347.html
</guid><description>
Psiphon is a firewall bypass tool by Psiphon Inc. Uses VPN, SSH and HTTP Proxy technology to give you uncensored access to Internet content. Your Psiphon app automatically learns about new hotspots to maximize your chances of bypassing censorship.
The way the software works is that Psiphon constantly changes the proxy, so the user's IP address is also constantly changing, the server will not detect the user's real address, so you can feel free. roof. access to websites and software...
</description></item><item><title>Download MiniTool Partition Wizard Enterprise 13.5 + Server</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Dec 2025 23:30:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minitool-partition-wizard-enterprise-3338.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minitool-partition-wizard-enterprise-3338.html
</guid><description>
MiniTool Partition Wizard Enterprise is a rich feature partition tool, designed to optimize the use of disk and to protect your data. It comes with a lot of powerful features that you can completely control your hard disk and partition. With a user-friendly interface and simple guidance, you can change the size of the partition, copy the disk, scan the lost parties and move the OS to the SSD easily and safely.
The features of MiniTool Partition Wizard Enterprise
	All-in-One Disk...
</description></item><item><title>Download JWIZARD Cleaner 1.10.4</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Dec 2025 23:27:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jwizard-cleaner-12853.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jwizard-cleaner-12853.html
</guid><description>
Effective Windows cleaning software to remove unnecessary files from your PC. JWIZARD Cleaner for Windows quickly frees up disk space and keeps your system in an optimal state, ensuring your PC runs stably and efficiently. This application is designed to provide you with a comprehensive tool to analyze and optimize your PC by performing a comprehensive cleanup or a more detailed cleanup, targeting specific areas such as system, browser, mail, etc.
Features of JWIZARD Cleaner
	Clean...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDF24 PDF Creator 11.29.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Dec 2025 23:26:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf24-pdf-creator-926.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf24-pdf-creator-926.html
</guid><description>
PDF24 PDF Creator is a printer driver application that lets you convert any document or image can be printed into PDF format. With any application that supports printing any user can also create a PDF file of the document through the virtual printer PDF24. Virtual printer can also save the file under format image files other than PDF such as PNG, JPEG, BMP, TIFF, and PSD. After printing, a help section of the program that pops up allows the user to view, save, send, edit that...
</description></item><item><title>Download gSyncing 1.1.73</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Dec 2025 23:26:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gsyncing-10173.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gsyncing-10173.html
</guid><description>
gSyncing allows you to synchronize your contacts, calendar, and Outlook tasks with your Google account and other supported services such as smartphones and tablets runs on iOS, Android, Windows Phone, etc. For example, sync Outlook calendar with Google calendar. You can easily use your Gmail account while traveling and then continue using Outlook on your desktop. Syncing your Google contacts with Outlook helps you access and manage your contacts on any device.
The program runs on...
</description></item><item><title>Download BricsCad Ultimate 26.1.07</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Dec 2025 23:25:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bricscad-ultimate-3256.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bricscad-ultimate-3256.html
</guid><description>
BricsCad Ultimate is a software solution, CAD powerful and comprehensive, providing both tools advanced 2D and model 3D live smart on Linux and windows platform. Utility that allows you to sort the file DWG in hierarchical structures and allows you to easily assemble their products with the help of a set of tools and ingredients powerful 3D.
BricsCad Ultimate allows you to rotate and move any part of your model to solve all problems kinematics in real time. The program also allows you to...
</description></item><item><title>Download SysTools EML Attachment Extractor 5.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Dec 2025 23:25:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-systools-eml-attachment-extractor-12405.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-systools-eml-attachment-extractor-12405.html
</guid><description>
SysTools EML Attachment Extractor is designed to seamlessly extract attachments from EML/EMLX files with ease. The software does not only download attachments embedded in EML/EMLX files. But also allows saving it to the drive. It is also capable of supporting all EML files generated from major email clients like Thunderbird, The Bat, Live Mail, etc.
Features
	Extract attachments from EML/EMLX files and save to local drive
	Supports extracting EML/EMLX attachments from multiple files...
</description></item><item><title>Download Awesome Miner Ultimate 11.3.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Dec 2025 23:24:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-awesome-miner-9041.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-awesome-miner-9041.html
</guid><description>
Awesome Miner is a software application designed to manage and monitor cryptocurrency mining operations. It supports a wide variety of mining hardware, including ASICs and GPUs, and can be used to manage mining for a variety of cryptocurrencies, including Bitcoin, Ethereum, and Litecoin.
Powerful tool to manage and monitor cryptocurrency mining activities. With support for a wide variety of mining hardware and cryptocurrencies, mobile apps, and customizable alerting and performance...
</description></item><item><title>Download DBF Recovery 4.62</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Dec 2025 23:24:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbf-recovery-7931.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbf-recovery-7931.html
</guid><description>
DBF Recovery is software that gives users the ability to restore a damaged database back to its original condition without the expertise required to complete that task. It fixes headers and data structures in an automated process that doesn't involve user interaction. With DBF Recovery, you will truly have a lean, honest DBF repair machine without any functionality.
Features of DBF Recovery
	Quick and simple to use DBF file repair software.
	Repair almost any DBF...
</description></item><item><title>Download Revo Uninstaller 2.6.5</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Dec 2025 22:54:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-revo-uninstaller-free-6752.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-revo-uninstaller-free-6752.html
</guid><description>
Revo Uninstaller is a freeware that helps you to uninstall software and remove unwanted programs easily. Revo Uninstaller acts as a replacement and complement to the built-in functionality of Windows by running the built-in uninstaller for the program first and then scanning for leftover data, making it obsolete. become your best option when it comes to removing stubborn pieces completely. Programs, temporary files, and other unnecessary program data are left behind after the standard...
</description></item><item><title>Download Task Explorer 1.7.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Dec 2025 22:54:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-task-explorer-4305.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-task-explorer-4305.html
</guid><description>
Task Explorer is a management application task navigate to advanced users can track and display details about the running apps, memory and more. For example: on the top of the page, you can find memory, GPU memory, object, Processor, GPU, TCP / IP and many more. Right click and you can customize what you can track exactly what you want easily. In addition, CPU, GPU, memory Read / Write and up / down are also displayed directly at the bottom.
Task Explorer - task Manager Windows
Related...
</description></item><item><title>Download ControlMyMonitor 1.40</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Dec 2025 17:23:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-controlmymonitor-1801.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-controlmymonitor-1801.html
</guid><description>
ControlMyMonitor allows you to view and modify most settings of the screen (brightness, contrast, sharpness, color balance, red / green / blue, etc.) without using the OSD. You can modify the settings from the application interface or from the command line, at the same time export all the settings into a config file and then reload them to quickly switch between the configuration screen. ControlMyMonitor works with any monitor which supports DDC / CI.
ControlMyMonitor - Modified The...
</description></item><item><title>Download RepairKit 1.3.5</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Dec 2025 17:23:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-repairkit-11968.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-repairkit-11968.html
</guid><description>
RepairKit is an all-in-one Java-based Windows repair and maintenance toolkit. RepairKit aims to provide a package that provides users with a dedicated system repair tool as well as quick access to some operating system features and some other PC maintenance software that comes with it. it.
If you want to keep your PC running smoothly and want to do it conveniently, RepairKit offers a simple and effective solution for that, with an automatic repair/cleanup module , as well as access to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Advanced SystemCare Pro 19.1.0.176</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Dec 2025 17:21:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-systemcare-pro-368.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-systemcare-pro-368.html
</guid><description>
Advanced SystemCare Pro is software that provides features to optimize a PC system professional cleanup, repair, speed up and protect PC.  Advanced SystemCare Pro tab Protect new is added, is designed to provide quick access to protect browsing from being tracked by automatically delete traces of privacy when browser closed and detect and resist the attack of the plugin / malicious toolbar by Browser Anti -Backing and Plugin / toolbar cleaner.
Program speed up pc top
Advanced SystemCare...
</description></item></channel></rss>