<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 12:01:16 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 12:01:16 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download TidyWindow 3.9.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 01:34:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tidywindow-14454.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tidywindow-14454.html
</guid><description>
TidyWindow is a Windows desktop assistant that automates developer PC setup, cleanup, diagnostics, software package installation, registry tweaking, and driver updates—powered by a WPF interface and robust PowerShell 7 automation capabilities in the background.
Key Features
	Essentials Repair Center (docs/essentials.md): Queues selected automation tasks Filter for network, Defender, printing, and Windows Update issues. Each task supports preview run, sequential execution, restore...
</description></item><item><title>Download AnyDesk 9.6.8</title><pubDate> Thu, 22 Jan 2026 01:33:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anydesk-1321.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anydesk-1321.html
</guid><description>
AnyDesk is software computer control remote, easy connection with remote computer management and manipulation on the computer. After installing the AnyDesk up 2 the computer then you can easily use the software to provide technical support for a friend or family member or you have access to your computer while you away from home or office.
AnyDesk - control your computer remotely
The process of using very simple software, want to allow access to his computer, only need to provide for...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Acrobat Pro DC 2025.001.21111 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jan 2026 22:19:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-001en-adobe-acrobat-pro-458.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-001en-adobe-acrobat-pro-458.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Acrobat Pro DC is a comprehensive software that helps you create and edit the PDF&amp;nbsp;document, or create form, sign, protect PDF, connect, split PDF, export PDF to various formats. The Acrobat Pro DC is the latest version of Adobe with improvements in the interface with the polished ribbon bar and the ability to create and handle pdf files as well as its male versions.
The highlight of the Acrobat Pro DC is probably the ability to connect, store documents on the cloud, you can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Drive SnapShot 1.50.0.1830</title><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jan 2026 22:18:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-drive-snapshot-701.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-drive-snapshot-701.html
</guid><description>
Drive SnapShot is a backup software, Restore disk, including operating system, installed programs, your data and all security attributes - while windows is running and you continue to work. With Drive SnapShot you backup partition or hard drive and it can also create disk image of your system. If a disaster occurs (a virus, trojan or the fixed hard disk), the recover complete and accurate your system will be able to accomplish after only a few minutes. The image file can be mounted as...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Substance 3D Designer 15.1.1 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jan 2026 22:17:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-substancee-designer-adobe-908.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-substancee-designer-adobe-908.html
</guid><description>
Substance Designer is the tool aggregated structure to help design, create 3D material. Create the file Quality or texture bitmap. Substance Designer helps users to create materials with full control and infinite variations. Edit the texture complete immediately and create texture, Quality and material of MDL will be handled directly in the renderer or game engine of you.
Substance Designer - design, create 3D material
The main features of Substance Designer
	Substance Designer...
</description></item><item><title>Download PhotoPad Image Editor Pro 15.00 Beta</title><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jan 2026 22:16:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photopad-image-editor-572.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photopad-image-editor-572.html
</guid><description>
PhotoPad Image Editor is a software to help edit photos and supports lots of features like edit, cut, rotate, resize and flip digital photos. With PhotoPad Image Editor, you can freely perform the basic editing for their images and also can add some neat effect. It has the option to create a photo collage and mosaic images from your photos, and you can also add text and captions. If you prefer, you can complete your masterpiece by adding the frame or contour is simple.
The main features...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sante DICOM Worklist Server 2.4.5</title><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jan 2026 22:15:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sante-dicom-worklist-server-12615.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sante-dicom-worklist-server-12615.html
</guid><description>
Sante DICOM Worklist Server (MWL Server) is an automated program that can receive via HL7 communication messages the patient's demographic information and examination schedules stored in the HIS/RIS system. Hospital Information System/Radiology Information System) and transfer them to any modality/medical scanner via DICOM communication protocol (C-FIND). The program provides automatic, error-free and reliable transfer of HL7 information (HIS/RIS) nodes to DICOM (medical scanner) nodes...
</description></item><item><title>Download Advanced SystemCare Ultimate 18.1.0.87</title><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jan 2026 20:53:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-systemcare-ultimate-132.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-systemcare-ultimate-132.html
</guid><description>
Advanced SystemCare Ultimate 17: Antivirus software that also helps protect, repair, clean and optimize your PC. Based on BitDefender antivirus technology and IObit anti-malware engine, it is part of IObit antivirus project devoted to providing better and value-added services to our users.
With real-time protection against viruses, spyware and phishing attacks, powerful tuning and cleaning functions, Advanced SystemCare Ultimate provides always-on protection, Automatic and all-in-one...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Lightroom Classic 2026 v15.1.1 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jan 2026 20:52:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-photoshop-lightroom-classic-0004-734.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-photoshop-lightroom-classic-0004-734.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Photoshop Lightroom Classic is a desktop-optimized photo editing and organizing software. Lightroom Classic gives you powerful one-click tools and advanced controls to make your photos look great. Easily organize all your photos on your desktop and share them in a variety of ways.
In addition, Lightroom Classic has a powerful import process that allows users to preview images before importing. It supports many camera raw formats and includes a database system for efficient photo...
</description></item><item><title>Download Perfectly Clear WorkBench 5.0.1.3052</title><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jan 2026 20:51:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfectly-clear-workbench-6892.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfectly-clear-workbench-6892.html
</guid><description>
Perfectly Clear Workbench is an application that uses image editing libraries Perfectly Clear by Athentech and is provided to demonstrate the capabilities of the Perfectly Clear processing libraries, which recognize faces and allow quick export of processing settings for use.
One of the key features in Workbench is the ability to "export to API" when saving a Preset. This allows you to make image edits in Workbench and adjust the settings to suit your editing style and needs. You can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Donemax Disk Clone Enterprise 3.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jan 2026 20:51:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-donemax-disk-clone-enterprise-9076.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-donemax-disk-clone-enterprise-9076.html
</guid><description>
Donemax Disk Clone Enterprise is a software tool designed for Windows computers that allows users to create a complete backup of their hard drive or partition. The software can be used to clone an entire hard drive, including the operating system, applications, and data to another hard drive or SSD, making it a useful tool for administrators. systems and IT professionals who need to manage multiple computers.
This software provides users with several options for creating backups,...
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 7.9.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jan 2026 20:51:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-10-7759.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-10-7759.html
</guid><description>
TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 is a utility that allows users to discover hidden settings in Windows 10. This application is specially designed for Windows 10, groups many registry settings and provide them from an easy and secure user interface. With TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 you can move the Windows taskbar to the top and resize the taskbar by editing the registry value. With any application that modifies the registry, we recommend that you have a backup copy to...
</description></item><item><title>Download O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro 22.1.239 / Server</title><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jan 2026 20:50:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-diskimage-pro-218.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-diskimage-pro-218.html
</guid><description>
O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro is software backup data comprehensive and effective is provided to protect the data of the computer system, it creates images for individual drives or the entire system that still does not affect your system.
O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro allows the user to backup the entire computer or drive, the and files whenever you want even while the computer is being used. Or can use O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro to create a copy chinh sac of computer disk drives, can be used instead of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download PhotoLine 25.50</title><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jan 2026 20:50:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photoline-1721.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photoline-1721.html
</guid><description>
PhotoLine is a powerful image editing full-featured with support for layers, text, vectors and images. In addition to the editing features, standards, it supports 16 bits per channel, CMYK and Lab as well as color management with an ICC profile. PhotoLine support display and edit IPTC data and EXIF, batch conversion, output library, HTML, batch rename, and more. Image processing professional - despite the low price PhotoLine 32 offers every function needed to handle professional image: 16...
</description></item><item><title>Download Scrapbook Factory Deluxe 5.0.3.5</title><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jan 2026 20:49:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-scrapbook-factory-deluxe-12669.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-scrapbook-factory-deluxe-12669.html
</guid><description>
Scrapbook Factory Deluxe offers the ultimate collection of over 6,500 exclusive templates as well as over 75,000 beautiful graphics and over 5000 surreal decorative details that are sure to capture the excitement of any occasion. You can also create beautiful CD Photo Scrapbooks that you can watch on TV and as an added bonus, personalized photo calendars!
Scrapbook Factory Deluxe Features
	Over 6,500 exclusive templates and customizable projects
	Over 75,000 beautiful graphics...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tribler 8.3.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jan 2026 20:48:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tribler-4761.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tribler-4761.html
</guid><description>
Tribler is free software comes with a set of neat features not only to download faster, but also more security. application retains the fashion style with modern interface, the layout is well-organized and intuitive features. The side panel provides quick access to most of the areas you will visit, such as home, search results loader, channel list downloads, as well as the video player is deployed. No need to say that all of the corresponding options pop up in the rest of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download DBF Converter 7.73</title><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jan 2026 20:48:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbf-converter-6362.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbf-converter-6362.html
</guid><description>
DBF Converter is a common solution for all your DBF format conversion needs. Whenever you need to extract data from the DBF file to CSV, XLS, XLSX, SQL or pure text, the software will provide a simple way to do this with minimal effort.
Features of DBF Converter
	Work with DBF Converter is easy. You specify a DBF file or a directory with DBF files that you want to convert, select the fields and filter out the records you need. Then, just a click to DBF Converter to turn the source...
</description></item><item><title>Download FRITZ 20.9</title><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jan 2026 20:47:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fritz-14060.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fritz-14060.html
</guid><description>
FRITZ 20 is more than just a chess engine – it’s a training revolution for aspiring players and professionals. Whether you’re taking your first steps into the world of professional chess training, or are already playing at tournament level, FRITZ 20 will help you train more efficiently, intelligently and personally than ever before.
Simulate playing styles at the highest level
FRITZ 20 analyzes your next opponent – and plays just like them!
Use the style analysis feature in...
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 7.9.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jan 2026 20:47:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-11-7760.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-11-7760.html
</guid><description>
TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 is a program that allows users to discover hidden settings in Windows 11. This application is specially designed for Windows 11, groups many registry settings and distribute them from the easy and secure user interface. With TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 you can move the Windows taskbar to the top and resize the taskbar by editing the registry value. With any application that modifies the registry, we recommend that you have a backup copy...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Video Downloader 12.1.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jan 2026 20:46:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-video-downloader-9636.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-video-downloader-9636.html
</guid><description>
YT Video Downloader is software used to easily and quickly download any video or audio content from any website in HD quality using video downloader online. Save videos from almost any website supported by a video downloader on your local hard drive. Media search is a convenient way to do this.
Features of YT Video Downloader
	Download videos from hundreds of video sites.
	Really increase your download speed by up to 500% or even more!
	Download 8K, 5K, 4K Ultra HD, 2K Quad HD, 1080p...
</description></item><item><title>Download FireAlpaca 2.14.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jan 2026 20:45:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-firealpaca-2882.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-firealpaca-2882.html
</guid><description>
FireAlpaca is software painting Digital free available in 10 languages and is compatible with both Mac and Windows. The tools and simple controls allow you to draw a easy illustration. Convenient tool will be adding this one to the other! Download FireAlpaca right now! FireAlpaca is the utility to create and edit image files, add image overlays, as well as providing many other advanced features, bring an effective tool to help you draw a picture or edit a photo from the most basic...
</description></item><item><title>Download CAMWorks 2026 SP0 for Solid Edge 2025-2026</title><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jan 2026 17:49:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-camworks-for-solid-edge-8108.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-camworks-for-solid-edge-8108.html
</guid><description>
CAMWorks is a module for creating control programs for CNC machines. With the aim of providing new capabilities to increase productivity to help companies in the field of integration, design to build and save costs. CAMWorks design software offers customer-centric multi-personal advancement, allowing operators to increase productivity during tool production. The software has a more automated and time-saving process of tool programming, CNC operation and machining.
The processing is done...
</description></item><item><title>Download Java SE Development Kit 25.0.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jan 2026 17:45:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-java-se-development-kit-6881.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-java-se-development-kit-6881.html
</guid><description>
Java allows you to play online games, chat with people around the world, and view images in 3D. These applications, written in the Java programming language and accessible from your browser, are called applets. Companies also use Java applications for intranet applications and other e-business solutions.
Java is used by companies in all major industries. Whether deployed on mobile phones, embedded devices, game consoles, laptops, or in data centers, Java provides rich user interfaces,...
</description></item><item><title>Download ShareX 19.0.1 + Portable</title><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jan 2026 17:44:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sharex-946.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sharex-946.html
</guid><description>
ShareX is a screen capture tool lets you capture an area on your desktop and automatically save to clipboard, your hard drive or download now up more than 25 file storage service different, including Imgur, Flickr , ImageShack, TinyPic, Dropbox and others.
With the "After Capture" allows you to choose whether you want to download snapshots of yourself up hosting service or keep it locally and support more action even adding watermarks to mark copyright photos.
ShareX - Capture screen...
</description></item><item><title>Download Q-Dir 12.46</title><pubDate> Wed, 21 Jan 2026 16:47:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-q-dir-348.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-q-dir-348.html
</guid><description>
Q-Dir is software to manage the entire file and folder on the computer, allowing to see file in same time 4 different positions (viewport quadro) while still maintaining all the standard features of the Explorer.
It also provides a variety of management features, additional files included the filter file color-coding, layouts and columns can be customized, quick access to file and folder favorites and more.
Other features of Q-Dir , including directory listings (.txt, .doc .html .csv),...
</description></item></channel></rss>