<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 23:34:57 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 23:34:57 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Revo Uninstaller for Android 3.4.330G</title><pubDate> Sun, 31 Aug 2025 22:15:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-revo-uninstaller-for-android-10156.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-revo-uninstaller-for-android-10156.html
</guid><description>
Revo uninstaller for Android helps you uninstall Android apps as well as organize and clean your device. Remove all leftover and hidden files for a clean and bloatware-free device. Easy-to-use tool to uninstall Android apps, their leftovers and hidden files. We specialize in uninstalling apps and optimizing smartphone storage space.
Every application leaves residual data after uninstallation. Revo Uninstall Mobile detects these leftovers and deletes them after showing you the files, so...
</description></item><item><title>Download All Document Reader and Viewer 2.8.5</title><pubDate> Sun, 31 Aug 2025 22:14:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-all-document-reader-and-viewer-8877.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-all-document-reader-and-viewer-8877.html
</guid><description>
All Document Reader: PDF, excel, word, Documents is a smart office application that helps you read all documents downloaded from the internet, supports reading PDF files, PDF Reader, doc, docx xls, ppt, txt, excel, xlxs files... fast, easy and convenient.. All Document Reader: PDF, excel, word, Documents are providing multiple Document reading features including PDF Reader, Docs Reader &amp;amp; Docx, ppt reader, xls reader, txt, excel &amp;amp; documents different from readers.
All Document...
</description></item><item><title>Download All PDF Editor &amp;amp; Reader | Xodo 10.6.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 31 Aug 2025 22:14:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-xodo-pdf-reader-editor-8451.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-xodo-pdf-reader-editor-8451.html
</guid><description>
Xodo PDF Reader &amp;amp; Editor is a mobile application for reading and editing PDF documents on Android and iOS devices. The app allows users to view, annotate, and edit PDF files using a variety of tools, including highlighting, underlining, and adding notes. With Xodo, you can read, annotate, sign, and share PDFs and fill out PDF forms, all while syncing with Google Drive, Dropbox, and OneDrive.
Xodo PDF Reader &amp;amp; Editor Features
	PDF Viewer: Application that allows users to view...
</description></item><item><title>Download AZIP Master: ZIP RAR Extractor 4.2.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 31 Aug 2025 22:14:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-azip-master-zip-rar-extractor-9785.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-azip-master-zip-rar-extractor-9785.html
</guid><description>
AZIP Master is a file manager application, zip file reader, creates archives in ZIP or 7Z file format. Unzip multiple archive file formats: unZIP (unzip ZIP files) unRAR (unzip RAR files), etc. Being a stable application - AZIP Master is an attractive choice for mobile users globally.
AZIP Master Features: ZIP RAR Extractor
	Decompress multiple files at once
	️Create a packaged 7Z ZIP archive
	️Quick decompression: open compressed files with the ZIP RAR 7Z file decompression...
</description></item><item><title>Download Photo Editor 11.9</title><pubDate> Sun, 31 Aug 2025 22:13:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-iudesk-photo-editor-8321.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-iudesk-photo-editor-8321.html
</guid><description>
Photo Editor is a small but powerful photo editing application. If you have some knowledge about photography, you can do a lot with Photo Editor. Now use Photo Editor to edit photos on your mobile phone just like on your PC.
Photo Editor Features
	Color: exposure, brightness, contrast, saturation, temperature, tone, and hue
	Curves &amp;amp; levels: color fine-tuning
	Effects: gamma correction, auto contrast, auto tone, vibrance, blur, sharpen, oil painting, sketch, high contrast black...
</description></item><item><title>Download AdGuard Ad Blocker 4.11.63 Final</title><pubDate> Sun, 31 Aug 2025 22:13:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-adguard-block-ads-without-root-8215.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-adguard-block-ads-without-root-8215.html
</guid><description>
AdGuard for Android is the only root-free ad blocker for Android that removes ads in apps and browsers, protects your privacy, and helps you manage your apps. Adguard is designed to block unwanted ads, pop-ups and banners while you browse the web on your device. It uses a combination of local VPN technology and a custom DNS server to block ads, meaning it can block ads in apps as well as in web browsers.
In addition, Adguard also blocks tracking scripts from collecting information about...
</description></item><item><title>Download IPTV Pro 9.1.3</title><pubDate> Sun, 31 Aug 2025 22:12:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-iptv-pro-9093.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-iptv-pro-9093.html
</guid><description>
IPTV Pro is an Android application that allows you to watch live TV channels and movies on your Android device. It provides access to many channels from around the world, including sports, news, movies, and entertainment channels. IPTV Pro supports both M3U and XSPF playlists, and allows you to add your own playlists.
IPTV Pro Features
	Supports M3U and XSPF playlists
	Playlist history
	Play a multicast stream using a UDP proxy (the proxy needs to be installed in your LAN)
	Grid, list...
</description></item><item><title>Download Duolingo: language lessons 6.45.3</title><pubDate> Sun, 31 Aug 2025 22:12:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-duolingo-language-lessons-8265.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-duolingo-language-lessons-8265.html
</guid><description>
Duolingo is a popular language learning app that offers interactive lessons to help users learn new languages. This application offers many languages for you to choose from, including Spanish, French, German, Italian, Portuguese, Chinese, Japanese and many more.
This app offers an gamified learning experience with interactive lessons, exercises, and quizzes designed to help users learn new words, phrases, and grammar rules. This app is designed to be easy to use and suitable for people...
</description></item><item><title>Download Talking Translator - Languages 3.4.6</title><pubDate> Sun, 31 Aug 2025 22:11:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-talking-translator-9776.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-talking-translator-9776.html
</guid><description>
With the instant translation feature, the Talking Translator application will help you communicate in any multilingual environment such as when traveling, going on business trips, meeting buyers or just simple conversations. You can translate into more than 100 languages ​​with just this one app: Talking Translator! You don't know how to read sentences? Nothing! Talking Translator provides handwritten text translation.
Supports more than 100 languages ​​including English,...
</description></item><item><title>Download NokoPrint - Mobile Printing 5.23.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 31 Aug 2025 22:11:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-nokoprint-mobile-printing-8528.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-nokoprint-mobile-printing-8528.html
</guid><description>
Print photos and share them with family and friends. Print documents, PDFs, invoices, receipts, boarding passes, and more. at home, at work or on the go! You can print images, photos, web pages, PDF and Microsoft Office documents without downloading any additional apps or printing tools anytime, anywhere on almost any WiFi, Bluetooth or USB printer .
Features of NokoPrint for Android
	Print directly from your Android phone or tablet to almost any inkjet, laser or thermal...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDF Scanner app - TapScanner 3.0.81</title><pubDate> Sun, 31 Aug 2025 22:11:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pdf-scanner-app-tapscanner-12104.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pdf-scanner-app-tapscanner-12104.html
</guid><description>
TapScanner is a mobile application that allows you to scan documents with your smartphone camera and convert them into PDF files or image formats. It essentially turns your device into a portable scanner, making capturing and digitizing physical documents convenient on the go.
TapScanner Features
	Scan documents, receipts, QRs and business cards
	Document Scanner App - Automatic Border Detection
	Tweak your images with multiple filters to achieve perfection
	Easily manage your...
</description></item><item><title>Download ChatBox: AI Chat Bot Assistant 1.69.5</title><pubDate> Sun, 31 Aug 2025 22:11:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-chatbox-ai-chat-bot-assistant-12995.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-chatbox-ai-chat-bot-assistant-12995.html
</guid><description>
ChatBox is an advanced AI chat application and your virtual assistant built on the most advanced AI chat models. Designed to seamlessly integrate into your daily life, this AI chatbot uses advanced machine learning to improve productivity and provide instant solutions. Whether you're looking for help with a task or need answers to complex questions, your AI chatbot will leverage the latest advances in AI chat to help.
Some Highlights
	ChatBox leverages the latest AI technology to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Easy Notes - Note Taking Apps 1.3.23.0825</title><pubDate> Sun, 31 Aug 2025 22:10:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-easy-notes-notebook-notepad-8388.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-easy-notes-notebook-notepad-8388.html
</guid><description>
Easy Notes - Great note taking app, Notepad, Notebook, Free Notes is a free easy to use note taking app for notes app. With this easy notebook and notepad app, take quick notes with colorful backgrounds and checklists to organize notes and tasks easily. Use this aesthetic note taker and note taker to add photos or audio to your notes. Easy Notes is a useful notebook and note-taking app for taking notes and organizing work.
Features of Easy Notes - Notebook, Notepad
	Free Notepad and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Digital Compass 16.8 Build 165</title><pubDate> Sun, 31 Aug 2025 22:10:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-digital-compass-13590.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-digital-compass-13590.html
</guid><description>
This app is a smart compass with high accuracy and a great tool for outdoor activities. This compass app allows you to easily determine the direction you are facing. This app is built using the device's gyroscope, accelerometer, magnetometer, gravity sensor to determine the direction. Make sure your device has an accelerometer and magnetometer sensor or it will not work.
Features
	Show current location (longitude, latitude, address)
	Show altitude
	Show magnetic field strength
	Show...
</description></item><item><title>Download SnapTube for Android 7.46.1.74671001</title><pubDate> Sun, 31 Aug 2025 22:10:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-snaptube-youtube-downloader-hd-video-8351.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-snaptube-youtube-downloader-hd-video-8351.html
</guid><description>
SnapTube is a mobile application that allows users to download videos from various platforms, such as YouTube, Vimeo, and Dailymotion. It provides video resolution in multiple formats 144p, 720p, 1080p HD, 2K HD, 4K HD and audio formats MP3 and M4A. With Snaptube, users can search for content across all their platforms without using multiple apps.
Features of SnapTube for Android
Download in multiple resolutions
	MP4 videos are available in resolutions: choose small 360 pixels or...
</description></item><item><title>Download radio.net PRIME 5.17.4.0app build 100060</title><pubDate> Sun, 31 Aug 2025 22:09:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-radionet-prime-8335.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-radionet-prime-8335.html
</guid><description>
radio.net PRIME is a mobile application that allows users to listen to a variety of radio stations on their Android devices. This app provides access to more than 30,000 radio stations around the world, including local and international stations in a variety of genres and formats.
Features of radio.net PRIME
	Access to more than 30,000 radio stations around the world
	Supports multiple genres and formats, including news, music, sports, and chat
	Option to create a list of favorite...
</description></item><item><title>Download NetMonitor Pro 1.91</title><pubDate> Sun, 31 Aug 2025 22:06:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-netmonitor-pro-8423.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-netmonitor-pro-8423.html
</guid><description>
NetMonitor Pro is a mobile application that allows users to monitor and troubleshoot network connectivity on their Android devices. It often includes features like testing network speed, signal strength, and the ability to view network information like IP address, ports, and DNS. The app also includes many customizable settings, such as the ability to choose between different network types and customize the app's layout and appearance.
Features of NetMonitor Pro for Android
	Online...
</description></item><item><title>Download Storage Analyzer &amp;amp; Disk Usage 4.1.7.48</title><pubDate> Sun, 31 Aug 2025 22:05:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-storage-analyzer-disk-usage-10142.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-storage-analyzer-disk-usage-10142.html
</guid><description>
Storage Analysis &amp;amp; Disk Usage Displays information about SDCARD, USB devices, external and internal memory in simple and clear graphical form (infographics). The application reads from the device storage list of files and file-specific data (name, path, size, last modified date, file preview) to build device statistics and display it in the form of reports and file usage diagrams (pie charts, Sunburst charts).
The application allows users to connect cloud drives (Google Drive,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Canary Mail - AI Email App 3.63</title><pubDate> Sun, 31 Aug 2025 22:05:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-canary-mail-ai-email-app-11665.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-canary-mail-ai-email-app-11665.html
</guid><description>
Canary is an AI email app created to help you do more in your conversations. Compose emails, prioritize subjects, turn off spam, and more. with just a few taps. Avoid organizing different accounts manually and manage all your contacts, files, and profiles in one place.
With Canary, you can compose emails with just one tap thanks to suggestions generated by Copilot AI. Write professional emails easily with sentence suggestions and custom drafts that Canary saves for regular use. Our AI...
</description></item><item><title>Download Document Scanner - PDF Creator 6.8.17</title><pubDate> Sun, 31 Aug 2025 22:04:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-document-scanner-pdf-creator-9783.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-document-scanner-pdf-creator-9783.html
</guid><description>
Sometimes in a day, you need to scan your different documents multiple times. In that situation, if everything is planned, you will definitely not have to suffer any more. But if the need to scan those documents arises one by one, it will definitely be a disaster. To rescue you from that situation CV Infotech brings you a mobile Doc Scanner. This document scanner allows you to scan your documents anytime, anywhere.
The application also has some additional features that help your scanned...
</description></item><item><title>Download Avast Cleanup – Phone Cleaner 25.17.0 build 800011244</title><pubDate> Sun, 31 Aug 2025 22:04:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-avast-cleanup-phone-cleaner-8885.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-avast-cleanup-phone-cleaner-8885.html
</guid><description>
Avast Cleanup - Phone Cleaner is a mobile app for Android devices designed to help users optimize their phone's performance and free up storage space. This application provides many tools and features to clean and speed up your phone.
One of the main features of Avast Cleanup is the Junk Cleaner, which scans your phone for unnecessary files such as temporary files, app cache, and other junk data. The app will then provide a list of files that can be safely deleted to free up space on...
</description></item><item><title>Download Drivvo - car management 8.6.5</title><pubDate> Sun, 31 Aug 2025 22:03:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-drivvo-car-management-8614.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-drivvo-car-management-8614.html
</guid><description>
Drivvo is a car management app that helps users track and manage expenses related to their vehicles. It provides a platform to record and analyze fuel consumption, maintenance costs and other expenses, making it easier to budget and manage car-related expenses.
Save Money: Manage fuel consumption and economic costs, car maintenance costs and service costs of your car, motorcycle, bus or truck.
Control Finances: Track average KM/liter, monthly costs, average per day, fuel,...
</description></item><item><title>Download WiFi Analyzer 6.3 build 101</title><pubDate> Sun, 31 Aug 2025 22:03:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wifi-analyzer-10225.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wifi-analyzer-10225.html
</guid><description>
Introducing a new way to analyze and optimize your WiFi, Turn your Android device into a WiFi Analyzer! WiFi Analyzer Recommends the best channels and locations for your network. WiFi Analyzer gives you the most useful optimization information to help reduce interference and increase connection speed and stability.
WiFi Analyzer Features
	WiFi optimizer for interference issues
	Channel analyzer for neighboring APs
	Real-time data and distance calculation.
	Signal strength...
</description></item><item><title>Download Money Manager Expense &amp;amp; Budget 4.10.2 GF build 1101</title><pubDate> Sun, 31 Aug 2025 22:02:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-money-manager-expense-budget-13837.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-money-manager-expense-budget-13837.html
</guid><description>
Money Manager - the #1 financial planning, budgeting, expense tracking and personal wealth management app for Android! Money Manager makes managing your personal finances as easy as pie! Now you can easily record personal and business financial transactions, generate spending reports, review daily, weekly and monthly financial data and manage your assets with Money Manager's spending tracker and budget planner.
Key Features
- Adopt double-entry bookkeeping system
Money Manager...
</description></item><item><title>Download Smart Launcher 6 ‧ Home Screen 6.5 build 040</title><pubDate> Sun, 31 Aug 2025 22:02:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-smart-launcher-8412.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-smart-launcher-8412.html
</guid><description>
Smart Launcher is a mobile app that provides users with a customized home screen and app launcher on their Android devices. It includes features like minimalist interface, automatic app sorting, and gesture controls. The app also includes many customizable settings, such as the ability to change the theme, icon size, and screen layout, as well as the ability to create custom categories for the app.
Smart Launcher Features
	Ambient theme: Smart launcher automatically changes theme...
</description></item></channel></rss>