<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 13:43:45 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 13:43:45 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Unicodia 3.0.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 24 Oct 2025 16:43:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-unicodia-8521.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-unicodia-8521.html
</guid><description>
Unicodia is free, open source software that can be used as an alternative character map for your Windows machine. The interface contains everything you need, allowing you to easily cycle through all the available ASCII symbols and copy them to the clipboard. Uncicodia is a great alternative to your standard Unicode characters and is filled with symbols/characters that make it useful for a number of different uses.
Features of Unicodia
	In Windows 10/11 — all characters of Unicode 15...
</description></item><item><title>Download AnyTrans for iOS 8.9.13.20251023</title><pubDate> Fri, 24 Oct 2025 16:43:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anytrans-for-ios-755.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anytrans-for-ios-755.html
</guid><description>
AnyTrans for iOS is content manager essential fully managed iPhone, Android and content of your cloud. Including all mobile devices, all cloud drives from your iPhone, iPad, iPod touch to phones and tablets. From local disk to cloud storage. AnyTrans has protected them all, providing you convenient management for all data and your files, regardless of whether they are stored where.
AnyTrans is the one stop solution to meet all the management needs of your data. For the first time, you can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Secret Disk Pro 2025 v314</title><pubDate> Fri, 24 Oct 2025 16:42:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secret-disk-pro-933.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secret-disk-pro-933.html
</guid><description>
Secret Disk Pro 4 is a software to create a virtual disk can be hidden and password protected to keep your data private and safe. You can store any file and folder on the disk. Disc secret works like a hard disk typically, and is compatible with any any other program that you have installed. You can have more than one disk secret, and you can also choose disk letter.
Secret Disk Pro 4 - Create and secure drive
Secret Disk does not encrypt any files, it just limits access to your files...
</description></item><item><title>Download Gilisoft DRM Protection 9.1.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 24 Oct 2025 16:41:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-video-drm-protection-5260.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-video-drm-protection-5260.html
</guid><description>
Gilisoft Video DRM Protection is software that helps you can protect your videos and the E-Learning content to another by secure, encrypted the files, your content and distribute them to the target audience authorized of you. Very easy to make video / sound / pictures of you can't see are for anyone except those you allow. Gilisoft Video DRM Protection can encrypt and pack video &amp;amp; codec &amp;amp; player into exe.
Gilisoft Video DRM Protection can easily encode almost any kind of Video...
</description></item><item><title>Download FurMark 2.10.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 24 Oct 2025 16:40:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-furmark-1718.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-furmark-1718.html
</guid><description>
FurMark is free software to help check the operation of the computer graphics card at the same time can emulator the situation, unplanned incidents of the CPU, the video card to you have how to handle best. FurMark allows you to set resolutions that card check will pass directly, you can perform both in full-screen mode and window, there are many parameters smoothing, in general, have enough parameters, you just need to artfully place them and you can immediately proceed to check out. If...
</description></item><item><title>Download ThinkAutomation Studio Professional 5.1.1094.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 24 Oct 2025 16:39:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thinkautomation-studio-professional-9635.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thinkautomation-studio-professional-9635.html
</guid><description>
ThinkAutomation Studio Professional is software that automates on-premises and cloud-based business processes to cut costs and save time. Automate incoming communication channels, monitor databases, react to incoming webhooks, web forms and chat bots. Handles documents, attachments, local files, and other message sources.
Parse and extract data from incoming messages and take actions in business processes, such as outbound communications, updating on-premises and cloud databases,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Zoner Photo Studio X 19.2509.2.661</title><pubDate> Fri, 24 Oct 2025 16:39:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zoner-photo-studio-x-95.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zoner-photo-studio-x-95.html
</guid><description>
Zoner Photo Studio X Pro helps you to control your photos. Zoner Photo Studio is a complete toolbox for managing and processing digital photos. Get photos from your camera, organize your archive, and edit and share your photos - never been easier! Zoner Photo Studio is useful for beginners, advanced users and photographers with experience, who can choose one of four different variations. Zoner Photo Studio is made for every user of digital cameras, scanners, and mobile devices. It contains...
</description></item><item><title>Download OEM Recovery Partition Creator 6.1.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 24 Oct 2025 16:37:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oem-recovery-partition-creator-6883.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oem-recovery-partition-creator-6883.html
</guid><description>
OEM Recovery Partition Creator for advanced users can clone your partition and bootable rescue media to restore your computer to its original state . The idea behind the app is to be able to create a factory reset just like a factory reset with Dell, HP and others. However, if you are not an advanced user, and possibly even if you are at it, you may not know where to start or how to use the program. The document is very large and can easily be replaced with a graphical user...
</description></item><item><title>Download O&amp;amp;O Defrag Pro 30.0.1073</title><pubDate> Fri, 24 Oct 2025 16:36:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-o-o-defrag-pro-149.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-o-o-defrag-pro-149.html
</guid><description>
O&amp;amp;O Defrag Pro is the professional software has the ability to defragment the hard disk and can work with the file system different from FAT / 32 to NTFS / 5, and support for the different arrays Volume / Stripe Sets. You can also set the schedule which O &amp;amp; O Defrag will be booted and perform a number of manipulation certain. Regular defragmentation of the disk partition optimized performance of your computer. The user interface is very easy to use. It has a ribbon bar displays all...
</description></item><item><title>Download O&amp;amp;O Defrag Server 30.0.1073</title><pubDate> Fri, 24 Oct 2025 16:36:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-defrag-server-2521.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-defrag-server-2521.html
</guid><description>
O&amp;amp;O Defrag Server professional software has the ability to defragment the hard disk and can work with the file system different from FAT / 32 to NTFS / 5, and support for the different arrays Volume / Stripe Sets. You can also set the schedule which O &amp;amp; O Defrag will be booted and perform a number of manipulation certain. Regular defragmentation of the disk partition optimized performance of your computer. The user interface is very easy to use. It has a ribbon bar displays all the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft PowerToys for Windows 10/11 0.95.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 24 Oct 2025 16:36:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-powertoys-for-windows-6014.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-powertoys-for-windows-6014.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft PowerToys is a user-proficiency set to adjust and streamline their Windows experience for higher productivity. Inspired by Windows 95's PowerToys project, this reboot provides users with proficiency in ways to exploit the more efficient Windows 10 and customisable processes it provides for each work process.
Utility of Microsoft PowerToys
	FancyZones is a window manager that allows you to easily create complex windows layout and quickly locate windows in those layout.
	Image...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDFsam -PDF Split and Merge 5.4.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 24 Oct 2025 16:29:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-split-and-merge-2337.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-split-and-merge-2337.html
</guid><description>
PDF Split and Merge is free software that makes it easy to split PDF files into smaller files or merge them all into one complete PDF file. PDF Split and Merge is considered to be one of the best PDF file merging software available today, the special thing about this PDF file merge software is that it is completely free, this is one of the reasons that make up the attraction of this software.
PDF Split and Merge - Split and merge PDF 
This is a great alternative to the famous ARTS PDF...
</description></item><item><title>Download ToneBoosters Plugin Bundle 2.1.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 24 Oct 2025 16:27:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-toneboosters-plugin-bundle-3675.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-toneboosters-plugin-bundle-3675.html
</guid><description>
ToneBoosters Plugin Bundle is a package tool sound is to combine the digital signal processing advanced and deployed multi-platform is optimized with the easy to use interface to optimize workflow of you. We combine the digital signal processing advanced and highly optimized deployment platform interface with simple-to-use to optimize your work.
ToneBoosters Plugin Bundle - audio tools
ToneBoosters Plugin Bundle includes:
	Barricade: True-peak mastering limiter.
	BitJuggler: The...
</description></item><item><title>Download Plasticity CAD 2025.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 24 Oct 2025 13:42:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-plasticity-cad-for-artists-11178.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-plasticity-cad-for-artists-11178.html
</guid><description>
With a workflow optimized for creativity, amazing fillets and the most advanced modeling tools, Plasticity is the perfect choice for those who need the best. Plasticity CAD for artists is the ultimate tool for creative professionals in video games, product design and more. It provides all the power of NURBS modeling combined with the best workflow improvements from polygon modeling software. This unique combination gives you the flexibility and creativity you need to turn your ideas into...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ahoge for Maya 0.9.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 24 Oct 2025 13:35:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ahoge-for-maya-14250.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ahoge-for-maya-14250.html
</guid><description>
Ahoge for Maya is a plugin designed to simplify the creation of hair, including both stylized and complex styles commonly found in anime, manga, and games. It supports Autodesk Maya versions 2023 to 2026 on Windows and works with the Arnold renderer. The plugin allows for converting polygons to hair, editing NURBS surfaces for hair, creating hair surface effects, and detailing various hair elements such as tufts and eyelashes. The plugin also has tools for hair mesh shaping and supports...
</description></item><item><title>Download DriverMax Pro 16.22.0.25</title><pubDate> Fri, 24 Oct 2025 01:09:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-drivermax-pro-156.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-drivermax-pro-156.html
</guid><description>
DriverMax Pro : utility that allows to download the update the latest driver for your computer. In addition, DriverMax collects information about the drivers installed in system and prints a list of devices that use them. It scans and collects information about drivers installed in the system and create a list of the driver version, date, digital signature and many more.
DriverMax Pro offers information about the driver version, date, developer, number of files and you have digital...
</description></item><item><title>Download CyberLink PowerDirector Ultimate 2026 v24.0.1022.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 24 Oct 2025 01:08:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-powerdirector-ultimate-425.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-powerdirector-ultimate-425.html
</guid><description>
CyberLink PowerDirector Ultimate is software editor, edit video and make movies on the computer from a variety of templates are made available, complete with effects, transitions, animations, and music. CyberLink PowerDirector 17 is a combination of video editing software with advanced video editing features powerful. Cblowing need to add your clips into the time line and click on 'Production'!
The tool design video in CyberLink PowerDirector have the ability to customize helps you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ashampoo Photo Recovery 3.0.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 24 Oct 2025 01:07:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-photo-recovery-7133.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-photo-recovery-7133.html
</guid><description>
Ashampoo Photo Recovery is software to recover lost photos on your computer with just a few simple steps using modern search algorithms. The software supports the recovery of images lost due to various causes, allowing to recover many image formats, using many different search criteria, and returning the original image with no image quality. change.
Ashampoo Photo Recovery supports image recovery on various storage devices such as: your hard drives, USB drives and storage cards to find...
</description></item><item><title>Download Atlantis Word Processor 5.0.0.6</title><pubDate> Fri, 24 Oct 2025 01:02:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-atlantis-word-processor-585.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-atlantis-word-processor-585.html
</guid><description>
Atlantis Word Processor is a word processor app with features format, standard text, autocorrect, and spell check.  Atlantis is a word processor in accordance with most of the tasks handled daily text. The interface is very easy to use and offers the toolbars, hotkeys and sound effects thanh can customize (can turn off). It includes a clip library for quick access to the text or images used regular preview, font format and many other features aimed at improving the process of your...
</description></item><item><title>Download TechSmith Snagit 2025 v25.4.0.8498</title><pubDate> Fri, 24 Oct 2025 01:02:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-techsmith-snagit-01en-280.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-techsmith-snagit-01en-280.html
</guid><description>
TechSmith Snagit software screen capture anything on your screen, then easily add text arrows or effects and save the snapshot to a file or share it immediately by e-mail or IM. With TechSmith Snagit you can capture and share the article, photo or Web page directly from your screen.
TechSmith Snagit
TechSmith Snagit help you can take a photo screen in the form of roll, panoramic shooting, shooting photos of and easy photo editing after shooting. Besides it is feature - video recording...
</description></item><item><title>Download Far Manager 3.0 Build 6575</title><pubDate> Fri, 24 Oct 2025 01:01:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-far-manager-1609.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-far-manager-1609.html
</guid><description>
Far Manager is an application for managing files and archives in Windows operating systems. Far Manager works in text mode and provides a simple interface and intuitive to perform the action.
Far Manager - Manage file documents
The main features of Far Manager include:
	Viewing files and directories; editing, copying and renaming files; and many other actions.
	The function of Far Manager is significantly expanded by the module DLL outside - the plugin, created by a special...
</description></item><item><title>Download VovSoft VCF Editor 2.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 24 Oct 2025 01:00:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-vcf-editor-12583.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-vcf-editor-12583.html
</guid><description>
Vovsoft VCF Editor is a powerful, offline tool designed to manage and edit vCard (VCF) files on Windows. Running locally on the user's computer, the tool ensures privacy and security by processing all data offline without the need for an internet connection. This makes this tool ideal for users who prioritize keeping their communications private and secure.
Features of VovSoft VCF Editor
	This vCard editor software allows users to easily load, view and edit key contact fields such as...
</description></item><item><title>Download MiniTool Video Converter 4.5.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 24 Oct 2025 00:14:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minitool-video-converter-5358.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minitool-video-converter-5358.html
</guid><description>
MiniTool Video Converter is the most direct solution for converting audio and video files to a wide variety of formats. This free video converter is available to convert audio to video and convert video to audio. This free video converter supports over 1000 conversion formats including 4K / FHD / HD files MP4, MOV, MKV, AVI, WMV, M4V and audio formats like MP3, WAV, M4A, WMA High Quality, AAC, AC3.
MiniTool Video Converter allows you to convert batches of files at the same time. Just...
</description></item><item><title>Download MEmu Android Emulator 9.2.9</title><pubDate> Fri, 24 Oct 2025 00:09:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-memu-2975.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-memu-2975.html
</guid><description>
MEmu or also known as Android Emulator is the Android emulator light and free, allowing Windows users to enjoy Android experience the original on the computer and device Microsoft their. This app provides outstanding performance, allowing you to play on PC a series of games designed to run on Android devices. This app allows you to play the game favorite Android on larger screens, to bring you a better gaming experience.
MEmu - Android emulator, lightweight and free
Software MEmu also...
</description></item><item><title>Download Apowersoft Video Download Capture 6.6.1.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 24 Oct 2025 00:07:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-apowersoft-video-download-capture-1556.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-apowersoft-video-download-capture-1556.html
</guid><description>
Apowersoft Video Download Capture is a comprehensive tool with advanced technologies for media streaming to choice cost-effective to download videos from YouTube, Dailymotion, Vimeo, Yahoo Screen and Hulu, as well as millions of other websites. Apowersoft Video Download Capture is your download video powerful and effective this can download and save videos, movies, tv episodes and music videos online. It also has the switch function, supports convert any video to MP4, AVI, MKV, WMV and the...
</description></item></channel></rss>