<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 09:30:51 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 09:30:51 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Display Driver Uninstaller (DDU) 18.1.3.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 18 Aug 2025 01:02:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-display-driver-uninstaller-1999.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-display-driver-uninstaller-1999.html
</guid><description>
Display Driver Uninstaller (DDU) help to easily completely remove the packages and drivers graphics cards AMD, NVIDIA and Intel from your system without leaving any rest whatsoever. Display Driver Uninstaller will automatically detect your current GPU and allows you to delete drivers, registry and files related only by the click of a button. It will also prevent Windows automatically re-install drivers when you reboot your computer, leaving you a drivers graphics common until you install...
</description></item><item><title>Download BrightVPN 1.560.626</title><pubDate> Mon, 18 Aug 2025 01:01:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-brightvpn-8960.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-brightvpn-8960.html
</guid><description>
BrightVPN is a virtual private network (VPN) service that provides users with a private and secure internet browsing experience. The service uses encryption and tunneling protocols to protect users' online activities and personal data from being intercepted or tracked by third parties.
BrightVPN frees you from restrictions or censorship by unblocking any website from 150+ countries, connecting you to the Internet for free from anywhere. In addition, Bright VPN protects your internet...
</description></item><item><title>Download RapidRAW 1.3.9</title><pubDate> Mon, 18 Aug 2025 00:52:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rapidraw-13957.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rapidraw-13957.html
</guid><description>
RapidRAW is a modern, high-performance, open-source RAW photo editor, designed to deliver a fast and clean editing experience with a lightweight footprint (under 30MB). Built with performance and usability in mind, the software is aimed at photographers who want a simple, efficient, and fun workflow without compromising performance.
Key Features
	GPU-accelerated processing: Uses a custom WGSL shader to process all image adjustments on the GPU, allowing for smooth, responsive editing...
</description></item><item><title>Download PeaZip 10.6.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 18 Aug 2025 00:51:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-peazip-1800.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-peazip-1800.html
</guid><description>
PeaZip is an Archive Utility And Compressed open-source, support multiple compression formats. It lets you create 7Z, ARC, BZ2, GZ, PAQ / ZPAQ, PEA, QUAD / BALZ, TAR, UPX, and ZIP, and enables you to open and extract 133 format additional storage, including RAR. PeaZip has the ability to open and extract over 150 file formats compressed downloads, have the ability to create and switch between multiple file formats, different background on an interface intuitive and easy to use. In...
</description></item><item><title>Download Fort Firewall 3.19.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 18 Aug 2025 00:51:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fort-firewall-6439.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fort-firewall-6439.html
</guid><description>
Fort Firewall is a network security system that monitors and controls network traffic and goes based on predefined security rules. A firewall often establishes a barrier between a trusted internal network and untrusted external networks, such as the Internet.
Features of Fort Firewall
	Filter by network address, application group
	Support of representative characters in the name path name
	Application group speed limit
	Access Traffic Statistics
	Display bandwidth
	Based on the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Kill-Update 1.1.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 17 Aug 2025 17:06:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kill-update-5991.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kill-update-5991.html
</guid><description>
Kill-Update allows you to control the time of your Windows 10 update in a manual, this utility allows you to control the time of an update. You can set up an operating time for updates in Windows 10 or by shutting down the Group Policy Editor but for new users to get used to and those who want to control more; this may be a simpler solution.
All you need to do is click on the sistray icon that will show the menu. From there you have two options; download when starting, which will load...
</description></item><item><title>Download Shotcut 25.08</title><pubDate> Sun, 17 Aug 2025 17:06:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-shotcut-2756.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-shotcut-2756.html
</guid><description>
Shotcut is a video editing application multi-platform free and open source for FreeBSD, Linux, macOS and Windows. Was started in 2011 by Dan Dennedy, Shotcut is developed on the multimedia MLT, which was developed from 2004. With age grow quite long years, Shotcut offers users many tools to perform the manipulation, Video editing based on adjusting each frame to enhance image quality. You can add an introduction, edit rate, bitrate, resolution or file encryption, and optionally use the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Flyby11 1.2.152</title><pubDate> Sun, 17 Aug 2025 17:04:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-flyby11-12467.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-flyby11-12467.html
</guid><description>
Flyby11 is a simple patcher that removes annoying restrictions that prevent you from installing Windows 11 (24H2) on unsupported hardware. Do you have an old PC? No TPM, Secure Boot or your processor is not supported? Flyby11 allows you to install Windows 11 24H2. There are no complicated steps. Just run the tool and you'll be running Windows 11 on your outdated machine in no time.
Technical overview
Flyby11 takes advantage of a feature of the Windows 11 setup process that uses the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Flyoobe 1.2.152</title><pubDate> Sun, 17 Aug 2025 17:04:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oobelux-13956.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oobelux-13956.html
</guid><description>
Flyoobe was born out of the frustration many users felt with the Windows 11 setup experience. Whether it was the mandatory online account, the endless "Next, next, next..." screens, or the incomplete configuration options when you finally reached the desktop, the current setup lacked focus on what users really wanted.
Why choose Flyoobe?
	Simplifies the Windows 11 setup process right out of the box.
	Allows easy local account creation without need to hunt for hidden options.
	Includes...
</description></item><item><title>Download MobiPDF: PDF Editor &amp;amp; Scanner 11.8.267264</title><pubDate> Sun, 17 Aug 2025 17:01:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pdf-extra-scan-edit-sign-8390.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pdf-extra-scan-edit-sign-8390.html
</guid><description>
PDF Extra PDF Editor &amp;amp; Scanner is a mobile application that allows users to create, edit and sign PDF documents on their Android or iOS devices. It includes many tools and features that make it easy to work with PDF files, including scanning, editing, and signing. This application also allows users to combine multiple PDF files into a single document and export PDF files in various file formats, such as JPEG, PNG, and Microsoft Word.
Features of PDF Extra PDF Editor &amp;amp;...
</description></item><item><title>Download Silent Camera [High Quality] 8.15.9</title><pubDate> Sun, 17 Aug 2025 17:01:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-silent-camera-10536.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-silent-camera-10536.html
</guid><description>
Introducing the best silent camera! Without the shutter sound, photos can be taken in complete silence! It also ranks number 1 among many silent cameras thanks to its high image quality! Take high-quality photos with the silent camera! You won't disturb anyone around you because the shutter sound can't be heard. You can take high-quality photos of any situation, such as your baby's cute sleeping face, your pet's natural behaviors, and words written on a blackboard!
Silent Camera...
</description></item><item><title>Download All PDF Editor &amp;amp; Reader | Xodo 10.5.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 17 Aug 2025 17:01:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-xodo-pdf-reader-editor-8451.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-xodo-pdf-reader-editor-8451.html
</guid><description>
Xodo PDF Reader &amp;amp; Editor is a mobile application for reading and editing PDF documents on Android and iOS devices. The app allows users to view, annotate, and edit PDF files using a variety of tools, including highlighting, underlining, and adding notes. With Xodo, you can read, annotate, sign, and share PDFs and fill out PDF forms, all while syncing with Google Drive, Dropbox, and OneDrive.
Xodo PDF Reader &amp;amp; Editor Features
	PDF Viewer: Application that allows users to view...
</description></item><item><title>Download PowerDirector - Video Editor 15.6.0 build 2508151</title><pubDate> Sun, 17 Aug 2025 17:00:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-powerdirector-video-editor-8123.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-powerdirector-video-editor-8123.html
</guid><description>
PowerDirector APK - Video Editor (Unlocked Version) is video editing software developed by CyberLink. It is available for Windows and Android devices. If you are looking for the Android version of PowerDirector, you can download the APK (Android Package Kit) file from the Google Play Store or from taiwebs.com.
Features of PowerDirector APK - Unlocked Version:
	Easy-to-use interface: PowerDirector has a user-friendly interface that makes it easy to edit and create videos, even if...
</description></item><item><title>Download Rosetta Stone: Learn, Practice 8.34.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 17 Aug 2025 17:00:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-rosetta-stone-learn-practice-11241.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-rosetta-stone-learn-practice-11241.html
</guid><description>
Interactive and contextual lessons combined with Extended Learning features are truly at your fingertips–anytime, anywhere, on any device; online or offline and completely ad-free. Learn to speak Spanish, French, German, Italian, English, Japanese, Korean, Chinese, Arabic, Portuguese, Russian, Dutch, Filipino, Greek , Hebrew, Hindi, Irish, Persian, Polish, Swedish, Turkish, Vietnamese and more!
Rosetta Stone helps you speak confidently: With many lessons and features focused on...
</description></item><item><title>Download Duolingo: language lessons 6.43.4</title><pubDate> Sun, 17 Aug 2025 17:00:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-duolingo-language-lessons-8265.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-duolingo-language-lessons-8265.html
</guid><description>
Duolingo is a popular language learning app that offers interactive lessons to help users learn new languages. This application offers many languages for you to choose from, including Spanish, French, German, Italian, Portuguese, Chinese, Japanese and many more.
This app offers an gamified learning experience with interactive lessons, exercises, and quizzes designed to help users learn new words, phrases, and grammar rules. This app is designed to be easy to use and suitable for people...
</description></item><item><title>Download Photo Editor 11.8</title><pubDate> Sun, 17 Aug 2025 17:00:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-iudesk-photo-editor-8321.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-iudesk-photo-editor-8321.html
</guid><description>
Photo Editor is a small but powerful photo editing application. If you have some knowledge about photography, you can do a lot with Photo Editor. Now use Photo Editor to edit photos on your mobile phone just like on your PC.
Photo Editor Features
	Color: exposure, brightness, contrast, saturation, temperature, tone, and hue
	Curves &amp;amp; levels: color fine-tuning
	Effects: gamma correction, auto contrast, auto tone, vibrance, blur, sharpen, oil painting, sketch, high contrast black...
</description></item><item><title>Download File Commander Manager &amp;amp; Vault 10.7.54240</title><pubDate> Sun, 17 Aug 2025 16:59:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-file-commander-manager-cloud-8582.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-file-commander-manager-cloud-8582.html
</guid><description>
File Commander is a powerful file manager that allows you to handle any file on your Android device, cloud storage or network location through a clear and intuitive interface. Fully optimized for Android P, File Commander has many features - Vault Security, Recycle Bin, Storage Analyzer, File Converter and also get 5GB free storage on MobiSystems Drive.&amp;lt; /p&amp;gt;
File Manager and Cloud Features
Access and manage files
	Easily find files from a fully customizable Home screen with...
</description></item><item><title>Download PhotoDirector: AI Photo Editor 20.4.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 17 Aug 2025 16:59:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-photodirector-photo-editor-8144.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-photodirector-photo-editor-8144.html
</guid><description>
PhotoDirector is a photo editing app for Android devices that allows you to edit and enhance your photos with a variety of tools and effects. With PhotoDirector, you can adjust your photo's color and lighting, remove blemishes and other imperfections, and apply filters to give your photos a unique look. You can also use PhotoDirector to create photo collages and slideshows, add text and stickers to photos, and share your edited photos on social networks or through other sharing...
</description></item><item><title>Download Passwords &amp;amp; Passkeys－Safe 26.1.6</title><pubDate> Sun, 17 Aug 2025 16:58:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-password-manager-safeincloud-pro-10227.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-password-manager-safeincloud-pro-10227.html
</guid><description>
Protect your data with a unique and secure password! Forget the headache of remembering PINs and passwords! START USING PASSWORD MANAGER TODAY! SafeInCloud is a complete password management solution: Free desktop app + Mobile app for phones and tablets.
Features of Password Manager SafeInCloud Pro
	Material Design
	Dark theme
	Strong encryption (AES)
	Cloud synchronization (Google Drive, Dropbox, OneDrive)
	Finger Scan and Multi-Window (Samsung devices)
	Analyze password...
</description></item><item><title>Download OsmAnd+ — Maps &amp;amp; GPS Offline 5.1.9</title><pubDate> Sun, 17 Aug 2025 16:58:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-osmand-maps-gps-offline-8245.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-osmand-maps-gps-offline-8245.html
</guid><description>
OsmAnd+ (OSM Automatic Navigation Directions) is a mapping and navigation application with access to free, global, and high-quality OpenStreetMap (OSM) data. Enjoy voice and optical navigation, view POIs (points of interest), create and manage GPX routes, use contour visualization and elevation information, choose between driving modes, cyclists, pedestrians, OSM editing, etc.
This is a mobile navigation app that uses OpenStreetMap (OSM) data to provide users with detailed maps and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Smart Launcher 6 ‧ Home Screen 6.5 build 038</title><pubDate> Sun, 17 Aug 2025 16:58:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-smart-launcher-8412.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-smart-launcher-8412.html
</guid><description>
Smart Launcher is a mobile app that provides users with a customized home screen and app launcher on their Android devices. It includes features like minimalist interface, automatic app sorting, and gesture controls. The app also includes many customizable settings, such as the ability to change the theme, icon size, and screen layout, as well as the ability to create custom categories for the app.
Smart Launcher Features
	Ambient theme: Smart launcher automatically changes theme...
</description></item><item><title>Download Shazam: Find Music &amp;amp; Concerts 16.5.0-250807</title><pubDate> Sun, 17 Aug 2025 16:53:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-shazam-music-discovery-10763.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-shazam-music-discovery-10763.html
</guid><description>
Shazam will identify any song in seconds. Discover, artists, lyrics, videos &amp;amp; playlists, all for free. Over 1 billion installs and counting. Use Pop-up Shazam to identify music in any app - Instagram, YouTube, TikTok... No connection? No problem! Shazam while offline.
Features of Shazam: Music Discovery
	Find the name of any song in seconds.
	Listen and add to Apple Music playlists.
	Follow along with time-synced lyrics.
	Watch music videos from Apple Music or YouTube.
	Enable...
</description></item><item><title>Download Polarr: Photo Filters &amp;amp; Editor 6.11.6</title><pubDate> Sun, 17 Aug 2025 16:53:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-polarr-photo-filters-editor-8389.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-polarr-photo-filters-editor-8389.html
</guid><description>
Polarr: Photo Filters &amp;amp; Editor is a mobile application for editing and enhancing photos on Android and iOS devices. It offers a wide range of editing tools, including basic adjustments like cropping, rotation, and brightness control, as well as advanced features like color grading, masking, and layer-based editing. . The app also includes many filters and presets that can be used to change the look of your photos.
Polar Features: Filters &amp;amp; Photo Editor
	Basic adjustments:...
</description></item><item><title>Download Reminder Pro 4.0.6</title><pubDate> Sun, 17 Aug 2025 16:53:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-reminder-pro-8695.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-reminder-pro-8695.html
</guid><description>
Are you looking for a simple pop-up reminder app? Do you want to create reminders for one-time and recurring tasks? Get reminders and increase your productivity. Never forget an important task again! Finally, a simple and easy way to set reminders or deadline notifications. This hourly reminder app gets straight to the point. Set notifications to remind you of all your tasks, chores, and to-do list items, then sit back and clear your head.
No unnecessary or complicated features....
</description></item><item><title>Download AdGuard Ad Blocker 4.11.55 Beta-1</title><pubDate> Sun, 17 Aug 2025 16:53:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-adguard-block-ads-without-root-8215.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-adguard-block-ads-without-root-8215.html
</guid><description>
AdGuard for Android is the only root-free ad blocker for Android that removes ads in apps and browsers, protects your privacy, and helps you manage your apps. Adguard is designed to block unwanted ads, pop-ups and banners while you browse the web on your device. It uses a combination of local VPN technology and a custom DNS server to block ads, meaning it can block ads in apps as well as in web browsers.
In addition, Adguard also blocks tracking scripts from collecting information about...
</description></item></channel></rss>