<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 17:37:36 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 17:37:36 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download RapidRAW 1.3.11</title><pubDate> Mon, 01 Sep 2025 17:09:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rapidraw-13957.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rapidraw-13957.html
</guid><description>
RapidRAW is a modern, high-performance, open-source RAW photo editor, designed to deliver a fast and clean editing experience with a lightweight footprint (under 30MB). Built with performance and usability in mind, the software is aimed at photographers who want a simple, efficient, and fun workflow without compromising performance.
Key Features
	GPU-accelerated processing: Uses a custom WGSL shader to process all image adjustments on the GPU, allowing for smooth, responsive editing...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sejda PDF Desktop Pro 7.9.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 01 Sep 2025 17:09:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sejda-pdf-desktop-pro-1301.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sejda-pdf-desktop-pro-1301.html
</guid><description>
Sejda PDF Desktop Pro is a professional PDF file action software with full features to help you with PDF tasks. Sejda PDF Desktop is used free of charge in the daily limit. Upgrade of advanced and non-limited features.
Sejda PDF Desktop Pro fully integrate PDF editing features from basic to complex such as document editing, file compression, page removal, inclusion or separation, page publication, PDF conversion. all in the same modern and efficient program.
Features of Sejda PDF...
</description></item><item><title>Download Agisoft Metashape Professional 2.2.2 Build 21069</title><pubDate> Mon, 01 Sep 2025 17:08:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-agisoft-metashape-professional-1731.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-agisoft-metashape-professional-1731.html
</guid><description>
Agisoft Metashape (formerly PhotoScan) is a software product independently perform image processing and digital data creation, 3D space used in GIS applications, material cultural heritage and the production visual effects as well as the indirect measurement of the different subjects scale. Technical digital photography is deployed wisely is applied with the method of computer vision led to the system processor, smart auto, on the one hand, can be managed by a new person in the field of...
</description></item><item><title>Download BoostPing 1.5.9</title><pubDate> Mon, 01 Sep 2025 17:08:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-boostping-12519.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-boostping-12519.html
</guid><description>
BoostPing helps optimize your online gaming experience by modifying the network throttling index and disabling the Nagle algorithm. By turning this feature off, you can achieve more instantaneous data transfer speeds, potentially reducing latency.
What is Nagle's algorithm?
The Nagle algorithm is designed to improve network efficiency by combining small data packets into larger packets, which can cause lag in online games. Disabling it can result in more responsive gameplay. On the...
</description></item><item><title>Download OkMap Desktop 19.0.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 01 Sep 2025 17:07:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-okmap-desktop-581.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-okmap-desktop-581.html
</guid><description>
OkMap Desktop is interactive software working on the computer with web maps or digital maps bought or scanned. OkMap can also import a data vector from the most common formats and data DEM related to information height.
Through the map you can organize your path by creating waypoints , routesand tracks on the screen your computer, and upload this data to your GPS . OkMap set data high speedautomatic and estimated moving time . Furthermore OkMap provides you also have autorouting and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Bulk Rename Utility 4.1.0.0 Commercial</title><pubDate> Mon, 01 Sep 2025 17:07:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bulk-rename-utility-2119.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bulk-rename-utility-2119.html
</guid><description>
Bulk Rename Utility is a utility batch rename allows you to easily rename multiple files and folders, based on the criteria flexible. Bulk Rename Utility lets you easily Add time / date stamp, replace numbers, insert text, convert case, add auto number, processing folder and sub-folder,..
Bulk Rename Utility - Change the name of the file series
Rename many files and / or directories has never been easier! It has a small memory footprint so it can be left running all the time without...
</description></item><item><title>Download Telegram for Desktop 6.1.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 01 Sep 2025 17:06:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-telegram-3376.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-telegram-3376.html
</guid><description>
Telegram is an instant messaging service and voice over IP services on the cloud platform. Client application Telegram is available for Android, iOS, Windows Phone, Windows NT, macOS, and Linux. Users can send messages and exchange photos, videos, stickers, audio and files of any kind.
Telegram - Messaging and free phone calls
Telegram seamless sync across all your devices and can be used on desktop, tablet and phone. You can send unlimited amount of messages, photos, videos and files...
</description></item><item><title>Download Private Windows Script (PrivWindoze) 5.6.7</title><pubDate> Mon, 01 Sep 2025 17:06:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-private-windows-script-12878.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-private-windows-script-12878.html
</guid><description>
Are you concerned about your personal information sent to others? Or do you feel that your Windows settings have many programs that you never use? Private Windows Script (or Privwindoze) provides a comprehensive anti -remote monitoring set designed to enhance your privacy when using Windows operating system.
The main features
	End the positive process. All unnecessary processes are turned off while the scanning program. A small white list is maintained.
	Clean up the positive runonce....
</description></item><item><title>Download PhotoFiltre Studio 11.7</title><pubDate> Mon, 01 Sep 2025 17:06:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photofiltre-studio-x-4891.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photofiltre-studio-x-4891.html
</guid><description>
PhotoFiltre Studio X is a program for editing graphics that can be used to edit and change images through features simple and advanced. It's not as complex as Photoshop, although for the eyes has not been training of an average user it may seem like it. It allows you to work with layers, transparent colors for images.
PhotoFiltre Studio X provides support for the filter of Adobe Photoshop (format 8bf, only 32 bits! Be installed in any folder, the folder attachment allows) allows you to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wipe Pro 2025.10</title><pubDate> Mon, 01 Sep 2025 17:05:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wipe-pro-710.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wipe-pro-710.html
</guid><description>
Wipe Pro is software that helps clean up litter, increase in hard drive space besides also protect your privacy on the Internet, it removes records about personal activity on the computer. You will be able to delete browser history and the cache, the file index.dat, registry, files, cookies, internet history, auto complete, temporary internet files and many other items. This program also delete all activities other individuals that you made when using the PC and regardless of which...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Downloader 9.16.7</title><pubDate> Mon, 01 Sep 2025 17:05:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html
</guid><description>
YTD Youtube Downloader is an application that reliable and intuitive, allowing you to quickly download YouTube videos and save them to your computer. You can also convert the media files to the format desired video or extract audio streams and save separately. YTD Youtube Downloader lets you save your favorite clips of yourself from Youtube, Facebook, Vimeo and Dailymotion to your desktop. The software supports URLS from many web site hosting, multimedia and allows you to download desired...
</description></item><item><title>Download GIMP 3.1.4</title><pubDate> Mon, 01 Sep 2025 17:04:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gimp-286.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gimp-286.html
</guid><description>
GIMP is a photo editor and software photo manipulation advanced often compared with Photoshop. It offers a lot of features, including support for layers, masks, filters, effects and many other features found in the graphics program professional.
GIMP has many special functions such as restoring old photos, creative effects, photo collage ... It has the ability to edit and restore photos, graphics processor array, vector graphics, at the same time support photo editor according to the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Reallusion Character Creator 5.0.0827.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 01 Sep 2025 16:58:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reallusion-character-creator-5434.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reallusion-character-creator-5434.html
</guid><description>
Reallusion Character Creator is the leading application for 3D character design for Animation, Games, AR and VR. Character Creator 3 is a complete character creation solution for designers to easily create, import and customize character content. Connect industry-leading pipes into one system for 3D character creation, animation, rendering, and interactive design.
Character Quad-based characters ready for animation with complete body scaffold and facial morphology ready for lip sync and...
</description></item><item><title>Download RIGOTECH Pre-Cut Optimizer Pro 4.6.24</title><pubDate> Mon, 01 Sep 2025 16:58:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rigotech-pre-cut-optimizer-8860.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rigotech-pre-cut-optimizer-8860.html
</guid><description>
Pre-Cut Optimizer is a software program designed to optimize cutting patterns for sheet materials such as plywood, MDF and particle board. Pre-Cut Optimizer is mainly aimed at the woodworking and furniture manufacturing industries, as well as other industries that require efficient cutting and use of materials. The software allows the user to enter the dimensions and quantities of the required parts, then create optimized cutting patterns to minimize waste and maximize material...
</description></item><item><title>Download VovSoft Text Edit Plus 15.6</title><pubDate> Mon, 01 Sep 2025 16:57:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-text-edit-plus-2872.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-text-edit-plus-2872.html
</guid><description>
VovSoft Text Edit Plus is app designed replacement for Notepad by offering a feature set wider. Text Edit Plus is a lightweight tool that allows users to easily create new text document or edit the existing document. This app is designed replacement for Notepad by offering a feature set wider.
VovSoft Text Edit Plus - text editing
A number of features: dark Mode. Add date and time. The change of the background color and the font. Encrypt and decrypt text. Combine the lines. System...
</description></item><item><title>Download NormCap 0.6.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 01 Sep 2025 16:56:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-normcap-11969.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-normcap-11969.html
</guid><description>
NormCap is an OCR-enabled screen capture tool that captures information instead of images. Once installed, you can adjust the language(s) you are trying to recognize in the settings. The star icon and three bars next to the selection rectangle indicate the active shooting mode. NormCap is a cool little tool that makes copying text from web pages a breeze. Additionally, if you have ever copied text using markup, you have certainly experienced the exact copy being created, including the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mypal 74.1.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 01 Sep 2025 16:56:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mypal-4504.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mypal-4504.html
</guid><description>
Mypal is a web browser Windows XP current and to be maintained. Mypal is based on the code of Pale Moon by Moonchild Productions, it is separated from the code of Mozilla's FireFox a few years ago, but is well maintained and preserved. The goal of Mypal is to provide a web browser current, safe and reliable for Windows XP. Mypal operation identical to Pale Moon with some small exceptions. Introduced system new mobile and a number of certain settings, including code Mozilla old not used,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Dont Sleep 9.79</title><pubDate> Mon, 01 Sep 2025 16:55:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dont-sleep-89.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dont-sleep-89.html
</guid><description>
Don't Sleep allows you can set the date and custom time that you want to reactivate the feature manager usual sources or you can set a countdown fast to pause the power management in X hours.
Can temporarily disable the protection of your screen or off your computer at a certain time.
The main features of the Dont Sleep:
- Optimal power supply for computer
- Installation time power source according to
- Prevent computer reboot
Content update Dont Sleep 5.66:
The official website...
</description></item><item><title>Download SolveigMM Video Splitter Business 8.1.2508.21 Broadcast Edition</title><pubDate> Mon, 01 Sep 2025 16:54:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-solveigmm-video-splitter-business-597.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-solveigmm-video-splitter-business-597.html
</guid><description>
SolveigMM Video Splitter Business is editing video highlights to work with the file MPEG-2, AVI, WMV, ASF, MP3, WMA. Editor, no data loss and fast, completely remove the unwanted parts of the video just by few mouse clicks - cutting and splicing the video and audio streams perfectly. Friendly interface and visually appealing user very easy to use. Based on SDK video editing SolveigMM, editing, audio - video of we offer quality and incredible speed without the use of any process to encrypt...
</description></item><item><title>Download lessmsi 2.8.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 01 Sep 2025 16:54:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lessmsi-12392.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lessmsi-12392.html
</guid><description>
Lessmsi (Less MSIerables) is a free and portable application that allows users to view and extract the contents of MSI files.
How does it work? Files with the .msi extension are not as widely used as their .exe cousins, but both contain programs for Windows. The main difference between them is that the latter does not always come with an installer, while it comes standard with the former. However, there will be cases where you just need to view or want to extract specific content from...
</description></item><item><title>Download wsltty 3.8.0.3</title><pubDate> Mon, 01 Sep 2025 16:53:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wsltty-3237.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wsltty-3237.html
</guid><description>
wsltty use Mintty do the terminal for WSL (System con Windows for Linux).
wsltty
The composition wsltty:
	The component package wsltty (see below) in the application folder of the users% LOCALAPPDATA%
	a folder configuration wsltty in the application folder in user's% APPDATA% (the configuration file is allocated according to the type of housing from one version to be installed before it will be move to default position new)
	Start Menu shortcuts to start the terminal WSL
	* .bat...
</description></item><item><title>Download TubeMate Downloader 5.22.5</title><pubDate> Mon, 01 Sep 2025 16:53:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubemate-downloader-4250.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubemate-downloader-4250.html
</guid><description>
TubeMate Downloader is a smart application that lets you download any clip you want from the website hosting the main video and convert them in when download at or then. If you need a simple and effective tool to download videos, you can give it a try. With TubeMate Downloader, you can directly drag and drop video link from your browser into the drop-down box or application window to start downloading. You don't even need to copy and paste the video URL.
TubeMate Downloader - Support...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mecway 28.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 01 Sep 2025 16:52:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mecway-7204.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mecway-7204.html
</guid><description>
Mecway is a comprehensive user-friendly finite element analysis package for Windows, focusing on mechanical and thermal simulations such as stress and vibration analysis. and heat flow. It is inexpensive and has an intuitive graphical interface to easily grid and display solutions.
Features of Mecway
	Dynamic, static, heat, warping, negative, etc.
	Full nonlinear capability despite seamless integration with included CalculiX solver
	Various types of elements, loads, and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sync Breeze Ultimate 17.2.24 + Enterprise + Pro</title><pubDate> Mon, 01 Sep 2025 16:52:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sync-breeze-ultimate-enterprise-1462.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sync-breeze-ultimate-enterprise-1462.html
</guid><description>
Sync Breeze Ultimate / Enterprise is software sync files fast, powerful and reliable for the local disk, shared network storage devices, NAS and storage systems business. Users are provided with multiple modes sync files one-way and two-way sync files periodically, sync file real time sync file-level bits, sync files multi-threading, synchronization, files, wallpaper and more.
Sync Breeze Ultimate / Enterprise - synchronize files
App GUI main Sync Breeze Ultimate allows a person to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Psiphon 186.202500831</title><pubDate> Mon, 01 Sep 2025 16:51:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-psiphon-7347.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-psiphon-7347.html
</guid><description>
Psiphon is a firewall bypass tool by Psiphon Inc. Uses VPN, SSH and HTTP Proxy technology to give you uncensored access to Internet content. Your Psiphon app automatically learns about new hotspots to maximize your chances of bypassing censorship.
The way the software works is that Psiphon constantly changes the proxy, so the user's IP address is also constantly changing, the server will not detect the user's real address, so you can feel free. roof. access to websites and software...
</description></item></channel></rss>