<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 20:03:50 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 20:03:50 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Irix HDR Pro 2.3.56</title><pubDate> Mon, 22 Dec 2025 17:16:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-irix-hdr-pro-10653.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-irix-hdr-pro-10653.html
</guid><description>
Irix HDR Pro is an AI-powered photo editing application for Windows, it is available on Microsoft Store. This program has tons of professional HDR photo editing features including Sky Replacement, Face Sculpting &amp;amp; body, over 200 presets &amp;amp; AI powered tool' and is a Photo Editor in the category of photo &amp;amp; Graphics. It delivers true-to-life HDR photo editing, providing one-click edits for a full-scale professional editing toolkit.
Features of Irix HDR Pro
	Sky Replacement...
</description></item><item><title>Download Activation Program 1.16.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 22 Dec 2025 17:16:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-activation-program-12767.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-activation-program-12767.html
</guid><description>
Activation Program is a Windows and Office activator from Ratiborus for Windows 7 to 11. The program is created based on the MASSGRAVE code.
What advantages does this method have over other activation methods?
It offers the most advantages for activating older versions of Windows, such as Windows 7 to 8.1, as it can permanently activate any version of the versions This without modifying the Windows system boot process or executable files. This is the only public activator that provides...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tenorshare 4DDiG File Repair 4.3.4.6</title><pubDate> Mon, 22 Dec 2025 17:12:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tenorshare-4ddig-file-repair-5630.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tenorshare-4ddig-file-repair-5630.html
</guid><description>
Tenorshare 4DDiG File Repair is AI-powered software to repair damaged or damaged videos, photos, files and audios, improve their quality and add color to black media white. 4DDiG photo editing solves all photo problems like blurry photos, overexposed photos, etc. Powered by AI, it can dramatically improve image resolution and colorize black and white photos in seconds, not hours.
Features of Tenorshare 4DDiG File Repair
	Easily repair any blurry, overexposed and damaged videos, photos...
</description></item><item><title>Download Irix HDR Classic Pro 2.3.56</title><pubDate> Mon, 22 Dec 2025 17:11:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-irix-hdr-classic-pro-10652.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-irix-hdr-classic-pro-10652.html
</guid><description>
Irix HDR Classic Pro is an AI-powered photo editor that delivers true-to-life HDR photo editing, providing one-click edits to the editing toolkit professional at full scale with a highly cognitive user interface (UI).
Main features:
	Sky replacement (SkyXpress): replaces the sky and imports weather. Import custom skies and merge, blend, and integrate with your images for a natural look with AI Edge Detect.
	Presets &amp;amp; Filters: 200+ social media optimized presets with just one tap...
</description></item><item><title>Download Fan Control v252</title><pubDate> Mon, 22 Dec 2025 17:11:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fancontrol-5749.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fancontrol-5749.html
</guid><description>
FanControl is a highly customizable fan control software for Windows. Stay in control of every aspect of your PC's GPU and CPU fan with the help of this highly customizable fan control app.
Features of FanControl
	Save, edit and load multiple configurations
	Multiple temperature sources (CPU, GPU, motherboard, hard drive, ".sensor" files)
	Custom fan curve
	Fine tune fan control response with steps,% start,% stop, response time and delay
	Mix different curves and sensors...
</description></item><item><title>Download Private Windows Script (PrivWindoze) 5.8.7</title><pubDate> Mon, 22 Dec 2025 17:11:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-private-windows-script-12878.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-private-windows-script-12878.html
</guid><description>
Are you concerned about your personal information sent to others? Or do you feel that your Windows settings have many programs that you never use? Private Windows Script (or Privwindoze) provides a comprehensive anti -remote monitoring set designed to enhance your privacy when using Windows operating system.
The main features
	End the positive process. All unnecessary processes are turned off while the scanning program. A small white list is maintained.
	Clean up the positive runonce....
</description></item><item><title>Download VovSoft Auto Mouse Clicker 3.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 22 Dec 2025 17:05:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-auto-mouse-clicker-7805.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-auto-mouse-clicker-7805.html
</guid><description>
VovSoft Auto Mouse Clicker is free, simple and straightforward desktop clicker software that frees users from repetitive clicking work. This program can simulate left, right and middle mouse clicks on any window. The software maps the screen based on the coordinates to ensure that it clicks exactly where the user wants it. The program identifies clicks using user-set X and Y coordinates.
It is fully compatible with all popular programs and games that require a lot of mouse clicks such...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cppcheck 2.19.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 22 Dec 2025 17:05:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cppcheck-3379.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cppcheck-3379.html
</guid><description>
Cppcheck is a tool for static code analysis for the C programming language and C ++. It is a versatile tool can check the code is not standard. Creator and lead developer is Daniel Marjamäki. Cppcheck is free software under The GNU general public License. Cppcheck is an analysis tool static code C / C ++. It provides code analysis only for error detection and focus on detecting behaviors not defined and the coding structure dangerous. The goal is only to detect the actual error in the...
</description></item><item><title>Download VovSoft Duplicate File Finder 2.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 22 Dec 2025 16:58:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-duplicate-file-finder-6639.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-duplicate-file-finder-6639.html
</guid><description>
VovSoft Duplicate File Finder is a tool to find duplicate files on your computer. It can scan file name, file size or file content (using SHA-1 algorithm).
You may have hundreds of photos, videos, music files, or documents that you've lost track of. You're running out of disk space on your PC, but organizing your files can seem overwhelming because there are so many of them.
This utility will help you locate and remove useless file duplicates to free up disk space and better organize...
</description></item><item><title>Download GnuCash 5.14</title><pubDate> Mon, 22 Dec 2025 16:57:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gnucash-1312.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gnucash-1312.html
</guid><description>
GnuCash is an accounting application, powerful financial is designed to help you to perform all tasks related to finance. The application can be used to track all activities of your finances from bank accounts, shares and income and other costs.
GnuCash supports databases including PostgreSQL, SQLite3 and MySQL (XML backend). Note, memory is the default XML file is compressed and use the SQL database replace is optional. Note, memory is the default XML file is compressed and use the SQL...
</description></item><item><title>Download Gammadyne Scratchboard 38.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 22 Dec 2025 16:53:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gammagyne-scratchboard-7306.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gammagyne-scratchboard-7306.html
</guid><description>
The average savvy Internet user amasses countless usernames, passwords, links, contacts, account numbers, software keys, and who knows what else. Scratchboard is a store of this kind of information, the data is arranged in a "tree" structure, like a hard drive. Text can be entered into each branch of the tree and copied to the clipboard with a simple double click.
Features of Scratchboard
	Works with all versions of Windows 10, 8, 2012, 7, 2008, Vista, XP, 2003 and 2000.
	Tree data...
</description></item><item><title>Download ProfExam Suite 8.2.2.334</title><pubDate> Mon, 22 Dec 2025 16:52:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-profexam-suite-12008.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-profexam-suite-12008.html
</guid><description>
ProfExam Suite is a comprehensive software solution designed to create, manage and administer exams and tests. It is widely used in educational institutions, certification bodies and corporate training departments.
The software suite includes two main components: ProfExam Creator and ProfExam Simulator
	ProfExam Creator: This tool allows users to create and design tests with a variety of question types, including multiple choice, true/false fill-in-the-blanks, matching, and more. It...
</description></item><item><title>Download Double Commander 1.1.31</title><pubDate> Mon, 22 Dec 2025 16:52:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-double-commander-7801.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-double-commander-7801.html
</guid><description>
Double Commander is an open source file manager with two panels side by side. The idea is based on Total Commander but with new and different features. Double Commander has multi-rename tool, tabbed interface, custom columns, internal text editor, built-in file viewer, archive support (ZIP, RAR), extensive search functionality, configurable button bar, file activity logging, plug-in support and more.
Features of Double Commander
	Internal text editor (F4) with syntax...
</description></item><item><title>Download Darktable 5.4.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 22 Dec 2025 16:51:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-darktable-3959.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-darktable-3959.html
</guid><description>
Darktable is an application process work, photography, open source and developer rough. A lighttable virtual and Darktable for the photographer. It manages the negative of your digital in the database, lets you view them through a lamp can zoom and allows you to develop raw images and enhance them. Original image of you never be modified! Features color management professional to ensure fidelity in all the way in and handle GPU acceleration means you can speed up the process of his work by...
</description></item><item><title>Download Kotato All Video Downloader Pro 10.0.8</title><pubDate> Mon, 22 Dec 2025 16:50:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kotato-all-video-downloader-pro-5228.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kotato-all-video-downloader-pro-5228.html
</guid><description>
Kotato All Video Downloader Pro is a Windows application professional to download and convert your favorite videos from the video sharing website. It speeds up your downloads up to 5 times! Kotato All Video Downloader Pro can download videos from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion and hundreds of video sharing sites, other. After downloading, you will be able to play them smoother on your PC or your mobile device, even when you don't have Internet access.
The main features of Kotato All...
</description></item><item><title>Download ProShot 8.32.4 build 540</title><pubDate> Mon, 22 Dec 2025 16:16:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-proshot-8195.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-proshot-8195.html
</guid><description>
ProShot is a camera app for Android devices that offers advanced manual controls for photography enthusiasts. It allows users to manually adjust settings such as shutter speed, ISO, white balance, and focus. It also offers a level of integration, a powerful time-lapse mode, and many other features for advanced photography. It's designed for advanced users who want more control over their photos than the default camera app offers.
Camera features of ProShot
	Auto, Program, Manual and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Multi language Translator Text 97.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 22 Dec 2025 16:16:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-multi-language-translator-text-11918.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-multi-language-translator-text-11918.html
</guid><description>
In today's globalized world, it is normal to communicate with people who speak different languages. Whether you are traveling abroad, conducting business with international customers, or simply trying to connect with people from different cultures, the ability to quickly and accurately translate text is essential. necessity. This is where a multilingual text translation app can become a valuable tool.
Multi language Translator Text is a mobile application that allows users to translate...
</description></item><item><title>Download Photo Studio PRO 2.8.8.4702</title><pubDate> Mon, 22 Dec 2025 16:16:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-photo-studio-pro-8247.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-photo-studio-pro-8247.html
</guid><description>
Photo Studio APK is a powerful multifunctional photo editing application for photographers of all levels. It contains a huge set of editing tools for basic and advanced editing of your photos. Turn each of your photos into a finished work of art using a variety of effects, filters, text editing and color enhancement tools, and many other available features.
Features of Photo Studio Pro APK
	More than 200 unique filters, amazing special effects, large collection of picture-in-picture...
</description></item><item><title>Download Chat Smith: AI Chatbot &amp;amp; Agent 8.251215.2 build 1209</title><pubDate> Mon, 22 Dec 2025 16:15:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ai-chat-smith-smart-assistant-13276.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ai-chat-smith-smart-assistant-13276.html
</guid><description>
Ask AI Chat Smith Smart Assistant anything about the latest AI Models and get instant answers. Open &amp;amp; Chat with the most advanced AI! With advanced artificial intelligence, enjoy a personalized experience and chat with your AI Chatbot personal assistant. Chat Smith's intuitive and user-friendly interface makes it easy to interact and get informative responses to your questions.
AI Chatbot Chat Smith offers a variety of useful smart assistants to choose from: Business, Content,...
</description></item><item><title>Download AI Video Editor - VideoShow AI 11.0.2.4</title><pubDate> Mon, 22 Dec 2025 16:15:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-video-editor-maker-videoshow-8149.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-video-editor-maker-videoshow-8149.html
</guid><description>
Video Editor &amp;amp; Maker VideoShow is a video editing and movie making app that allows you to create and edit videos on your mobile device. With this movie maker, creating memes, creating videos or slideshows with photos, images, music, stickers and sound effects is easy and fun. Providing the latest Halloween materials! Young filmmakers can even beautify videos with text, FX, effects, GIFs, trendy filters, transitions or live dubbing in a creative and personalized way.
All-in-one...
</description></item><item><title>Download Annotium - Photo Annotation 3.13.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 22 Dec 2025 16:10:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-annotium-photo-annotation-11211.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-annotium-photo-annotation-11211.html
</guid><description>
Users can draw lines/curves with many types of arrows and formats, besides rectangles, ellipses, rounded rectangles, triangles, quadrilaterals, polygons, many types of text like plain text, caption text box (comics), cursor text, spotlight, magnifier, text highlight, free drawing, icon... User can point and illustrate directly directly to the point of attention, helping work faster and more effectively.
Main features:
	Many built-in tools such as lines, curves, rectangles, ovals,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Add Text: Text on Photo Editor 12.8.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 22 Dec 2025 16:10:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-add-text-text-on-photo-editor-10483.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-add-text-text-on-photo-editor-10483.html
</guid><description>
Add Text app is an all-in-one tool for creating text. You can add text to photos, gradients, solid colors, or transparent backgrounds.
Highlights
	Besides text, add other overlays: photos, shapes, stickers, and saved text styles
	Design parts of text separately: supported in Format, Color, Stroke, Markup tools
	3D Text Tools: 3D Rotation, 3D Depth, Perspective
	In addition to 800+ fonts, add an unlimited number of custom fonts (including emoji fonts)
	Change text size, line wrapping,...
</description></item><item><title>Download YoWindow Weather - Unlimited 2.54.11</title><pubDate> Mon, 22 Dec 2025 16:09:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-yowindow-weather-unlimited-8421.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-yowindow-weather-unlimited-8421.html
</guid><description>
YoWindow is a unique new weather app. The magic of YoWindow is a living landscape that reflects your real-life weather. For example, if it rains - it will rain in YoWindow. Sunset and sunrise in YoWindow take place at the same time as in real life. But the cool thing is you can roll time forward. Just swipe the screen and you'll see how the weather changes throughout the day.
YoWindow Weather Features - Unlimited
	All the weather at your fingertips. You see the current weather,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Lucky Patcher 11.9.8</title><pubDate> Mon, 22 Dec 2025 16:09:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-lucky-patcher-11914.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-lucky-patcher-11914.html
</guid><description>
Lucky Patcher is a free Android app that can modify many apps and games, Block ads, remove unwanted system apps, backup apps before and after modification, Move apps apps to SD card, remove license verification from paid apps and games, etc.
Lucky Patcher features and details:
	Remove or block ads on Android apps and games. You can easily block ads with Lucky Patcher.
	Block in-app purchase verification with the app. You can use premium apps and games for free by removing in-app...
</description></item><item><title>Download WillyWeather 4.1.7</title><pubDate> Mon, 22 Dec 2025 16:08:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-willyweather-10929.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-willyweather-10929.html
</guid><description>
WillyWeather is a feature-packed weather app that includes radar and NOAA satellites, detailed forecasts for wind, rain, tides, ocean waves and UV, as well as moon phases as well like sunrise and sunset times. In addition to our regular weather service, we process and refine coordinate-specific forecast data for more than 175,000 locations across the United States, including all towns, cities, beaches, rivers, parks, lakes and islands.
Weather data
	Weather - Six-day NOAA weather...
</description></item></channel></rss>