<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 23:34:22 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 23:34:22 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download ASCOMP PDF-compress 1.012 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Sun, 02 Nov 2025 00:10:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ascomp-pdf-compress-7415.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ascomp-pdf-compress-7415.html
</guid><description>
ASCOMP PDF-compress provides PDF compression so you can optimize your PDF files so that they don't take up more storage space than necessary. Depending on the structure and content of the PDF document, up to 95% compression can be achieved. In a test with more than 1,000 randomly selected PDF files from different sources, an average compression ratio of close to 50% was achieved.
ASCOMP PDF-compress uses different approaches to compression. For example, images contained in a document...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDF-compress Professional 1.012</title><pubDate> Sun, 02 Nov 2025 00:10:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-compress-professional-10856.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-compress-professional-10856.html
</guid><description>
The PDF format is ideal for presenting and sharing complex documents, diagrams, graphics, and forms. However, as a result, PDFs are often very extensive, so it's really a knockout criterion for sharing. PDF-compress Professional is a solution that compresses your PDF files reliably and in the best possible way.
With PDF compression, you can optimize your PDF files so they don't take up more storage space than is absolutely necessary. Depending on the structure and content of the PDF...
</description></item><item><title>Download Secure-PDF Professional 2.013</title><pubDate> Sun, 02 Nov 2025 00:10:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secure-pdf-professional-4234.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secure-pdf-professional-4234.html
</guid><description>
Secure-PDF Professional is security tools, including encryption and signing PDF documents. Secure-PDF Professional will encrypt PDF document of yourself or of other people with the intensity key up to 256 bits (AES) to ensure your PDF document is not who can view and edit it. Add password to open it to users can only view the encrypted document by entering the correct password.
Secure-PDF Professional - encrypted PDF document
PDF format is used worldwide to distribute document to be...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDF Conversa Pro 3.013</title><pubDate> Sun, 02 Nov 2025 00:09:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-conversa-pro-1271.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-conversa-pro-1271.html
</guid><description>
PDF Conversa Pro is software that converts PDF files into Microsoft Word documents and vice versa quickly and can apply password protection. PDF Conversa is one such application that can turn PDF files into your DOC as well as reverse the process, while retaining the options original format is not changed.
PDF Conversa Pro - convert PDFS into Microsoft Word documents
If you choose PDF to DOC, everything is quite simple: you just need to specify the source filename as well as the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Franzis HDR 11 professional 11.43.04285</title><pubDate> Sun, 02 Nov 2025 00:09:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-franzis-hdr-projects-professional-1238.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-franzis-hdr-projects-professional-1238.html
</guid><description>
Franzis HDR projects Professional is an editor to create HDR images boast about contrast, not realistic with a gradient. The image resolution so high is created by combining a number of images of the same point, with the exposure parameters different, together. Use algorithm mapped tone has won prizes to the image sensor, HDR image contrast full spectacular.
Franzis HDR projects Professional
The function of HDR projects Professional
	Filter processing
	7 HDR algorithm different
	The...
</description></item><item><title>Download ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro 15.25.1101</title><pubDate> Sun, 02 Nov 2025 00:08:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-videotube-downloader-pro-1276.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-videotube-downloader-pro-1276.html
</guid><description>
ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro is the professional version support download videos and playlists from YouTube, videos from Dailymotion, BBC iPlayer, ITV Player, ABC,  FOX,CBS.com Vimeo, Prosieben, Metacafe, Blip.tv CBC.ca many more video sites. After the video is downloaded, you can convert them to the formats compatible with iPad, iPhone, iPod, MPEG-4, H. 264, MP3, AC3.
ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro - Download videos on Youtube
This is one of the software download the most...
</description></item><item><title>Download Universal Media Server 15.1.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 02 Nov 2025 00:07:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-universal-media-server-2364.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-universal-media-server-2364.html
</guid><description>
Universal Media Server is a media server UPnP compatible multi-platform DLNA. The purpose of this software is to give you a chance to stabilize to make the exchange quick and convenient files necessary. Server the device supports the different output and facilitate the process of exchanging information between a computer and necessary equipment. The development is based on PS3 Media Server, which means you can interact with the Playstation 3, Xbox 360, as well as TV Samsung or...
</description></item><item><title>Download Text-R Professional Edition 2.011</title><pubDate> Sun, 02 Nov 2025 00:07:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-text-r-professional-4402.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-text-r-professional-4402.html
</guid><description>
Text-R Professional - text Recognition optical simple (OCR) for Windows. Files and image PDF from a paper document to be scanned contains text can not copy or edit. However, can't type craft due to the size of material and time related to high. Text-R! The software also recognize text in PDF, and image files can be operated immediately.
Text-R Professional - Recognize text in PDFS and images
Text can be saved in PDF documents or RTF editable new (Word). Format still close to the...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDF Imager Professional 2.011</title><pubDate> Sun, 02 Nov 2025 00:06:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-imager-7136.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-imager-7136.html
</guid><description>
PDF Imager is software that converts all pages of a selected PDF document into an image file. The most popular image formats are supported. In addition to BMP, JPEG and PNG, EPS, GIF and TIFF are available as target formats. PDF Imager is also the ideal solution for creating PDF documents from one or more images instantly, without the need for expensive PDF editors!
Features of PDF Imager
	Supports various file formats like PDF, BMP, JPEG and PNG, EPS, GIF and TIFF,..
	Support fast...
</description></item><item><title>Download Pianoteq Pro 9.0.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 02 Nov 2025 00:05:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pianoteq-pro-14244.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pianoteq-pro-14244.html
</guid><description>
Pianoteq 8 is a virtual instrument from Modartt, which uses physical modeling to recreate the sound and behavior of pianos and other instruments. Unlike sampled instruments, it takes up very little disk space, while delivering high realism and a wide dynamic range.
	Dual Polarity: An advanced physics engine simulates the vibration of strings in multiple directions, resulting in a more complex and realistic sound, especially in the low range.
	Reproduced Sounds: All modern acoustic...
</description></item><item><title>Download Media Player Classic Home Cinema 2.5.5</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 17:27:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-media-player-classic-home-cinema-2839.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-media-player-classic-home-cinema-2839.html
</guid><description>
Media Player Classic Home Cinema is a multimedia compact for Microsoft Windows 32 bit and 64 bit. MPC mimics the interface of Windows Media Player 6.4, but provides most options and features available in the modern means. Media Player Classic Home Cinema for free 100% no advertising, so you can directly access content and enjoy media playback without being distracted.
With Media Player Classic Home, you can now change the design a multimedia of the custom toolbar. There is a range to...
</description></item><item><title>Download UniGetUI 3.3.6</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 17:27:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-unigetui-12209.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-unigetui-12209.html
</guid><description>
UniGetUI (formerly WingetUI) is a graphical user interface for WinGet (and other package managers), a command-line package manager for Windows 10 and Windows 11 such as Winget, Scoop, Chocolatey, Pip, NPM, .NET Tool and PowerShell Gallery. It allows users to install, update and uninstall software from the package manager easily. Additionally, it provides features like backup, restore, group and update your packages and receive notifications about new updates.
With this program, you can...
</description></item><item><title>Download K-Lite Codec Pack Full 19.3.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 17:25:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-115.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-115.html
</guid><description>
K Lite Codec Pack Full brings pc users an optimal solution for watching movies, listening to music, support most popular format today by using collection codec rich. This software also allows you to refine the quality of videos and music to enjoy, create a list of music and video to comfortable enjoy.
Prompt to software, listen to music, watch movies, currently, part, user will prompt to programs like VLC or KMP ... With VLC, it was too familiar with users, not just watch videos, listen...
</description></item><item><title>Download K-Lite Codec Pack Mega 19.3.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 17:25:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-mega-3202.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-mega-3202.html
</guid><description>
K-Lite Mega Codec Pack is a collection of components needed for audio playback and the video in the player DirectShow like Windows Media Player, Media Center, and Media Player Classic. This is the latest beta version, Pack Codec K-Lite latest stable. The Mega variant is the biggest of the four variants of the codec pack. It provides everything you need to play all audio and video files. In addition, it also contains some codecs ACM / VFW can be used by the application coding / video...
</description></item><item><title>Download Alfa eBooks Manager Pro / Web 9.4.8.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 17:23:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-alfa-ebooks-manager-web-981.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-alfa-ebooks-manager-web-981.html
</guid><description>
Alfa eBooks Manager Web is a program that enables to arrange the electronic books and paper of you in a single electronic library. eBooks Manager Website will host the electronic books and print in an electronic library. Group, filter and sort books by multiple parameters. Find any book in just a second by title, author or ISBN.
Alfa eBooks Manager Web - ebook library
Alfa eBooks Manager Web provides comprehensive set of fields, including the author, category, publisher, series, ISBN,...
</description></item><item><title>Download PanoramaStudio Pro 4.1.6.445</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 17:22:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-panoramastudio-pro-1604.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-panoramastudio-pro-1604.html
</guid><description>
PanoramaStudio Pro is software is the complete solution for creating panoramic images as matching images are arranged arbitrary in the panorama. PanoramaStudio Pro creates panoramic images in a row and multiple rows of up to 360x180 spherical full. In addition, this software provides viewer / player application HTML5 interactions are compatible with all web browsers and on multiple systems to display the panoramic image 3D, 360 degree images and image zoom on the site.
PanoramaStudio...
</description></item><item><title>Download Free Download Manager 6.30.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 17:16:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-download-manager-3105.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-download-manager-3105.html
</guid><description>
Free Download Manager is free application download manager, Free Download Manager will significantly increase downloads by splitting the files into several smaller parts and then downloads at the same time. Speed your download will be significantly increased. Manager download free can also continue to download at broken or not responding, so you don't need start downloading from the beginning after occasionally interrupted.
Free Download Manager - Manage and speed up downloads
You can...
</description></item><item><title>Download ViewCompanion Premium 16.22.0.1116</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 17:15:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-viewcompanion-premium-1868.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-viewcompanion-premium-1868.html
</guid><description>
ViewCompanion Premium version is the most powerful in all versions of ViewCompmate. ViewCompanion Premium can view, print and convert the file plot PLT, Adobe PDF, Autodesk DWF, Postcript, CGM, TIFF, CALS and other formats. ViewCompanion premium files, support PLT plotter using HPGL, HPGL / 2, HP-RTL, and formats Calcomp.
ViewCompanion Premium
With ViewCompanion Premium, you can add bookmarks to files has download. The markup elements are supported, including rectangles, lines,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Full Convert Ultimate 25.10.1692</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 17:15:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-full-convert-enterprise-997.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-full-convert-enterprise-997.html
</guid><description>
Full Convert Enterprise is a conversion software database. Full Convert Enterprise create all the tables, copy all of your data. Full Convert Enterprise has the custom features and mapped powerful at your disposal, your data will be moved out of the box without custom. Full Convert automatically adjusted the basis of your data and use copy modes optimized for each separate table to achieve information best possible quality.
Full Convert Enterprise - convert data base
Full Convert...
</description></item><item><title>Download UltFone Windows Data Recovery 10.6.3.7</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 17:14:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ultfone-windows-data-recovery-14195.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ultfone-windows-data-recovery-14195.html
</guid><description>
UltFone Windows Data Recovery is a comprehensive data recovery software designed for Windows system to recover lost or deleted files from various storage devices such as hard drive, USB drive, SD card, etc. The software supports recovering many file types, including photos, videos, documents, music and archive files. The software offers two scanning modes—quick scan for recently deleted files and deep scan for comprehensive recovery, and also allows users to preview recoverable files...
</description></item><item><title>Download Autodesk AutoCAD 2026.1.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 17:14:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-autodesk-autocad-2025-0002-4077.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-autodesk-autocad-2025-0002-4077.html
</guid><description>
Autodesk AutoCAD design software is computer-aided (CAD) which the architects, engineers and construction professionals rely on to create the 2D and 3D drawings accurately. Autodesk AutoCAD will allow you to design and shape the world around you using the powerful features and flexibility of it. Speed documentation, share ideas seamlessly, and explore ideas more intuitively in 3D. With thousands of add-ons available, AutoCAD offers maximum flexibility, is customized for the specific needs...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cockos REAPER 7.52</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 17:13:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cockos-reaper-889.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cockos-reaper-889.html
</guid><description>
Cockos REAPER is a powerful software for for windows, chp lets you record, arrange, edit, and display the audio waveform multi-track. Cockos REAPER offers an extensive feature set includes many effects and a sample project. REAPER supports ASIO, Kernel Streaming, WaveOut, and DirectSound for playback and recording. It reads the files in WAV, OGG and MP3 files and records WAV files. You can arrange any number of items in any number of tracks and use plug-in sound processing (DirectX and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Autodesk AutoCAD LT 2026.1.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 17:13:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-autodesk-autocad-lt-0001-7351.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-autodesk-autocad-lt-0001-7351.html
</guid><description>
AutoCAD LT 2024 is designed for the development and detailing of 2D drawings. The program automates most of the phases of the project. A complete set of 2D commands allows you to create drawings, modify them, and publish working documents for projects. can easily transfer files to other professionals. Additionally, you can customize the program's user interface to fit your needs.
Features of AutoCAD LT
	Create and edit 2D drawings.
	Annotate drawings with text, dimensions, paths, and...
</description></item><item><title>Download KeyScrambler Premium 3.18.0.8 + Professional</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 17:12:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-keyscrambler-premium-professional-143.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-keyscrambler-premium-professional-143.html
</guid><description>
KeyScrambler Premium / Professional allows users to search for and remove the malicious program, the spy program on the computer system. This program support users to handle a number of spy programs send user information to the server by way thoroughly remove them from the system.
KeyScrambler Premium Key key encryption real-time encryption key, every key you type deep in the Windows. It protects the personal information of you against all malware keylog already know and not know on...
</description></item><item><title>Download SQL Backup Master 8.0.1015 Enterprise</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 17:11:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sql-backup-master-6687.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sql-backup-master-6687.html
</guid><description>
SQL Backup Master backup your SQL Server database into any popular cloud hosting service such as Dropbox, OneDrive, Amazon S3, Microsoft Azure, Box and Google Drive. It can also backup the database to the FTP server-or a directory on your local machine, network server or storage device.
The backup of your SQL Server database to the cloud will not be complex or expensive. SQL Backup Master is born by providing an easy way to download copies of your database to one or more of the most...
</description></item></channel></rss>