<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 05:35:38 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 05:35:38 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download OnlyOffice Desktop Editors 9.2.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Dec 2025 23:37:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-onlyoffice-7488.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-onlyoffice-7488.html
</guid><description>
OnlyOffice is a free office suite that can open documents, presentations, and spreadsheets in different tabs of the same window, providing interoperability Compatible with the most popular file formats. With an attractive intuitive interface and intuitive controls, OnlyOffice allows users to open documents, spreadsheets and presentations, or create new ones from scratch. It comes with support for the most common file formats, even those native to Microsoft's office suite. Moreover, it can...
</description></item><item><title>Download RegCool 3.0.0.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Dec 2025 23:34:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-regcool-42.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-regcool-42.html
</guid><description>
RegCool is a powerful and user-friendly registry editor for Windows operating systems. The registry is an important part of the Windows operating system, containing important settings and configurations that determine how your computer functions. With RegCool, users can easily navigate, edit, and manage registry keys and values, making it a valuable tool for advanced users and IT professionals.
RegCool's main features:
	User-friendly interface: RegCool has a clear and intuitive user...
</description></item><item><title>Download FxSound (FxSound Enhancer Premium) 1.2.5 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Dec 2025 23:34:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fxsound-enhancer-premium-2013.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fxsound-enhancer-premium-2013.html
</guid><description>
FxSound Enhancer Premium formerly DFX Audio Enhance, is accessories multimedia software most popular in the world with over 46 million downloads worldwide. FxSound enhances the sound of most of the music content and online video is live streaming on the Web, including the streaming service, YouTube, Pandora, Spotify and Apple Music. FxSound Enhancer Premium also implemented enhanced real-time audio on the player PC multimedia most popular include iTunes, Windows Media Player, Winamp and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Pepakura Designer 6.1.3</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Dec 2025 23:33:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pepakura-designer-748.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pepakura-designer-748.html
</guid><description>
Pepakura Designer is software to create 2D models, 3D quick, easy and developed in Japan. Pepakura Designer helps easily design the template paper craft by importing data 3D model. No special knowledge is required to model papercraft. All you have to do is prepare the 3D model. You can use some software 3DCG released from other developers to make the 3D models for unfolding.
Pepakura Designer - Create model 2D 3D
Pepakura Designer to create the form of 2D images that you can share it...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter 3.9.18 (0412)</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Dec 2025 23:32:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-to-mp3-converter-1744.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-to-mp3-converter-1744.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter is the software support download youtube video and convert video to mp3 format fast and most simple. MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter allows you download and convert videos from YouTube and other websites to MP3 format by pasting the YouTube URL into the application. When you paste the URL, the program will display thumbnails for videos and you have the option to customize the title information, artist and album before you begin the process of...
</description></item><item><title>Download FxSound Pro 1.2.5 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Dec 2025 23:32:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fxsound-5966.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fxsound-5966.html
</guid><description>
FxSound Pro is a professional software that helps to enhance the quality of sound, volume, depth, and sound on your PC. FxSound brings you a great sound just with a downloadable download. After using FxSound, you will know if it is for you or not. Most people do n' t know what they ' re missing in their sound until they try their software/sound hardware better. It ' s hard to convey if you do n' t really experience yourself.
Reason to use FxSound Pro:
	The perfect sound on every...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cisdem VideoPaw (Video Converter) 5.0.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Dec 2025 23:31:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cisdem-video-converter-9557.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cisdem-video-converter-9557.html
</guid><description>
Cisdem Video Converter is an all-in-one solution for converting video and audio files of any format, ripping DVD movies and converting online videos. The converter provides support for more than 150 audio and video file formats, and helps you download or share content with others. Cisdem Video Converter gives you the ability to make audio or video content compatible with almost any device.
Save videos and music from 1000+ hosting sites for offline viewing, including YouTube, Facebook,...
</description></item><item><title>Download UltFone Windows Data Recovery 10.6.11.3</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Dec 2025 23:30:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ultfone-windows-data-recovery-14195.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ultfone-windows-data-recovery-14195.html
</guid><description>
UltFone Windows Data Recovery is a comprehensive data recovery software designed for Windows system to recover lost or deleted files from various storage devices such as hard drive, USB drive, SD card, etc. The software supports recovering many file types, including photos, videos, documents, music and archive files. The software offers two scanning modes—quick scan for recently deleted files and deep scan for comprehensive recovery, and also allows users to preview recoverable files...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaMonkey Gold 2024.2.1.3200 Beta</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Dec 2025 23:29:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediamonkey-gold-231.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediamonkey-gold-231.html
</guid><description>
MediaMonkey Gold is music manager and music player multimedia for the music collection and iPod users. MediaMonkey lists the audio file of you as CD, OGG, WMA, MPC, FLAC, APE, WAV and MP3 and includes the edit smart card and an automatic file and folder to arrange your music library.
MediaMonkey Gold also has CD ripper, CD / DVD Burner, and audio converter for saving music, and manual or editor list automatically to create mixed music.
Features MediaMonkey Gold
	Automatically find...
</description></item><item><title>Download Halfpricesoft ez1095 12.0.3</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Dec 2025 23:29:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-halfpricesoft-ez1095-8453.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-halfpricesoft-ez1095-8453.html
</guid><description>
Halfpricesoft ez1095 is software designed to help users prepare and file Forms 1095-B, 1095-C and 1094-B, 1094-C to comply with the Care Act Affordable Care (ACA). It aims to be user-friendly and efficient, allowing users to easily enter information and create the necessary forms to file with the IRS. This software is commonly used by small businesses, accountants, and tax professionals to automate the process of preparing and filing ACA forms. It supports all 1095 form types including...
</description></item><item><title>Download CFTurbo 2026 R1.0.126 + CFTurbo FEA 2026 R1.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Dec 2025 23:28:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cfturbo-3713.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cfturbo-3713.html
</guid><description>
CFTurbo is a powerful program but easy to use software for pump design can help you design pumps from scratch or redesign the rotor is there. Simply tell it the flow rate, head, RPM and any vortex before (optional) and CFTurbo which will automatically generate a pump design. Then you have the option to go back and change any detail of design with the guidance of CFTurbo. Easy but flexible, this approach to pump design saves you time and still lets you get exactly the pump design you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Personal Backup 6.4.5.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Dec 2025 22:36:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-personal-backup-1117.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-personal-backup-1117.html
</guid><description>
Personal Backup is software to backup data on computer hard drive professional with the ability to copy data on the hard drive and save any folder. Personal Backup is the most optimal solutions to ensure safety for data on avoid computer viruses, malicious code, intrusion and data loss because you can restore lost data at any time if it has to be backed up and stored on the folder of the computer.
Personal Backup - backup computer data
Features of Personal Backup
	Backup cross data...
</description></item><item><title>Download Distant Desktop 4.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Dec 2025 22:35:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-distant-desktop-8490.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-distant-desktop-8490.html
</guid><description>
Distant Desktop is free software that allows you to control your computer from any device anywhere. Only 2 computers need to have Distant Desktop software installed and one of them needs to provide a unique ID and password to establish a remote desktop connection.
Distant Desktop allows remote control of your computer through your mouse and keyboard. Multiple connections can be made at the same time. This applies to both the managing party and the controlled party. You can perform file...
</description></item><item><title>Download HopToDesk 1.45.4</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Dec 2025 22:35:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hoptodesk-11056.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hoptodesk-11056.html
</guid><description>
HopToDesk is a remote desktop application that allows users to access their remote computer or server from anywhere using a mobile device or browser their website. It provides a secure and convenient way to control and manage computers remotely, making it easier for individuals and teams to work remotely or access their files and applications on the go.
With HopToDesk, users can establish a secure connection to a remote computer or server and perform tasks as if they were sitting in...
</description></item><item><title>Download PowerDirector - Video Editor 15.9.2 build 2512221</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Dec 2025 22:33:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-powerdirector-video-editor-8123.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-powerdirector-video-editor-8123.html
</guid><description>
PowerDirector APK - Video Editor (Unlocked Version) is video editing software developed by CyberLink. It is available for Windows and Android devices. If you are looking for the Android version of PowerDirector, you can download the APK (Android Package Kit) file from the Google Play Store or from taiwebs.com.
Features of PowerDirector APK - Unlocked Version:
	Easy-to-use interface: PowerDirector has a user-friendly interface that makes it easy to edit and create videos, even if...
</description></item><item><title>Download Knots 3D 10.6.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Dec 2025 22:33:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-knots-3d-8500.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-knots-3d-8500.html
</guid><description>
Knots 3D is a mobile application that provides visual and interactive instructions for tying different types of knots. This app can be used to learn and practice different knots, with detailed animations and illustrations showing the correct technique for each knot. Used by arborists, fishermen, firefighters, climbers, military, and boy and girl scouts worldwide, Knots 3D will quickly teach you how to tie even the most difficult knots!
With more than 175 nautical miles, Knots 3D will be...
</description></item><item><title>Download JPEG Optimizer PRO 1.1.21</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Dec 2025 22:33:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-jpeg-optimizer-pro-with-pdf-support-10818.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-jpeg-optimizer-pro-with-pdf-support-10818.html
</guid><description>
Can't send images due to email attachment size limits? No room to save them on your SD card? JPEG Optimizer is the best solution for you. This app will allow you to compress large photos into smaller ones with little or no loss of quality. Furthermore, the unique ISO Noise Optimization algorithm allows you to reduce image file size to improve quality.
Features of JPEG Optimizer PRO
	Compress, resize photos
	Compress or resize multiple photos at once
	Allows you to adjust the quality...
</description></item><item><title>Download Librera PRO - Book reader 9.2.8</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Dec 2025 22:32:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-librera-pro-all-my-books-9008.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-librera-pro-all-my-books-9008.html
</guid><description>
PRO Librera Reader is an easy-to-use and highly configurable reading application that supports most popular document formats, including: PDF, EPUB, EPUB3, MOBI, DjVu, FB2, FB2.zip, TXT, RTF, AZW, AZW3, CBR, CBZ, HTML, XPS, MHT and more. With a simple yet powerful interface, Librera Reader makes reading documents a real pleasure. Librera even has a unique hands-free, auto-scrolling music mode.
Some key features of Librera reader include:
Easily explore documents with optional and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Aiarty Image Enhancer 3.7</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Dec 2025 16:02:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aiarty-image-enhancer-12181.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aiarty-image-enhancer-12181.html
</guid><description>
Aiarty Image Enhancer is an AI-powered image enhancement software to de-noise, de-blur, enhance images and create more image details. It uses advanced deep learning technologies to enhance and upscale images while creating realistic details. Whether you want to enlarge low-resolution images by 200%, 400% or 800% for printing, deliver 2K/4K/8K images while preserving realistic details, correcting low-quality photos , remove blur and noise or restore compressed JPEGs, Aiarty Image Enhancer...
</description></item><item><title>Download SoftMaker Office NX Universal 2024 Rev S1230.1206</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Dec 2025 16:02:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-softmaker-office-professional-819.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-softmaker-office-professional-819.html
</guid><description>
SoftMaker Office Professional version, professional office support in terms of writing, calculation, presentation, E-mail, tasks,.. When using SoftMaker Office documents, calculations and presentations are handled as fast as e-mail or appointment and task planning. From the simple work daily to these documents, the most demanding, SoftMaker Office 2018 is the indispensable help of you.
SoftMaker Office is compatible with all the Microsoft Office. It edit Microsoft Office documents true to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Digiarty Aiarty Video Enhancer 3.3</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:58:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-digiarty-aiarty-video-enhancer-13862.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-digiarty-aiarty-video-enhancer-13862.html
</guid><description>
Digiarty Aiarty Video Enhancer is an AI-powered desktop software designed to upscale, denoise, deblur, and enhance videos up to 4K resolution with professional quality and speed. It uses advanced AI models optimized for GPU acceleration and Turbo mode, enabling real-time or near-real-time video processing, including frame interpolation for smooth motion up to 90fps, 120fps, or higher. This tool is effective in restoring low-resolution, old, blurry, jerky or underexposed footage,...
</description></item><item><title>Download 4DDiG Partition Manager 3.9.1.9</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:57:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4ddig-partition-manager-2024-9781.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4ddig-partition-manager-2024-9781.html
</guid><description>
4DDiG Partition Manager is a powerful Windows disk partition software expert in system migration, disk cloning and disk partition management. It can effectively clone your entire disk or partition, providing a reliable solution for data backup.
This is Windows 10 fast system and data transfer solution &amp;amp; 11. 4DDiG Partition Manager can move the system and large files or folders from one disk partition to a larger one with just one click. Or you can use it to move the system and large...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube Downloader 3.9.18 (0412)</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:57:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube Downloader  is a dedicated software that helps users  downloading youtube videos  Favorites on PC for offline viewing. With MediaHuman YouTube  Downloader  you can download videos from youtube website to your computer with  fast speed , with special software development technology that automatically receives videos from Websites, in addition to the ability to download videos from software websites, can convert downloaded video formats to various formats for the purpose...
</description></item><item><title>Download StaxRip 2.50.5</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:56:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-staxrip-2930.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-staxrip-2930.html
</guid><description>
StaxRip app is a comprehensive and powerful, allowing you to convert all video files DVB, DVD, or DV video into a variety of file formats. The program is open Source, meaning completely free to download and use. StaxRip can support many video formats such as x264, MPEG-4, DivX, XviD, MPEG-2 and many other formats. The format sounds different also be supported, including MP2 / MPA, AAC, WAV, Ogg Vorbis, MP3, AC3, DTS and other formats. Moreover, the program also supports a variety of...
</description></item><item><title>Download reaConverter Pro 8.0.173</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:56:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html
</guid><description>
reaConverter Pro is software image processing feature with batch conversion and image editing periodically becomes simple. eaConverter also provide command line utilities allow you to process images automatically, thus helping you shorten the time for other work.
reaConverter Pro integrated powerful tool of Uber with many great features. It provides advanced solutions to process and adjust images. Management of the conversion process the base image with the latest version of...
</description></item></channel></rss>