<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 22:07:04 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 22:07:04 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download WonderFox HD Video Converter Factory Pro 28.4</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 01:05:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hd-video-converter-factory-pro-1458.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hd-video-converter-factory-pro-1458.html
</guid><description>
WonderFox HD Video Converter Factory Pro is a software powerful video conversion . This program can convert the video files the quality standard of the file SD card, the files HD as HD MP4, HD MKV, HD AVI, HD MTS, HD TRP. This can also in the opposite direction. This software includes more than 100 video formats, while maintaining quality output, faster than 50 times compared to some software. This software also supports VBR or VBR, using this option will keep the original quality of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download MusConv 4.10.451 Lifetime</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 01:04:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html
</guid><description>
MusConv transfers playlists, albums, followed artists and liked songs across a variety of services – Spotify, Apple Music, Amazon Music, YouTube, YouTube Music, iTunes, Deezer, Tidal, SoundCloud, Pandora and more 125 music services!
Features of MusConv Ultimate
	Transfer playlists, albums, followed artists and liked tracks between over 125 music servicesManage playlists (Delete, Merge, Split, Copy...)
	More than 125 music services supported
	Access DAILY updated music charts on...
</description></item><item><title>Download ChessBase 26.6</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 01:04:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chessbase-13889.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chessbase-13889.html
</guid><description>
ChessBase is the personal, independent chess database that has become the world standard. Everyone uses ChessBase, from World Champions to the amateur player next door. It is the program of choice for anyone who loves the game and wants to learn more about it. Start your personal success story with ChessBase and enjoy the game even more.
Whether it's preparing for an individual opponent or tournament, managing and analyzing your own games, developing training materials for self-study or...
</description></item><item><title>Download WizFlow Flowcharter Professional 7.50.2220</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 01:03:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wizflow-flowcharter-professional-3604.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wizflow-flowcharter-professional-3604.html
</guid><description>
WizFlow Flowcharter Professional is a tool for drawing diagrams and diagram easy-to-use, feature-rich, abundant for Windows. WizFlow lets you define "styles" shape using more than a hundred shapes and arrow heads to be determined first. Save your styles in the template to set the method of mapping your own. WizFlow comes with the template complete diagram to help you get started. WizFlow can create flowcharts and diagrams similar with minimal effort. When you draw a diagram of WizFlow...
</description></item><item><title>Download Product Key Decryptor 11.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 01:03:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-product-key-decryptor-7646.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-product-key-decryptor-7646.html
</guid><description>
Product Key Decryptor is a useful tool to recover license CD keys of more than 200 popular software including Windows, Adobe, Winamp, etc. It automatically detects and decrypts license/serial keys of all popular software from your system.
After successful restore, you can backup the recovered CD License Key list to HTML/XML/TEXT/CSV file. You can also right-click any displayed product license key to quickly copy it. It works on both 32-bit and 64-bit platforms starting from Windows XP...
</description></item><item><title>Download Icecream Video Editor Pro 3.25</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 01:02:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-icecream-video-editor-4521.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-icecream-video-editor-4521.html
</guid><description>
Icecream Video Editor Pro is a video editing app powerful but easy to use allows you to easily trim, crop, flip and rotate videos. The program also allows you to add subtitles, and apply a watermark text for your video file. In addition, you can transfer the video files were edited into various devices, such as iPod, iPhone, iPad or other mobile device.
Icecream Video Editor Pro - Video editing
Intuitive interface, familiar
Icecream Video Editor Pro has the layout somewhat familiar...
</description></item><item><title>Download EDGE Diagrammer 7.50.2220</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 01:02:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-edge-diagrammer-9462.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-edge-diagrammer-9462.html
</guid><description>
EDGE Diagrammer is a software application used to create graphical diagrams, especially in the field of systems engineering. The term "EDGE" stands for "Enhanced Diagram Graphics Environment". It provides a user-friendly interface and a set of tools for designing and documenting complex systems, processes, and workflows.
EDGE Diagrammer is all you need for block diagrams, flowcharts, organization charts, family trees, data flow diagrams and more. Free extension packs are available to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Icecream Video Converter Pro 1.49</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 01:01:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-icecream-video-converter-9618.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-icecream-video-converter-9618.html
</guid><description>
Icecream Video Converter is a nicely made video converter that makes the process as simple as possible while still producing quality results. You can also apply output settings to all files if needed. All popular formats are supported, like MP4, AVI, MKV, 3GP, WMV, MOV, M4V, MPG, M2TS, MTS, etc. It also has device presets for those times when you are unsure about the format and resolution of the output document. Built-in presets include iPad, iPhone, Android, and PS5, among...
</description></item><item><title>Download Monkeys Audio 12.11</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 00:46:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-monkeys-audio-949.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-monkeys-audio-949.html
</guid><description>
Monkey\'s Audio is software that compresses digital music without loss of quality. Supports high quality WAV files and CD ripping. Monkeys Audio will compress .wav tracks into .ape files to reduce their size without loss of sound quality, decompress .ape, convert files, check file integrity and manage tags.
Unlike traditional methods like MP3 and OGG, which permanently remove quality to save space, Monkey\'s Audio only creates perfect copies with the same sound quality as the originals....
</description></item><item><title>Download FireAlpaca 2.15.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 00:45:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-firealpaca-2882.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-firealpaca-2882.html
</guid><description>
FireAlpaca is software painting Digital free available in 10 languages and is compatible with both Mac and Windows. The tools and simple controls allow you to draw a easy illustration. Convenient tool will be adding this one to the other! Download FireAlpaca right now! FireAlpaca is the utility to create and edit image files, add image overlays, as well as providing many other advanced features, bring an effective tool to help you draw a picture or edit a photo from the most basic...
</description></item><item><title>Download Avast Clear 26.1.10738</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 00:44:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avast-clear-4437.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avast-clear-4437.html
</guid><description>
Avast Clear is a utility to remove accurately and completely line product anti-virus AVAST. Avast to leave a lot of garbage behind the computer and in the register. In particular, the registry hassle can, for example, can be an obstacle to install a program anti-virus Avast other then. In such cases, you can use a special utility Avast!
Avast Clear - Uninstall program Avast
Recommended avoid any inconvenience, should always engage the help of a dedicated tool to know where to search...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ant Download Manager Pro 2.16.6 Build 92479</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:29:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ant-download-manager-pro-137.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ant-download-manager-pro-137.html
</guid><description>
Ant Download Manager Pro is software support download has the same features as IDM, even it has many prominent features, more user friendly more and have speed download data incredible. Ant Download Manager is a Internet content downloader quickly with support download at video! Function: fully Integrated with the web browsers most popular: Internet Explorer 8+, Mozilla Firefox 32 +, Google Chrome 31+ and the copies of them (Pale Moon, Opera, Vivaldi, Slimjet, ComodoDragon, etc.). you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ashampoo Music Studio 12.0.4</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:29:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-music-studio-1207.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-music-studio-1207.html
</guid><description>
Ashampoo Music Studio is software to work with audio files. Includes the process of taking the disc recording CD, DVD and Blu-ray discs module to organize music collections, editing audio files, recording module and the tool to restore audio files broken.
Ashampoo Music Studio
Functions of Ashampoo Music Studio
	Edit audio files quickly
	Cut perfect slices including direct recording
	Convert to any format and listen anywhere
	The most convenient tool to extract CD
	Create a list from...
</description></item><item><title>Download AI Aquarium Screensaver 1.3.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:28:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ai-aquarium-screensaver-14538.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ai-aquarium-screensaver-14538.html
</guid><description>
AI Aquarium Screensaver is a realistic 3D screen saver that transforms your idle screen into a vibrant underwater world. Powered by AI-controlled fish behavior, it delivers smooth, natural motion and non-repetitive scenes – making it the ideal relaxing screen saver for Windows desktops, offices, and large screens.
With a wide selection of beautifully designed aquarium wallpapers, including rock arches, rainforests, coral reefs, Dutch-style aquariums, cartoon worlds, and electronic...
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 7.9.5</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:28:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-11-7760.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-11-7760.html
</guid><description>
TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 is a program that allows users to discover hidden settings in Windows 11. This application is specially designed for Windows 11, groups many registry settings and distribute them from the easy and secure user interface. With TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 you can move the Windows taskbar to the top and resize the taskbar by editing the registry value. With any application that modifies the registry, we recommend that you have a backup copy...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ashampoo Privacy Inspector 3.00.11</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:28:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-privacy-inspector-8733.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-privacy-inspector-8733.html
</guid><description>
Windows keeps extensive records of what you do and when you do it on your PC (offline and online). So what is logged and more importantly, what can you do about it? Ashampoo Privacy Inspector lifts the veil of secrecy and shows you exactly what activities are logged along with the ability to erase your data and regain your privacy.
Features of Ashampoo Privacy Inspector
	See used objects neatly organized
	Delete confidential usage data securely
	Analysis of browsing behavior for all...
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 7.9.5</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:27:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-10-7759.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-10-7759.html
</guid><description>
TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 is a utility that allows users to discover hidden settings in Windows 10. This application is specially designed for Windows 10, groups many registry settings and provide them from an easy and secure user interface. With TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 you can move the Windows taskbar to the top and resize the taskbar by editing the registry value. With any application that modifies the registry, we recommend that you have a backup copy to...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Downloader 10.1.10</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:27:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html
</guid><description>
YTD Youtube Downloader is an application that reliable and intuitive, allowing you to quickly download YouTube videos and save them to your computer. You can also convert the media files to the format desired video or extract audio streams and save separately. YTD Youtube Downloader lets you save your favorite clips of yourself from Youtube, Facebook, Vimeo and Dailymotion to your desktop. The software supports URLS from many web site hosting, multimedia and allows you to download desired...
</description></item><item><title>Download Fast Video Cutter Joiner 6.9.8</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:26:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fast-video-cutter-joiner-7542.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fast-video-cutter-joiner-7542.html
</guid><description>
Fast Video Cutter Joiner is a fast video cutter and joiner with an easy to use interface. It allows users to trim parts of a video quickly while maintaining the quality of the original video. It supports various formats like AVI, MPEG, MP4, WMV, 3GP, FLV...
This tool helps you to cut video files into small parts, to keep only the parts you need and remove unwanted parts like trailers and advertisements in a movie. The clips you cut can then be used for other video productions or for a...
</description></item><item><title>Download PreviSat 7.2.1.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:26:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-previsat-3144.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-previsat-3144.html
</guid><description>
PreviSat is software satellite tracking with the aim of helping you to monitor and observe the position of artificial satellites in real-time. This tool can make predictions about the passes of the satellites and Iridium flares. There are also a number of parameters integrated help you collect important information about the location of satellites in the different frames, the elements of appraisal (elements of Keplerian orbits), TLE (element two lines) is set to calculate the location of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tomabo MP4 Downloader Pro 6.1.9</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:25:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tomabo-mp4-downloader-pro-3602.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tomabo-mp4-downloader-pro-3602.html
</guid><description>
Tomabo MP4 Downloader Pro is the app designed exclusively for Windows users to help them download videos from the Internet. In addition, it also increase download speeds by up to 500%, or even more. Tomabo MP4 Downloader Pro, interface design, simple, well-organized, beautifully. Here, users can view a list of videos has download with gravatar, URL, quality, duration and size of them. Software allows download video series at the same time, at the same time, support create a list of clips...
</description></item><item><title>Download AVG Clear 26.1.10738</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:24:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avg-clear-4945.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avg-clear-4945.html
</guid><description>
AVG Clear is free program help completely erase everything from installing AVG current your including the registry entries, file, settings, files, users, etc. AVG Clear is provided by AVG and is the last measure to use if you encounter a problem when deleting AVG current whether it is error repair, reinstall, or delete altogether.
Please note that all user settings AVG will be removed after the uninstall process is complete. The items should be deleted to include content from Virus...
</description></item><item><title>Download TubeMate Downloader 6.1.10</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:24:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubemate-downloader-4250.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubemate-downloader-4250.html
</guid><description>
TubeMate Downloader is a smart application that lets you download any clip you want from the website hosting the main video and convert them in when download at or then. If you need a simple and effective tool to download videos, you can give it a try. With TubeMate Downloader, you can directly drag and drop video link from your browser into the drop-down box or application window to start downloading. You don't even need to copy and paste the video URL.
TubeMate Downloader - Support...
</description></item><item><title>Download Dragonrise Games YoloX 1.7</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:23:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dragonrise-games-yolox-11598.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dragonrise-games-yolox-11598.html
</guid><description>
Use YoloX to change your game crosshair.Including color inversion, sound sensor, motion sensor, heat safety and other features never seen before.Development your target with the next revolution in crosshair technology!
YoloX Features
	Effect: Invert colors and other effects.
	Animation: Separate animations for primary fire, secondary fire, and jump.
	Sound sensor: Animated response to game sounds. Now you can listen to your own music without missing any key sounds.
	Motion sensor:...
</description></item><item><title>Download Moneyspire 2026 v26.0.9</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:22:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-moneyspire-14310.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-moneyspire-14310.html
</guid><description>
Moneyspire is a personal and small business finance management program that lets you track your basic accounts, budgets, bills, loans, and investments. Categorize your spending and income into customizable categories. Track bills so you never forget to pay and avoid late fees. Set budgets to track spending and avoid overspending in specific categories like eating out. Forecast account balances to avoid overdrafts and cash shortages. Balance your checkbook and compare it to your bank...
</description></item></channel></rss>