<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 17:37:39 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 17:37:39 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download ON1 Photo RAW 2026.1 v20.1.0.17740</title><pubDate> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 19:58:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-on1-photo-raw-1791.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-on1-photo-raw-1791.html
</guid><description>
ON1 Photo RAW 2023  includes the essential tools and features every photographer needs in their workflow. Our state-of-the-art, super-fast, non-destructive processing engine gives you an extremely smooth and efficient editing experience.
ON1 Photo RAW focuses on letting you get the most out of every photo. Photographers now have a quick photo management engine, hundreds of customizable photo effects, fast and beautiful HDR, masking and selection tools, layers and more in one app. Quickly...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinPE 11-10-8 Sergei Strelec 2025.11.19</title><pubDate> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 19:58:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winpe-10-8-sergei-strelec-8027.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winpe-10-8-sergei-strelec-8027.html
</guid><description>
WinPE 11-10-8 Sergei Strelec is a Windows 11, 10 and 8 PE boot disk for computer maintenance, hard disks and partitions, disk and partition backup and restore, computer diagnostics, data recovery, installation Windows.
Assembly components include:
	WinPE 11 x64
	WinPE 10 x64
	WinPE 10 x86
	WinPE 8 x86
	WinPE 8 x86 (Native)
System Requirements:
1. RAM 1 GB or more
2. PC can boot from CD/DVD or USB drive.
</description></item><item><title>Download ON1 Photo RAW MAX 2026.1 v20.1.0.17740</title><pubDate> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 19:57:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-on1-photo-raw-max-10717.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-on1-photo-raw-max-10717.html
</guid><description>
ON1 Photo RAW MAX 2024 is powerful photo editing software that provides photographers with many tools and features to enhance and edit their images. With a user-friendly interface, it offers advanced editing capabilities, including non-destructive editing, AI-powered adjustments, and precise control over color and tone. It also supports raw files from over 800 cameras and works with JPEG, TIF, PSD, PSB, PNG and DNG files. Additionally, it also includes photo organization tools to manage...
</description></item><item><title>Download Windows Video Converter 2025 v10.0.3.5</title><pubDate> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 19:57:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-video-converter-6371.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-video-converter-6371.html
</guid><description>
Windows Video Converter is a comprehensive software with many features such as Transaction, Download and Rapid Video Editing. Windows Video Converter supports video conversion to 1000 formats at a rate of 30 times faster without reducing the quality. Download and convert video online. Cut, Cut, Add Text, Effect, Appendix, And More.
Features of Windows Video Converter
	The conversion of video to over 1000 formats.
	The speed is 30 times faster.
	The quality is not reduced.
	Download...
</description></item><item><title>Download Secret Video Downloader 1.0.6</title><pubDate> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 19:56:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secret-video-downloader-13775.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secret-video-downloader-13775.html
</guid><description>
Secret Video Downloader is a free application designed to facilitate easy video downloading from various websites. It leverages the yt-dlp command line program to efficiently grab video content, allowing users to save videos in the highest quality available without complicated installation or configuration. The tool has a minimalist interface focused on simplicity: the user pastes the video URL into the built-in browser, clicks the Download button, and the video is added to the download...
</description></item><item><title>Download Windows Video Editor Pro 2025 v10.0.3.5</title><pubDate> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 19:56:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-video-editor-6420.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-video-editor-6420.html
</guid><description>
Windows Video Editor is the 2021 editing tool collection that has everything you need to edit your video file. You can easily Cut, Crop, Rotate, Split, Trim or Join your videos. You can add Effects, Text, Animations, Watermarks, Subtitles, Music to your videos. You can adjust video speed, brightness, contrast, saturation or anything else of your videos. You can do almost everything to edit your videos! And You can edit videos in batch!
Features of Windows Video Editor
	With Windows...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ocenaudio 3.16.4</title><pubDate> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 19:55:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ocenaudio-837.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ocenaudio-837.html
</guid><description>
Ocenaudio: software for windows, this is the sound editing easy, fast and powerful. ocenaudio is a program for audio editing multi-platform, easy to use, fast and functional. This is the ideal software for those who need to edit and analyze audio files.
Ocenaudio - editor powerful audio for windows
This software is based on Ocen Framework , a powerful library developed to simplify and standardize the development of application analysis and sound processing on many platforms.
Features...
</description></item><item><title>Download Alternate Password DB 3.670</title><pubDate> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 19:55:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-alternate-password-db-2723.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-alternate-password-db-2723.html
</guid><description>
Alternate Password DB is a program to securely store the password and your PIN code. With just one password, you have access to the encrypted data (BLOWFISH 256 bit). The password file can be converted into an executable file, can be transferred on a USB memory stick or other removable drive without the need to install this program.
Alternate Password DB - password storage safe
You can also configure the program locks itself after a period of time (main password will be required...
</description></item><item><title>Download ClassicDesktopClock 5.17</title><pubDate> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 19:54:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-classicdesktopclock-3986.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-classicdesktopclock-3986.html
</guid><description>
ClassicDesktopClock is a simple clock, and can customize allow you to see the current time on the computer to your desk. The program provides a number of topics that will help you change the look just by a click of the mouse. In addition, you can set the clock anywhere you want on your screen. ClassicDesktopClock comes with a variety of features and rich options, such as transparency, the ability to show or hide the second hand, some themes, multiple language support, portability, etc.,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Any MP3 Converter 2025 v10.0.3.5</title><pubDate> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 19:54:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-mp3-converter-11983.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-mp3-converter-11983.html
</guid><description>
Any MP3 Converter is a user-friendly tool that supports many audio formats, including MP3. It allows you to convert audio files quickly and easily. It supports more than 1000 Video/Audio Formats. 30 times faster speed and no quality loss. Optimized for high quality HD Video and large Video files. Download and convert online videos like YouTube, Vimeo, etc. Trim/Join/Crop/Rotate, Add Text, Effects, Subtitles and more...
Main features of Any MP3 Converter
	MP3 converter allows you to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Win Screen Recorder 2025 v10.0.3.5</title><pubDate> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 19:54:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-win-screen-recorder-7793.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-win-screen-recorder-7793.html
</guid><description>
Win Screen Recorder 2022 is a convenient and easy to use screen recording software that allows you to record any part of the screen, record HD video and audio, and capture screenshot any time you want.
Features of Win Screen Recorder
	Includes Filmmaker and Video Editor.
	It's easy to create your own movies from images and video clips.
	Add Music, Text, Animation, Effects and Mosaic to your videos.
	Cut, join, crop and rotate your video.
	Publish your video to the Internet or DVD.
</description></item><item><title>Download DesktopDigitalClock 6.17</title><pubDate> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 19:53:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopdigitalclock-4114.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopdigitalclock-4114.html
</guid><description>
DesktopDigitalClock is a program that desktop clock digital simply and beautifully with the theme and different custom for all MS-OS was inspired from the lock screen! Be made according to numerous requests of users, with the idea of the clock lock screen appearance in Windows 10 / 8.1 after login, display the time and date when the log in the left corner, to the analog clock to appear on desktop Windows.
DesktopDigitalClock - the clock on the computer
The basic function: high...
</description></item><item><title>Download Total Uninstaller 2026 v3.0.0.802</title><pubDate> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 19:53:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-total-uninstaller-5527.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-total-uninstaller-5527.html
</guid><description>
Total Uninstaller is a software that completely removes unwanted applications from your PC with just a few clicks. 3 simple steps allow you to effectively complete the deletion: select the program, Run the Analysis and Delete. Completely uninstall all files, registry entries and configuration related to the removal program and you will get an automatic and fast removal process. Completely remove stubborn files and data, especially those that always lurk in your hard drive.
Total...
</description></item><item><title>Download Windows Movie Maker 2025 v10.0.3.5</title><pubDate> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 19:52:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-movie-maker-4542.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-movie-maker-4542.html
</guid><description>
Windows Movie Maker is a video editing app that allows you to transform images, audio files and short clips into full movies. It accepts all types of media, including photos from digital cameras, flash cards, mobile phone and DVD. With this helpful program, it's easy to sort and select the photos and videos you want to use in the next film of his. You can also add text, transitions, effects, etc. change as much as you want or let Windows Movie Maker do it for you.
Windows Movie Maker -...
</description></item><item><title>Download BitRecover OST Converter Wizard 15.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 19:51:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bitrecover-ost-converter-wizard-5533.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bitrecover-ost-converter-wizard-5533.html
</guid><description>
BitRecover OST Converter Wizard is a software to export OST files to PST, MSG, EML, EMLX, TXT, MBOX, HTML, MHT, XPS, RTF, DOC, Windows Live Mail, ICS, vCard, CSV, PDF, Lotus Notes, Zimbra, Maildir, Thunderbird, Office 365, Outlook.com, Gmail, G Suite, IMAP, Entourage (RGE), Outlook for Mac (OLM), IBM Verse, Amazon WorkMail, etc.
BitRecover OST Converter Wizard Features
	Converts Outlook OST file into various file types
	Option to convert corrupt OST file using Recovery...
</description></item><item><title>Download Quick Access Popup 12.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 19:51:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quick-access-popup-984.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quick-access-popup-984.html
</guid><description>
Quick Access Popup  ( QAP ) is a software that provides quick access to files, files, windows applications and is  shortcut manager , mouse and keyboard.  Quick Access Popup  helps you quickly move between FILE, DOCUMENT, APPS in Windows Explorer or file dialog to quickly launch applications, documents or web pages at once 
To launch the pop-up menu, click the  QAP  icon in the Notifications area, press the Middle mouse button, or press Windows + W (these triggers can be changed under...
</description></item><item><title>Download ezCheckPrinting for Quickbook 9.1.14</title><pubDate> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 19:51:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ezcheckprinting-5204.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ezcheckprinting-5204.html
</guid><description>
Software ezCheckPrinting for any business need design and in Czech republic professional. The big business and start-up companies are able to organize payments and print checks, customized from any laser printer or MICR how. Professional has never been so easy.
ezCheckPrinting can support the account and check the unlimited without paying an additional fee. It also allows users to QuickBooks / Quicken print checks on the blank through the virtual printer ezCheckPrinting options (only...
</description></item><item><title>Download KS DB Merge Tools for SQLite Pro 1.23.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 19:50:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ks-db-merge-tools-for-sqlite-pro-10406.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ks-db-merge-tools-for-sqlite-pro-10406.html
</guid><description>
KS DB Merge Tools for SQLite Pro is a software utility that provides a convenient way for you to compare databases and monitor their changes. It not only allows you to explore the contents of SQLite databases but also helps you identify differences and apply filters to detect modifications to tables, indexes, triggers and views .
Features of KS DB Merge Tools for SQLite Pro
	Compare and merge SQLite databases
	Run SQL queries and export data to Excel
	Compare, synchronize and merge...
</description></item><item><title>Download qBittorrent 5.1.4</title><pubDate> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 19:30:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qbittorrent-23.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qbittorrent-23.html
</guid><description>
qBittorrent runs and provides the same features on all major platforms (Linux, macOS, Windows, OS / 2, FreeBSD). It supports RSS feeds with filters download at advanced (incl. Regex). qBittorrent provides many useful features in the download and share the resource on the P2P network, with the ability to support on all operating system platforms.
Features qBittorrent
	Download and share data on a peer-to-peer P2P
	Optimize bandwidth and reduce overcrowding
	Integration of search engine...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wireshark 4.6.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 19:23:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wireshark-56.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wireshark-56.html
</guid><description>
Wireshark (aka Ethereal) is a network protocol analyzer allows you to capture and examine data from a live network or from a snapshot file on disk.You can browse the captured data in an interactive way and view summary information and details for each package. Wireshark has several powerful features, including a language filter rich display and ability to view flow created back of the TCP.
Wireshark - network protocol analyzer
The program can read the capture file from tcpdump...
</description></item><item><title>Download Argente System Repair 1.0.3.7</title><pubDate> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 19:04:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-argente-system-repair-13813.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-argente-system-repair-13813.html
</guid><description>
Argente System Repair is a lightweight utility designed to diagnose and fix common Windows system problems. It scans your system to identify errors in operating system components, file systems, installation files, and other system components, and then applies targeted fixes to resolve these problems. The tool provides different scan modes, including simple scan, recommended scan, and custom scan, allowing users to customize the repair process according to their needs.
System Repair...
</description></item><item><title>Download Macrium Reflect Workstation / Server / Server Plus 10.0.8731</title><pubDate> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 19:04:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-macrium-reflect-1444.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-macrium-reflect-1444.html
</guid><description>
Macrium Reflect is software backup and recovery files, image files, with big improvements in speed, simplicity and strength. The software we provide taiwebs.com 've included 3 version is Macrium Reflect Workstation / Server / Server Plus. Whole our focus is to help organizations protect critical data and business systems, without fuss and budget breaking.
Macrium Reflect - backup and restore files
The function of Macrium Reflect
	Backup tool new: image gradually increases and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Directory List and Print Pro 4.37</title><pubDate> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 19:03:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-list-and-print-pro-481.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-list-and-print-pro-481.html
</guid><description>
Directory List and Print Pro is software that provides function lists and support printing content, quick, simple. In addition, the file list can be formatted, filtered, saved to several file formats and also further processed (delete / copy / move files). By copying to the clipboard the list can be exported into other programs or opened directly in Word and Excel.
The features Directory List and Print basic
	Choose the folders listed in a tree structure.
	Select the folder by...
</description></item><item><title>Download reaConverter Pro 8.0.158</title><pubDate> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 19:02:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html
</guid><description>
reaConverter Pro is software image processing feature with batch conversion and image editing periodically becomes simple. eaConverter also provide command line utilities allow you to process images automatically, thus helping you shorten the time for other work.
reaConverter Pro integrated powerful tool of Uber with many great features. It provides advanced solutions to process and adjust images. Management of the conversion process the base image with the latest version of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Macrium Reflect X Server (WinPE) 10.0.8731</title><pubDate> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 19:02:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-macrium-reflect-winpe-7237.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-macrium-reflect-winpe-7237.html
</guid><description>
Macrium Reflect's image-based backup and disaster recovery solutions have taken another big leap forward in speed, simplicity, and power. The whole focus of Macrium Reflect is on helping organizations protect their business-critical data and systems without causing hassles and breaking budget costs.
Features of Macrium Reflect WINPE
	New Backup Engine: Up to 60x Faster Incremental and Differential Images
	Quick virtual startup of backup images: instantly create, start, and manage...
</description></item></channel></rss>