<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 15:48:00 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 15:48:00 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download GstarCAD Professional 2026.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 18:25:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gstarcad-professional-2041.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gstarcad-professional-2041.html
</guid><description>
Gstarsoft, solution provider CAD creations top the world, will be launched GstarCAD 2019 SP2, is software CAD famous alternative has high compatibility with ACAD. With 27 years continuous improvement and innovation enables today GstarCAD has far exceeded in terms of performance, stability, and the only other important numbers and become software CAD top of the world.
GstarCAD Professional - CAD software top
Optimized version GstarCAD 2019 comes with new features and enhancements to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ant Download Manager Pro 2.16.4 Build 92194</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 18:24:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ant-download-manager-pro-137.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ant-download-manager-pro-137.html
</guid><description>
Ant Download Manager Pro is software support download has the same features as IDM, even it has many prominent features, more user friendly more and have speed download data incredible. Ant Download Manager is a Internet content downloader quickly with support download at video! Function: fully Integrated with the web browsers most popular: Internet Explorer 8+, Mozilla Firefox 32 +, Google Chrome 31+ and the copies of them (Pale Moon, Opera, Vivaldi, Slimjet, ComodoDragon, etc.). you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Office Timeline Plus 13.17.00.00 Expert / Pro / Pro+ Edition</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 18:23:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-timeline-2106.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-timeline-2106.html
</guid><description>
Office Timeline is an add-on very useful and powerful software for Microsoft PowerPoint. With add-ons, you can create PowerPoint documents look more beautiful. With add-ons, you can add the time Line on the project by yourself. Application time for the composition and different segments of the document, your PowerPoint will not only increase the beauty for your work, but also for customers and your manager. The people who created this product is also believe that add-ons this is the only...
</description></item><item><title>Download Net Monitor for Employees Professional 6.4.13</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 18:20:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-network-lookout-net-monitor-for-employees-professional-2098.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-network-lookout-net-monitor-for-employees-professional-2098.html
</guid><description>
Network LookOut Net Monitor for Employees Professional is a software platform to help manage user activity, gives the ability to inspect and control computer activities, as well as record activity on the screen as AVI file. Net Monitor for Employees Professional allows access from remote computers. This feature proved particularly useful when you want to see the activity of each user on the computer, or assist them perform the work on the computer with the mouse manipulation or the...
</description></item><item><title>Download ToolsToo Pro 12.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 18:19:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-toolstoo-4430.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-toolstoo-4430.html
</guid><description>
ToolsToo - enhance the capabilities of PowerPoint with the help of additional yield useful and simple this comes with more than 85 powerful tool. Although it may be considered somewhat limiting and likely even too complicated for some people, the PowerPoint, without a doubt, is one of the best options when creating presentations and illustrations. Among other things, the effect of it stems from the fact that it managed to pack a lot of useful features wrapped around a Office UI...
</description></item><item><title>Download Abelssoft YouTube Song Downloader Plus 2026 v26.02</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 18:17:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-abelssoft-youtube-song-downloader-plus-111.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-abelssoft-youtube-song-downloader-plus-111.html
</guid><description>
Abelssoft YouTube Song Downloader Plus 2018.18.17 Program YouTube Song Downloader Plus will help you search the music and video files from YouTube, after you can download them at. To search for music you just need to enter song name in the required field and you will get results, then you can download all videos and audio files. The program can search the entire album, this function will help to find individual songs from separate albums, because of this we specify the name of the artist...
</description></item><item><title>Download Soluling Enterprise 1.0.1085</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 18:08:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-soluling-enterprise-12670.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-soluling-enterprise-12670.html
</guid><description>
Soluling Enterprise is the easiest way to create and maintain multilingual software, documents, and data. Add Soluling to your development process. It will scan your files locally on your build server or development machine without sending source code to the localization service or giving access to your repository to the localization service. When scanning, Soluling completely separates strings from your files, allowing translators and developers to work simultaneously.
Soluling allows...
</description></item><item><title>Download Yuhan Blu-ray DVD Creator 4.7.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:18:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yuhan-blu-ray-creator-13480.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yuhan-blu-ray-creator-13480.html
</guid><description>
Yuhan Blu-ray Creator is an all-in-one authoring software for creating high-quality DVD, Blu-ray and 4K UHD discs. The software supports many popular video formats (e.g. MP4, MKV, AVI, MOV) and image formats (including HEIC from iPhone), making it flexible with a variety of media sources.
Key features include:
	Supports DVD (PAL, NTSC), Blu-ray (720p, 1080p), and 4K UHD Blu-ray authoring.
	Preserves advanced video and audio standards such as Dolby Vision, HDR10, Blu-ray PCM, TrueHD,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Print Conductor 11.0.2512.15130</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 16:50:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-print-conductor-1559.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-print-conductor-1559.html
</guid><description>
Print Conductor is the software supports automatic printing of documents, text in different formats at the same time, all without opening each one. Print Conductor supports more than 75 kinds of different material and works with all types of printers. With Print Conductor, the printing of large volume of files as easy as 1-2-3. You no longer need to manually open each file, select printer, make settings to print, click "Print" and repeat. Instead, just drag and drop your documents into the...
</description></item><item><title>Download AutoPowerOptionsOK 6.29</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 16:39:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-autopoweroptionsok-1820.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-autopoweroptionsok-1820.html
</guid><description>
AutoPowerOptionsOK is a small program that can automatically turn off your screen, put your computer in sleep mode or switch between the power options. Each action can be triggered based on the absence of events keyboard and / or mouse for a specified time interval. For example, you can automatically turn off the screen if the mouse or keyboard has not been used in 10 minutes.
AutoPowerOptionsOK - power Management automatically
AutoPowerOptionsOK is a compact tool designed to help you...
</description></item><item><title>Download SoundVolumeView 2.49</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 16:30:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-soundvolumeview-2695.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-soundvolumeview-2695.html
</guid><description>
SoundVolumeView is a simple tool for Windows Vista / 7/8/2008/10, displays general information and current volume levels for all components sound activity on your system and allows you to mute and unmute them instantly. SoundVolumeView also allows you to save audio configuration to a file, containing the current volume level status and mute / unmute of all audio components, as well as the audio devices to default, then upload the same file to restore exactly the same file volume levels and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Certificate Manager 18.47</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 16:29:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-certificate-manager-13958.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-certificate-manager-13958.html
</guid><description>
Certificate Manager provides an in-depth overview of your current certificates, allowing you to easily access detailed information. It also provides functions for both exporting existing certificates and importing new certificates, enhancing your certificate management capabilities.
Application certificates are often overlooked by most users until problems arise during application installation. For the average end user, there is little reason to focus on application certificates....
</description></item><item><title>Download Reinisch MetaMass 1.0.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 15:14:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reinisch-metamass-14355.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reinisch-metamass-14355.html
</guid><description>
As a developer, you often receive design blueprints from designers that need to be implemented by programmers. Our new tool significantly simplifies this process by allowing you to measure position, distance, and dimensions directly from provided images. With this tool, layout implementation is not only faster but also more accurate. Ideal for any developer who values ​​accuracy and efficiency.
Features of Reinisch MetaMass
	Simple image processing: Open images, drag and drop, or...
</description></item><item><title>Download BytesMorph PDF Element Extractor 2.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 15:06:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bytesmorph-pdf-element-extractor-14354.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bytesmorph-pdf-element-extractor-14354.html
</guid><description>
PDF Element Extractor is a professional application for Windows desktop computers, designed to extract all types of data from your PDF files quickly and efficiently. Whether you're working with invoices, reports, contracts, or any other PDF document, our tool gives you complete control over what to extract and how to extract it.
The most comprehensive feature set
Unlike competitors that focus on only one or two types of extraction, PDF Element Extractor handles ALL
	Text extraction...
</description></item><item><title>Download BytesMorph USB History Viewer 2.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 14:57:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bytesmorph-usb-history-viewer-14353.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bytesmorph-usb-history-viewer-14353.html
</guid><description>
USB History Viewer is a powerful, enterprise-grade application designed for IT professionals, system administrators, and forensic investigators. It provides the most comprehensive tracking and analysis of all USB devices ever connected to a Windows system, offering detailed forensic information and real-time monitoring capabilities.
View all USB devices ever connected to your system, even after they have been removed. Access historical data from multiple Windows sources including...
</description></item><item><title>Download BytesMorph PST Email Address Extractor 2.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 14:51:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bytesmorph-pst-email-address-extractor-14352.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bytesmorph-pst-email-address-extractor-14352.html
</guid><description>
Transform Outlook PST files into useful contact lists with BytesMorph PST Email Address Extractor - a specialized tool designed specifically for handling PST files. Whether you're migrating from Outlook, building a contact database, or analyzing communication patterns, this professional tool handles PST files accurately and easily.
Supports PST file format
	Outlook PST file: Personal Archive Table file from Microsoft Outlook
	All PST versions: Compatible with PST files from Outlook 97...
</description></item><item><title>Download BytesMorph Image Metadata Cleaner 2.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 14:25:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bytesmorph-image-metadata-cleaner-14351.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bytesmorph-image-metadata-cleaner-14351.html
</guid><description>
BytesMorph Image Metadata Cleaner is a powerful, privacy-focused application designed to help you remove sensitive metadata from images while maintaining quality. This app is ideal for photographers, content creators, and privacy-conscious users who want to share images without revealing personal information.
Privacy-first design
	All processing is done locally on your device
	No data is uploaded to external servers
	Complete control over your images
Supports full format Image...
</description></item><item><title>Download BytesMorph EML Converter 2.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 14:17:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bytesmorph-eml-converter-14350.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bytesmorph-eml-converter-14350.html
</guid><description>
BytesMorph EML Converter is the ultimate solution for converting EML (email) files to various formats, including PDF, CSV, JSON, MBOX, and EMLX. Whether you're a business professional, developer, or individual user, this powerful tool will simplify your email data management with enterprise-grade reliability.
Multi-format export capabilities:
	Export PDF - Convert emails into professional PDF documents with customizable layouts
	Export CSV - Extract email data to spreadsheets for...
</description></item><item><title>Download BytesMorph PST File Attachments Extractor 2.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 14:13:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bytesmorph-pst-file-attachments-extractor-14349.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bytesmorph-pst-file-attachments-extractor-14349.html
</guid><description>
BytesMorph PST File Attachments Extractor is a powerful Windows application specifically designed to extract attachments from Microsoft Outlook's PST (Personal Storage Table) files. Whether you're moving data, recovering important documents, or organizing your email archive, this tool makes the process simple and efficient.
Dedicated PST Processing
	Extract only attachments from PST files
	Supports all PST file versions and formats
	Batch processing of multiple PST files
	Preserves...
</description></item><item><title>Download Schaefer Informatik Case Relation 1.0.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 14:07:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-schaefer-informatik-case-relation-14348.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-schaefer-informatik-case-relation-14348.html
</guid><description>
This application was created to help you, as a lawyer, work with large PDF files and then easily navigate through them. Case Relation allows you to open a PDF file in a two-column format, making it easier to work with the file. Both columns have separate navigation bars, so you can highlight and link text from the plaintiff's and defendant's perspectives, even if they are far apart in the document.
The highlighted text will appear below the open file for easy adding of descriptions and...
</description></item><item><title>Download BytesMorph Attachments Extractor 2.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 14:03:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bytesmorph-attachments-extractor-14347.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bytesmorph-attachments-extractor-14347.html
</guid><description>
Attachment Extractor is a powerful Windows application designed to extract attachments from PST, OST, EML, EMLX, MSG, MBOX, and PDF formats with an intuitive, modern interface. Ideal for IT professionals, business users, and anyone needing to efficiently organize email attachments.
Supported file formats:
	Email files: .eml, .emlx, .msg, .mbox
	PDF documents: .pdf (with attachments)
	Outlook data files: .ost, .pst
	Batch processing: Entire Folder with subfolders
Smart file...
</description></item><item><title>Download Coneno QuikFlow Pro 1.7.10</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 13:58:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coneno-quikflow-pro-14346.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coneno-quikflow-pro-14346.html
</guid><description>
Create flowcharts (and mind maps) without worrying about layout with QuikFlow. With our innovative interactive layout algorithms, you can work as if you were using a mind mapping application while creating flowcharts. Define your structure and the application will handle the layout!
Features of Coneno QuikFlow Pro
CREATE FLOWCHARTS, NOT JUST MIND MAPS
Creating flowcharts is similar to creating mind maps. But without the limitations. Allows for convergent flows or loops back. All while...
</description></item><item><title>Download BytesMorph OST PST Converter 2.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 13:47:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bytesmorph-ost-pst-converter-14345.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bytesmorph-ost-pst-converter-14345.html
</guid><description>
Convert your Outlook email archive (both PST and OST files) to a variety of industry-standard formats. Whether you need to migrate email data, create a searchable archive, comply with regulations, or simply preserve your Outlook mailbox, this tool provides enterprise-grade conversion capabilities.
Supports two file formats
	PST file support: Convert Outlook's personal archive files (.pst) with full attribute extraction capabilities
	OST file support: Convert Outlook's offline archive...
</description></item><item><title>Download BytesMorph Secure File Eraser 2.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 13:43:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bytesmorph-secure-file-eraser-14344.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bytesmorph-secure-file-eraser-14344.html
</guid><description>
BytesMorph Secure File Eraser is your trusted solution for permanently and securely deleting files. Protect your sensitive data with military-grade erasure algorithms, ensuring files can never be recovered.
Military-Grade Security
Choose from industry-standard secure erasure algorithms:
	DoD 5220.22-M - 3-Step Department of Defence Standard
	Gutmann Method - Maximum 35-Step Security
	Schneier Method - Professional 7-Step Standard Random number of steps - Custom multi-step...
</description></item><item><title>Download BytesMorph Universal XML Converter 2.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 13:37:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bytesmorph-universal-xml-converter-14343.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bytesmorph-universal-xml-converter-14343.html
</guid><description>
BytesMorph Universal XML Converter is the most comprehensive and professional tool designed to convert XML files to many popular formats with advanced features and robust error handling capabilities. Whether you're dealing with large datasets, corrupted XML files, or need batch processing across different formats, this application consistently delivers reliable results.
Superior Multi-Format Export
	Excel (.xlsx) - Professional Spreadsheet with Auto-Adjusting Columns and...
</description></item></channel></rss>