<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 11:33:50 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 11:33:50 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Wondershare Recoverit 14.0.3.9</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 02:30:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-recoverits-374.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-recoverits-374.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare Recoverit is a data recovery software that is easily lost at a rapid rate and is used by many people. You will do what happens if one day your data is suddenly lost due to the virus or deleted it, .. Wondershare Recoverit will provide you with an environment to protect important data.
Wondershare Recoverit has all the scanning processes that are divided into multiple types, from the typical recovery of the deleted files that are deleted to the recovery of missing files due...
</description></item><item><title>Download Modbus Poll 12.1.0.2473</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 02:29:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-modbus-poll-3852.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-modbus-poll-3852.html
</guid><description>
Modbus Poll is the simulator the Modbus is designed primarily to help developers device Modbus or others want to test and simulate the Modbus protocol. With the multiple document interface you can monitor a number of slave Modbus and / or the zone data at the same time. For each window you simply specify the ID slave, Modbus, function, address, size, and proportion of poll. You can read and write registers and coils from any window. If you want to change a register, just double-click the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Blue Iris 5.9.9.91</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 02:29:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blue-iris-5656.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blue-iris-5656.html
</guid><description>
Blue Iris is professional surveillance software that allows you to view and record up to 64 cameras (IP cameras, web cameras, DVR / CCTV based cameras) simultaneously and is compatible with the vast majority of IP camera brands. and DVR. Besides. It takes advantage of H.264 video compression that allows you to save hard drive space and reduce bandwidth consumption. Use Blue Iris to turn your existing Windows PC into a full featured professional video surveillance system. Additional...
</description></item><item><title>Download UPDF 2.0.12</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 02:27:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-updf-14160.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-updf-14160.html
</guid><description>
UPDF for Windows is easy-to-use PDF software for Windows! Enjoy powerful editing tools for text, images, links, and more in your PDFs. Customize backgrounds, watermarks, and page sizes as easily as in Word. AI-powered PDF editor and manager that offers a wide range of features including editing, annotating, converting, OCR (Optical Character Recognition), organizing, protecting, sharing, printing, summarizing, translating, and interpreting PDF files.
Features of UPDF
Analyze PDFs with...
</description></item><item><title>Download DriversCloud 12.0.33.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 02:27:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-driverscloud-6228.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-driverscloud-6228.html
</guid><description>
DriversCloud is a complex tool that helps you retrieve full data on your system configuration, both hardware and software, while simultaneously implementing additional maintenance tasks such as installing and updating drivers, tracking hard real-time or BSOD analysis. The incident. This tool does not only accurately detect your complete system configuration but also allows you to export this important data to PDF documents to allow you to easily share them online.
Not only did the...
</description></item><item><title>Download MyPublicWiFi 31.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 02:27:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mypublicwifi-6609.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mypublicwifi-6609.html
</guid><description>
MyPublicWiFi is an easy-to-use software that can turn your laptop/tablet/PC into a Wi-Fi wireless access point. MyPublicWiFi allows you to turn your computer or laptop into a virtual Wi-Fi access point using wireless network technology to share Internet connectivity for other devices based on safety authentication procedures with firewalls and tracking URLs. MyPublicWiFi is designed to be used at home as well as larger environments such as hotels, cafes, meeting rooms, and other...
</description></item><item><title>Download 4KSoftware 4K Downloader 5.18.8</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 02:26:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-downloader-3858.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-downloader-3858.html
</guid><description>
4K Downloader is a Windows application small but powerful to download and convert video in 4K and 8K Ultra HD from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion and thousands of other video-based websites. It speeds up your download by up to 5 times. Consider that most smart phones, TVS, computers, and tablets all support the high definition format, don't be surprised when many users want to enjoy quality content on their device. 4K Downloader is a lightweight software designed to help you grab videos...
</description></item><item><title>Download Helium Music Manager Premium 17.4.538</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 02:26:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-helium-music-manager-premium-164.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-helium-music-manager-premium-164.html
</guid><description>
Helium Music Manager is a music manager that can rip, tag, play, browse, search, rename, burn and synchronize your music with the mobile. You can control your music collection with Helium Music Manager. Stop using time looking for the file on your computer or looking through CDS, vinyl records and tapes - instead, simply enjoy and explore your music! Helium Music Manager can replace the ripper, the player, tag editor and related software to audio your other.
Helium Music Manager...
</description></item><item><title>Download Pazu StreamGet All-In-One Video Downloader 2.8.4</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 02:25:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pazu-streamget-all-in-one-video-downloader-12037.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pazu-streamget-all-in-one-video-downloader-12037.html
</guid><description>
StreamGet All-In-One Video Downloader is the ultimate downloading solution for you. It supports downloading any movies and shows from the most popular streaming sites including Netflix, Prime Video, Disney Plus, Max, Hulu, and Apple TV Plus. The downloader is continuously updated to support more platforms in the future.
Download movies and shows from various streaming platforms to MP4/MKV on your Windows device and enjoy them anywhere you want.
Features of Pazu StreamGet All-In-One...
</description></item><item><title>Download ASCOMP Image Former Pro 2.013</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 02:25:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ascomp-image-former-pro-6131.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ascomp-image-former-pro-6131.html
</guid><description>
ASCOMP Image Former Pro  is a batch converter, basic adjustments can be made quickly and easily to multiple images at once. ASCOMP Image Former Pro is an extremely useful, very easy to use and time-saving, manageable program that is both useful in the private sector and also useful for professional purposes. There are only five functions, but almost everyone needs them every day.
The core function of the software is undoubtedly the ability to adapt and convert any number of images in...
</description></item><item><title>Download PVS-Studio 7.39.99802.2047</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 02:24:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pvs-studio-1480.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pvs-studio-1480.html
</guid><description>
PVS-Studio is software that performs static code analysis and generate a report to help programmers find and fix bugs. PVS-Studio implements a series of check code, it is also useful to search the prints wrong error and Copy-Paste. Examples of such errors: V501, V517, V522, V523, V3001.
The main value of static analysis is in regular use, hence the error is identified and corrected at the earliest stages. There's no point of wasting 50 hours to search for a fault can be found with static...
</description></item><item><title>Download SEO Checker 10.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 02:24:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-seo-checker-2514.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-seo-checker-2514.html
</guid><description>
SEO Checker (A product of genuine VOVSoft) is a tool to analyze all type of web site or personal web page. The software works in many different ways, it can help you discover the content that you have specifically chosen to analyze from suitable site. As the authors write, the program, as this program allows you to plan for your SEO strategy by providing information about the function of it, you will get a set of keyword analysis and tracking the reverse link.
SEO Checker - Support SEO...
</description></item><item><title>Download QueueExplorer Professional 5.0.62</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 02:23:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-queueexplorer-professional-4823.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-queueexplorer-professional-4823.html
</guid><description>
QueueExplorer is a tool indispensable to work with queues and messages: understand and manage your system, find the error and fix it. Or you can use QueueExplorer to sort them by any field available. Because of the sort display the messages in another order with them will be handled, QueueExplorer more columns of Ms Ms # # so you can still see what is processed first.
The features of QueueExplorer
Move, copy or delete messages
	Messages can be handled the same as in process explorer,...
</description></item><item><title>Download ASCOMP F-Rename Professional 2.111</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 02:23:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ascomp-f-rename-6327.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ascomp-f-rename-6327.html
</guid><description>
ASCOMP F-Rename allows you to rename the number of files at the same time. With it, you can assign the file names that mean a large amount of data that does n' t cost much work. Besides, it allows you to find all the files on your hard drive after this without having to send a search group.
Features of ASCOMP F-Rename
	The numbering or date for the entire file collection and name of your MP3 file is only a few clicks based on the ID3 card.
	The function of renaming the individual...
</description></item><item><title>Download SmartGit 25.1.093</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 02:22:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-smartgit-13978.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-smartgit-13978.html
</guid><description>
SmartGit is a cross-platform, graphical Git application designed for professional users to simplify and enhance Git version control workflows. SmartGit supports major Git hosting services like GitHub, Bitbucket, GitLab, and Azure DevOps with built-in features to handle pull requests, comments, and code reviews directly in the app.
Why choose SmartGit as your Git Client?
	One for all.
	SmartGit helps new Git users as well as helps experienced developers work more efficiently.
	SmartGit...
</description></item><item><title>Download Bitwig Studio 6.0 Beta 4</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 02:22:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bitwig-studio-3626.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bitwig-studio-3626.html
</guid><description>
Find new standard in the process of individual work. Bitwig Studio excite you good control over his music, give you access to all features of your production. Streamline course creation of you and quickly develop your ideas into the songs, compositions and music full.
Bitwig Studio - Create your own music
Arrange and record, perform and improvise, or do all at the same time. Choose among the many records displayed. Design your sound with the equipment container commitment. Mixing the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Guardian Of Data Professional 3.010</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 02:22:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-guardian-of-data-professional-11423.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-guardian-of-data-professional-11423.html
</guid><description>
Guardian Of Data Professional is a compact software that provides AES encryption (Rijndael Encryption Algorithm), you protect any type of document so that it can only be read after entering the correct password. mouth! With up to 256-bit encryption, the software meets current security standards. The program makes it possible for you to encrypt your documents directly from the context menu of Windows Explorer! To deliver encrypted documents to your colleagues, business partners or other...
</description></item><item><title>Download Serato Sample 2.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 02:21:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-serato-sample-5811.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-serato-sample-5811.html
</guid><description>
Serato Sample is the fastest way to sample audio. A powerful and intuitive new sampling plugin for maker that lets you quickly find, crop, change keys, and time-stretching patterns. Serato Sample gives you the best time stretching quality on the market. Serato Sample will work in most DAWs that support additional AU / VST * including Ableton Live, FL Studio, Logic Pro and Maschine.
New feature of Serato Sample
software
	Adjust the beatgrids so they are perfectly timed
	Flick through...
</description></item><item><title>Download KeyCtrl Professional 2.104</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 02:20:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-keyctrl-professional-10948.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-keyctrl-professional-10948.html
</guid><description>
Ctrl+C and Ctrl+V are the most commonly used keyboard shortcuts in Windows. They save users a lot of time and work on the PC much faster.
Wouldn't it be great if you could also use keyboard shortcuts for other possible tasks? For example, to automatically insert frequently used texts in an email program or in Word, to translate web page content, take screenshots, or to load the most used folders in Windows Explorer? KeyCtrl makes it possible!
Appropriate keystrokes and the identified...
</description></item><item><title>Download DISMTools 0.7.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 02:20:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dismtools-12200.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dismtools-12200.html
</guid><description>
Inspired by Visual Studio, DISMTools is a user interface for DISM that allows you to manage Windows Imaging (WIM) files and much more. You can use it to uninstall apps, add driver or tool packages, etc.
DISM: This is a tool used to maintain and repair Windows images. This includes Windows Recovery Environment, Windows Setup, and Windows PE (WinPE). You can also use DISM to repair Windows images locally on your computer.
DISMTools: This is a user-friendly interface that allows you to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe InDesign 2026 v21.0 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 23:28:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-001en-adobe-indesign-334.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-001en-adobe-indesign-334.html
</guid><description>
Adobe InDesign is the industry-leading page design and layout software for print and digital media. Create beautiful graphic designs with typography from the world's leading foundries and images from Adobe Stock. Quickly share content and feedback as PDFs. Easily manage production with Adobe Experience Manager. InDesign has everything you need to create and publish books, digital magazines, eBooks, posters, interactive PDFs, and more.
Adobe InDesign was developed by Adobe Systems, first...
</description></item><item><title>Download Power-user Premium 1.7.60.200</title><pubDate> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 19:43:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-power-user-premium-3149.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-power-user-premium-3149.html
</guid><description>
Power-user is a plugin for software, Microsoft Excel, PowerPoint and Word help you to provide more visual content so you can create the spreadsheet attractive. It contains templates, icons, tables, drawings and charts, modern, professional, allows you to build professional looking documents. You can add custom content to your project just by a click of the mouse and surprise clients and colleagues with your skills on Excel, PowerPoint and Word.
Power-user Premium - Plugin Excel,...
</description></item><item><title>Download CyberLink PowerDirector Ultimate 2026 v24.0.1029.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 19:43:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-powerdirector-ultimate-425.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-powerdirector-ultimate-425.html
</guid><description>
CyberLink PowerDirector Ultimate is software editor, edit video and make movies on the computer from a variety of templates are made available, complete with effects, transitions, animations, and music. CyberLink PowerDirector 17 is a combination of video editing software with advanced video editing features powerful. Cblowing need to add your clips into the time line and click on 'Production'!
The tool design video in CyberLink PowerDirector have the ability to customize helps you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare Repairit 6.5.17.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 19:42:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-recoverit-video-repair-3889.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-recoverit-video-repair-3889.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare Recoverit Video Repair is a reliable application that helps you fix the broken video, Wondershare Recoverit Video Repair supports file formats MP4, MOV, M4V, M2TS, MKV, MTS, 3GP, AVI and FLV is corrupt and broken. Great service we provide. It fixes the video that there is corruption in the process of shooting, when done, file transfer, while editing, convert.
Wondershare Recoverit Video Repair - video repair broken
Features of Wondershare Recoverit Video Repair
	Repair...
</description></item><item><title>Download Allavsoft Video Downloader Converter 3.28.5.9427</title><pubDate> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 19:42:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allavsoft-video-downloader-converter-248.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allavsoft-video-downloader-converter-248.html
</guid><description>
Allavsoft Video Downloader Converter software supports download movies, music videos, playlist, sport videos from video sharing website for free like Facebook, Youtube and over 100 video sharing sites.
Allavsoft is many users favorite thanks to the combined features simultaneous transmission of multiple videos and speed limit download video. Besides, the program also supports pause and resume data transmission, to help you interfere with the process of transmitting download data to...
</description></item></channel></rss>