<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 21:33:33 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 21:33:33 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download BricsCad Ultimate 25.2.09.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 23:29:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bricscad-ultimate-3256.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bricscad-ultimate-3256.html
</guid><description>
BricsCad Ultimate is a software solution, CAD powerful and comprehensive, providing both tools advanced 2D and model 3D live smart on Linux and windows platform. Utility that allows you to sort the file DWG in hierarchical structures and allows you to easily assemble their products with the help of a set of tools and ingredients powerful 3D.
BricsCad Ultimate allows you to rotate and move any part of your model to solve all problems kinematics in real time. The program also allows you to...
</description></item><item><title>Download FrontFace Lockdown Tool 5.5.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 23:28:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-frontface-lockdown-tool-6281.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-frontface-lockdown-tool-6281.html
</guid><description>
FrontFace Lockdown Tool is software that allows you to protect and lock any Windows PC to use as a public kiosk terminal, digital signage application or other non-monitoring use. The program allows you to disable multiple features and functionality of Windows to prevent users from making changes to the operating system. This includes options to hide the system tray, turn off the Machine and Log out, disable the Windows key and Task Manager, prevent changes in the password, turn off the...
</description></item><item><title>Download RocketCake Professional 6.4</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 23:26:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rocketcake-professional-2632.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rocketcake-professional-2632.html
</guid><description>
RocketCake Professional is a WYSIWYG HTML editor that allows you to create a website based on the responsive template without coding. Simply choose your template and customize it or create a new design from scratch.In addition to text content you can add images, galleries, slideshows, YouTube videos, Flash, buttons, audio / video HTML5, table and many page elements enhance the other.
RocketCake Professional - design application Website
Allows you to create a website as quickly as...
</description></item><item><title>Download HE - Hardware Read and Write Utility 1.25.09.26</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 23:25:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-he-hardware-read-and-write-utility-4287.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-he-hardware-read-and-write-utility-4287.html
</guid><description>
HE - Hardware Read and Write Utility is a powerful utility intended for hardware engineer, engineer, BIOS developer, driver, engineer, QA engineers, performance test engineers, diagnostic, etc., this utility access almost all the computer hardware, including PCI (PCI Express), index / Data, PCI, memory, index memory / Data space I / O, Index I / O / Data, Super I / O, DIMM SPD, CPU The registers MSR, screen, SMART, physical area of the hard drive identification data, ATA, dump tables ACPI...
</description></item><item><title>Download tinyMediaManager 5.2.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 23:25:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tinymediamanager-1819.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tinymediamanager-1819.html
</guid><description>
tinyMediaManager is a media manager full-featured to arrange and cleanup your media library your. Just choose (s) the folder containing your movies and the program can automatically get all meta data required for movies and program your TV from TheMovieDB.org, Imdb.com, OFDb.de and other online sources. tinyMediaManager download at artwork, film, cast, plot and details of other communication. Each film or program is presented with a unique art background, category, and appropriate...
</description></item><item><title>Download Syncios iOS Eraser Pro 1.3.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 23:24:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncios-ios-eraser-pro-5721.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncios-ios-eraser-pro-5721.html
</guid><description>
Syncios iOS Eraser Pro is this application which helps you to delete data and files from your iPhone, iPad and iPod with 100% irreversible results without effort. Once a successful connection has been established, you need to scan your device so that the Syncios iOS Eraser Pro can analyze in depth. After you complete this action, you will receive information about free space, temporary files, or large amounts of space on your device. Gallery and photo galleries were also checked, along...
</description></item><item><title>Download Syncios Mobile Manager 7.2.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 23:23:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncios-mobile-manager-5943.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncios-mobile-manager-5943.html
</guid><description>
Syncios Mobile Manager is the best iTunes alternative, which can help you manage your vehicle collection in the way you want. Simple to move the song between Android/iPhone/iPad/iPod Touch and the computer.
The features of Syncios Mobile Manager
	Exposition music, bell music, talk books, music videos, podcasts, iTunes U, TV shows, etc.
	Enter a file or a song folder or video from the computer
	Manage the playlist on your mobile phone.
	The duplicate/delete the song on your Android/iOS...
</description></item><item><title>Download MobiKin Transfer for Mobile 5.1.12</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 23:23:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mobikin-transfer-for-mobile-4879.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mobikin-transfer-for-mobile-4879.html
</guid><description>
MobiKin Transfer for Mobile is software that helps you easily copy data from a device (iDevice / Android) to other mobile phones without any restrictions. All the transmission can be done only with 1 click simply and without risk. Switch to a new phone and want to transfer data from old phone to new phone? Or simply want to share something between two different devices? MobiKin Transfer for Mobile can help you complete the data transmission with ease.
MobiKin Transfer for Mobile could...
</description></item><item><title>Download Coolmuster Mobile Transfer 4.1.12</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 23:23:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-mobile-transfer-4904.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-mobile-transfer-4904.html
</guid><description>
Coolmuster Mobile Transfer is a prominent tool to help you move data from this device to another device without causing any damage to the data. Help the conversion easily with the help of Coolmuster Mobile Transfer to help you have the ability to transfer master data between two mobile phones (Click to find out how to transfer photos between two Android phones).
Coolmuster Mobile Transfer is always the best choice of you to sync data between two phones, even when they're running the...
</description></item><item><title>Download RocketCake 6.4</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 23:22:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rocketcake-1697.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rocketcake-1697.html
</guid><description>
RocketCake is WYSIWYG HTML editor allows you to create a website based on the responsive template without coding. Simply choose your template and customize it or create a new design from scratch.In addition to text content you can add images, galleries, slideshows, YouTube videos, Flash, buttons, audio / video HTML5, table and many page elements enhance the other.
RocketCake - WYSIWYG HTML editor
RocketCake does not require any knowledge of HTML or CSS, you only need to drag the page...
</description></item><item><title>Download Disk Sorter Ultimate 17.3.12 + Server + Pro</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 23:21:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-disk-sorter-ultimate-1464.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-disk-sorter-ultimate-1464.html
</guid><description>
Disk Sorter Ultimate is the utility classification file lightweight and simple helps people detect files on most types of drives, as well as manage them according to many different criteria to create more capacity on the disc. This app allows you to search through the 500,000 files, have storage capacity of 2TB. To start sorting, all what you have to do is select a directory, drive or server and click the button "Classification". You should know that you can search for the type specific...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tower 9.3.532</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 23:21:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tower-6598.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tower-6598.html
</guid><description>
Tower is software that helps you build better software, over 100,000 developers and designers are more productive with Tower, the most powerful Git client for Mac and Windows.
Tower Features
	Beautiful new features like interactive facility or Quick Actions and tons of improvements
	Undo everything
	Unique Conflict Wizard
	File history
	Rich documents
	Great customer support...
	Tower helps you master version control with Git.
	One-click cloning
	Automatically store and fetch
	Quickly...
</description></item><item><title>Download ToDoList 9.1.2.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 23:21:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-todolist-1637.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-todolist-1637.html
</guid><description>
ToDoList is an application note and task management with multiple options, set up help you to easily split and track the progress of the work. Todolist helps millions of people feel in control of their lives more and be the leader in a number of organizations inspired the world to believe. Todolist keep all to-dos of I in one place and perfectly integrated with the other tools that I use. It helps me turn everything faster.
ToDoList - management software job
Every day you have to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Premiere Elements 2026 v26.0 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 20:27:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-premiere-elements-03en-3678.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-premiere-elements-03en-3678.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Premiere Elements is a software application video editing, published by Adobe Systems. This is a scaled down version of Adobe Premiere Pro and is adjusted for the edit and new consumers get acquainted. The entry screen provides the option to organize clips, edit and create movies automatically. Adobe Premiere Elements supports slideshows, cut and paste images and videos automatically created just for you and distributed before launch. Make photos and videos look your best with the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Internet Download Manager (IDM) 6.42 Build 47</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 19:44:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-inetnet-download-manager-161.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-inetnet-download-manager-161.html
</guid><description>
Internet Download Manager is the download acceleration software, the best download support now, it can help you speed up the download up to five times, continue and schedule downloads. The latest version of IDM adds the compatibility of Windows 10 and Windows 11, it has supported all current popular browsers such as Internet Explorer, Mozilla Firefox, Opera, Google Chrome, ..
Download IDM with the latest version on taiwebs.com making it easy to download and manage your downloaded files...
</description></item><item><title>Download IDM Retail 6.42 Build 47</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 19:44:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-internet-download-manager-retail-3609.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-internet-download-manager-retail-3609.html
</guid><description>
IDM - Internet Download Manager Retail is a reliable utility and high efficiency will help you to increase your download speed and manage download at better. The program allows you to easily schedule, pause and resume downloads with a single click. Moreover, the application provides error resilience robust and can restart the download at the interrupted or broken. You can restore the download is interrupted due to network problems, lost connections, unexpected power outages, computer...
</description></item><item><title>Download Visual Studio Code 1.104.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 18:35:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-visual-studio-code-3182.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-visual-studio-code-3182.html
</guid><description>
Visual Studio Code is the encryption tool of Microsoft has met most of the needs of the developer. Environment this encoding was introduced to compete with other products such as Sublime and Nodepad ++ . Microsoft, in its new product, has not been released in many years, has provided many features in a simple environment. In addition to the familiar with a dozen programming languages, the syntax and get to know coding language as soon as be encrypted and allows for syntax highlighting, it...
</description></item><item><title>Download pdfFactory Pro 9.17</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 18:32:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdffactory-pro-277.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdffactory-pro-277.html
</guid><description>
pdfFactory Pro is software to create PDF files according to standards in a simple and secure documents secure. pdfFactory Pro on taiwebs.com that support encryption (40 or 128bit) and control access to the PDF file.
pdfFactory Pro has all the features of pdfFactory and adds bookmarks, job order, title a letter and the email function automatically. Only pdfFactory allows printing to paper or PDF without printing twice. Acrobat is not needed for the printing. Increases the convenience of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Photoshop 2025 v26.11.0 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 18:32:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-0010-adobe-photoshop-737.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-0010-adobe-photoshop-737.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Photoshop is a powerful raster graphics editor developed by Adobe Systems, primarily used for image editing, photo editing, and graphic design. Currently,&amp;nbsp;Adobe Photoshop 2025 is considered a graphic design software, creating and enhancing images, illustrations, and 3D artwork. In addition, it also supports website and mobile app design, video editing, real-life painting simulation, and more.
Adobe Photoshop 2025 - Graphic design
When it comes to Adobe Photoshop, it is...
</description></item><item><title>Download Topaz Video AI Pro 7.1.5 / 1.0.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 18:30:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-video-enhance-ai-3733.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-video-enhance-ai-3733.html
</guid><description>
Topaz Video Enhance AI is a tool to increase video quality with this great technology ONE. Topaz Video Enhance WHO wide open your video to resolutions up to 8K with the details and consistency of motion. Until the present, there is no way to re-create a perfect high resolution video from the footage is low resolution. From the family film to SD low quality to DVD quality and more than that, Video Enhance WHO will convert your video into the footage is upgrade clear with resolutions up to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Photoshop Elements 2026 v26.0 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 18:29:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photoshop-elements-0001-5433.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photoshop-elements-0001-5433.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Photoshop Elements is this full-featured program that guides you when you first learn how to edit photos and grows with you as your skills develop. If you're looking for a program that maintains usability and offers plenty of support, then Adobe Photoshop Elements is worth a look.
Creating amazing pictures has never been easier. Bring your best shots forward with auto-generated compositions and smart editing options. Easily organize your photos and share them in fun ways. Cool photo...
</description></item><item><title>Download FinePrint 12.17</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 18:28:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fineprint-276.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fineprint-276.html
</guid><description>
FinePrint is a software support you work in text saves paper and increases the lifespan of your printer. FinePrint is a software connected printer, you can print 4 or 8 pages file on the computer on a page of paper that still ensure the font is clear, easy to read.
With FinePrint works for you, the incidents of printing annoyances will disappear. Below are just some examples of incidents in which FinePrint can fix. Read more part of our Business for the benefit of the FinePrint in the...
</description></item><item><title>Download CoolUtils PDF Combine Pro 7.5.0.62</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 18:28:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-pdf-combine-pro-580.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-pdf-combine-pro-580.html
</guid><description>
CoolUtils PDF Combine Pro  is software that helps you combine  PDF, DOC, TXT, DOCX, HTML, XLS, images  h (TIFF, JPEG, PNG) and  email  as a  PDF  file. With PDF Combine Pro it is easier than ever to combine documents into one PDF file. Now you don't have to use some programs and converters to get a PDF. Everything for PDF Combine Pro to do for you.
Office, fax, email files - get combined PDF in seconds for personal use, commercial needs, electronic discovery, or manufacturing.  PDF...
</description></item><item><title>Download Helium Music Manager Premium 17.4.529</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 18:27:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-helium-music-manager-premium-164.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-helium-music-manager-premium-164.html
</guid><description>
Helium Music Manager is a music manager that can rip, tag, play, browse, search, rename, burn and synchronize your music with the mobile. You can control your music collection with Helium Music Manager. Stop using time looking for the file on your computer or looking through CDS, vinyl records and tapes - instead, simply enjoy and explore your music! Helium Music Manager can replace the ripper, the player, tag editor and related software to audio your other.
Helium Music Manager...
</description></item><item><title>Download VideoPad Video Editor Pro 17.43 Beta</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 18:27:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-videopad-video-editor-pro-268.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-videopad-video-editor-pro-268.html
</guid><description>
VideoPad Video Editor Pro is software edit video from any camcorder, DV camcorder, VHS player or webcam for best quality. The interface of this utility is divided into several parts (for example: list of multi-media, Effects, transitions, Files, Clips, video track, audio track, overlay), which makes everything seem difficult to operate. You can capture videos from camcorder or other devices like webcam or capture card TV and after you have added files and sequence clips to the queue, you...
</description></item></channel></rss>