<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 17:35:41 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 17:35:41 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download DesktopOK 12.16</title><pubDate> Fri, 17 Oct 2025 17:50:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopok-1635.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopok-1635.html
</guid><description>
DesktopOK is software save and restore the positions of icons. DesktopOK also offers a solution small but effective for the user to change the screen resolution often. DesktopOK is not installed and can be executed easily from the desktop, and can be carried on a small USB or memory device to another. Start of the program. The first time you use the program, the program will show you screen license. Free program and license info is only displayed the first time (on each PC).
DesktopOK -...
</description></item><item><title>Download QOwnNotes 25.10.3</title><pubDate> Fri, 17 Oct 2025 17:50:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qownnotes-3178.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qownnotes-3178.html
</guid><description>
QOwnNotes is notes bookmark file simple text (GPL) open source application for GNU / Linux , Mac OS X and Windows of Patrizio Bekerle ( pbek on GitHub and IRC) (optional) activity along with the notes application of ownCloud or Nextcloud. QOwnNote store your notes as plain text files and can be synchronized with synchronization function file of ownCloud / Nextcloud. You can also use other apps like Syncthing or Dropbox . Just write out your thoughts as they appear, and edit them if...
</description></item><item><title>Download Windows Firewall Control 6.20</title><pubDate> Fri, 17 Oct 2025 17:48:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-firewall-control-3395.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-firewall-control-3395.html
</guid><description>
Windows Firewall Control is a application which help extend the functionality of the Microsoft Windows Firewall and provides quick access to the most common options of Windows firewall. It works in the system tray and allows users to adjust firewall simple root which does not have to lose time by navigating to the specific part of the firewall.
Windows Firewall Control - firewall App for windows
It runs in the system tray and allows user to control the firewall easily without having to...
</description></item><item><title>Download TreeSize Professional 9.6.1.2156</title><pubDate> Fri, 17 Oct 2025 17:48:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-treesize-professional-390.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-treesize-professional-390.html
</guid><description>
TreeSize Pro is a software to manage hard disk space powerfully and flexibly for Windows 2003/2008 / XP / Vista / 7/8/10. TreeSize will find out which directory the largest on your drives and recover megabytes on disk. TreeSize Professional shows you the size, allocated and wasted space, number of files, 3D charts, last accessed date, file owner and permissions, the speed NTFS compression and much more information for several folders or drives you choose. It also lets you search drives,...
</description></item><item><title>Download VMware InstallBuilder Enterprise 25.10.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 17 Oct 2025 17:47:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vmware-installbuilder-enterprise-6055.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vmware-installbuilder-enterprise-6055.html
</guid><description>
VMware InstallBuilder Enterprise  is a development tool for building cross-platform installers for desktop and server software. With InstallBuilder, you can quickly create professional, dynamic installers for Linux, Windows, Mac OS X, Solaris, and other platforms from a project file and build environment. In addition to the installer, InstallBuilder will create RPM and Debian packages and rich CD / DVD. The automatic update function makes it easy to deliver updates directly to users...
</description></item><item><title>Download Calibre 8.13.0 + Portable</title><pubDate> Fri, 17 Oct 2025 17:47:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-calibre-1669.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-calibre-1669.html
</guid><description>
Calibre  is an eBook library management application that allows you to manage your eBook collection, convert eBooks between different formats, Sync with popular e-reading devices and read your e-books with included viewer. You can sort books by author, title, date and other details, download meta information and book covers, add personalized tags and comments, and view your images in the cover display.
Collection of essential tools for adding metadata editing books or managing your...
</description></item><item><title>Download Reuschtools CopyWin 4.72</title><pubDate> Fri, 17 Oct 2025 17:47:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reuschtools-copywin-14136.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reuschtools-copywin-14136.html
</guid><description>
Reuschtools CopyWin is a versatile program designed to copy the contents of your Windows drive, including all files and programs, to another drive, USB or MicroSD card. This is especially useful for upgrading or replacing storage hardware, as it simplifies the migration process. The tool does not require installation; it can be used by running the executable file, but requires administrative rights to operate. CopyWin also offers features like incremental backups after the initial backup,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Calcpad 7.4.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 17 Oct 2025 17:46:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-calcpad-12576.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-calcpad-12576.html
</guid><description>
Calcpad is free software for mathematical and engineering calculations. It is a flexible and modern programmable calculator with Html report generator. Calcpad uses a simple programming language that is fast and easy to learn. It does not require any special programming skills, which makes it suitable for engineers without any computer programming background. You can create calculation notes simply by writing your formula and text, enclosed in 'quotation marks'.
The program includes...
</description></item><item><title>Download RealPlayer RealTimes 24.0.4.303</title><pubDate> Fri, 17 Oct 2025 17:45:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-realplayer-cloud-3927.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-realplayer-cloud-3927.html
</guid><description>
RealPlayer Cloud is a simple way to move, watch and share your clips and make sure that it will play correctly on a TV, smart phone and computer bảngRealPlayer Cloud allows you to move, watch and share your videos. When you are sharing video with friends and family, they will be able to play them on any gadget or operating system, without needing to download at app RealPlayer Cloud. No longer worry about format or encoding videos, or carrying HDMI and USB to link the extensions together...
</description></item><item><title>Download 4KSoftware 4K Downloader 5.18.5</title><pubDate> Fri, 17 Oct 2025 17:45:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-downloader-3858.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-downloader-3858.html
</guid><description>
4K Downloader is a Windows application small but powerful to download and convert video in 4K and 8K Ultra HD from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion and thousands of other video-based websites. It speeds up your download by up to 5 times. Consider that most smart phones, TVS, computers, and tablets all support the high definition format, don't be surprised when many users want to enjoy quality content on their device. 4K Downloader is a lightweight software designed to help you grab videos...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Downloader 9.17.9</title><pubDate> Fri, 17 Oct 2025 17:44:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html
</guid><description>
YTD Youtube Downloader is an application that reliable and intuitive, allowing you to quickly download YouTube videos and save them to your computer. You can also convert the media files to the format desired video or extract audio streams and save separately. YTD Youtube Downloader lets you save your favorite clips of yourself from Youtube, Facebook, Vimeo and Dailymotion to your desktop. The software supports URLS from many web site hosting, multimedia and allows you to download desired...
</description></item><item><title>Download QuarkXPress 2026 v22.0.0.58101</title><pubDate> Fri, 17 Oct 2025 17:43:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quarkxpress-259.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quarkxpress-259.html
</guid><description>
QuarkXPress  is the leading graphic design and page layout software for creative professionals used by hundreds of thousands of users worldwide and highly rated for quality and performance in digital and printed products.
QuarkXPress software provides users with all the tools to design publications in both text and electronic formats such as books, newspapers and magazines, which can then be easily transmitted and shared. through many media. This software provides a graphical interface...
</description></item><item><title>Download O&amp;amp;O Defrag Pro 30.0.1069</title><pubDate> Fri, 17 Oct 2025 17:43:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-o-o-defrag-pro-149.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-o-o-defrag-pro-149.html
</guid><description>
O&amp;amp;O Defrag Pro is the professional software has the ability to defragment the hard disk and can work with the file system different from FAT / 32 to NTFS / 5, and support for the different arrays Volume / Stripe Sets. You can also set the schedule which O &amp;amp; O Defrag will be booted and perform a number of manipulation certain. Regular defragmentation of the disk partition optimized performance of your computer. The user interface is very easy to use. It has a ribbon bar displays all...
</description></item><item><title>Download O&amp;amp;O Defrag Server 30.0.1069</title><pubDate> Fri, 17 Oct 2025 17:43:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-defrag-server-2521.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-defrag-server-2521.html
</guid><description>
O&amp;amp;O Defrag Server professional software has the ability to defragment the hard disk and can work with the file system different from FAT / 32 to NTFS / 5, and support for the different arrays Volume / Stripe Sets. You can also set the schedule which O &amp;amp; O Defrag will be booted and perform a number of manipulation certain. Regular defragmentation of the disk partition optimized performance of your computer. The user interface is very easy to use. It has a ribbon bar displays all the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Coder Technologies Coder 2.26.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 17 Oct 2025 17:41:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coder-oss-enterprise-8726.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coder-oss-enterprise-8726.html
</guid><description>
Coder OSS Enterprise is a development platform that provides a complete cloud-based solution for software development, testing and deployment. It is designed to simplify the software development process by providing developers with a collaborative and streamlined environment.
Coder offloads development from local workstations to your on-premises infrastructure and public cloud. Boost developer productivity with powerful server resources and instant integration. Keep the code and data...
</description></item><item><title>Download Imagiro Piano 2.2.300</title><pubDate> Fri, 17 Oct 2025 17:40:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-imagiro-piano-9987.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-imagiro-piano-9987.html
</guid><description>
Imagiro Piano is a virtual piano instrument packed with lofi character. combines gentle, intimate piano recordings with creative processing. Recorded in the bedroom and pulled from extensive internet repositories, the imagiro's piano delivers piano sounds with flawless beauty. Use loops and inversions to create lush frozen piano sounds, or use the ADSR controls to turn a celeste into an EDM strum.
Features of Imagiro Piano
	loop mode for infinite intimacy
	reverse mode for mellower...
</description></item><item><title>Download TubeMate Downloader 5.23.5</title><pubDate> Fri, 17 Oct 2025 17:39:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubemate-downloader-4250.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubemate-downloader-4250.html
</guid><description>
TubeMate Downloader is a smart application that lets you download any clip you want from the website hosting the main video and convert them in when download at or then. If you need a simple and effective tool to download videos, you can give it a try. With TubeMate Downloader, you can directly drag and drop video link from your browser into the drop-down box or application window to start downloading. You don't even need to copy and paste the video URL.
TubeMate Downloader - Support...
</description></item><item><title>Download 3C All-in-One Toolbox 3.1.2c</title><pubDate> Fri, 17 Oct 2025 17:11:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-3c-all-in-one-toolbox-8399.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-3c-all-in-one-toolbox-8399.html
</guid><description>
3C All-in-One Toolbox combines many features into one giant toolbox with a modern and easy-to-use interface. All the tools you need to monitor, control and fine-tune all your Android devices. This app uses the Accessibility service to help you stop the app on non-rooted devices but will never collect any information.
Features of 3C All-in-One Toolbox
	Device Manager offers very powerful configurations, task scheduling, and device watchdogs that you can find to optimize performance and...
</description></item><item><title>Download PC Remote 8.1.4</title><pubDate> Fri, 17 Oct 2025 17:11:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pc-remote-10934.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pc-remote-10934.html
</guid><description>
Enhance your PC experience with Monect PC Remote, a flexible and free application designed to give you full control of your computer, whether you're nearby or miles away .
Main features:
	Enhanced Gaming: Immerse yourself in PC gaming with customizable button layouts and built-in sensors. Adjust them to your preferences for the best gaming experience.
	Real-time screen and camera sharing: Seamlessly share your PC screen and camera feed with your smartphone. Experience your PC as if it...
</description></item><item><title>Download AC Universal Remote Control 1.2.7</title><pubDate> Fri, 17 Oct 2025 17:10:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ac-universal-remote-control-10081.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ac-universal-remote-control-10081.html
</guid><description>
Agree that it would be great if you could control almost all the devices in your home with the help of one of your smartphones or tablets! Remote controls for TVs, robot vacuums or other smart devices are no longer a surprise, but what about universal remote controls for air conditioners (ACs)? Try our app and we will change the way you think about this technique!
Download our application based on Android now and you can throw in the farthest box the standard remote control from the air...
</description></item><item><title>Download WiFi Direct + 10.0.18</title><pubDate> Fri, 17 Oct 2025 17:10:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wifi-direct-10153.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wifi-direct-10153.html
</guid><description>
Wi-Fi Direct is a Wi-Fi standard for peer-to-peer wireless connections that allows two devices to establish a direct Wi-Fi connection without the need for an intermediate wireless access point, router, or Internet connection.
Features of WiFi Direct +
	Fast
	Completely free, no intrusive ads.
	Supports all file transfers.
	Supports multiple file transfers.
	Supports folder transfer.
	Supports file transfer to and from external sdcard.
	Tested on many devices.
	Advanced file chooser.
</description></item><item><title>Download Duolingo: language lessons 6.52.3</title><pubDate> Fri, 17 Oct 2025 17:09:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-duolingo-language-lessons-8265.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-duolingo-language-lessons-8265.html
</guid><description>
Duolingo is a popular language learning app that offers interactive lessons to help users learn new languages. This application offers many languages for you to choose from, including Spanish, French, German, Italian, Portuguese, Chinese, Japanese and many more.
This app offers an gamified learning experience with interactive lessons, exercises, and quizzes designed to help users learn new words, phrases, and grammar rules. This app is designed to be easy to use and suitable for people...
</description></item><item><title>Download Flowx: Weather Map Forecast 4.128</title><pubDate> Fri, 17 Oct 2025 17:09:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-flowx-weather-map-forecast-8535.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-flowx-weather-map-forecast-8535.html
</guid><description>
Visualize forecasts anywhere in the world with unique Flowx weather maps and charts. Move your finger across the screen to control the forecast animation over time. Choose data according to your needs from over 30 data types and several forecast models, including GFS, GDPS, NAM, HRRR, ICON, ICON-EU, APERGE, AROME, HIRLAM, COSMO, RDPS &amp;amp; HRDPS. Use Flowx for weather planning, for aviation, fishing, boating, surfing, cycling, hiking, photography, storm tracking, or anyone interested in...
</description></item><item><title>Download FlexCalc: Linked Calculations 2.4.0-2</title><pubDate> Fri, 17 Oct 2025 17:09:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-calc-smart-calculator-9299.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-calc-smart-calculator-9299.html
</guid><description>
Does your calculator have features such as: touch to edit numbers and operators, reuse previous calculation results for the next calculation, share and store results with a note-taking application? Calc can do all of that. Calc is a special calculation application. It is the smartest and most powerful to date. In addition, the interface is designed to be user-friendly with a flat style and more beautiful themes.
Calc Features: Smart Calculator
	Compute numbers using operators and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Compass 6.2.6</title><pubDate> Fri, 17 Oct 2025 17:09:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-compass-11090.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-compass-11090.html
</guid><description>
The magnetic compass has the function of correcting magnetic field deviation for the best accuracy. A compass is an instrument used for navigation and orientation that shows the direction relative to geographical North. Geographic North is calculated based on magnetic North and magnetic field declination at your current location. In some parts of the world, the magnetic North pole can be up to 20 degrees away from the geographical North pole.
Compass Features
	Use GPS or Network...
</description></item></channel></rss>