<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 13:49:00 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 13:49:00 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Python 3.14.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Dec 2025 16:48:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-python-4355.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-python-4355.html
</guid><description>
Python is a programming language high-level for the purpose of programming multi-function, due to Guido van Rossum created and first launched in 1991. Python is designed with strong advantages is easy to read, easy to learn and easy to remember. Python is a language can form very bright, clear structure, convenient for new people to learn programming. Python fully create a dynamic and user mechanisms to allocate the memory automatically; so it is similar to Perl, Ruby, Scheme, Smalltalk,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Softwarenetz Invoice Rechnung 11.26</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Dec 2025 16:48:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-softwarenetz-invoice-5588.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-softwarenetz-invoice-5588.html
</guid><description>
Softwarenetz Invoice is a useful program for self-employed, freelancers and small companies who are in need of a simple and user-friendly program for invoicing. The invoice program contains the complete address / customer database. You can see at a glance all invoices, payments and reminders for a particular customer. The memo field gives you the opportunity to enter customer specific information. Importing existing client from csv file is also included.
You can print your invoice on your...
</description></item><item><title>Download DBF Viewer 2000 v8.92</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Dec 2025 16:47:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbf-viewer-2000-7869.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbf-viewer-2000-7869.html
</guid><description>
DBF Viewer 2000 is a fast, efficient solution for viewing and editing all types of DBF files. It can handle files from dBase, Visual dBase, Foxpro, Visual FoxPro and Clipper, just to name a few, with performance that easily rivals expensive professional database utilities. DBF Viewer 2000 is extremely fast, does any task, just one simple query and cleanup copy to export data at lightning speed.
With DBF Editor's simple, dynamically generated visual dialogs, you can easily view the...
</description></item><item><title>Download BrightVPN 1.572.298</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Dec 2025 16:47:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-brightvpn-8960.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-brightvpn-8960.html
</guid><description>
BrightVPN is a virtual private network (VPN) service that provides users with a private and secure internet browsing experience. The service uses encryption and tunneling protocols to protect users' online activities and personal data from being intercepted or tracked by third parties.
BrightVPN frees you from restrictions or censorship by unblocking any website from 150+ countries, connecting you to the Internet for free from anywhere. In addition, Bright VPN protects your internet...
</description></item><item><title>Download Monkeys Audio 11.89</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Dec 2025 16:46:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-monkeys-audio-949.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-monkeys-audio-949.html
</guid><description>
Monkey\'s Audio is software that compresses digital music without loss of quality. Supports high quality WAV files and CD ripping. Monkeys Audio will compress .wav tracks into .ape files to reduce their size without loss of sound quality, decompress .ape, convert files, check file integrity and manage tags.
Unlike traditional methods like MP3 and OGG, which permanently remove quality to save space, Monkey\'s Audio only creates perfect copies with the same sound quality as the originals....
</description></item><item><title>Download MapInfo Pro 2023.2.231</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Dec 2025 16:46:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mapinfo-pro-1872.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mapinfo-pro-1872.html
</guid><description>
MapInfo Pro is the software helps the business analysts and GIS experts get new insights about their markets, by sharing the map and the rich information to improve decision-making strategies. MapInfo Pro is an application that analyzes geography and mapping strong provider of space solutions geography. MapInfo Pro help you presented the results his business in a new way, more intuitive. It clearly demonstrates the relationship between geography and data, thanks to the map and detailed...
</description></item><item><title>Download LastPass Password Manager 5.3.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Dec 2025 16:45:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lastpass-269.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lastpass-269.html
</guid><description>
LastPass is a free software to help manage passwords allows you to store all the login information of your site in a warehouse password cross-platform compatibility only. Instead of remember the user name and personal password, you only need to remember the main password to open the lock the password of his safe.
LastPass
LastPass can automatically fill in the login box for all the account website is your hosting. Whenever you log into a website has stored your vault, the program will...
</description></item><item><title>Download MSI Center 2.0.63.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Dec 2025 16:45:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-msi-center-12314.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-msi-center-12314.html
</guid><description>
The AI ​​era of computing: MSI laptops are equipped with MSI's exclusive AI technology capable of providing completely new smart features. The AI ​​revolution has arrived on MSI laptops. MSI AI Engine automatically recognizes various user situations, triggering appropriate adjustments in performance, sound effects, display modes and keyboard backlighting. Users do not need to make manual adjustments to achieve optimal situations.
MSI Center combines all of MSI's exclusive...
</description></item><item><title>Download Operant Peak Spectroscopy 4.00.538</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Dec 2025 16:45:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-operant-peak-spectroscopy-7976.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-operant-peak-spectroscopy-7976.html
</guid><description>
Operant Peak Spectroscopy for Spectroscopy reads and converts over 60 spectral file formats. It includes library search, spectrum manipulation and many other functions. Mid IR, Near IR, FTIR, Raman, Fluorescence, LIBS, XRF, UV-VIS, Raman and EELS.
Features of Operant Peak Spectroscopy
	Peak can read data from more than 70 spectral file types.
	Convert files in bulk from closed proprietary formats.
	Peak is used worldwide in industry, education, government and military
	Peak has a...
</description></item><item><title>Download SAPIEN PrimalScript 2025 v8.1.222</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Dec 2025 16:44:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sapien-primalscript-6923.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sapien-primalscript-6923.html
</guid><description>
PrimalScript is the next generation of our industry-leading Universal Script Environment. As a system, database or network administrator, web developer, or end-user developer, you need to work with multiple technologies, languages, and file formats at the same time. The ribbon interface of PrimalScript has been carefully designed to provide almost all the functions you use every day on the Home tab. Create scenario templates based on your requirements and business needs to drive faster...
</description></item><item><title>Download SAPIEN PowerShell Studio 2025 v5.9.262</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Dec 2025 16:44:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sapien-powershell-studio-7201.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sapien-powershell-studio-7201.html
</guid><description>
PowerShell Studio is the premier editing and tooling environment for PowerShell. Create graphical tools using PowerShell with an easy-to-use GUI designer. Eliminates the need to manually write hundreds of lines of code. Use PowerShell Studio's built-in templates and wired controls to create advanced GUIs quickly. Create a PowerShell script module in minutes with PowerShell Studio. Easily convert your existing functions into a deliverable module. PowerShell Studio has a powerful editor...
</description></item><item><title>Download Disk Pulse Ultimate 17.5.24 + Enterprise + Pro</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Dec 2025 16:43:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-disk-pulse-ultimate-1465.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-disk-pulse-ultimate-1465.html
</guid><description>
Disk Pulse Ultimate is a monitoring solution change disk real-time allows one to monitor one or more disks or directories, save reports and statistics monitoring disk changes, the change is detected to the SQL database focus, execute custom commands and send E-Mail notifications when unauthorized changes are detected in the file system important.
Disk Pulse Ultimate - Monitor disc change
DiskPulse provides the ability for users to start / stop the monitoring operation disc change,...
</description></item><item><title>Download ValhallaDSP Bundle 2025.12</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Dec 2025 16:43:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-valhalladsp-bundle-10899.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-valhalladsp-bundle-10899.html
</guid><description>
Valhalla DSP has built a strong reputation in the audio industry for delivering cutting-edge solutions and impressive performance. ValhallaDSP Bundle includes many powerful tools, making it one of the top choices for creating unique and high-quality sounds in music and audio projects.
Audio plugins include:
	FreqEcho v1.2.0 - free freqshifter delay
	Delay v3.0.5 - tape/BBD/digital/pitch delay
	Plate v1.6.3 - classic plate reverb
	Room v2.0.5 - true stereo algorithmic reverb
	Shimmer...
</description></item><item><title>Download Argente System Repair 1.0.3.9</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Dec 2025 16:43:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-argente-system-repair-13813.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-argente-system-repair-13813.html
</guid><description>
Argente System Repair is a lightweight utility designed to diagnose and fix common Windows system problems. It scans your system to identify errors in operating system components, file systems, installation files, and other system components, and then applies targeted fixes to resolve these problems. The tool provides different scan modes, including simple scan, recommended scan, and custom scan, allowing users to customize the repair process according to their needs.
System Repair...
</description></item><item><title>Download VLC Media Player 3.0.22</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 22:43:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vlc-media-player-63.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vlc-media-player-63.html
</guid><description>
VLC Media Player is a multimedia player supporting many audio formats and video (MPEG-1, MPEG-2, MPEG-4, DivX, mp3, ogg, etc.) without the need for additional codecs , as well as DVDS, VCDS, and various streaming protocols different online.It also comes with a server, streaming allows you to stream media in unicast or multicast from your network.
VLC Media Player 
VLC Media Player provides a simple interface, with simple buttons control the playback standard and make the most of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Zero Install 2.28.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 22:42:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zero-install-1632.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zero-install-1632.html
</guid><description>
Zero Install is a system, install the software distribution cross africa focus. Other features include full support for shared libraries (with the SAT for resolution dependent), share between users, and integration with the package manager original foundation. Zero Install supports both binary packages and source and works on Linux systems , OS X , Unix and Windows. It is completely open source.
Zero Install - System software installation
Zero Install also has a number of interesting...
</description></item><item><title>Download Revo Uninstaller Pro 5.4.5</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 22:39:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-revo-uninstaller-pro-35.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-revo-uninstaller-pro-35.html
</guid><description>
Revo Uninstaller Pro is software that helps you to uninstall unnecessary software and easily remove unwanted programs installed on your personal computer. Revo Uninstaller Pro gives you the convenience to optimize your device, as well as get rid of all the program files you don't need and slow down your computer.
Traces such as registry entries or program files and folders may remain. Now with Revo Uninstaller Pro, you can be sure that you can clean your system of all these residues,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Revo Uninstaller Pro Portable 5.4.5</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 22:39:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-revo-uninstaller-pro-portable-4370.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-revo-uninstaller-pro-portable-4370.html
</guid><description>
Revo Uninstaller Pro Portable helps you to uninstall the program and delete the unwanted program is installed on your PC the easy way! Even if you have problems uninstalling and cannot uninstall them from control panel, Programs and features of Windows. Revo Uninstaller is an alternative agile and stronger for optional Programs and features of Windows. It has the very powerful feature to uninstall and remove programs.
Revo Uninstaller Pro Portable - Uninstall software
With complex...
</description></item><item><title>Download Syncthing 2.0.12</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 22:38:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncthing-2115.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncthing-2115.html
</guid><description>
Syncthing is synchronization service, cloud and open and non-focus allows you to share and sync files with other computers and gives you full control how to share your data and who can access it. Syncthing does not store your data in any other place, there is no server side Tuesday how to join. In addition, all the communication is secured by TLS and every button is determined by the certificate the strength of the encryption. Only computers that have explicitly allowed can connect with...
</description></item><item><title>Download Revo Registry Cleaner Pro 2.0.5</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 22:38:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-revo-registry-cleaner-pro-12750.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-revo-registry-cleaner-pro-12750.html
</guid><description>
Revo Registry Cleaner Pro provides complete solutions to advanced Registry cleaning. It uses more than 15 separate scanning categories to identify and completely delete invaluable and redundant registry items that can slow down your system performance. You can customize the cleaning process by specifying the items including and the main exclusion, allowing a more appropriate approach to maintain the integrity of the registration book. In addition, Revo Registry Cleaner has four flexible...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDQ Inventory 19.6.2.0 Enterprise</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 22:37:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdq-inventory-1468.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdq-inventory-1468.html
</guid><description>
PDQ Inventory is a software application to manage your system. This software will be able to manage your system by scanning the Windows operating system of you to provide information hardware, software, and configuration for the Windows operating system in your your tools. The tools available in this software helps you can scan the computer correctly.
In addition, the software PDQ Inventory can give you very detailed information. This software application is one of the management...
</description></item><item><title>Download AOMEI Partition Assistant Professional 10.9.2 + Technician + Unlimited + Server</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 22:37:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aomei-partition-assistant-281.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aomei-partition-assistant-281.html
</guid><description>
AOMEI Partition Assistant is partition software hard disk all in one easy to use, offers many features partition manager free. AOMEI Partition Assistant to ensure the full features to create, resize, move, copy, delete, delete, align, format, merge, split partitions.
AOMEI Partition Assistant
AOMEI Partition Manager enables you to expand the available space on hard disk quickly for improve the capacity for the root partition. The instructions move smart can easily support you move the...
</description></item><item><title>Download ZW3D 2026 SP1</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 22:35:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zwcad-zw3d-1782.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zwcad-zw3d-1782.html
</guid><description>
ZWSOFT solution provider CAD creation for the industry, the AEC and MCAD announced that the official version of the solution to top of the brand, ZWCAD ZW3D is now available. ZWCAD ZW3D official is provided by a hybrid technology completely new, and it couples the familiar interface with support systems, 64bit so that users can do more, faster, easier and better.
ZWCAD ZW3D
The features and functions of ZW3D
Notable upgrades
	Is optimization and innovation, the assembly proceed to a...
</description></item><item><title>Download DaVinci Resolve Studio 20.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 22:35:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-davinci-resolve-studio-1072.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-davinci-resolve-studio-1072.html
</guid><description>
DaVinci Resolve Studio is professional video editing and color grading software developed by Blackmagic Design. This is an enhanced version of the free DaVinci Resolve software, providing additional features and capabilities for professional video editing, color correction, and post-production.
One of the outstanding features of DaVinci Resolve Studio is its powerful color correction capabilities. It provides a comprehensive set of tools and features for advanced color correction,...
</description></item><item><title>Download XnViewMP 1.9.6</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 22:34:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xnview-mp-1074.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xnview-mp-1074.html
</guid><description>
XnViewMP "XnView MP" is the enhanced version of XnView Classic. This is the view and convert images multi-platform powerful, compatible with more than 500 image formats, different today. XnView MP easily export images to about 70 file format is different. Similar to XnConvert, XnView MP also features integrated switch at the same time batch file to help you process photos faster. XnView is another version of the photo viewer but with the ability to support formats more limited.
XnView...
</description></item></channel></rss>