<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 21:35:10 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 21:35:10 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Ant Download Manager Pro 2.16.2 Build 91828</title><pubDate> Fri, 07 Nov 2025 18:31:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ant-download-manager-pro-137.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ant-download-manager-pro-137.html
</guid><description>
Ant Download Manager Pro is software support download has the same features as IDM, even it has many prominent features, more user friendly more and have speed download data incredible. Ant Download Manager is a Internet content downloader quickly with support download at video! Function: fully Integrated with the web browsers most popular: Internet Explorer 8+, Mozilla Firefox 32 +, Google Chrome 31+ and the copies of them (Pale Moon, Opera, Vivaldi, Slimjet, ComodoDragon, etc.). you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Any Video Downloader Pro 9.7.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 07 Nov 2025 18:31:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-video-downloader-pro-3731.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-video-downloader-pro-3731.html
</guid><description>
Any Video Downloader Pro is software support you can download video HD 720p, 1080p, 2K, 4K and 8K from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion, Vimeo, Metacafe and thousands of video sharing sites, other. It is a tool to speed up multi-threading can speed up your download faster up to 5 times. This helpful program support download at the same time. Any Video Downloader Pro lets you download multiple videos at the same time. Moreover, it allows you to pause and resume downloads if you need more...
</description></item><item><title>Download Coolutils Total PDF Converter 6.5.0.153</title><pubDate> Fri, 07 Nov 2025 18:30:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-total-pdf-converter-830.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-total-pdf-converter-830.html
</guid><description>
Coolutils Total PDF Converter is software to convert PDF convert PDF files to HTML, DOC (Word), text, Excel, PostScript, CSV or image files. The advantage of Coolutils Total PDF Converter is the fast, easy-to-handle, accurate, does not require Adobe Acrobat, supports many target format and have the option of batch (can convert hundreds of PDF files as well as the single file). Added to this, registered users get command line support to manage the utility with maximum...
</description></item><item><title>Download Luminar Neo 1.25.0 (15875)</title><pubDate> Fri, 07 Nov 2025 18:30:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-luminar-neoo-7194.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-luminar-neoo-7194.html
</guid><description>
Luminar Neo is an innovative image editor powered by futuristic AI technologies that simplifies complex editing workflows and allows creators to turn their boldest ideas into reality. Luminar Neo calculates image depth and generates 3D maps, allowing you to naturally scatter light in 3D across a 2D image. This opens the door to unleash your creativity to bring your artistic vision to life.
MaskAI automates the masking process by identifying objects in the image and creating the correct...
</description></item><item><title>Download Musify 5.0.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 07 Nov 2025 18:29:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musify-4422.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musify-4422.html
</guid><description>
Musify is the convert YouTube Music best can download music from more than 1000 website share music to listen to offline without reducing sound quality. Such as: YouTube, Spotify, SoundCloud, Facebook, Instragram, and more. Easily convert music files mp3 to iPhone, iPad, iPod, Samsung and iOS devices and other Android. High speed and high quality. Musify is a YouTube converter is very efficient and fast, support format converting YouTube to MP3. You can batch convert mp3 files at the same...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ahnenblatt 4.37.0.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 07 Nov 2025 18:29:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ahnenblatt-3844.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ahnenblatt-3844.html
</guid><description>
Ahnenblatt is a genealogy software full-featured, easy to use suitable for beginners and even pedigree has the experience to organize genealogy research by you. Use plausibility checks to find out the inaccuracies in your family and create the chart impressive with just a few mouse clicks.
Ahnenblatt - Create family tree,
Recently, there has been strong increase of the general interest of the public for genealogical tree. Users who desire to track their heritage have many tools at...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cutting Optimization Pro 5.18.16.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 07 Nov 2025 18:28:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cutting-optimization-pro-6573.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cutting-optimization-pro-6573.html
</guid><description>
Cutting Optimization Pro is a cutting software used to obtain the optimal cut layout for one-dimensional (1D) and two-dimensional (2D) pieces. The software also allows you to define and process complex products, such as desks, tables, cabinets, cabinets, bookshelves... Cutting Optimization Pro can be used to cut rectangular panels made of glass, wood, metal, plastic or any other material used in industrial applications.
Features of Cutting Optimization Pro
	Optimize 1D and 2D in the...
</description></item><item><title>Download VCap Downloader Pro 0.1.40.6802</title><pubDate> Fri, 07 Nov 2025 18:27:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vcap-downloader-pro-8474.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vcap-downloader-pro-8474.html
</guid><description>
VCap Downloader Pro (VCapDL) is a popular piece of software that allows you to record video and audio from websites on the internet. The interface of the software is similar to a normal browser, making it easy for users to get used to and work with this software. User just need to copy video url from favorite browser and convert it to VCap Downloader Pro. It will capture the video and make the quality available for download. You can also extract the audio track from any video and convert...
</description></item><item><title>Download MoneyWorks Gold 9.2.3</title><pubDate> Fri, 07 Nov 2025 18:27:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-moneyworks-gold-12652.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-moneyworks-gold-12652.html
</guid><description>
MoneyWorks Gold is comprehensive accounting software designed for small and medium businesses, providing many superior features compared to MoneyWorks Express. It has all the features of MoneyWorks Express plus cost center accounting, multi-currency, job costing, advanced inventory management and more.
Main features
	Cost center accounting: Allows businesses to manage and report on different departments or projects, facilitating better budgeting and financial analysis.
	Multi-currency...
</description></item><item><title>Download Grub2Win 3.0.0.8</title><pubDate> Fri, 07 Nov 2025 17:24:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-grub2win-3177.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-grub2win-3177.html
</guid><description>
Grub2Win is a open source program to dual boot Windows and Linux safely. Grub2Win boot code the GNU Grub version 2.04. Everything is in a folder of 20 MB on Windows drive C: On the EFI system, a few small modules to be installed into the EFI partition of your.
Grub2Win - Boot system, Windows
Using GUI Windows and simple instructions you can install Grub2Win quickly and safely. Notice the boot time and help can be displayed in multiple languages. After installing interface, it's easy to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Speak &amp;amp; Translate all Language 4.8</title><pubDate> Fri, 07 Nov 2025 17:23:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-speak-translate-all-language-13181.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-speak-translate-all-language-13181.html
</guid><description>
Speak &amp;amp; translate provides both voice and text translator features, just speak and it will translate your voice into the desired language and the same goes for text. It is based on real conversation translator where two people can translate their voice and text into different languages, it works like a real conversation between two people which makes it easier while translating. Voice to voice translator helps to translate the speech of both people into desired languages ​​and it...
</description></item><item><title>Download AI Video Editor - VideoShow AI 11.0.2.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 07 Nov 2025 17:23:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-video-editor-maker-videoshow-8149.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-video-editor-maker-videoshow-8149.html
</guid><description>
Video Editor &amp;amp; Maker VideoShow is a video editing and movie making app that allows you to create and edit videos on your mobile device. With this movie maker, creating memes, creating videos or slideshows with photos, images, music, stickers and sound effects is easy and fun. Providing the latest Halloween materials! Young filmmakers can even beautify videos with text, FX, effects, GIFs, trendy filters, transitions or live dubbing in a creative and personalized way.
All-in-one...
</description></item><item><title>Download Unit Converter 2.2.60</title><pubDate> Fri, 07 Nov 2025 17:22:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-unit-converter-8436.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-unit-converter-8436.html
</guid><description>
Unit converter is a simple, smart and elegant tool with more than 44 types of units used in daily life. This is the only unit converter app in Google Play Store that has such a wide range of unit conversion features with a very simple and easy to use interface.
Features of Unit Converter for Android
	Built-in real-time currency conversion with 150+ world currencies and their latest exchange rates.
	44 Unit Categories, 12700+ Unit Conversions
	Smart Tools - Bubble Level, Compass,...
</description></item><item><title>Download All PDF Editor &amp;amp; Reader | Xodo 10.9.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 07 Nov 2025 17:22:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-xodo-pdf-reader-editor-8451.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-xodo-pdf-reader-editor-8451.html
</guid><description>
Xodo PDF Reader &amp;amp; Editor is a mobile application for reading and editing PDF documents on Android and iOS devices. The app allows users to view, annotate, and edit PDF files using a variety of tools, including highlighting, underlining, and adding notes. With Xodo, you can read, annotate, sign, and share PDFs and fill out PDF forms, all while syncing with Google Drive, Dropbox, and OneDrive.
Xodo PDF Reader &amp;amp; Editor Features
	PDF Viewer: Application that allows users to view...
</description></item><item><title>Download Total Launcher 3.3.6</title><pubDate> Fri, 07 Nov 2025 17:22:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-total-launcher-8673.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-total-launcher-8673.html
</guid><description>
Total Launcher is a custom launcher for Android devices. The launcher is the interface that controls the home screen, app drawer, and overall look and feel of your Android device. Total Launcher offers a high level of customization and allows users to personalize their device to suit their personal needs and preferences.
Total Launcher Features
	Customizable home screen: Users can arrange icons, widgets, and shortcuts on the home screen to their liking.
	Themes and icon packs: Total...
</description></item><item><title>Download Send Anywhere (File Transfer) 23.2.11</title><pubDate> Fri, 07 Nov 2025 17:22:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-send-anywhere-file-transfer-8425.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-send-anywhere-file-transfer-8425.html
</guid><description>
Send Anywhere (File Transfer) is a file transfer service that allows users to easily share files between devices, regardless of platform or operating system. This service uses a peer-to-peer connection so files are transferred directly between devices instead of going through a server. This makes the service fast and efficient, and eliminates the need for a cloud storage account.
Features of Send Anywhere for Android
	Transfer any type of file without changing the original
	All you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Barquode: Barcode &amp;amp; QR Scanner 8.1.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 07 Nov 2025 17:21:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-barquode-matrix-manager-8858.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-barquode-matrix-manager-8858.html
</guid><description>
Barcode is a tool to create, capture and manage many types of matrix codes including Barcodes and QR codes. It is highly customizable with a dynamic theme engine to match your style. Try exploring its other features.
Barcode features
Matrix code
	Codabar
	Code 39
	Code 128
	EAN-8
	EAN-13
	ITF
	UPC-A
	Aztec
	Data matrix
	PDF417
	QR Code
Data format
	URL
	Wi-Fi
	Location
	Email
	Phone
	Message
	Contact
	Event
Get code
	Integrated scanner
	Image
	Device camera
Code...
</description></item><item><title>Download Peak – Brain Games &amp;amp; Training 4.30.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 07 Nov 2025 17:21:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-peak-brain-games-training-8236.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-peak-brain-games-training-8236.html
</guid><description>
Peak is a brain training application aimed at improving cognitive abilities and brain activity. It has many games and exercises designed to target different areas of the brain such as memory, attention, problem solving and more. It only takes 10 minutes a day to complete a brain training exercise. And, with 45 brain games for adults and new brain training exercises every day, there's always a fun challenge waiting for you.
Some features of the application include:
	Daily brain...
</description></item><item><title>Download Camera FV-5 5.4.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 07 Nov 2025 17:20:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-camera-fv-5-10516.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-camera-fv-5-10516.html
</guid><description>
Camera FV-5 is a professional camera app for mobile devices that puts DSLR-like manual controls at your fingertips. Designed specifically for professional and enthusiast photographers, with this camera app, you can capture the best raw photos so you can post-process them later and get stunning results. The only limits are your imagination and creativity!
Features of Camera FV-5
	All shooting parameters are adjustable and always at hand: exposure compensation, ISO, metering mode, focus...
</description></item><item><title>Download Speedtest by Ookla 6.5.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 07 Nov 2025 17:20:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-speedtest-by-ookla-for-android-8605.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-speedtest-by-ookla-for-android-8605.html
</guid><description>
Speedtest by Ookla is a popular online service that allows users to measure the speed of their internet connection. The service works by sending small amounts of data to a user's device and measuring the time it takes for that data to return to the server. Based on this measurement, the service provides reports on the user's download and upload speeds as well as connection latency.
Features of Ookla Speedtest
	Explore your downloads, uploads, and pings
	The only Internet connection...
</description></item><item><title>Download FolderSync Pro 4.8.0 build 2020100183</title><pubDate> Fri, 07 Nov 2025 17:19:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-foldersync-pro-8221.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-foldersync-pro-8221.html
</guid><description>
FolderSync Pro allows users to synchronize files and folders between their mobile devices and various cloud storage services, such as Dropbox, Google Drive and OneDrive. Back up music, pictures, and other important files from your phone to your cloud storage, or vice versa. It has never been easier. Automation support with Tasker and similar programs allows granular control over your synchronization process.
FolderSync contains a full file manager, allowing you to manage your files...
</description></item><item><title>Download Storage Space 29.0.4</title><pubDate> Fri, 07 Nov 2025 17:19:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-storage-space-8139.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-storage-space-8139.html
</guid><description>
Storage Space is an APK application designed to help users manage the storage space on their devices and free up space by deleting unnecessary files and identifying large files that can be moved to another location.
Storage Space APK Features
	Overview: A simple overview of your storage space, clearly showing the amount of memory available for your apps and files you.
	App Manager: How many apps are installed and how much space do they take up? Convenient links to uninstall apps and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Floor Plan Creator 3.7</title><pubDate> Fri, 07 Nov 2025 17:19:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-floor-plan-creator-8875.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-floor-plan-creator-8875.html
</guid><description>
Create detailed and accurate ground diagram. See them in 3D form. Add furniture to design your home interior. Bring the ground diagram when shopping to check if there is enough room for new furniture.
Features of Floor Plan Creator
	Projects may have many floors with rooms with any shape (only straight wall).
	Automatically calculate room area, wall and ground; perimeter; Count the symbol.
	S-pen and mouse support.
	3D sightseeing mode.
	Symbol library: doors, windows, furniture,...
</description></item><item><title>Download ezPDF Reader PDF Annotate Form 2.7.1.11</title><pubDate> Fri, 07 Nov 2025 17:19:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ezpdf-reader-pdf-annotate-form-9766.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ezpdf-reader-pdf-annotate-form-9766.html
</guid><description>
ezPDF Reader is the best-selling, best-rated, and most-reviewed PDF viewer, annotator, form filler, and paperless solution and frame-animated multimedia PDF viewer. Share your sensitive documents such as contracts, invoices and literary works with ezPDF DRM Service.
Features of ezPDF Reader PDF Annotation Form
Viewing PDF
	Support changing reading direction, page layout settings
	Support Text Search, Scrolling Direction, Table of Contents, Hyperlinks, Lists (Annotations,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Toolmaps 5.69</title><pubDate> Fri, 07 Nov 2025 17:18:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-toolmaps-12981.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-toolmaps-12981.html
</guid><description>
Toolmaps for Google Maps to highlight, edit and capture maps from Google Maps. Maps from Google Maps are displayed in full screen or immersive mode without any intervening objects.
	You can add and edit polylines, polygons, rectangles, circles and markers.
	You can also add colored text, resize and rotate them
	All colors support transparency.
Other features
	calculate perimeter and area of ​​polygons
	calculate distance between two points
	import / export to kml format
	easy...
</description></item></channel></rss>