<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 21:36:17 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 21:36:17 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Power-user Premium 1.7.60.200</title><pubDate> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 19:43:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-power-user-premium-3149.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-power-user-premium-3149.html
</guid><description>
Power-user is a plugin for software, Microsoft Excel, PowerPoint and Word help you to provide more visual content so you can create the spreadsheet attractive. It contains templates, icons, tables, drawings and charts, modern, professional, allows you to build professional looking documents. You can add custom content to your project just by a click of the mouse and surprise clients and colleagues with your skills on Excel, PowerPoint and Word.
Power-user Premium - Plugin Excel,...
</description></item><item><title>Download CyberLink PowerDirector Ultimate 2026 v24.0.1029.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 19:43:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-powerdirector-ultimate-425.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-powerdirector-ultimate-425.html
</guid><description>
CyberLink PowerDirector Ultimate is software editor, edit video and make movies on the computer from a variety of templates are made available, complete with effects, transitions, animations, and music. CyberLink PowerDirector 17 is a combination of video editing software with advanced video editing features powerful. Cblowing need to add your clips into the time line and click on 'Production'!
The tool design video in CyberLink PowerDirector have the ability to customize helps you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare Repairit 6.5.17.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 19:42:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-recoverit-video-repair-3889.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-recoverit-video-repair-3889.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare Recoverit Video Repair is a reliable application that helps you fix the broken video, Wondershare Recoverit Video Repair supports file formats MP4, MOV, M4V, M2TS, MKV, MTS, 3GP, AVI and FLV is corrupt and broken. Great service we provide. It fixes the video that there is corruption in the process of shooting, when done, file transfer, while editing, convert.
Wondershare Recoverit Video Repair - video repair broken
Features of Wondershare Recoverit Video Repair
	Repair...
</description></item><item><title>Download Allavsoft Video Downloader Converter 3.28.5.9427</title><pubDate> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 19:42:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allavsoft-video-downloader-converter-248.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allavsoft-video-downloader-converter-248.html
</guid><description>
Allavsoft Video Downloader Converter software supports download movies, music videos, playlist, sport videos from video sharing website for free like Facebook, Youtube and over 100 video sharing sites.
Allavsoft is many users favorite thanks to the combined features simultaneous transmission of multiple videos and speed limit download video. Besides, the program also supports pause and resume data transmission, to help you interfere with the process of transmitting download data to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tenorshare 4DDiG 10.6.3.7</title><pubDate> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 19:40:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tenorshare-4ddig-professional-5629.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tenorshare-4ddig-professional-5629.html
</guid><description>
Tenorshare 4DDiG is software to recover data from laptop / PC, external drive or USB flash disk. Recover Windows partitions, such as raw partitions, formatted partitions, damaged partitions, etc. Recover lost or deleted photos, videos, audio, videos, documents, etc.
With 4DDiG, you can recover many different types of data from this powerful Windows Data Recovery Tool feature. No matter what you have lost, 4DDiG is capable of recovering deleted files Windows 10 / 8.1 / 8/7 /...
</description></item><item><title>Download Aiseesoft Video Converter Ultimate 10.9.26</title><pubDate> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 19:39:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aiseesoft-video-converter-ultimate-613.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aiseesoft-video-converter-ultimate-613.html
</guid><description>
Aiseesoft Video Converter Ultimate software is the powerful converter to assist you convert DVD and video to / 3D / video 2D HD with the video editing features and great support iPhone / iPad / iPod and other mobile devices most popular. Aiseesoft Video Converter Ultimate make update of his great to support more audio tracks and music, multi-sounds, to fully meet your needs. Compatible with audio formats and various video (check tracking technology, audio multi-audio / external), you can...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube Downloader 3.9.17 (3010)</title><pubDate> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 19:39:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube Downloader  is a dedicated software that helps users  downloading youtube videos  Favorites on PC for offline viewing. With MediaHuman YouTube  Downloader  you can download videos from youtube website to your computer with  fast speed , with special software development technology that automatically receives videos from Websites, in addition to the ability to download videos from software websites, can convert downloaded video formats to various formats for the purpose...
</description></item><item><title>Download Any Video Downloader Pro 9.6.6</title><pubDate> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 19:38:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-video-downloader-pro-3731.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-video-downloader-pro-3731.html
</guid><description>
Any Video Downloader Pro is software support you can download video HD 720p, 1080p, 2K, 4K and 8K from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion, Vimeo, Metacafe and thousands of video sharing sites, other. It is a tool to speed up multi-threading can speed up your download faster up to 5 times. This helpful program support download at the same time. Any Video Downloader Pro lets you download multiple videos at the same time. Moreover, it allows you to pause and resume downloads if you need more...
</description></item><item><title>Download Chris-PC RAM Booster 7.25.1031</title><pubDate> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 19:38:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chris-pc-ram-booster-1181.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chris-pc-ram-booster-1181.html
</guid><description>
ChrisPC RAM Booster is software speed up your system by managing and acceleration of the RAM in the operating system. RAM Booster will monitor the RAM usage (memory random access) and upon reaching the threshold memory certain low, it will trigger the process of freeing up memory for the new program open while moving at the same time the old programs from the RAM memory into virtual memory on disk.
Chris-PC RAM Booster - speed up processing RAM
Certainly this is a slower process...
</description></item><item><title>Download AnyTrans for iOS 8.9.13.20251030</title><pubDate> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 19:37:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anytrans-for-ios-755.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anytrans-for-ios-755.html
</guid><description>
AnyTrans for iOS is content manager essential fully managed iPhone, Android and content of your cloud. Including all mobile devices, all cloud drives from your iPhone, iPad, iPod touch to phones and tablets. From local disk to cloud storage. AnyTrans has protected them all, providing you convenient management for all data and your files, regardless of whether they are stored where.
AnyTrans is the one stop solution to meet all the management needs of your data. For the first time, you can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Full Convert Ultimate 25.10.1691</title><pubDate> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 19:37:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-full-convert-enterprise-997.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-full-convert-enterprise-997.html
</guid><description>
Full Convert Enterprise is a conversion software database. Full Convert Enterprise create all the tables, copy all of your data. Full Convert Enterprise has the custom features and mapped powerful at your disposal, your data will be moved out of the box without custom. Full Convert automatically adjusted the basis of your data and use copy modes optimized for each separate table to achieve information best possible quality.
Full Convert Enterprise - convert data base
Full Convert...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cisdem Duplicate Finder 4.1.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 19:36:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cisdem-duplicate-finder-6973.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cisdem-duplicate-finder-6973.html
</guid><description>
Cisdem Duplicate Finder is software that supports you to find and delete duplicate files quickly and accurately and retrieve more content on your computer. Cisdem Duplicate Finder uses advanced scanning algorithms to compare files based on content, not only name, time or size. With the advanced scanning engine and you can configure, you can easily control the location and file type that will be scanned.
With advanced scanning algorithms, Cisdem Duplicate Finder can quickly filter out...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cockos REAPER 7.51</title><pubDate> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 19:36:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cockos-reaper-889.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cockos-reaper-889.html
</guid><description>
Cockos REAPER is a powerful software for for windows, chp lets you record, arrange, edit, and display the audio waveform multi-track. Cockos REAPER offers an extensive feature set includes many effects and a sample project. REAPER supports ASIO, Kernel Streaming, WaveOut, and DirectSound for playback and recording. It reads the files in WAV, OGG and MP3 files and records WAV files. You can arrange any number of items in any number of tracks and use plug-in sound processing (DirectX and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sony Catalyst Production Suite 2025.3</title><pubDate> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 19:35:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sony-catalyst-production-suite-1201.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sony-catalyst-production-suite-1201.html
</guid><description>
Sony Catalyst Production Suite is a package tool, create and edit video files can transfer content from camera to processing and preparing to install the tools, organization, function, adjustment and monitoring of colors and the tools to work with metadata. In addition, when working with Catalyst Production Suite in Windows, you can take maximum advantage of the touch interface modern.
Sony Catalyst Production Suite - Create and edit video files
The product information of Sony Catalyst...
</description></item><item><title>Download Geometric Glovius Prime 6.7.0.57</title><pubDate> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 19:35:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-geometric-glovius-pro-754.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-geometric-glovius-pro-754.html
</guid><description>
Geometric Glovius Pro is viewer CAD 3D modern for files CATIA, NX, STEP, IGES, Pro/ENGINEER and Creo, SolidWorks, Inventor and Solid Edge. The work of Geometric Glovius Pro is made exact measurements, cut dynamic sections, compare differences between models and export to 3D PDF, STL and Glovius Mobile.
Geometric Glovius Pro - manager, and view CAD 3D
The features of Geometric Glovius Pro
	Modern interface, simple, easy to use
	Mobile app for free for iOS &amp;amp; Android powerful...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sony Catalyst Browse / Prepare Suite 2025.3</title><pubDate> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 19:34:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sony-catalyst-browse-suite-4860.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sony-catalyst-browse-suite-4860.html
</guid><description>
Sony Catalyst Browse Suite is a tool for viewing and logging platform for all the formats Sony Pro, supply management, reasonable means to help simplify the process of your work and protect your content. Sony Catalyst Browse Suite is a communications assistant that allows you to browse the files from the camera, the machine or card reader Sony of you with a detailed view of the clip individually; view and edit metadata media; see the exact video using source color space, and apply color...
</description></item><item><title>Download AmoyShare BeeConverter Pro 3.2.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 19:34:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-amoyshare-beeconverter-pro-7285.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-amoyshare-beeconverter-pro-7285.html
</guid><description>
BeeConverter Pro is a great application for video converter capable of converting multiple files simultaneously, converting videos for specific devices, handling multiple audio formats and video and most importantly, do all of this with 60x faster conversions. With its help, you can convert video or audio in any popular formats, such as MP4, MKV, AVI, FLV, WEBM and MP3, WMA, WAV, M4A, etc., as well as 4K video.
Features of BeeConverter Pro
	All popular video/audio formats are...
</description></item><item><title>Download Power-user for PowerPoint and Excel 1.7.60.200</title><pubDate> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 19:33:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-power-user-for-powerpoint-and-excel-522.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-power-user-for-powerpoint-and-excel-522.html
</guid><description>
Power-user for PowerPoint and Excel is a utility providing you with a library of templates, icons, charts, maps and diagrams for spreadsheet and presentation. With Power-user for PowerPoint and Excel, you will attract the attention of your audience with stunning graphics will certainly impress.
Power-user comes with a collection of 2,000 icons to illustrate your slides. The icons are vector shapes so you can resize them without distortion and color back as you with. With Power-user, you...
</description></item><item><title>Download PreSonus Studio One Pro 7.2.3</title><pubDate> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 19:33:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-presonus-studio-one-pro-780.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-presonus-studio-one-pro-780.html
</guid><description>
PreSonus Studio One Pro is software production music professional perfect combination between the studio model with the production process according to the beat and loop today so you can bring music ideas to actual sounds. Screen interface, simple, effective contains the number of tracks is not limited to , the editing tools are intuitive and the tools advanced virtual. Spend precious time to create music instead of wondering what to click next. Studio One does not dictate how you work or...
</description></item><item><title>Download MusConv 4.10.429 Lifetime</title><pubDate> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 18:03:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html
</guid><description>
MusConv transfers playlists, albums, followed artists and liked songs across a variety of services – Spotify, Apple Music, Amazon Music, YouTube, YouTube Music, iTunes, Deezer, Tidal, SoundCloud, Pandora and more 125 music services!
Features of MusConv Ultimate
	Transfer playlists, albums, followed artists and liked tracks between over 125 music servicesManage playlists (Delete, Merge, Split, Copy...)
	More than 125 music services supported
	Access DAILY updated music charts on...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter 3.9.17 (3010)</title><pubDate> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 18:03:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-to-mp3-converter-1744.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-to-mp3-converter-1744.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter is the software support download youtube video and convert video to mp3 format fast and most simple. MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter allows you download and convert videos from YouTube and other websites to MP3 format by pasting the YouTube URL into the application. When you paste the URL, the program will display thumbnails for videos and you have the option to customize the title information, artist and album before you begin the process of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Photo Supreme 2025.3.3.8125</title><pubDate> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 18:02:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photo-supreme-430.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photo-supreme-430.html
</guid><description>
Photo Supreme is a software product management professional pictures of idimager. With Photo Supreme you can arrange, manage back stock photo archive of yourself and share them with you here and relatives easily via Email or Facebook. Photo Supreme provides users method to sort images effective, logical, as well as edit and share your photos with friends and relatives in the family. Especially the Photo Supreme allows to work with multiple image formats and support mounting support,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Robin YouTube Video Downloader Pro 6.17.6</title><pubDate> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 17:59:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-video-downloader-pro-2828.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-video-downloader-pro-2828.html
</guid><description>
YouTube Video Downloader Pro is a Windows application professional to download and convert videos from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion and thousands of video sharing sites, other. It accelerates your download up to 5 times. YouTube Video Downloader Pro allows you to download multiple videos at the same time. It also allows you to pause, resume and cancel a download at any time.
YouTube Video Downloader Pro - Download online videos on social networks
Features of YouTube Video Downloader...
</description></item><item><title>Download ElectraSoft Speed Dial 25.10.31</title><pubDate> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 17:59:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-electrasoft-speed-dial-5967.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-electrasoft-speed-dial-5967.html
</guid><description>
ElectraSoft Speed Dial is used as a contact book to store detailed information about all your friends and acquaintats, allowing you to quickly find the number of phones you need and dial that number without having to look into your contacts. The main interface of the application displays a structured table, where all contacts are displayed, along with their short description. It can store a maximum of five phone numbers for each contact number and five different notes, too enough for any...
</description></item><item><title>Download Android Studio 2025.2.1.7</title><pubDate> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 17:59:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-android-studio-3890.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-android-studio-3890.html
</guid><description>
Android Studio is an Android development environment, completely new, provides many improvements and new features compared to Eclipse ADT. This software solution will is IDE the official Android when is finishing. This tool provides many tools and features such as editing, layout, rich set of tools to capture usability, compatibility version, performance and other issues, create a lot APK, build system based on Gradle flexibility, extended support for Google Services, integrated support...
</description></item></channel></rss>