<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 19:50:59 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 19:50:59 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Internet Download Accelerator Pro 7.2.1.1737</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Sep 2025 22:50:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-internet-download-accelerator-pro-234.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-internet-download-accelerator-pro-234.html
</guid><description>
Internet Download Accelerator Pro is software acceleration support download support users in the download file like IDM running on multiple network protocols, including FTP. Internet Download Accelerator will help your computer be file download speed is fast even when the transmission line do not have high speed. Internet Download Accelerator Pro is completely compatible with most web browsers such as Internet Explorer, Firefox, Mozilla, Opera,..
Internet Download Accelerator also...
</description></item><item><title>Download DroidKit 2.3.7.20250912</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Sep 2025 22:50:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-droidkit-6578.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-droidkit-6578.html
</guid><description>
DroidKit is data recovery software for your mobile device, it will quickly scan your phone memory and save photos, WhatsApp chats and files, messages Messages, contacts and more essential data up to 13 categories, covering almost everything you need every day. All Android phones and tablets are supported. Without rooting your device. No tech skills required. No need to wait many days. You can get back what you've lost with just a few simple clicks, instantly.
Besides, DroidKit also has...
</description></item><item><title>Download Vivaldi Browser 7.5.3735.74</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Sep 2025 22:49:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vivaldi-159.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vivaldi-159.html
</guid><description>
Vivaldi is a browser designed for users who have power and offer the option to customize high. You can choose the location of the tabs and the address bar, put the hotkeys for the common tasks and many other features. Also, Vivaldi also provides a number of improvements such as Tab Stacks to group multiple open tabs into a tab, leads to interface less cluttered. Can notes and added a screenshot of a web page while browsing, storing an attachment, and add the URL to easily sort and locate...
</description></item><item><title>Download Vivaldi for macOS 7.5.3735.74</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Sep 2025 22:49:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/mac/download-vivaldi-for-macos-3443.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/mac/download-vivaldi-for-macos-3443.html
</guid><description>
The Vivaldi for MacOS browser does not track users and offers more features than any other modern browser. Managed by Jon von Tetzchner (co-founder of Opera browser), Vivaldi for MacOS is driven by the real needs of today's users and ensures that they have the best tools to browse and get work done.
Vivaldi for MacOS - Modern web browser
Users can adjust Vivaldi to suit their browsing needs them without limiting customization options. Vivaldi takes the browser to the next level with a...
</description></item><item><title>Download priPrinter Professional 7.0.0.2609 Beta</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Sep 2025 22:48:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-priprinter-professional-633.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-priprinter-professional-633.html
</guid><description>
priPrinter Professional is the printer driver allows you to manipulate the output of the printer before being printed. PriPrinter is installed and select the same as the printer driver other. After printing it automatically displays the preview in where you can preview his print, change the layout, page position back, cut them, and much more. Then, you print it to printer or save your document for later use. With PriPrinter you will always be sure his prints will look like. You can measure...
</description></item><item><title>Download TubeDownload Pro 6.29.5</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Sep 2025 22:47:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubedownload-pro-12035.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubedownload-pro-12035.html
</guid><description>
TubeDownload Pro is a professional Windows application for downloading your favorite videos from YouTube and hundreds of other video sites. TubeDownload Pro can increase download speed up to 500% or even more.
Features of TubeDownload Pro
	Download your favorite videos from YouTube and hundreds of other video sites.
	Increase download speed up to 500% or even more.
	Download 720p, 1080p, 2K, 4K and 8K HD videos from YouTube.
	Download entire playlists in just a few clicks.
	Download...
</description></item><item><title>Download Flyby11 1.11.361</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Sep 2025 22:47:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-flyby11-12467.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-flyby11-12467.html
</guid><description>
Flyby11 is a simple patcher that removes annoying restrictions that prevent you from installing Windows 11 (24H2) on unsupported hardware. Do you have an old PC? No TPM, Secure Boot or your processor is not supported? Flyby11 allows you to install Windows 11 24H2. There are no complicated steps. Just run the tool and you'll be running Windows 11 on your outdated machine in no time.
Technical overview
Flyby11 takes advantage of a feature of the Windows 11 setup process that uses the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Internet Video Downloader 7.5.5</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Sep 2025 22:46:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hdapplications-hd-downloader-6041.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hdapplications-hd-downloader-6041.html
</guid><description>
Internet Video Downloader is a small tool designed to help you download video clips from YouTube, Dailymotion and many other similar sites with high quality that can easily run on smartphones, tablets or the latest Xbox devices. After the quick and simple installation process, you will be welcomed by a user-friendly interface without the ability to cause any problems for you.
Although you can set the app start to download immediately, but you can also create a download list that can be...
</description></item><item><title>Download Flyoobe 1.11.361</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Sep 2025 22:45:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oobelux-13956.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oobelux-13956.html
</guid><description>
Flyoobe was born out of the frustration many users felt with the Windows 11 setup experience. Whether it was the mandatory online account, the endless "Next, next, next..." screens, or the incomplete configuration options when you finally reached the desktop, the current setup lacked focus on what users really wanted.
Why choose Flyoobe?
	Simplifies the Windows 11 setup process right out of the box.
	Allows easy local account creation without need to hunt for hidden options.
	Includes...
</description></item><item><title>Download Muziza YouTube Downloader Converter 8.12.5</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Sep 2025 22:45:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-muziza-youtube-downloader-converter-3972.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-muziza-youtube-downloader-converter-3972.html
</guid><description>
Muziza YouTube Downloader Converter is a tool to create conditions for an attractive interface and many features to help you to download video clips from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion, Instagram and other sites. Muziza YouTube Downloader Converter can also download the video UHD 8K, 5K, 4K, QHD 2K, HD 1080p and 720p from YouTube. The app allows you download only audio stream from YouTube and save as MP3. You don't need to download the entire video file.
Muziza YouTube Downloader...
</description></item><item><title>Download Physical Audio Modus 1.5.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Sep 2025 22:44:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-physical-audio-modus-9984.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-physical-audio-modus-9984.html
</guid><description>
Physical Audio Modus is a virtual world of conceptual instruments, modeled with advanced acoustics and physical behaviors. Modus uses our latest research on collision modeling to connect acoustic elements together. Literally, strings, discs, springs, and rattles collide in the air using the algorithm to create sounds that resonate and react just like they would outside the virtual world. These elements are combined in different ways to create three types of instruments.
Each voice has...
</description></item><item><title>Download Vector 35 Binary Ninja 5.1.8104 Personal</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Sep 2025 22:44:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vector-35-binary-ninja-8951.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vector-35-binary-ninja-8951.html
</guid><description>
Vector 35 Binary Ninja is a reverse engineering platform designed to help security researchers, developers and binary code analysts. It is a software tool that allows users to disassemble, decompile, and debug binaries, making it easier to understand how the program works and to identify potential vulnerabilities.
This tool provides a user-friendly interface that makes it easy to navigate and analyze binary files. It includes a wide range of features for code separation, including...
</description></item><item><title>Download Physical Audio Preparation 2.2.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Sep 2025 22:44:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-physical-audio-preparation-9817.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-physical-audio-preparation-9817.html
</guid><description>
Physical Audio Preparation is a physics modeling tool based on non-linear collision and string models. The Physical Audio Preparation is based on a mathematical model of 2 basic factors; strings can be configured as bars and rattle elements. Each voice has a pair of wires connected by a chime that responds to vibrations at each end.
This uses the latest research in collision modeling to compute the sound system in real time. The strings have parameters for non-linearity, dissonance,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Robin YouTube Video Downloader Pro 6.16.6</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Sep 2025 22:43:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-video-downloader-pro-2828.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-video-downloader-pro-2828.html
</guid><description>
YouTube Video Downloader Pro is a Windows application professional to download and convert videos from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion and thousands of video sharing sites, other. It accelerates your download up to 5 times. YouTube Video Downloader Pro allows you to download multiple videos at the same time. It also allows you to pause, resume and cancel a download at any time.
YouTube Video Downloader Pro - Download online videos on social networks
Features of YouTube Video Downloader...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft OneDrive 25.155.0811.0002</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Sep 2025 22:43:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-onedrive-48.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-onedrive-48.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft OneDrive is a client application file transmission to the service cloud storage of Microsoft. If you are familiar with Dropbox, you will find that OneDrive works in a similar way. It creates a OneDrive folder and any files you copy into the folder will automatically be synced and uploaded to the cloud service OneDrive.
Microsoft OneDrive
You can access your files from the client application other on PC. Mac or mobile devices as well as web interface. OneDrive also allows you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Radsystems Studio 9.0.4</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Sep 2025 22:42:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-radsystems-studio-7744.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-radsystems-studio-7744.html
</guid><description>
Radsystems Studio is an application development environment, which supports rapid application development by reducing excess coding time. Through its complex tool algorithm, an application can be made with a number of programming languages from a single codebase. Radsystems Studio allows you to create applications through PHP Laravel, Python Flask, Node Express.js, ASP.NET Core for Backend and using Bootstrap, jQuery, Vue.js, Quasar, PrimeVue, React and Flutter for Frontend.
Reasons to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Social Media Downloader 7.7.6</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Sep 2025 22:42:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-socialmediaapps-facebook-video-downloader-3742.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-socialmediaapps-facebook-video-downloader-3742.html
</guid><description>
SocialVideo Downloader (formerly SocialMediaApps Facebook Video Downloader) is a Windows application to download and convert your favorite videos from Facebook and hundreds of other video sharing sites. It increases your loading speed by up to 500%, or even more! The application has a simple and intuitive user interface, its main functions and features are quite obvious to anyone. , regardless of prior experience with similar purpose tools.
&amp;nbsp;
SocialVideo Downloader
The main...
</description></item><item><title>Download FireAlpaca 2.13.25</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Sep 2025 22:41:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-firealpaca-2882.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-firealpaca-2882.html
</guid><description>
FireAlpaca is software painting Digital free available in 10 languages and is compatible with both Mac and Windows. The tools and simple controls allow you to draw a easy illustration. Convenient tool will be adding this one to the other! Download FireAlpaca right now! FireAlpaca is the utility to create and edit image files, add image overlays, as well as providing many other advanced features, bring an effective tool to help you draw a picture or edit a photo from the most basic...
</description></item><item><title>Download Physical Audio Tetrad 1.1.4</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Sep 2025 22:41:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-physical-audio-tetrad-13938.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-physical-audio-tetrad-13938.html
</guid><description>
Tetrad is unlike any sound synthesizer you've ever used. Developed in collaboration with composer and multimedia artist Gadi Sassoon, the plugin uses four oscillators, routing them in combination through a Quad AM processor that acts as a pseudo-sequencer, a custom-designed particle generator, and four physically modeled plate resonators.
Inspired by Gadi's sculpture-based sound synthesis installation, heard on the album Modes of Vibration, Tetrad was originally designed to complement...
</description></item><item><title>Download Danil Pristupov Fork 2.12</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Sep 2025 22:40:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fork-6879.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fork-6879.html
</guid><description>
Fork is a great Git client app that allows you to keep tabs on every file line so you can know who is the last person to make changes. The simple and intuitive design of this app helps the management of all of your warehouses much easier. The Fork interface is extremely friendly to users. There is a long list of repositories, branches, origins, tags and archives on the left side of the screen.
With Fork, you can also search and open any of the repositories quickly, from the top of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download MSActBackUp 1.2.9</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Sep 2025 20:07:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-msactbackup-5215.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-msactbackup-5215.html
</guid><description>
MSActBackUp is a program to save and restore activation Windows versions: Vista, 7, Windows 8, 8.1, 10, Server 2008, 2008 R2, 2012, 2012 R2, 2016 and Office 2010/2016. Press the corresponding button, check the keys to determine the program and, if necessary, specify the correct key. When this button operation, the process flow activation is complete.
To restore activate: go to the tab "Restore activation", select the folder where you saved the activation and start activate the restore...
</description></item><item><title>Download iTop Easy Desktop 3.2.0.145</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Sep 2025 20:06:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-itop-easy-desktop-7879.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-itop-easy-desktop-7879.html
</guid><description>
iTop Easy Desktop is a lightweight and easy-to-use desktop manager that organizes desktop icons, files and folders according to your rules, helping you Freed from the tedious arrangement of icons on the screen. It provides various practical features including but not limited to grouping desktop items, awakening live search, and quickly accessing icons and files even across multiple desktop sites. desktop.
Untidy desktop If you're not one to diligently organize your Windows desktop icons...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Premiere Pro 2025 v25.5.0.013 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Sep 2025 20:03:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-premiere-pro-0021-1361.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-premiere-pro-0021-1361.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Premiere Pro is the leading video editing software for film, TV, and the web. Creative tools, integration with other Adobe apps and services, and the power of Adobe Sensei help you turn footage into finished movies and videos in a seamless workflow. It offers high-quality video editing at 4K x 4K resolution and beyond, with 32-bit color, in both RGB and YUV color spaces. Edit audio samples, support for VST audio plug-ins (plug-ins), and 5.1 surround sound tracks. The Premiere Pro...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Illustrator 2025 v29.8.1.2 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Sep 2025 20:02:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-illustrator-0016-749.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-illustrator-0016-749.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Illustrator is a powerful vector graphics editor developed by Adobe Inc., first released in 1987. It is primarily used by graphic designers, illustrators, and artists to create high-quality illustrations, logos, icons, and digital artwork. Unlike raster graphics editors like Adobe Photoshop, which manipulate images pixel by pixel, Illustrator uses mathematical formulas to create vector graphics. This allows designs to be scaled infinitely without losing quality, making it ideal for...
</description></item><item><title>Download Coolmuster Android Backup Manager 3.5.26</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Sep 2025 20:01:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-android-backup-manager-4744.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-android-backup-manager-4744.html
</guid><description>
Coolmuster Android Backup Manager is software assist you to data backup your Android phone before actually lost, such as contacts, SMS, photos, documents, etc. in Addition, if you need to restore backup Android phone to new Android phone, Coolmuster Android Backup Manager can help you realize all the requirements of backup and restore Android without any trouble.
Coolmuster Android Backup Manager allows you to backup Android phone to PC just by one-click and gives you full rights to...
</description></item></channel></rss>