<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 13:38:50 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 13:38:50 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download PDF Scanner app - TapScanner 3.0.85</title><pubDate> Sat, 04 Oct 2025 15:49:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pdf-scanner-app-tapscanner-12104.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pdf-scanner-app-tapscanner-12104.html
</guid><description>
TapScanner is a mobile application that allows you to scan documents with your smartphone camera and convert them into PDF files or image formats. It essentially turns your device into a portable scanner, making capturing and digitizing physical documents convenient on the go.
TapScanner Features
	Scan documents, receipts, QRs and business cards
	Document Scanner App - Automatic Border Detection
	Tweak your images with multiple filters to achieve perfection
	Easily manage your...
</description></item><item><title>Download All PDF Editor &amp;amp; Reader | Xodo 10.8.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 04 Oct 2025 15:48:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-xodo-pdf-reader-editor-8451.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-xodo-pdf-reader-editor-8451.html
</guid><description>
Xodo PDF Reader &amp;amp; Editor is a mobile application for reading and editing PDF documents on Android and iOS devices. The app allows users to view, annotate, and edit PDF files using a variety of tools, including highlighting, underlining, and adding notes. With Xodo, you can read, annotate, sign, and share PDFs and fill out PDF forms, all while syncing with Google Drive, Dropbox, and OneDrive.
Xodo PDF Reader &amp;amp; Editor Features
	PDF Viewer: Application that allows users to view...
</description></item><item><title>Download AdGuard Ad Blocker 4.12.71 Final</title><pubDate> Sat, 04 Oct 2025 15:48:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-adguard-block-ads-without-root-8215.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-adguard-block-ads-without-root-8215.html
</guid><description>
AdGuard for Android is the only root-free ad blocker for Android that removes ads in apps and browsers, protects your privacy, and helps you manage your apps. Adguard is designed to block unwanted ads, pop-ups and banners while you browse the web on your device. It uses a combination of local VPN technology and a custom DNS server to block ads, meaning it can block ads in apps as well as in web browsers.
In addition, Adguard also blocks tracking scripts from collecting information about...
</description></item><item><title>Download AI Speech to text: Transcribe 1.34</title><pubDate> Sat, 04 Oct 2025 15:47:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ai-speech-to-text-13800.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ai-speech-to-text-13800.html
</guid><description>
Welcome to AI Speech to Text: Audio to Text, an innovative and sophisticated solution designed to enhance your transcription experience. Our AI Speech to Text app sets new standards in speech to text conversion by combining cutting-edge technology with user-friendly features. Whether you are a professional who wants to transcribe real-time conversations, an academic who needs to convert audio files, or a business professional managing important meeting notes, our AI audio to text...
</description></item><item><title>Download Moon+ Reader Pro 10.2 build 1002001</title><pubDate> Sat, 04 Oct 2025 15:47:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-moon-reader-pro-8577.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-moon-reader-pro-8577.html
</guid><description>
Moon+ Reader Pro is an all-in-one ebook document manager and better designed book reader with powerful and fully functional controls, supporting EPUB, PDF, DJVU, AZW3, MOBI, FB2, PRC, CHM, CBZ, CBR, UMD, DOCX, ODT, RTF, TXT, HTML, MD(MarkDown), WEBP, RAR, ZIP or OPDS formats.
This is a versatile e-book reading application that gives users a rich reading experience, while helping them easily access and manage their e-book library. Whether you're looking to read your favorite novels,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Speedtest by Ookla 6.4.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 04 Oct 2025 15:47:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-speedtest-by-ookla-for-android-8605.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-speedtest-by-ookla-for-android-8605.html
</guid><description>
Speedtest by Ookla is a popular online service that allows users to measure the speed of their internet connection. The service works by sending small amounts of data to a user's device and measuring the time it takes for that data to return to the server. Based on this measurement, the service provides reports on the user's download and upload speeds as well as connection latency.
Features of Ookla Speedtest
	Explore your downloads, uploads, and pings
	The only Internet connection...
</description></item><item><title>Download Super File Manager Explorer 1.5.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 04 Oct 2025 15:46:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-esuper-file-explorer-9196.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-esuper-file-explorer-9196.html
</guid><description>
ESuper File Explorer is a file management app for Android devices that allows users to browse and manage files on their devices. Free, safe and simple, manage your files efficiently and easily with ESuper File Explorer. ESuper File Explorer is a simple and powerful file explorer for Android devices. It's free, fast and fully functional.
Features of ESuper File Explorer
	Shortcut bar: Supports all file operations
	Cleaner: Clean all junk files with just one click
	Disk analysis:...
</description></item><item><title>Download Librera PRO - Book reader 9.0.20 beta</title><pubDate> Sat, 04 Oct 2025 15:46:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-librera-pro-all-my-books-9008.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-librera-pro-all-my-books-9008.html
</guid><description>
PRO Librera Reader is an easy-to-use and highly configurable reading application that supports most popular document formats, including: PDF, EPUB, EPUB3, MOBI, DjVu, FB2, FB2.zip, TXT, RTF, AZW, AZW3, CBR, CBZ, HTML, XPS, MHT and more. With a simple yet powerful interface, Librera Reader makes reading documents a real pleasure. Librera even has a unique hands-free, auto-scrolling music mode.
Some key features of Librera reader include:
Easily explore documents with optional and...
</description></item><item><title>Download KMPlayer Plus (Divx Codec) 35.10.020</title><pubDate> Sat, 04 Oct 2025 15:46:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-kmplayer-plus-divx-codec-8720.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-kmplayer-plus-divx-codec-8720.html
</guid><description>
KMPlayer Plus with DivX codec is also available for Android devices, providing a powerful media player that supports many video and audio formats. These features include ad-free playback, cloud storage support, and high-resolution video playback support.
With support for DivX, KMPlayer Plus for Android allows users to watch high-quality DivX encoded videos on their mobile devices without the need for additional codecs or software. This is a convenient feature for users who want to watch...
</description></item><item><title>Download Today Weather: Radar &amp;amp; Widgets 2.4.0-8</title><pubDate> Sat, 04 Oct 2025 15:45:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-today-weather-alerts-widgets-8915.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-today-weather-alerts-widgets-8915.html
</guid><description>
Weather Today is a beautiful and easy-to-use weather app that provides the world's most accurate local weather forecasts.
Features of Weather Today for Android
	Displays clear, easy-to-understand weather forecasts.
	Enjoy every moment you open the app with thousands of beautiful photos corresponding to the weather and day.
	Prepare for any situation with 24/7 weather forecasts and chance of rain.
	Protect your health with air quality, UV index and pollen count.
	Capture beautiful...
</description></item><item><title>Download Clipboard CopyPaster Pro v55</title><pubDate> Sat, 04 Oct 2025 15:45:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-clipboard-copypaster-pro-11369.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-clipboard-copypaster-pro-11369.html
</guid><description>
Clipboard CopyPaster Pro is a manager that simplifies work with standard clipboards; you can use it to copy and paste various texts and images as well as manage clipboard history.
CopyPaster Pro is a clipboard manager and has many additional and very useful functions:
	Save all copied data (text, links, images).
	Copy the saved data and paste it to the desired location.
	Edit data.
	Create your own notes.
	Share saved data.
	Voice listens to saved notes
	Search in saved data.
	Create...
</description></item><item><title>Download Voice Recorder Plus: Rec Sound 1.13.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 04 Oct 2025 15:45:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sound-recorder-plus-voice-rec-13795.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sound-recorder-plus-voice-rec-13795.html
</guid><description>
Unlock the full potential of your recordings with Sound Recorder Plus &amp;amp; Dictaphone, your solution for perfect audio quality at your fingertips. Designed with a beautiful, intuitive interface, this app is suitable for both beginners and seasoned professionals. Whether it is for working, studying, listening to music or recording the essence of everyday life, Audio Recorder Free is the embodiment of high-quality and flexible audio recording or voice recording.
Key features of Voice...
</description></item><item><title>Download MDScan + OCR 3.9.89</title><pubDate> Sat, 04 Oct 2025 15:44:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-mobile-doc-scanner-mdscan-ocr-8307.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-mobile-doc-scanner-mdscan-ocr-8307.html
</guid><description>
Mobile Doc Scanner (MDS) is an application that allows users to scan, edit and save documents using the Android device's camera. It's designed to work as a portable scanner so you can easily digitize documents, receipts, business cards, and more.
All image processing is done on your device only! No material will be posted online without your wishes! Take photos with your camera, edit them with many advanced features, save to your favorite format and share on social networks, email,...
</description></item><item><title>Download FlashLight HD LED Pro 2.10.24</title><pubDate> Sat, 04 Oct 2025 15:44:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-flashlight-hd-led-pro-8446.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-flashlight-hd-led-pro-8446.html
</guid><description>
FlashLight HD LED Pro is a flashlight app for Android devices that provides strong and bright light using the device's camera flash. This app is compatible with most phones, including those where other apps don't work. This includes for example: Sony Xperia, Samsung Galaxy S8, S7 Edge, S6, J7, Xiaomi Redmi Note, Oppo, Huawei, LG, Lenovo,Vivo, HTC, Alcatel, ZTE, Asus ZenFone, Motorola Moto G4, E2. .. and much more.
Features of FlashLight HD LED Pro
	The brightest and strongest light...
</description></item><item><title>Download Lower Brightness Pro 2.0.11_pro</title><pubDate> Sat, 04 Oct 2025 15:44:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-lower-brightness-pro-11283.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-lower-brightness-pro-11283.html
</guid><description>
The application helps you reduce brightness to any level. You can set the brightness level from 0% to 100% simply by opening the app and selecting the brightness level you want. By enabling the service, the app will be able to dim the entire screen including the status bar, notification panel, navigation bar, etc.
Main features:
	Reduce screen brightness below system minimum brightness
	Easy to use. Just turn it on and set the brightness level percentage (0-100%)
	Automatically starts...
</description></item><item><title>Download Magnet Search - Torrent Search 1.2.98</title><pubDate> Sat, 04 Oct 2025 15:43:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-magnet-search-pro-torrent-tool-10821.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-magnet-search-pro-torrent-tool-10821.html
</guid><description>
You can use this app to search for the resource you want, then copy the magnet link and download it. That's easy. You can also search for torrents, have a good time.
</description></item><item><title>Download Math Tricks Workout 2.7.3.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 04 Oct 2025 15:43:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-math-tricks-workout-8232.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-math-tricks-workout-8232.html
</guid><description>
Math Tricks Exercises can be an Android app designed to help users improve their math skills and speed through the use of various tricks and techniques. Math Tricks Exercises is one of the best math tricks app that brings you the most interesting exercises and practice to test and improve your math skills. Inspired by Vedic Maths, This is the most fun and free math learning app ever!
Features of Math Tricks Workout
	Various math problems, including addition, subtraction,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Speed Camera Radar (PRO) 3.2.41</title><pubDate> Sat, 04 Oct 2025 15:43:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-speed-camera-radar-pro-9777.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-speed-camera-radar-pro-9777.html
</guid><description>
Speed ​​camera radar (PRO) for Android is used to detect road hazards, such as speed cameras (mobile ambush, static speed cameras, red light cameras), bumps deceleration, bad roads, etc. This application works differently, it uses a database of dangers previously discovered by other users. For example, if the app is notified about a mobile ambush, it means that at this moment it is probably a mobile ambush.
The application plays sounds and displays hazards on the map as well as the...
</description></item><item><title>Download IELTS Listening 2.6</title><pubDate> Sat, 04 Oct 2025 15:42:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ielts-listening-13643.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ielts-listening-13643.html
</guid><description>
Self-study reference materials to practice, assess and improve your IELTS Listening score. The IELTS Listening app allows you to practice questions similar to those you will encounter in the test. It helps you prepare confidently for your upcoming IELTS Academic or General Training test.
1. IELTS Listening Practice Test
	Practice your listening skills with our expert tool. Each practice test has a transcript and detailed explanations.
2. Full IELTS Listening Test
	Practice with...
</description></item><item><title>Download Scientific Calculator Pro 6.10.14</title><pubDate> Sat, 04 Oct 2025 15:42:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-scientific-calculator-pro-11445.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-scientific-calculator-pro-11445.html
</guid><description>
Turn your phone into the best scientific calculator you've ever used with this essential app. Basic, advanced, and graphing modes let you use only what you need, when you need it. It's fast, easy to use and looks real.
Main features
	No advertising
	Full-color graph
	Works in landscape and portrait mode
	Trigonometry, log, exponent
	Calculate fractions
	Complex numbers
	Linear equations and polynomials
	Basic statistical functions
	Binary, decimal, hexadecimal operations
	Bitwise...
</description></item><item><title>Download CALCU Stylish Basic Calculator 4.7.11</title><pubDate> Sat, 04 Oct 2025 15:42:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-stylish-calculator-calcu-8716.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-stylish-calculator-calcu-8716.html
</guid><description>
Express your style with a computer made just for you. Choose a stylish, colorful theme to brighten your day while you calculate with ease. CALCU™ is easy to use for everyday calculations, with all the scientific capabilities you need for work and school at a swipe. And for your most demanding needs, CALCU™ lets you add or remove the functions and constants you need to create the perfect calculator you designed for you.
Features of Fashion Calculator - CALCU
	Try our new Material...
</description></item><item><title>Download Caller Name Announcer App 2.2.5</title><pubDate> Sat, 04 Oct 2025 15:41:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-auto-caller-name-announcer-12068.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-auto-caller-name-announcer-12068.html
</guid><description>
Auto Caller Name Announcer is a top Android app that notifies you instantly when you receive an incoming call or text message. Faster, better and 100% free, exclusively on Google Play. Caller Name Announcer and Flashlight: Caller ID, Call Announcer a powerful caller ID number Android app, helps find out who called you instantly, even before you take out your phone out and view the screen to check the contact or message.
Main features:
	Turn on/off speaking caller's...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mindz - Mind Map &amp;amp; Lists Pro 1.4.22</title><pubDate> Sat, 04 Oct 2025 15:41:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-mindz-mind-mapping-pro-11841.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-mindz-mind-mapping-pro-11841.html
</guid><description>
Mindz is a mind map. Structure your thoughts, collect ideas or plan projects clearly in nested lists. You can then easily visualize, present and send them as mind maps. Users can easily create, edit and customize their mind maps with different shapes, colors and symbols. This visual representation of ideas can help users see the connections and relationships between different concepts, making brainstorming and organizing thoughts easier.
Mindz Features
	Clear and fast list...
</description></item><item><title>Download IgeBlock - Tube ad blocker 2.0.6 Build 311</title><pubDate> Sat, 04 Oct 2025 15:37:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-igeblock-tube-ad-blocker-11113.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-igeblock-tube-ad-blocker-11113.html
</guid><description>
IgeBlock is an app that allows you to watch videos without ads, watch videos with sound, and watch videos in pop-up player while using other apps.
IgeBlock Features
Block ads
	Automatically skip annoying video ads.
	Automatically skip ads even in sound and pop-up player mode.
Pop-up player (PIP)
	You can play videos in floating mode without additional permissions.
Can be added
	Full screen touch lock function
	looped video
	Bookmark function without logging in
	Timer to turn...
</description></item><item><title>Download Perfectly Clear WorkBench 4.8.0.2857</title><pubDate> Fri, 03 Oct 2025 19:37:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfectly-clear-workbench-6892.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfectly-clear-workbench-6892.html
</guid><description>
Perfectly Clear Workbench is an application that uses image editing libraries Perfectly Clear by Athentech and is provided to demonstrate the capabilities of the Perfectly Clear processing libraries, which recognize faces and allow quick export of processing settings for use.
One of the key features in Workbench is the ability to "export to API" when saving a Preset. This allows you to make image edits in Workbench and adjust the settings to suit your editing style and needs. You can...
</description></item></channel></rss>