<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 01:50:17 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 01:50:17 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download WinSetView 3.1.7</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 00:07:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winsetview-8971.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winsetview-8971.html
</guid><description>
WinSetView is a tool that allows you to easily set File Explorer's default folder view (including disabling grouping everywhere if desired). It works by setting registry values that File Explorer already supports. It does not modify Explorer or add any tasks or services.
Features of WinSetView
	Is a portabe application. That is, it requires no installation (just unzip and run) and it saves its settings in an INI file with the application. So you can easily run it from a flash drive or...
</description></item><item><title>Download Synchredible Professional 9.100</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 00:07:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-synchredible-professional-1923.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-synchredible-professional-1923.html
</guid><description>
Synchredible Professional is the most advanced version help synchronize the folder and your drive quickly and easily. Whether it is a single file or an entire drive - Synchredible Professional will synchronize, copy and save them for you. The software guide will assist you to identify the work that is scheduled in advance or be done through the USB connection. This way, you can keep your files in sync - automatically.
In the past years, the advanced technology of the us in Synchredible...
</description></item><item><title>Download Room Arranger 10.3.2.739</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 00:06:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-room-arranger-3779.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-room-arranger-3779.html
</guid><description>
Room Arranger is a 3D application lets you easily plan for the room, office or his apartment just a few mouse clicks. The application comes with a simple interface will significantly simplify your work. You can draw many kinds of objects and items to create furniture of your own. This app also includes a library of object rich.
Software Room Arranger enables you to view your project in 3D form. You can also upload the 3D scene interact on your blog or your website. The application uses...
</description></item><item><title>Download Flip PDF Plus Corporate 7.10.15</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 00:06:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-flip-pdf-corporate-edition-3438.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-flip-pdf-corporate-edition-3438.html
</guid><description>
Flip PDF Corporate Edition is Windows software that helps to convert PDF to publications page flip digital with many powerful features. Version Corporate Edition contains all the great features in Flip PDF Professional and Flip Shopping Catalog. Version Flip PDF Corporate Edition is an edited version PDF most powerful for small and medium enterprises.
Software Flip PDF Corporate Edition provides all features of Flip PDF Professional and Flip Shopping Catalog, including the conversion mode...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube Downloader 3.9.18 (0401)</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 00:05:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube Downloader  is a dedicated software that helps users  downloading youtube videos  Favorites on PC for offline viewing. With MediaHuman YouTube  Downloader  you can download videos from youtube website to your computer with  fast speed , with special software development technology that automatically receives videos from Websites, in addition to the ability to download videos from software websites, can convert downloaded video formats to various formats for the purpose...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinTools.one Professional / Home 26.0.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 00:05:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wintoolsone-10808.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wintoolsone-10808.html
</guid><description>
WinTools.one is a program designed to help both regular and advanced users as well as computer engineers fine-tune the MS Windows operating system. It allows you to increase the performance of the operating system, maintain its performance at a high level, fix operating system errors, free up space on the computer's hard drive and control the operation of installed programs. In addition, the program allows you to store and protect your secret and confidential information, as well as work...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wipe Pro 2026.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 00:04:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wipe-pro-710.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wipe-pro-710.html
</guid><description>
Wipe Pro is software that helps clean up litter, increase in hard drive space besides also protect your privacy on the Internet, it removes records about personal activity on the computer. You will be able to delete browser history and the cache, the file index.dat, registry, files, cookies, internet history, auto complete, temporary internet files and many other items. This program also delete all activities other individuals that you made when using the PC and regardless of which...
</description></item><item><title>Download Synchredible 9.100</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 00:03:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-synchredible-53.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-synchredible-53.html
</guid><description>
Synchredible is an easy to use tool to synchronize folders and files. It provides a wizard interface lets you set up the sync job, select files to exclude, schedule the job to execute automatically, and more.Additional features include support for network and external drives, check CRC32, and more.
Synchredible - synchronization of folders and files
Among other things, you can use the filter for the file type specific data synchronization according to the time or routine deletion of...
</description></item><item><title>Download URL Disabler 1.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 00:03:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-url-disabler-7422.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-url-disabler-7422.html
</guid><description>
URL Disabler is a web-blocking software that controls Internet access, especially for businesses, schools that want to comply with child protection laws and WiFi services that can access public wanting to provide eco-friendly browsing environments with family and family users.
By blocking certain websites greatly reduces this risk and protects accidental browsing of adult, explicit and sensitive websites. It can also help save bandwidth for mission-critical applications and reduce those...
</description></item><item><title>Download GibbsCAM 2026 v26.0.54.00</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 00:02:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gibbscam-001-732.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gibbscam-001-732.html
</guid><description>
GibbsCAM is a full-featured CAM system that provides powerful CNC programming capabilities to optimize manufacturing production.GibbsCAM 12 introduces a modern, updated system Updated interface designed to increase efficiency and improve overall user experience.
GibbsCAM
GibbsCAM updates with a new interface that gives users the ability to customize, along with the ease-of-use features users expect, while still maintaining character, personality and traditional workflows. by...
</description></item><item><title>Download LLBLGen Pro 5.13.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 00:01:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-llblgen-pro-5979.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-llblgen-pro-5979.html
</guid><description>
LLBLGen Pro is a solution to create a fast and easy model model and actually creates a class of entity models. LLBLren is a good working framework with most existing ORMs such as the Entity Framework, NHibernate, Linq To SQL or even your custom ORM, you can just design the database model layer and then map it to your database. From now on, you only have to write the query. LLBLten maps the objects easily in the relationship model. It is widely used in many commercial projects around the...
</description></item><item><title>Download X-Ability Winmostar 11.14.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 00:00:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-x-ability-winmostar-11156.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-x-ability-winmostar-11156.html
</guid><description>
Winmostar is an integrated GUI software designed for simulation programs such as GAMESS, MOPAC, LAMMPS, Gromacs and Quantum ESPRESSO. Winmostar serves as an integrated software solution, using programs (solvers) for MO, DFT and MD calculations as its backend. It provides pre- and post-processing capabilities, as well as file and process management functions. Software supported solvers include GAMESS, MOPAC, LAMMPS, Gromacs and Quantum ESPRESSO. Winmostar is designed to be installed and...
</description></item><item><title>Download SyMenu 8.11.9501</title><pubDate> Mon, 05 Jan 2026 23:59:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-symenu-2726.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-symenu-2726.html
</guid><description>
SyMenu is a menu USB mobile that you can use to quickly access applications and documents from a USB drive its mobile. The program runs as an icon in your system tray from which you can activate the custom menu allows you to launch your apps. To create your menu, just drag - drop the folder from drive on your mobile or browse to find the file you want to link. You can arrange the shortcuts according to the hierarchical structure with folders, icons and separator and also can configure the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Privoxy 4.0.0-1 + Portable</title><pubDate> Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:53:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-privoxy-6216.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-privoxy-6216.html
</guid><description>
Privoxy is a free web proxy that does not save on buffers with filtering capabilities to enhance privacy rights, cookies manipulation, and modification of the HTTP header and the HTTP header before the page is displayed. Privoxy is a "proxy to enhance privacy", filtering websites and removing ads. Privoxy has a flexible configuration and can be customized to fit the needs and personal tastes. It has applications for both stand-alone systems and multi-user networks.
Features of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Q-Dir 12.45</title><pubDate> Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:50:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-q-dir-348.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-q-dir-348.html
</guid><description>
Q-Dir is software to manage the entire file and folder on the computer, allowing to see file in same time 4 different positions (viewport quadro) while still maintaining all the standard features of the Explorer.
It also provides a variety of management features, additional files included the filter file color-coding, layouts and columns can be customized, quick access to file and folder favorites and more.
Other features of Q-Dir , including directory listings (.txt, .doc .html .csv),...
</description></item><item><title>Download Bulk Rename Utility 4.1.0.1 Commercial</title><pubDate> Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:48:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bulk-rename-utility-2119.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bulk-rename-utility-2119.html
</guid><description>
Bulk Rename Utility is a utility batch rename allows you to easily rename multiple files and folders, based on the criteria flexible. Bulk Rename Utility lets you easily Add time / date stamp, replace numbers, insert text, convert case, add auto number, processing folder and sub-folder,..
Bulk Rename Utility - Change the name of the file series
Rename many files and / or directories has never been easier! It has a small memory footprint so it can be left running all the time without...
</description></item><item><title>Download Database .NET 36.5.9491</title><pubDate> Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:48:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-databasenet-1818.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-databasenet-1818.html
</guid><description>
Database.NET a common database allows you to connect to most of the server database to perform SQL queries, create databases and tables and edit the rows of the table. Program Database.NET includes a syntax enabled editor SQL tagged as well as a number of additional tools to perform facility maintenance data base (shrinking, backing up and viewing process). You can also export the data to CSV, HTML, XML and some other formats.
Database.NET - Management database
Management features,...
</description></item><item><title>Download O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro 22.1.233 / Server</title><pubDate> Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:47:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-diskimage-pro-218.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-diskimage-pro-218.html
</guid><description>
O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro is software backup data comprehensive and effective is provided to protect the data of the computer system, it creates images for individual drives or the entire system that still does not affect your system.
O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro allows the user to backup the entire computer or drive, the and files whenever you want even while the computer is being used. Or can use O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro to create a copy chinh sac of computer disk drives, can be used instead of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download mIRC 7.83</title><pubDate> Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:47:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mirc-756.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mirc-756.html
</guid><description>
mIRC is a client application used to communicate, share, play or work with others on IRC networks around the world. The software interface is practical, clean, highly configurable and supports features such as friends lists, file transfer, connect to multiple servers, IPv6, SSL encryption, proxy support, display UTF-8, UPnP, custom sound, spoken message, notification tray , logs messages, and more.
mIRC - Chat, chat online
mIRC also has a language powerful script can be used both to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Clean Media Player 2026.1.4.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:46:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-clean-media-player-12416.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-clean-media-player-12416.html
</guid><description>
If you've ever been offended by profanity in a movie, chances are you'll want the censored version of the movie. However, until the director decides to release it, you still have the option of muting unwanted scenes or editing the subtitles manually, if you are able to do so. The application mutes and displays subtitles without offensive words and phrases. Customize the profanity filter to your preferences. Skip inappropriate scenes by selecting their start and end times.
Clean Media...
</description></item><item><title>Download VidCoder 12.13 + Portable</title><pubDate> Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:46:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vidcoder-534.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vidcoder-534.html
</guid><description>
VidCoder is software to convert movies to MKV and MP4, as well as extract video content from DVDS and Blu-ray. This is a software utility to help people extract the video content from the BD and DVD as well as convert the clips specific to MKV and MP4.
VidCoder has an interface that includes a clear design, including a menu bar, several buttons and a panel to display the queue. The file can be added with the help of the file browser or drag and drop-out.
Features VidCoder
	VidCoder...
</description></item><item><title>Download NWinfo 1.5.4</title><pubDate> Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:45:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nwinfo-12590.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nwinfo-12590.html
</guid><description>
NWinfo is a Win32 program that allows you to obtain system and hardware information. It displays essential information about CPU, memory, disk, network, and even system operating details. Because it's portable, you can carry NWinfo on a USB stick and use it on any Windows machine, making it a useful tool for both tech enthusiasts and troubleshooters.
Features of NWinfo
	Get detailed information about SMBIOS, CPUID, S.M.A.R.T., PCI, EDID, etc.
	Supports export in JSON, YAML and LUA...
</description></item><item><title>Download EZ CD Audio Converter 12.4.0.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:45:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ez-cd-audio-converter-174.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ez-cd-audio-converter-174.html
</guid><description>
EZ CD Audio Converter is a software application advanced with purpose helps you extract audio tracks from CDS, convert files to different formats and burn them to disc. When using functions separate the audio from the disc, you are also edit the type of metadata and specify the file name to be separated.
EZ CD Audio Converter Ultimate has the ability to convert between multiple audio formats with high output quality assured, supported input formats, including 3GA, 3GP, AAC, AIF, AIFF,...
</description></item><item><title>Download EZ Meta Tag Editor 12.3.4.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:44:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ez-meta-tag-editor-4043.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ez-meta-tag-editor-4043.html
</guid><description>
EZ Meta Tag Editor is manager audio file, the metadata editing easy-to-use user interface with Windows style File Explorer. EZ Meta Tag Editor offers editing solutions card, tag, file management easier. EZ Meta Tag Editor now supports many popular formats such as AAC, HE AAC, AIFF, Monkey's Audio, DSF, DFF, FLAC, MP3, MP2, MP1, Musepack, Opus, real audio (TTA), WAV, Wavpack, WMA, Vorbis, 3g2, 3ga, 3gp, aac, aif, aiff, ape, asf, DSF, dff, flac, m4a, M4B, MP1, mp2, mp3, mp4, mpc, ogg, opus,...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDFArea PDF to Image Converter 5.6</title><pubDate> Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:44:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdfarea-pdf-to-image-converter-6933.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdfarea-pdf-to-image-converter-6933.html
</guid><description>
PDFArea PDF to Image Converter is a quick and easy-use PDF mass conversion utility designed to convert PDF documents to the image file. Output images can be JPG, TIF, GIF, PNG, JP2 (JPEG 2000), BMP and EMF formats. It can convert encrypted PDF documents and allow you to choose to convert all pages or pages specified. PDFArea PDF to Image Converter is independent software, without using Adobe Acrobat Reader. It does not depend on any print drivers so it will NOT install any print drivers...
</description></item></channel></rss>