<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 17:46:14 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 17:46:14 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Garmin Express 7.28</title><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jan 2026 17:34:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-garmin-express-1579.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-garmin-express-1579.html
</guid><description>
Garmin Express is a tool developed by the company Garmin to enable you to manage equipment on your GPS from the computer. You can use this app to map updates, register the device, update software and even to create a backup. Garmin Express also allows you to install voices and vehicles for free, as well as download instructions for use product.
Garmin Express - Manage GPS devices
You can automatically update the map by only one click, so you always have accurate information when you go...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Acrobat Reader DC 2025.001.21078</title><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jan 2026 17:25:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-acrobat-reader-3707.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-acrobat-reader-3707.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Acrobat Reader DC is a system of application software and Web services developed by Adobe Systems to view, create, manipulate, print and manage PDF files. With Adobe Acrobat Reader DC, you can create, export, edit, and track PDF files from anywhere - and maintain connection with the recent set of files on all your devices.
Adobe Acrobat Reader current DC is connected with Adobe Document Cloud - help working on the computers and mobile devices becomes easier than ever before. This is...
</description></item><item><title>Download DesktopPic 2.0.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jan 2026 17:23:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktoppic-7444.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktoppic-7444.html
</guid><description>
DesktopPic allows you to display or watermark images on your Windows desktop wallpaper. Display one or more pictures in a resizable, movable window with no borders or captions, so all you see is the photo. This will give the illusion of the image being part of your wallpaper, but it's really just another window. Any icons on the desktop in the same area as the image will be masked. Bitmap image formats, such as PNG (recommended), JPG, BMP and animated GIF are supported.
Features of...
</description></item><item><title>Download TidyWindow 3.8.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jan 2026 17:12:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tidywindow-14454.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tidywindow-14454.html
</guid><description>
TidyWindow is a Windows desktop assistant that automates developer PC setup, cleanup, diagnostics, software package installation, registry tweaking, and driver updates—powered by a WPF interface and robust PowerShell 7 automation capabilities in the background.
Key Features
	Essentials Repair Center (docs/essentials.md): Queues selected automation tasks Filter for network, Defender, printing, and Windows Update issues. Each task supports preview run, sequential execution, restore...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinBin2Iso 6.61</title><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jan 2026 17:11:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winbin2iso-1777.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winbin2iso-1777.html
</guid><description>
WinBin2Iso is a small program and simple application that allows you to convert the file .bin format .iso. WinBin2Iso support files larger than 2 gigabytes and does not require installation. The interface is quite simple WinBin2Iso only 1 window embodying the features of the software, you can choose the button WinBin2Iso to convert images bin to iso then choose select folder containing source files and output, all the settings are done in just a few seconds for you to implement features of...
</description></item><item><title>Download DBF Recovery 4.64</title><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jan 2026 17:10:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbf-recovery-7931.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbf-recovery-7931.html
</guid><description>
DBF Recovery is software that gives users the ability to restore a damaged database back to its original condition without the expertise required to complete that task. It fixes headers and data structures in an automated process that doesn't involve user interaction. With DBF Recovery, you will truly have a lean, honest DBF repair machine without any functionality.
Features of DBF Recovery
	Quick and simple to use DBF file repair software.
	Repair almost any DBF...
</description></item><item><title>Download AnyDWG Software PDF to DWG Converter 2027.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jan 2026 17:10:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-pdf-to-dwg-converter-7583.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-pdf-to-dwg-converter-7583.html
</guid><description>
Any PDF to DWG Converter  is a software that batch converts PDF files to DWG and PDF to DXF format for quick and efficient editing in AutoCAD. It allows you to easily convert PDF to DWG and PDF to DXF without the need of AutoCAD. In addition, Any PDF to DWG Converter also allows users to set the DWG file settings such as: creating and optimizing lines, circles, arcs or keeping colors, resizing the page ... user can customize the settings as desired so that the DWG file looks the way it...
</description></item><item><title>Download StarReminder 4.23.06</title><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jan 2026 17:09:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-starreminder-6482.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-starreminder-6482.html
</guid><description>
StarReminder is a reminder scheduling software that you can easily use as an electronic calendar, job arrangements, daily planning, alarm clock, and birthday prompts. You can have a prompt, warning for the day and time in particular. With advanced scheduling options (but easy to use), you can set the periodic prompts (hours, daily, weekly, monthly, annual, etc.).
Features of StarReminder
	You can add notifications on the screen, the prompts sent via e-mail and audio alerts.
	You can...
</description></item><item><title>Download PortableApps.com Installer 3.9.7</title><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jan 2026 17:08:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-portableappscom-installer-7673.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-portableappscom-installer-7673.html
</guid><description>
PortableApps.com Installer is an easy-to-use multilingual installer that allows you to package your portable applications without writing code. PortableApps.com Installer can be run from a cloud folder, an external drive or a local folder without installing to Windows. It's even better with the PortableApps.com Platform for easy installation and automatic updates.
Features of PortableApps.com Installer
	Proven NSIS Installer Core
	Excellent compression for distribution
	Easy...
</description></item><item><title>Download Advanced Driver Updater 4.6.1086.8539</title><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jan 2026 17:08:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-driver-updater-1170.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-driver-updater-1170.html
</guid><description>
Advanced Driver Updater is software that automatically check, download and install the Driver for the fastest computer with the software always be updated with the latest. Advanced Driver Updater will help your system will always have the latest drivers and you will no longer have to make search for driver updates manually. Outdated drivers can slow your PC or even cause errors. Drivers for video cards are particularly prone to this. A program is clearly structured to provide access to...
</description></item><item><title>Download ExamDiff Pro Master Edition 16.0.1.19</title><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jan 2026 17:05:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-examdiff-pro-master-312.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-examdiff-pro-master-312.html
</guid><description>
ExamDiff Pro Master is a tool to compare files and folders intuitive and easy to use, intuitive and easy to use for Windows. ExamDiff Pro Master has unique features distinguishes ExamDiff Pro with the program compare other. ExamDiff Pro Master to help perform reviews of code and share other reports with your colleagues and compare local website with FTP server by plug-ins more integrated.
ExamDiff Pro Master can create a snapshot folder for comparison and storage in the future, compare...
</description></item><item><title>Download Multi Commander 15.7 Build 3133</title><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jan 2026 17:04:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-multi-commander-2038.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-multi-commander-2038.html
</guid><description>
Multi Commander is a file manager, multi tab and is an alternative to the Windows Explorer standard. It uses the table layout control dual very popular and effective. Multi Commander has everything you need in daily work with files to increase speed and efficiency.
Multi Commander - file Manager
Multi Commander has all the standard features that any manager files would have, such as copy, move, rename, view. But the strong point of Multi Command is the special feature allows you to...
</description></item><item><title>Download AnyDWG Software DWG to SVG Converter 2027.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jan 2026 17:03:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-dwg-to-svg-converter-7584.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-dwg-to-svg-converter-7584.html
</guid><description>
Any DWG to SVG Converter  is a software to batch convert DXF files to SVG, DWG to SVG and DWF to SVG without AutoCAD.
Features of Any DWG to SVG Converter
	Convert unlimited number of DWG/DXF/DWF files to SVG.
	does NOT require AutoCAD.
	Supports AutoCAD R2.5 files - AutoCAD 2023 DWG/DXF.
	Allows you to set the SVG Size.
	Allows you to set the SVG background color.
	Convert SHX, TTF, Xref fonts and embedded/Excel raster images in DWG/DXF to SVG.
	Render all layouts, paper spaces, and...
</description></item><item><title>Download SDL Trados Studio 2024 SR1 Professional 18.1.3.6657</title><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jan 2026 16:56:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sdl-trados-studio-4216.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sdl-trados-studio-4216.html
</guid><description>
SDL Passolo Collaboration Edition is a version of partnering with a user who has the common function with a Version group, but translation packages can also be automatically synchronized with translation agencies and translators via an FTP server or platform cloud storage Box. The string list Passolo can also be published directly onto the SDL Trados GroupShare.
Use resource services of you in the most efficient way possible during software localization. SDL Passolo Collaboration Edition...
</description></item><item><title>Download Any DWG DXF Converter Pro 2027.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jan 2026 16:52:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-dwg-dxf-converter-pro-7581.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-dwg-dxf-converter-pro-7581.html
</guid><description>
Any DWG DXF Converter Pro  is batch DWG and DXF bidirectional converter and file version converter, it allows you to convert DWG to DXF, DXF to DWG without AutoCAD.
Features of Any DWG DXF Converter Pro
	Utility standalone, does NOT require AutoCAD.
	Convert DWG to DXF and DXF to DWG in batch.
	Outputs DWG, ASCII DXF and Binary DXF.
	It is also a DWG / DXF file version converter, it outputs AutoCAD R2.5 files - AutoCAD 2023 DWG / DXF.
	All versions of DWG / DXF file are...
</description></item><item><title>Download Screencapt Professional 3.000</title><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jan 2026 16:51:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-screencapt-professional-12260.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-screencapt-professional-12260.html
</guid><description>
Screencapt Professional is powerful Windows software for screen recording that allows you to accurately and easily record any on-screen activity. Whether you want to create tutorials, record webinars, or simply record your favorite games, Screencapt gives you all the tools you need.
With Screencapt, you can record the entire screen, a selected area, or a specific window. This flexibility makes Screencapt the perfect screen recorder for any type of application. Thanks to the built-in...
</description></item><item><title>Download Any DWG to Image Converter Pro 2027.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jan 2026 16:50:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-dwg-to-image-converter-pro-7587.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-dwg-to-image-converter-pro-7587.html
</guid><description>
Any DWG to Image Converter Pro  is a batch converter that allows you to convert DWG, DXF and DWF files to TIF (TIFF), JPG (JPEG), BMP, GIF, PNG, TGA, PCX, WMF and EMF without AutoCAD.
Features of Any DWG to Image Converter Pro
	Utility standalone, does NOT require AutoCAD.
	Convert DWG, DXF and DWF to Batch Image.
	Supports paper space and model space.
	Supports all versions of DWG / DXF files (Supports format R2.5 / 2.6 to AutoCAD 2023)
	Very easy to use.
	Command line support.
</description></item><item><title>Download Waterfox 6.6.8 / 2022.11</title><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jan 2026 16:49:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-waterfox-114.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-waterfox-114.html
</guid><description>
Waterfox is a 64-bit version of the foundation Firefox was built and the compiler Intel is optimized for speed and performance on Windows systems.Waterfox does not add any additional features or bling, in fact, it will automatically import all the gadgets and install is have of you, so you will feel like at home when you run it the first time.All the add-on your Firefox will work with Waterfox, however, only support the plug-in more 64-bit, is includes Adobe Flash, Oracle Java and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Obsidian 1.11.4</title><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jan 2026 16:49:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-obsidian-10386.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-obsidian-10386.html
</guid><description>
Obsidian is a powerful knowledge base that operates on a local folder containing plain text Markdown files. It allows users to create internal links for notes and then display the connections as a graph. Additionally users can also organize and structure their thoughts and knowledge in a flexible, non-linear way.
Features of Obsidian
Personal notes:
	Links: Create connections between your notes.
	Graph: Visualize the relationships between your notes.
	Plugins: Build your ideal...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mountain Duck 5.1.1.28444</title><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jan 2026 16:49:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mountain-duck-4115.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mountain-duck-4115.html
</guid><description>
Mountain Duck allows you to mount servers and cloud storage as the disk on the computer to your desk. Open the file remotely with any application and act as on a local disk without the need to synchronize the file. Based on the platform open source solid of Cyberduck, all of the main protocols are supported to connect to any server you want, including FTP, SFTP, WebDAV, Azure Cloud Storage, Amazon S3, Google Cloud Storage, Google Drive, Dropbox, Backblaze B2 &amp;amp; OpenStack Swift. Transfer...
</description></item><item><title>Download AnyDWG Software DGN to DWG Converter 2027.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jan 2026 16:44:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-dgn-to-dwg-converter-7582.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-dgn-to-dwg-converter-7582.html
</guid><description>
Any DGN to DWG Converter  is a software to batch convert DGN files to DWG / DXF without AutoCAD and MicroStation.
Features of Any DGN to DWG Converter
	Convert DGN to DWG and DGN to DXF quickly.
	Standalone program, AutoCAD and MicroStation are not required.
	Batch Conversion, allowing you to convert unlimited number of DGN files at a time.
	Export AutoCAD R2.5 to an AutoCAD 2023 DWG / DXF file.
	Supports MicroStation DGN V7 and V8.
	Command line feature support (You can find a...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wing IDE Pro 11.0.7</title><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jan 2026 16:44:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wing-ide-pro-2080.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wing-ide-pro-2080.html
</guid><description>
Wing IDE Pro is a integrated development environment to create applications using the Python language. Wing IDE Pro provides a code editor professional, in which you can use the keyboard shortcuts vi and emacs, auto-complete code re-structure, follow up calls, reminders, contextual. A code debugger graphics to debug locally and remotely, an interface to version control system, a test unit, a search tool flexibility available.
Wing IDE Pro - programming language Python
Features of Wing...
</description></item><item><title>Download AnyDWG Software DWF to DWG Converter 2027.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jan 2026 16:43:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-dwf-to-dwg-converter-7586.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-dwf-to-dwg-converter-7586.html
</guid><description>
Any DWF to DWG Converter  is software that allows you to convert DWF files to AutoCAD DWG and DXF file formats, so you can restore DWF entities to DWG entities corresponding easily.
Features of Any DWF to DWG Converter
	Convert DWF to DWG and DXF.
	Supports all types of DWF entities exported by AutoCAD, including arcs, elliptical arcs, ellipses, real style fonts, and more
	Supports DWF multipage specification.
	Restore layers in DWF, rendering the entire DWF pages.
	Extract Embedded...
</description></item><item><title>Download Karaosoft Karma 2026.1.12</title><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jan 2026 16:38:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-karma-2379.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-karma-2379.html
</guid><description>
Karma is an enhancement program that helps you tune, karaoke can view the text of the files sound different. At first glance, after launch, the layout may seem complicated, unclear where to start. You can customize the display prompts to understand the function of each parameter is highlighted integrated.
Management program your karaoke a easy way. Search no need to click, drag and drop feature and many other unique features designed to bring you the easiest management for the program...
</description></item><item><title>Download AnyDWG Software DWG to DWF Converter 2027.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jan 2026 16:38:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-dwg-to-dwf-converter-7585.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-dwg-to-dwf-converter-7585.html
</guid><description>
Any DWG to DWF Converter  is a full featured DWG to DWF converter that allows you to convert DWG and DXF files to DWF without AutoCAD.
Features of Any DWG to DWF Converter
	Batch convert DWG to DWF and DXF to DWF.
	Utility standalone, does NOT require AutoCAD.
	Flexible and customizable output. Allows you to choose the Quality, Format, Version and Background Color of your DWF file.
	Supports SHX, Xref and Line Width.
	Supports DWF 6 and 3D DWF. The new DWF 6 format supports...
</description></item></channel></rss>