<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 13:49:01 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 13:49:01 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download NWinfo 1.5.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 16:40:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nwinfo-12590.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nwinfo-12590.html
</guid><description>
NWinfo is a Win32 program that allows you to obtain system and hardware information. It displays essential information about CPU, memory, disk, network, and even system operating details. Because it's portable, you can carry NWinfo on a USB stick and use it on any Windows machine, making it a useful tool for both tech enthusiasts and troubleshooters.
Features of NWinfo
	Get detailed information about SMBIOS, CPUID, S.M.A.R.T., PCI, EDID, etc.
	Supports export in JSON, YAML and LUA...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tixati 3.41.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 16:39:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tixati-2355.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tixati-2355.html
</guid><description>
A Bittorrent free, good have been updated, are designed for operating systems Microsoft Windows and Linux (for the OS Monday, you can download a version from the official website of the developer). The difference between a client and a large number of others is that users are provided a wide opportunity to control the torrent of them, they also write on your program that it consumes less memory than uTorrent and Halite famous.
Tixati - App download torrent
Tixati is also ready to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Vivaldi for macOS 7.7.3851.58</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 16:39:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/mac/download-vivaldi-for-macos-3443.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/mac/download-vivaldi-for-macos-3443.html
</guid><description>
The Vivaldi for MacOS browser does not track users and offers more features than any other modern browser. Managed by Jon von Tetzchner (co-founder of Opera browser), Vivaldi for MacOS is driven by the real needs of today's users and ensures that they have the best tools to browse and get work done.
Vivaldi for MacOS - Modern web browser
Users can adjust Vivaldi to suit their browsing needs them without limiting customization options. Vivaldi takes the browser to the next level with a...
</description></item><item><title>Download iTubeGo YouTube Downloader 10.10.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 16:36:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-itubego-youtube-downloader-3681.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-itubego-youtube-downloader-3681.html
</guid><description>
iTubeGo YouTube Downloader  is the best way to download live video from 1000+ streaming sites. iTubeGo YouTube Downloader is a powerful download tool that allows you to save video and audio for free. The output format of high speed converter is high quality MP4, MP3. Fully compatible with iPhone, iPad, iTunes, iMovie, Android Phone and more.
iTubeGo YouTube Downloader - Solution for downloading high quality Youtube video 
Features of iTubeGo YouTube Downloader
	Download videos from...
</description></item><item><title>Download iZotope Ozone Advanced 12.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 16:35:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ozone-advanced-2580.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ozone-advanced-2580.html
</guid><description>
iZotope Ozone Advanced is the overall most comprehensive in the industry, Ozone 8 additional to his legacy by introducing signal processing clever new shape the spectral balance control loudness, v. v. master your audio with more than the first fifteen years of the audio industry at your fingertips. Improved with new features, future, smart, Ozone 8 is your stop for a professional master, balanced with ten processors, the necessary. That is version smart most of the Ozone is...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Downloader 10.0.5</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 16:34:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html
</guid><description>
YTD Youtube Downloader is an application that reliable and intuitive, allowing you to quickly download YouTube videos and save them to your computer. You can also convert the media files to the format desired video or extract audio streams and save separately. YTD Youtube Downloader lets you save your favorite clips of yourself from Youtube, Facebook, Vimeo and Dailymotion to your desktop. The software supports URLS from many web site hosting, multimedia and allows you to download desired...
</description></item><item><title>Download Executor 2.1.10</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 16:34:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-executor-271.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-executor-271.html
</guid><description>
Executor for windows is a software alternative premium customization features for the Windows "Run" and "Search Programs". When you press WIN + Z and provides the search results instant, as-you-type for any keywords you enter. By default, Executor will index all the Desktop and Start Menu and you can easily expand the search range by adding the folder location additional.
Executor for windows
The program comes with a list of commands built in which you can use to quickly access many...
</description></item><item><title>Download Broot 1.54.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 16:34:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-broot-8588.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-broot-8588.html
</guid><description>
Broot is an open source command line tool for browsing and navigating file systems. Broot provides a fast and intuitive way to navigate the file system with a tree-like interactive interface. It provides various features like searching for files, opening files and folders, copying file paths to clipboard, etc. It also supports customizing keys and color themes.
Features of Broot
	Fast file browsing: Lets you quickly navigate through large directory structures with a tree-like...
</description></item><item><title>Download Muziza YouTube Downloader Converter 9.0.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 16:33:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-muziza-youtube-downloader-converter-3972.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-muziza-youtube-downloader-converter-3972.html
</guid><description>
Muziza YouTube Downloader Converter is a tool to create conditions for an attractive interface and many features to help you to download video clips from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion, Instagram and other sites. Muziza YouTube Downloader Converter can also download the video UHD 8K, 5K, 4K, QHD 2K, HD 1080p and 720p from YouTube. The app allows you download only audio stream from YouTube and save as MP3. You don't need to download the entire video file.
Muziza YouTube Downloader...
</description></item><item><title>Download 4KSoftware 4K Downloader 6.0.9</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 16:33:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-downloader-3858.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-downloader-3858.html
</guid><description>
4K Downloader is a Windows application small but powerful to download and convert video in 4K and 8K Ultra HD from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion and thousands of other video-based websites. It speeds up your download by up to 5 times. Consider that most smart phones, TVS, computers, and tablets all support the high definition format, don't be surprised when many users want to enjoy quality content on their device. 4K Downloader is a lightweight software designed to help you grab videos...
</description></item><item><title>Download Alibre Design Expert 28.1.1.28228</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 16:32:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-alibre-design-expert-12781.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-alibre-design-expert-12781.html
</guid><description>
Alibre Design Expert is a powerful 3D CAD software designed for professionals in a variety of industries, providing powerful tools for product design, simulation and manufacturing. Alibre Design Expert is part of the Alibre suite of solutions, designed specifically for engineers, designers, and manufacturers who need a comprehensive and user-friendly platform to bring their ideas to life.
3D Modeling &amp;amp; Design
Alibre Design Expert enables users to create accurate 3D models with...
</description></item><item><title>Download iDownerGo 10.10.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 16:31:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idownergo-12439.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idownergo-12439.html
</guid><description>
iDownerGo is the best tool that allows users to download videos, music and playlists from more than 10,000 streaming sites. It can easily convert videos to MP4, MOV, MKV, 3GP, AAC, WAV, FLAC and other formats on PC and Mac. With this amazing program, users can enjoy their favorite media content without restrictions.
iDownerGo Features
	Download any video up to 8K resolution
	Download 1080p videos online from over 10,000 popular streaming sites easily.
	Save any video in various...
</description></item><item><title>Download TeamViewer 15.72.6 + Portable</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 16:31:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-teamviewer-528.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-teamviewer-528.html
</guid><description>
TeamViewer is software that functions to connect and control the remote computer, the ability to connect with any system anywhere from all over the place. This is a support tool users is very convenient. TeamViewer to help users control remote computer becomes much more simple, help you interact and collaborate with others in the exchange and share of information, instruction manual, application software or fix the computer.
TeamViewer as a revolution of computer science. when you have...
</description></item><item><title>Download TeamViewer QuickSupport 15.72.6</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 16:31:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-teamviewer-quicksupport-1933.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-teamviewer-quicksupport-1933.html
</guid><description>
A different version of TeamViewer is TeamViewer QuickSupport is a solution easy to use allows you to share your desktop with a users TeamViewer other to receive technical support or other support. All what you need to do is run the TeamViewer QuickSupport and provides for the remote user ID and your password to grant access to the computer to your desk. Only people you trust can connect to your computer and access password will automatically change after each session.
The software also...
</description></item><item><title>Download XL-Connector 3.6.33.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 16:30:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xl-connector-12415.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xl-connector-12415.html
</guid><description>
XL-Connector is a popular plugin that securely integrates Excel and Salesforce to export, import, refresh and transform data seamlessly with ultra-fast api connection. It provides Salesforce administrators with a comprehensive toolbox that easily performs data and metadata management activities in a familiar Excel environment.
Features
Export from Salesforce to Excel
	Get data from existing Salesforce reports or build your own SOQL queries directly into Excel.
Import data into...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tower 10.1.540</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 16:29:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tower-6598.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tower-6598.html
</guid><description>
Tower is software that helps you build better software, over 100,000 developers and designers are more productive with Tower, the most powerful Git client for Mac and Windows.
Tower Features
	Beautiful new features like interactive facility or Quick Actions and tons of improvements
	Undo everything
	Unique Conflict Wizard
	File history
	Rich documents
	Great customer support...
	Tower helps you master version control with Git.
	One-click cloning
	Automatically store and fetch
	Quickly...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wireshark 4.6.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 16:29:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wireshark-56.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wireshark-56.html
</guid><description>
Wireshark (aka Ethereal) is a network protocol analyzer allows you to capture and examine data from a live network or from a snapshot file on disk.You can browse the captured data in an interactive way and view summary information and details for each package. Wireshark has several powerful features, including a language filter rich display and ability to view flow created back of the TCP.
Wireshark - network protocol analyzer
The program can read the capture file from tcpdump...
</description></item><item><title>Download Vivaldi Browser 7.7.3851.58</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 16:29:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vivaldi-159.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vivaldi-159.html
</guid><description>
Vivaldi is a browser designed for users who have power and offer the option to customize high. You can choose the location of the tabs and the address bar, put the hotkeys for the common tasks and many other features. Also, Vivaldi also provides a number of improvements such as Tab Stacks to group multiple open tabs into a tab, leads to interface less cluttered. Can notes and added a screenshot of a web page while browsing, storing an attachment, and add the URL to easily sort and locate...
</description></item><item><title>Download Delete.On.Reboot 3.44</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 16:28:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-deleteonreboot-2725.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-deleteonreboot-2725.html
</guid><description>
Delete.On.Reboot is a small and effective program when it comes to deleting undeletable files, folders, subfolders in an elegant way on Windows computer boot move again.&amp;nbsp;Unlike the brute force approach of deleting locked files using ThisIsMyFile, which is a regular procedure&amp;nbsp;offered by Microsoft on all Windows operating systems, but here you can still move files to a folder for example to check for possible culprit files. easy to use.
&amp;gt;Delete.On.Reboot -&amp;nbsp;Delete...
</description></item><item><title>Download XnViewMP 1.9.7</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Dec 2025 23:44:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xnview-mp-1074.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xnview-mp-1074.html
</guid><description>
XnViewMP "XnView MP" is the enhanced version of XnView Classic. This is the view and convert images multi-platform powerful, compatible with more than 500 image formats, different today. XnView MP easily export images to about 70 file format is different. Similar to XnConvert, XnView MP also features integrated switch at the same time batch file to help you process photos faster. XnView is another version of the photo viewer but with the ability to support formats more limited.
XnView...
</description></item><item><title>Download BluffTitler Ultimate 16.8.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Dec 2025 23:44:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bluffTitler-ultimate-39.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bluffTitler-ultimate-39.html
</guid><description>
Create 3D titles brilliant for your video with BluffTitler Ultimate. You want to impress your friends and clients with 3D titles interesting? But don't want to spend a fortune on 3D animation, as well as professional software video titling?
BluffTitler is the easiest way to add animated text, 3D spectacular for photos and videos of you! Other 3D programs always seemed too hard to learn and too expensive to justify. But thanks to BluffTitler, I can finally create all the wonderful...
</description></item><item><title>Download VideoProc Converter AI 8.6</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Dec 2025 23:43:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-videoproc-2473.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-videoproc-2473.html
</guid><description>
VideoProc (an improved version of WinX HD Video Converter Deluxe) - processing software the most powerful video designed to edit, cut, crop, merge, adjust, convert and compress (4K) video with full Hardware Acceleration. Is the heir to be improved a lot, VideoProc integrated conversion / compression video UHD, the download at videos (YouTube) with the video editor, gives you the power to control optimal for every video file much music, SD, HD and 4K on your PC. With technology hardware...
</description></item><item><title>Download Google Chrome 143.0.7499.41</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Dec 2025 23:43:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-chrome-1012.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-chrome-1012.html
</guid><description>
Google Chrome web browser is the most used today. Support surf the web, listen to music, watch movies, play web game effective no jerky lag with the internet connection stable. When you are surfing the web or performing an important task, whether it is operation big or small, work or entertainment, then Chrome has the smart features and the speed you need to make, create and explore on the net.
The latest version of Google Chrome is the third 114. But we are providing for users Google...
</description></item><item><title>Download Atlantis Word Processor 5.0.0.12</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Dec 2025 23:42:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-atlantis-word-processor-585.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-atlantis-word-processor-585.html
</guid><description>
Atlantis Word Processor is a word processor app with features format, standard text, autocorrect, and spell check.  Atlantis is a word processor in accordance with most of the tasks handled daily text. The interface is very easy to use and offers the toolbars, hotkeys and sound effects thanh can customize (can turn off). It includes a clip library for quick access to the text or images used regular preview, font format and many other features aimed at improving the process of your...
</description></item><item><title>Download PMAS - PowerShell Multi Activation System 8.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Dec 2025 23:42:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-powershell-tsf-activation-13584.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-powershell-tsf-activation-13584.html
</guid><description>
This advanced PowerShell script is a flexible and modular solution designed for licensing Windows and Office products. It runs a custom .NET library called LibTSforge.dll directly from memory to license Office. It can work in GUI mode or silent mode.
Features
	License management for both Windows and Office products
	Generate product keys with the help of LibTSforge.dll
	User-friendly graphical options with Out-GridView
	Compatible with KMS, MAK, RETAIL, OEM, AVMA license types
	In...
</description></item></channel></rss>