<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 13:52:41 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 13:52:41 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download NewFileTime 7.77</title><pubDate> Wed, 06 Aug 2025 14:17:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-newfiletime-1918.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-newfiletime-1918.html
</guid><description>
NewFileTime is a small utility independence allows you to change date modified, Created and Accessed of any file. You can modify the dates for one or multiple files, even entire folder structures at the same time. The date can be changed to a date and time specific or you can choose to make each file "older" or "younger," according to a certain number of days.
NewFileTime - edit time files
You can add files simply via Drag and Drop or by import from a folder. In any case, it opens...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft .NET Desktop Runtime 9.0.8 Build 35118</title><pubDate> Wed, 06 Aug 2025 14:16:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-net-desktop-runtime-5748.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-net-desktop-runtime-5748.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft .NET Desktop Runtime allows you to run existing Windows desktop applications. This release includes the .NET Runtime, which requires no separate installation. The Microsoft .NET Desktop Runtime redistributable package installs the .NET Desktop Runtime and related files needed to run many applications that use this programming language.
This is Microsoft's comprehensive and consistent programming model for building applications with stunningly intuitive user experiences,...
</description></item><item><title>Download ON1 Resize AI 2026 v20.0.0.17231</title><pubDate> Wed, 06 Aug 2025 14:15:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-on1-resize-2055.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-on1-resize-2055.html
</guid><description>
ON1 Resize 2019 is the edited final image when you need to zoom in the highest quality - with technology genuine Fractals® - to resize your photo to print. You can quickly change the image size without losing sharpness or detail. ON1 Resize also includes one of the fastest ways to view, remove and edit photos.
ON1 Resize - Zoom, change photo size
The features of ON1 Resize
	ON1 Resize using interpolation algorithm based on fractal - helps quickly change the image size without losing...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ashampoo UnInstaller 16.00.00</title><pubDate> Wed, 06 Aug 2025 14:14:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-uninstaller-247.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-uninstaller-247.html
</guid><description>
When you remove a program, but maybe some files will not be completely deleted, it will remain on your computer in hidden mode, thus causing your computer to slow down and not optimize. . But not with Ashampoo UnInstaller. Ashampoo UnInstaller is a powerful program uninstaller to completely remove unnecessary software, free up your drive, speed up your computer.
In addition, with Ashampoo UnInstaller you can also manage fonts, clean the registry, possibly, have support for defragmenting...
</description></item><item><title>Download R-Wipe &amp;amp; Clean 20.0 Build 2519</title><pubDate> Wed, 06 Aug 2025 14:14:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-wipe-clean-891.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-wipe-clean-891.html
</guid><description>
R-Wipe &amp;amp; Clean is software to delete junk files, unnecessary files from your computer to release the storage space and speed up your computer. In addition, R-Wipe &amp;amp; Clean also unleash the capacity of your drive and delete information invasion of privacy on different operations online and offline including your internet history and cookies, the list of downloaded files and documents were open, buffer different data, temporary files and many other items, created by the operating...
</description></item><item><title>Download Aiseesoft Screen Recorder 3.1.28</title><pubDate> Wed, 06 Aug 2025 14:07:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aiseesoft-screen-recorder-631.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aiseesoft-screen-recorder-631.html
</guid><description>
Aiseesoft Screen Recorder is the software supports recording, take a screenshot with any videos and save them back with high quality. Apps screen recording video strong this can help you get online movies and radio, game capture, make video tutorials, record videos, capture screenshot, etc. on Windows 10/8/7.
Screen capture software helps you record almost any video screen you want. You can use it to record online video, game, podcast, webinars, lectures, presentations, Skype calls,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Transcend SSD Scope 4.26</title><pubDate> Wed, 06 Aug 2025 14:06:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-transcend-ssd-scope-7662.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-transcend-ssd-scope-7662.html
</guid><description>
Transcend SSD Scope is an advanced and user-friendly software that makes it easier than ever to clone and maintain a healthy and efficient SSD. It brings together the latest technology to determine the health and optimize the performance of your SSD.
Useful features of Transcend SSD Scope include:
	View drive information
	View SMART status
	Diagnostic scan
	Clear Security
	Updating the firmware
	Enable TRIM, Health Indicator, and System Clone.
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Downloader 9.15.3</title><pubDate> Wed, 06 Aug 2025 14:04:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html
</guid><description>
YTD Youtube Downloader is an application that reliable and intuitive, allowing you to quickly download YouTube videos and save them to your computer. You can also convert the media files to the format desired video or extract audio streams and save separately. YTD Youtube Downloader lets you save your favorite clips of yourself from Youtube, Facebook, Vimeo and Dailymotion to your desktop. The software supports URLS from many web site hosting, multimedia and allows you to download desired...
</description></item><item><title>Download Oxynger KeyShield Premium 2.5.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 06 Aug 2025 14:04:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oxynger-keyshield-premium-8016.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oxynger-keyshield-premium-8016.html
</guid><description>
Oxynger KeyShield Premium is a private and secure virtual keyboard used to protect your passwords from keyloggers by allowing you to enter sensitive data such as passwords. password and credit card number, with the help of the on-screen keyboard. It offers the world's best protection against recording keystrokes. It is 100% protected against hook-based, API-based, kernel/driver and hardware keyloggers.
Oxynger KeyShield Premium is protected from creating screenshots or videos. Many...
</description></item><item><title>Download Zero Install 2.27.5</title><pubDate> Wed, 06 Aug 2025 13:58:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zero-install-1632.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zero-install-1632.html
</guid><description>
Zero Install is a system, install the software distribution cross africa focus. Other features include full support for shared libraries (with the SAT for resolution dependent), share between users, and integration with the package manager original foundation. Zero Install supports both binary packages and source and works on Linux systems , OS X , Unix and Windows. It is completely open source.
Zero Install - System software installation
Zero Install also has a number of interesting...
</description></item><item><title>Download ET Optimizer 6.07.15</title><pubDate> Wed, 06 Aug 2025 13:57:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-et-optimizer-9574.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-et-optimizer-9574.html
</guid><description>
ET-Optimizer is a free, open source script to improve your computer's overall performance and optimize it for your workflow through optimized scripting. With this optimization, setup takes little effort. The script is developed from many sources found on the Internet, tested and updated for different versions of the system. The whole script is contained in 1 file, it uses: command prompt, powershell, power plan configuration, startup configuration, registry changes, network interface...
</description></item><item><title>Download PowerRun 1.8</title><pubDate> Wed, 06 Aug 2025 13:57:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-powerrun-6631.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-powerrun-6631.html
</guid><description>
PowerRun is a mobile-free software that launches rededit.exe, Cmd.exe or other software with the same privileges as TrustedInstaller.
Why do you need it? Sometimes only running as Administrator is not enough, it may be that the file or registration key is locked or unable to edit, PowerRun a tool with this powerful privilege is very able to resolve that, PowerRun does not require any installation or additional file dll.
New features:
	Edit the program failed to save the size of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download MiniMeters 1.0.3.1865</title><pubDate> Wed, 06 Aug 2025 13:56:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minimeters-9410.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minimeters-9410.html
</guid><description>
MiniMeters is a simple standalone sound meter application for Windows. Monitor your System Audio*, Any Input, or insert the MiniMeter Server Plug-in (VST3/AU/CLAP) at the end of your main channel in the DAW of your choice. Customize the layout in a horizontal bar (perfect for above or below the audio engine of your choice) or pop out into modules to create custom layouts.
Features of MiniMeters
	6 modules to choose from to build your perfect metering setup: Spectrogram, Waveform,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Araxis Merge Professional 2025.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 06 Aug 2025 13:56:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-araxis-merge-professional-805.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-araxis-merge-professional-805.html
</guid><description>
Araxis Merge Professional is a software program created exclusively to help you visually compare, merge and synchronize text files and directories. Araxis Merge 2018 - control. Let's work efficiency. Join tens of thousands of other advantages in software Araxis.
The layout of the program Araxis Merge Professional
The app's interface has a modern design and it's quite intuitive. The top of the main window contains all the actions you might need to use, in the form of buttons, while at the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Photo Supreme 2025.3.1.7979</title><pubDate> Wed, 06 Aug 2025 13:55:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photo-supreme-430.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photo-supreme-430.html
</guid><description>
Photo Supreme is a software product management professional pictures of idimager. With Photo Supreme you can arrange, manage back stock photo archive of yourself and share them with you here and relatives easily via Email or Facebook. Photo Supreme provides users method to sort images effective, logical, as well as edit and share your photos with friends and relatives in the family. Especially the Photo Supreme allows to work with multiple image formats and support mounting support,...
</description></item><item><title>Download ASUS GPU Tweak III 2.0.0.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 06 Aug 2025 13:55:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-asus-gpu-tweak-3252.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-asus-gpu-tweak-3252.html
</guid><description>
ASUS GPU Tweak is a tools overclocking powerful and full-featured allows you to significantly enhance the performance of the graphics processor ASUS. Utility that allows you to get the best results just by few mouse clicks. ASUS GPU Tweak has a number mode allows you to adjust the parameters of graphics according to the specific needs of his. Mode OC allows you to benefit from maximum performance supplied by your graphics card. Game play mode allows you to play the game using the default...
</description></item><item><title>Download FontBase Awesome 2.22.67</title><pubDate> Wed, 06 Aug 2025 13:54:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fontbase-awesome-12674.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fontbase-awesome-12674.html
</guid><description>
FontBase is a modern font manager designed for designers, providing many features to enhance font management across a variety of platforms. With a FontBase Awesome subscription, in addition to all the free features, you'll get a suite of advanced features to improve your font management workflow.
FontBase Awesome Features
	OpenType features: The largest set of supported OpenType features among font software at your fingertips.
	Symbols: View and copy any icon for any language and font...
</description></item><item><title>Download RarmaRadio Pro 2.77.5</title><pubDate> Wed, 06 Aug 2025 13:54:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rarmaradio-pro-789.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rarmaradio-pro-789.html
</guid><description>
RarmaRadio Pro is the professional version allows you to listen to and record radio stations from around the world. While listening to the favorite radio station, you can record anytime you want by RarmaRadio Pro. Browse through the radio stations or just select a random station and enjoy Internet radio! You have full control of his radio, allowing you to add or delete a station anytime you want. Need to play a station from another application then just enable global hotkeys and control it...
</description></item><item><title>Download SonarQube Data Center Edition 2025.4.1.111832</title><pubDate> Wed, 06 Aug 2025 13:53:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sonarqube-data-center-edition-8059.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sonarqube-data-center-edition-8059.html
</guid><description>
SonarQube empowers all developers to write cleaner and safer code. Join the Open Community of over 200,000 developer groups. SonarQube provides reports on duplicate code, coding standards, unit testing, code coverage, code complexity, comments, bugs, and security recommendations.
Features of SonarQube
	Detect complex bugs to prevent undefined behavior from affecting end users.
	Fix your apps' vulnerabilities and learn about AppSec along the way with Secure Hotspot.
	Make sure your...
</description></item><item><title>Download Universal Virus Sniffer 5.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 06 Aug 2025 13:52:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-universal-virus-sniffer-8100.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-universal-virus-sniffer-8100.html
</guid><description>
Universal Virus Sniffer is a powerful yet easy-to-use tool for finding and removing malware components and viruses. This program is intended for advanced users only.
Features of Universal Virus Sniffer
	Three basic modes: work with active, inactive, remote systems.
	Work with the registry in three modes: remove the link to the virus, fix the problem after dealing with the virus.
	Create autorun image. (Example: for remote assistant).
	Fourth mode of operation: cimulyatsiya works in...
</description></item><item><title>Download Fort Firewall 3.18.11</title><pubDate> Wed, 06 Aug 2025 13:50:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fort-firewall-6439.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fort-firewall-6439.html
</guid><description>
Fort Firewall is a network security system that monitors and controls network traffic and goes based on predefined security rules. A firewall often establishes a barrier between a trusted internal network and untrusted external networks, such as the Internet.
Features of Fort Firewall
	Filter by network address, application group
	Support of representative characters in the name path name
	Application group speed limit
	Access Traffic Statistics
	Display bandwidth
	Based on the...
</description></item><item><title>Download TubeMate Downloader 5.21.3</title><pubDate> Wed, 06 Aug 2025 13:50:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubemate-downloader-4250.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubemate-downloader-4250.html
</guid><description>
TubeMate Downloader is a smart application that lets you download any clip you want from the website hosting the main video and convert them in when download at or then. If you need a simple and effective tool to download videos, you can give it a try. With TubeMate Downloader, you can directly drag and drop video link from your browser into the drop-down box or application window to start downloading. You don't even need to copy and paste the video URL.
TubeMate Downloader - Support...
</description></item><item><title>Download COAA PlanePlotter 6.7.2.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 06 Aug 2025 13:47:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coaa-planeplotter-7840.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coaa-planeplotter-7840.html
</guid><description>
PlanePlotter receives and decodes digital position reports directly from the aircraft and plots them on a chart. Using PlanePlotter, you can see the radar-like display of all aircraft around you transmitting the appropriate digital messages including ACARS, ADS-B and HFDL.
PlanePlotter Features
	PlanePlotter displays a table showing messages received and decoded from direct plane transmissions.
	PlanePlotter stores all digital data it receives and decodes into a log...
</description></item><item><title>Download PVS-Studio 7.38.96564.1952</title><pubDate> Wed, 06 Aug 2025 13:46:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pvs-studio-1480.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pvs-studio-1480.html
</guid><description>
PVS-Studio is software that performs static code analysis and generate a report to help programmers find and fix bugs. PVS-Studio implements a series of check code, it is also useful to search the prints wrong error and Copy-Paste. Examples of such errors: V501, V517, V522, V523, V3001.
The main value of static analysis is in regular use, hence the error is identified and corrected at the earliest stages. There's no point of wasting 50 hours to search for a fault can be found with static...
</description></item><item><title>Download ASBYTE Syncing NET 6.5.0.3898</title><pubDate> Wed, 06 Aug 2025 13:46:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-asbyte-syncing-net-9468.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-asbyte-syncing-net-9468.html
</guid><description>
ASBYTE Syncing NET provides a unique and powerful Outlook, Exchange and document synchronization tool for companies and professionals from all sectors, as well as any individual need to sync multiple PCs without using a server Real-time, automatic synchronization for Outlook, Exchange and documents anytime, anywhere.
Features of ASBYTE Syncing NET
	The combination of Outlook and Files synchronization in one powerful tool for companies, professionals and individuals who need to sync...
</description></item></channel></rss>