<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 20:41:51 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 20:41:51 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Tor Browser 15.0.6</title><pubDate> Tue, 17 Feb 2026 23:27:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tor-browser-1833.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tor-browser-1833.html
</guid><description>
Tor Browser also has full name is Tor Browser Bundle is a web browser give you ability to access the internet safety and security your personal information as well as sensitive documents absolutely. By Tor Browser Bundle will automatically change the IP address on the machine to hide the identity when surfing the web. Tor Browser is free web browser full-featured basic and advanced allows you to leverage the Tor network anonymously without need to make any configuration changes or install...
</description></item><item><title>Download Inno Setup Compiler 6.7.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 17 Feb 2026 23:27:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-inno-setup-compiler-2655.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-inno-setup-compiler-2655.html
</guid><description>
Inno Setup Compiler is a system installed based on free software created by Delphi by Jordan Russell. The first version was released in 1997. QuickStart of Inno Setup include main Inno Setup and also includes an option to install the script editor Inno Script Studio. The script editor is not official and is not mandatory for general use, but help Inno Setup easier to use.
Inno Setup Compiler - software create file setup.exe
The features of Inno Setup Compiler
	Support for every...
</description></item><item><title>Download Futuremark SystemInfo 5.91.1460</title><pubDate> Tue, 17 Feb 2026 23:26:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-futuremark-systeminfo-2568.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-futuremark-systeminfo-2568.html
</guid><description>
Futuremark SystemInfo is a small program created to conduct diagnostic analysis complete all kinds of processes, as well as equipment used on a personal computer of you. According to the author, you can use this tool as a component reference in the application be supported, it will determine the version of your operating system and other information about the hardware.
Note that Windows XP, 3DMark06, and PCMark05 are no longer be Futuremark support. Function SystemInfo on Windows XP is...
</description></item><item><title>Download Office Installer Plus 1.36</title><pubDate> Tue, 17 Feb 2026 20:37:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-installer-plus-11616.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-installer-plus-11616.html
</guid><description>
Office Installer Plus is the next version of Ratiborus that helps you download, install, update, uninstall, activate office 2024, 2021, 2019, 2016 and it has added an Office activator to the program. submit. Office Installer+ is considered a useful application that helps users install and manage office applications from Microsoft Office easily and quickly. This application is designed to help users save time and effort when installing popular office applications such as Word, Excel,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Advanced SystemCare Pro Portable 19.2.0.188</title><pubDate> Tue, 17 Feb 2026 20:37:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-systemcare-pro-portable-8964.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-systemcare-pro-portable-8964.html
</guid><description>
Advanced SystemCare Pro Portable (a portable version) is system optimization and maintenance software developed by IObit. It is designed to help users improve the performance and speed of their Windows computers by cleaning junk files, optimizing system settings, and fixing various system errors.
It specializes in ONE-Click solutions to detect, clean, repair, speed up and ultimately protect PC. With new system technology, Advanced SystemCare Pro lets you run your computer faster....
</description></item><item><title>Download KMSAuto Lite 1.9.9.9 b09</title><pubDate> Tue, 17 Feb 2026 20:36:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kmsauto-lite-188.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kmsauto-lite-188.html
</guid><description>
KMSAuto Lite - software activate Windows and Office license Windows XP, Windows Vista, 7, Windows 8, 8.1, 10, server 2008, 2008 R2, 2012, 2012 R2, Office 2010/2013/2016. In addition, you can activate Office 2010 VL on Windows XP. The switches provide access to the key GVLK installed and configured the scheduled task.
KMSAuto Lite
Features KMSAuto Lite:
The program does NOT require any version of .NET Framework.
is product activate windows and office license the most reliable...
</description></item><item><title>Download Perfectly Clear WorkBench 5.0.2.3103</title><pubDate> Tue, 17 Feb 2026 20:35:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfectly-clear-workbench-6892.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfectly-clear-workbench-6892.html
</guid><description>
Perfectly Clear Workbench is an application that uses image editing libraries Perfectly Clear by Athentech and is provided to demonstrate the capabilities of the Perfectly Clear processing libraries, which recognize faces and allow quick export of processing settings for use.
One of the key features in Workbench is the ability to "export to API" when saving a Preset. This allows you to make image edits in Workbench and adjust the settings to suit your editing style and needs. You can...
</description></item><item><title>Download MathType Portable 7.11.1.462</title><pubDate> Tue, 17 Feb 2026 20:35:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mathtype-portable-7171.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mathtype-portable-7171.html
</guid><description>
MathType Portable is a powerful interactive equation editor for Windows and helps you create mathematical notation for word processing, web pages, desktop publishing, and so on. desks, presentations, elearning and for TeX, LaTeX and MathML documents. Features are constantly being updated into the latest MathType to help users get more done, saving time when creating documents. What do you think, when you can enter equations as easy as writing math on paper and pencil using the...
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 8.0.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 17 Feb 2026 20:34:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-11-7760.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-11-7760.html
</guid><description>
TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 is a program that allows users to discover hidden settings in Windows 11. This application is specially designed for Windows 11, groups many registry settings and distribute them from the easy and secure user interface. With TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 you can move the Windows taskbar to the top and resize the taskbar by editing the registry value. With any application that modifies the registry, we recommend that you have a backup copy...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinToUSB Enterprise Portable 10.5</title><pubDate> Tue, 17 Feb 2026 20:34:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wintousb-portable-11910.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wintousb-portable-11910.html
</guid><description>
WinToUSB Portable (Windows To USB) is a handy tool that allows you to install and run a fully functional Windows operating system on an external hard drive, USB flash drive or Thunderbolt drive. It has a user-friendly interface that makes it easy for users to install and run Windows on a USB drive. It is suitable for both beginners and advanced users.
It's easy and effective, in just 3 steps and a few minutes you can create your first Windows 11/10/8/7 or portable Windows Server...
</description></item><item><title>Download Allavsoft Video Downloader Converter Portable 3.28.8.9526</title><pubDate> Tue, 17 Feb 2026 20:33:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allavsoft-video-downloader-converter-portable-12064.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allavsoft-video-downloader-converter-portable-12064.html
</guid><description>
Allavsoft Video Downloader Converter Portable is a portable version of the software application that allows users to download videos from various websites and convert them to different formats. It supports popular video sharing platforms such as YouTube Vimeo, Dailymotion and many others.
Besides downloading videos in their original format, Allavsoft also has a one-click feature to download as well as convert downloaded videos to popular video formats like MP4, AVI, WMV, MOV, MPEG-1,...
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 8.0.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 17 Feb 2026 20:33:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-10-7759.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-10-7759.html
</guid><description>
TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 is a utility that allows users to discover hidden settings in Windows 10. This application is specially designed for Windows 10, groups many registry settings and provide them from an easy and secure user interface. With TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 you can move the Windows taskbar to the top and resize the taskbar by editing the registry value. With any application that modifies the registry, we recommend that you have a backup copy to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Reg Organizer Portable 9.90</title><pubDate> Tue, 17 Feb 2026 20:32:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reg-organizer-portable-3534.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reg-organizer-portable-3534.html
</guid><description>
Reg Organizer Portable is a software solution that allows you to enhance the operational capabilities of the computer by cleaning and defragmenting the key registry of Windows, uninstall the program little or no need to use fix a bug in the system. Review ability to optimize the registry, Reg Organizer Portable feature support automatically shutdown computer after complete the task. In process handling and cleaning systems, you will not be able to open, disposal the manipulate on other...
</description></item><item><title>Download CapCut PC 8.1.1.3417 / 8.2.0.3433 Beta 1</title><pubDate> Tue, 17 Feb 2026 20:32:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capcut-pc-9995.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capcut-pc-9995.html
</guid><description>
CapCut PC is a simple video editing tool that you can freely use anywhere. You can create videos on your browser, desktop and laptop, or on your phone. Versatile editing, magical AI tools, team collaboration, and built-in assets. Create videos in a whole new way.
You can edit videos based on editing the timeline, in the process you can add different elements and effects to the video to give the best effect to your work. It is a simple and intuitive set of editing tools and effects that...
</description></item><item><title>Download Psiphon 186.20260217</title><pubDate> Tue, 17 Feb 2026 20:31:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-psiphon-7347.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-psiphon-7347.html
</guid><description>
Psiphon is a firewall bypass tool by Psiphon Inc. Uses VPN, SSH and HTTP Proxy technology to give you uncensored access to Internet content. Your Psiphon app automatically learns about new hotspots to maximize your chances of bypassing censorship.
The way the software works is that Psiphon constantly changes the proxy, so the user's IP address is also constantly changing, the server will not detect the user's real address, so you can feel free. roof. access to websites and software...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mozilla Thunderbird 147.0.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:44:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thunderbird-1788.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thunderbird-1788.html
</guid><description>
Thunderbird is an email program full featured with controls spam integration, mail filter, address book, news groups and more. It provides a clean interface and easy to use (customizable). Thunderbird also provides the security features such as S / MIME, digital signing, message encryption, support for certificates and security devices.
Before using this feature, you should review the settings IMAP, SMTP, and SSL/TLS his. Now, what all you need to do is provide your name, email address,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Media Player Classic Home Cinema 2.6.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:40:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-media-player-classic-home-cinema-2839.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-media-player-classic-home-cinema-2839.html
</guid><description>
Media Player Classic Home Cinema is a multimedia compact for Microsoft Windows 32 bit and 64 bit. MPC mimics the interface of Windows Media Player 6.4, but provides most options and features available in the modern means. Media Player Classic Home Cinema for free 100% no advertising, so you can directly access content and enjoy media playback without being distracted.
With Media Player Classic Home, you can now change the design a multimedia of the custom toolbar. There is a range to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Visual Studio Code 1.109.4</title><pubDate> Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:39:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-visual-studio-code-3182.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-visual-studio-code-3182.html
</guid><description>
Visual Studio Code is the encryption tool of Microsoft has met most of the needs of the developer. Environment this encoding was introduced to compete with other products such as Sublime and Nodepad ++ . Microsoft, in its new product, has not been released in many years, has provided many features in a simple environment. In addition to the familiar with a dozen programming languages, the syntax and get to know coding language as soon as be encrypted and allows for syntax highlighting, it...
</description></item><item><title>Download K-Lite Codec Pack Full 19.5.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:38:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-115.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-115.html
</guid><description>
K Lite Codec Pack Full brings pc users an optimal solution for watching movies, listening to music, support most popular format today by using collection codec rich. This software also allows you to refine the quality of videos and music to enjoy, create a list of music and video to comfortable enjoy.
Prompt to software, listen to music, watch movies, currently, part, user will prompt to programs like VLC or KMP ... With VLC, it was too familiar with users, not just watch videos, listen...
</description></item><item><title>Download CrystalDiskInfo Portable 9.8.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:38:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-crystaldiskinfo-portable-11173.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-crystaldiskinfo-portable-11173.html
</guid><description>
CrystalDiskInfo Portable (portable version) is utility software designed to monitor the health and performance of hard disk drives (HDD) and solid state drives (SSD). This tool is often used to check the status of drives in a computer to ensure they are operating normally and predict possible drive errors.
It provides detailed information about the drive, such as temperature, drive status, total operating hours, etc. Software to read S.M.A.R.T. (Self-Monitoring, Analysis and Reporting...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube Downloader 3.9.18 (1602)</title><pubDate> Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:37:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube Downloader  is a dedicated software that helps users  downloading youtube videos  Favorites on PC for offline viewing. With MediaHuman YouTube  Downloader  you can download videos from youtube website to your computer with  fast speed , with special software development technology that automatically receives videos from Websites, in addition to the ability to download videos from software websites, can convert downloaded video formats to various formats for the purpose...
</description></item><item><title>Download K-Lite Codec Pack Mega 19.5.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:36:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-mega-3202.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-mega-3202.html
</guid><description>
K-Lite Mega Codec Pack is a collection of components needed for audio playback and the video in the player DirectShow like Windows Media Player, Media Center, and Media Player Classic. This is the latest beta version, Pack Codec K-Lite latest stable. The Mega variant is the biggest of the four variants of the codec pack. It provides everything you need to play all audio and video files. In addition, it also contains some codecs ACM / VFW can be used by the application coding / video...
</description></item><item><title>Download Quick Access Popup 12.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:35:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quick-access-popup-984.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quick-access-popup-984.html
</guid><description>
Quick Access Popup  ( QAP ) is a software that provides quick access to files, files, windows applications and is  shortcut manager , mouse and keyboard.  Quick Access Popup  helps you quickly move between FILE, DOCUMENT, APPS in Windows Explorer or file dialog to quickly launch applications, documents or web pages at once 
To launch the pop-up menu, click the  QAP  icon in the Notifications area, press the Middle mouse button, or press Windows + W (these triggers can be changed under...
</description></item><item><title>Download Easy System Utility Pro 1.1.51</title><pubDate> Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:34:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easy-system-utility-pro-12380.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easy-system-utility-pro-12380.html
</guid><description>
Easy System Utility Pro is a powerful, all-in-one program designed for Windows 10 and 11 users. This versatile tool should be your primary choice to improve your computing experience ! This is the complete version with additional and enhanced features. It will help you easily determine your computer's hardware specifications with a system overview. You can view the operating system, CPU model, GPU, Memory, Motherboard, Network and even drivers.
It also supports launching programs,...
</description></item><item><title>Download K-Lite Codec Pack Update 19.5.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:34:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-update-5145.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-update-5145.html
</guid><description>
K-Lite Codec Pack Update is the update of the set of codecs and related tools. Codec stands for Compressor-decompressor. Codec is necessary to encode and decode (play) audio and video. K-Lite Codec Pack Update is designed as a user-friendly solution with users to play all movie files your. With Codec Pack K-Lite, you can play 99% of all the movies found on your computer. A number of packages codec is not friendly with computers, as they tend to slow down Windows, break down multimedia...
</description></item></channel></rss>