<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 17:33:21 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 17:33:21 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download PDF Annotator 9.0.0.929</title><pubDate> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 16:48:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-annotator-178.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-annotator-178.html
</guid><description>
PDF Annotator software user open any PDF file and add annotations, using the mouse or pen Tablet PC, directly on the Page of the PDF file. PDF Annotator allows users to perform editing operations on PDF files such as: add notes, edit signature, highlight, insert images or text... From the this useful tool, you can completely modify PDF files as you like in order to meet the different work.
PDF Annotator
With the PDF Annotator the document has annotations can then be saved directly back...
</description></item><item><title>Download GoldWave 7.03</title><pubDate> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 16:48:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-goldwave-1577.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-goldwave-1577.html
</guid><description>
GoldWave is a sound editor comprehensive digital be most appreciated. GoldWave ideal for those who work with sound to edit CD, restore, archive, speech analysis, radio and TV, Java and web pages, games or just to entertain. You can use it to do everything from reply elaborately message to content audio CD professional, high quality.
GoldWave - edit digital audio
The work that GoldWave done:
	Play, edit, mix, and analyze audio
	Record audio from cassettes, vinyl records, radio, etc....
</description></item><item><title>Download Topaz Video AI Pro 7.1.6 / 1.0.5</title><pubDate> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 16:47:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-video-enhance-ai-3733.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-video-enhance-ai-3733.html
</guid><description>
Topaz Video Enhance AI is a tool to increase video quality with this great technology ONE. Topaz Video Enhance WHO wide open your video to resolutions up to 8K with the details and consistency of motion. Until the present, there is no way to re-create a perfect high resolution video from the footage is low resolution. From the family film to SD low quality to DVD quality and more than that, Video Enhance WHO will convert your video into the footage is upgrade clear with resolutions up to...
</description></item><item><title>Download GoodSync Enterprise 12.9.12.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 16:46:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-goodsync-enterprise-163.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-goodsync-enterprise-163.html
</guid><description>
GoodSync Enterprise is a software that saves files and files easily and is reliable. It automatically analyts, synchronize and backup your email, family photos, contacts, MP3, financial documentation and other important files-between desktop computers, laptops, servers, external drives and Windows Mobile devices as well as remotely via FTP , SFTP, WebDAV and more. The GoodSync synchronized software combines bulletproof reliability with an extremely easy interface to compare, synchronize...
</description></item><item><title>Download Unicodia 3.0.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 16:46:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-unicodia-8521.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-unicodia-8521.html
</guid><description>
Unicodia is free, open source software that can be used as an alternative character map for your Windows machine. The interface contains everything you need, allowing you to easily cycle through all the available ASCII symbols and copy them to the clipboard. Uncicodia is a great alternative to your standard Unicode characters and is filled with symbols/characters that make it useful for a number of different uses.
Features of Unicodia
	In Windows 10/11 — all characters of Unicode 15...
</description></item><item><title>Download GiliSoft PDF Editor 8.2.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 16:46:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-pdf-editor-13719.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-pdf-editor-13719.html
</guid><description>
GiliSoft PDF Editor is a user-friendly and feature-rich PDF editor that simplifies the process of editing PDF files. With a comprehensive set of features, it helps users improve their office work efficiency. Text editing capabilities allow users to make quick changes to PDF documents by selecting, editing, and formatting text with ease.
Advanced image editing tools allow users to manipulate images in PDF files, including resizing, cropping, rotating, and applying various image...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tenorshare 4DDiG 10.6.5.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 16:45:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tenorshare-4ddigs-pro-5629.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tenorshare-4ddigs-pro-5629.html
</guid><description>
Tenorshare 4DDiG is software to recover data from laptop / PC, external drive or USB flash disk. Recover Windows partitions, such as raw partitions, formatted partitions, damaged partitions, etc. Recover lost or deleted photos, videos, audio, videos, documents, etc.
With 4DDiG, you can recover many different types of data from this powerful Windows Data Recovery Tool feature. No matter what you have lost, 4DDiG is capable of recovering deleted files Windows 10 / 8.1 / 8/7 /...
</description></item><item><title>Download ExamDiff Pro Master Edition 16.0.1.11</title><pubDate> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 16:45:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-examdiff-pro-master-312.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-examdiff-pro-master-312.html
</guid><description>
ExamDiff Pro Master is a tool to compare files and folders intuitive and easy to use, intuitive and easy to use for Windows. ExamDiff Pro Master has unique features distinguishes ExamDiff Pro with the program compare other. ExamDiff Pro Master to help perform reviews of code and share other reports with your colleagues and compare local website with FTP server by plug-ins more integrated.
ExamDiff Pro Master can create a snapshot folder for comparison and storage in the future, compare...
</description></item><item><title>Download 4K Tokkit Pro 25.4.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 16:44:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-tokkit-pro-6753.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-tokkit-pro-6753.html
</guid><description>
4K Tokkit Pro is an application created to bulk download TikTok content., save TikTok videos, captions, entire accounts, hashtags and single videos in high quality. . Watch TikToks offline, browse your TikTok feed without ads, repost clips to other social networks.
Features of 4K Tokkit Pro
	Download videos in bulk from your TikTok account. Save all videos from profile and get TikTok user's profile picture.
	Automatically get updates from your favorite TikTok creators and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Duplicate File Finder Professional 2025 v407</title><pubDate> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 16:44:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-duplicate-file-finder-professional-4425.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-duplicate-file-finder-professional-4425.html
</guid><description>
Duplicate File Finder Professional is a compact application helps you quickly find and remove files duplicate on the computer. With Duplicate File Finder Professional you can choose any folder on the hard drive or use the folder standard user and our app will analyze the deep content of the selected folder to copy. It will take only a few seconds. The files will be compared by the hash algorithm MD5, which means they will be compared by content, not by name. Then, use our convenient...
</description></item><item><title>Download TreeSize Free 4.8.0.606</title><pubDate> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 16:43:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-treesize-free-10656.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-treesize-free-10656.html
</guid><description>
TreeSize Free is a free disk space manager for Windows, it will show you the size of folders including its subfolders in a similar fashion like Explorer. Large folders can be identified at a glance thanks to the gradient bar displayed in the background. All scan results can be detailed at the file level and filters, e.g. for files of a certain type, can be applied.
Features of TreeSize Free
	Search space: clean up hard drive space
	Break down hard drive space usage to file level:...
</description></item><item><title>Download Screencapt Professional 2.007</title><pubDate> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 16:42:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-screencapt-professional-12260.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-screencapt-professional-12260.html
</guid><description>
Screencapt Professional is powerful Windows software for screen recording that allows you to accurately and easily record any on-screen activity. Whether you want to create tutorials, record webinars, or simply record your favorite games, Screencapt gives you all the tools you need.
With Screencapt, you can record the entire screen, a selected area, or a specific window. This flexibility makes Screencapt the perfect screen recorder for any type of application. Thanks to the built-in...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Downloader 9.18.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 16:42:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html
</guid><description>
YTD Youtube Downloader is an application that reliable and intuitive, allowing you to quickly download YouTube videos and save them to your computer. You can also convert the media files to the format desired video or extract audio streams and save separately. YTD Youtube Downloader lets you save your favorite clips of yourself from Youtube, Facebook, Vimeo and Dailymotion to your desktop. The software supports URLS from many web site hosting, multimedia and allows you to download desired...
</description></item><item><title>Download UltFone Windows Data Recovery 10.6.5.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 16:41:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ultfone-windows-data-recovery-14195.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ultfone-windows-data-recovery-14195.html
</guid><description>
UltFone Windows Data Recovery is a comprehensive data recovery software designed for Windows system to recover lost or deleted files from various storage devices such as hard drive, USB drive, SD card, etc. The software supports recovering many file types, including photos, videos, documents, music and archive files. The software offers two scanning modes—quick scan for recently deleted files and deep scan for comprehensive recovery, and also allows users to preview recoverable files...
</description></item><item><title>Download Macro Commander Pro+ 2.7.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 16:41:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-macro-commander-pro-12815.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-macro-commander-pro-12815.html
</guid><description>
Macro Commander is an all-in-one data entry and desktop automation software. It is designed to empower users to easily create, manage, and trigger macros and scripts to automate manual, repetitive tasks quickly and error-free. Its clean user interface allows for quick and easy creation and organization of macros either manually or using the built-in macro recorder.
While Macro Commander offers powerful data entry features to quickly and easily fill in data in other applications, it also...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tixati 3.39.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 16:41:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tixati-2355.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tixati-2355.html
</guid><description>
A Bittorrent free, good have been updated, are designed for operating systems Microsoft Windows and Linux (for the OS Monday, you can download a version from the official website of the developer). The difference between a client and a large number of others is that users are provided a wide opportunity to control the torrent of them, they also write on your program that it consumes less memory than uTorrent and Halite famous.
Tixati - App download torrent
Tixati is also ready to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft Safety Scanner 1.441.23</title><pubDate> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 16:40:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-safety-scanner-4512.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-safety-scanner-4512.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft Safety Scanner is a scanning tool designed to find and remove malware from a Windows computer. Just download and run the scan to find malware and try to reverse the changes made by the threat identified. Microsoft Safety Scanner has the ability to remove virus, spyware and files other dangers on your computer, Microsoft Safety Scanner completes scanning tasks in just a few minutes, while the computer is moderate stress during handling.
In other words, no real time protection...
</description></item><item><title>Download XRECODE3 1.174 Beta</title><pubDate> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 16:40:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xrecode-iii-2915.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xrecode-iii-2915.html
</guid><description>
"Xrecode II" is the switch and grab the audio allows you to convert from mp2, mp3, ac3, aiff, wma, amr, ogg, ape, flac, cue, mpc, wv, tak, mid, cue, m4b, tta, wav, dts , wav (rf64), m4a, mp4, ra, shn, rm, avi, aac, mpg, vob, mka, mkv, flv, Mov, swf, ofr, divx, wmv, spx, mp3, m4v, 3gp, m2v, 3g2, m4v, m2ts, ts, adts, tak, xm, mod, it, s3m, alac, umx, mtm, mlp to m4a, ape, flac, mp4 (using NeroAAC), raw, ogg, wav, wav (rf64) , wma, mpc, WavPack, mp2, ofr, Speex, ac3, tak, aiff, snd, Shorten...
</description></item><item><title>Download Anthemion Jutoh 3.27</title><pubDate> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 16:39:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anthemion-jutoh-801.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anthemion-jutoh-801.html
</guid><description>
Anthemion Jutoh is a software to create electronic books in popular formats and design your own cover with editor, cover integrated. Create your project in seconds from existing files using The guide to new projects; or create your book from scratch using the text editor as integrated.
Anthemion Jutoh - Create ebooks
The features of Anthemion Jutoh
	Quick to generate Epub, Mobipocket or other format of your.
	Fast to edit content and switch between variations of your ebooks.
	Jutoh...
</description></item><item><title>Download KDEnlive 25.08.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 16:38:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kdenlive-3288.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kdenlive-3288.html
</guid><description>
Kdenlive is a video editor open source. The project was started in about 2003. Kdenlive is built on the Qt libraries and the KDE Frameworks. Most of the video processing is done by the MLT Framework, based on many open-source projects other as FFmpeg , frei0r , Movit, ladspa, sox, etc.
KDEnlive - video editing quickly
Our software is designed to meet most needs, from basic video editing to professional work. Kdenlive allows you to use and arrange a number of music and video, each can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Daemon Tools Lite 12.3.0.2364</title><pubDate> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 16:38:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-daemon-tools-lite-3391.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-daemon-tools-lite-3391.html
</guid><description>
DAEMON Tools Lite is based on two key features, simulation of virtual disks and building the file disk image as iso. DAEMON Tools Lite can emulate up to 4 virtual drives, DVD, CD or Blu-ray on your computer. The virtual units will be present in your system the same as the unit. After you select the virtual drive you want, you will choose a disc image (nrg, iso, mdf, bin, cue, etc.) that you want to mount. Visit My Computer at the device have The mobile storage and you will find the disk...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tomabo MP4 Downloader Pro 5.9.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 16:37:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tomabo-mp4-downloader-pro-3602.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tomabo-mp4-downloader-pro-3602.html
</guid><description>
Tomabo MP4 Downloader Pro is the app designed exclusively for Windows users to help them download videos from the Internet. In addition, it also increase download speeds by up to 500%, or even more. Tomabo MP4 Downloader Pro, interface design, simple, well-organized, beautifully. Here, users can view a list of videos has download with gravatar, URL, quality, duration and size of them. Software allows download video series at the same time, at the same time, support create a list of clips...
</description></item><item><title>Download TubeMate Downloader 5.25.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 16:33:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubemate-downloader-4250.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubemate-downloader-4250.html
</guid><description>
TubeMate Downloader is a smart application that lets you download any clip you want from the website hosting the main video and convert them in when download at or then. If you need a simple and effective tool to download videos, you can give it a try. With TubeMate Downloader, you can directly drag and drop video link from your browser into the drop-down box or application window to start downloading. You don't even need to copy and paste the video URL.
TubeMate Downloader - Support...
</description></item><item><title>Download TeXstudio 4.9.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 16:33:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-texstudio-7399.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-texstudio-7399.html
</guid><description>
TeXstudio is an integrated writing environment for creating LaTeX documents. The goal of TeXstudio is to make writing LaTeX as easy and comfortable as possible. Therefore TeXstudio has many features such as syntax highlighting, built-in viewer, reference checking and various assistants.
Features of TeXstudio
	Advanced Syntax Highlighting
	Checking direct references
	Built-in PDF viewer
	Live Preview
	Complete Latex Command and Check Syntax
	Live grammar check
	Local and global...
</description></item><item><title>Download Silent Camera [High Quality] 8.16.5</title><pubDate> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 16:03:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-silent-camera-10536.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-silent-camera-10536.html
</guid><description>
Introducing the best silent camera! Without the shutter sound, photos can be taken in complete silence! It also ranks number 1 among many silent cameras thanks to its high image quality! Take high-quality photos with the silent camera! You won't disturb anyone around you because the shutter sound can't be heard. You can take high-quality photos of any situation, such as your baby's cute sleeping face, your pet's natural behaviors, and words written on a blackboard!
Silent Camera...
</description></item></channel></rss>