<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 21:33:41 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 21:33:41 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Drive SnapShot 1.50.0.1745</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Sep 2025 23:12:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-drive-snapshot-701.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-drive-snapshot-701.html
</guid><description>
Drive SnapShot is a backup software, Restore disk, including operating system, installed programs, your data and all security attributes - while windows is running and you continue to work. With Drive SnapShot you backup partition or hard drive and it can also create disk image of your system. If a disaster occurs (a virus, trojan or the fixed hard disk), the recover complete and accurate your system will be able to accomplish after only a few minutes. The image file can be mounted as...
</description></item><item><title>Download LDPlayer 9.1.63.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Sep 2025 23:11:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ldplayer-2331.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ldplayer-2331.html
</guid><description>
LDPlayer is software that emulates Android, allowing users to play games, run apps on a Windows computer. LDPlayer support play heavy games, run chat applications, photo editing, video and many other Android apps, LDPlayer compatible with Android 5.1 and above, supports multitasking for experience not inferior when used on Mobile.
Installation is a simple process and quickly without the need for special attention from your side, there's more. installed, you can't touch them. This...
</description></item><item><title>Download Remo Outlook Backup &amp;amp; Migrate 2.0.1.101</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Sep 2025 23:11:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-remo-outlook-backup-migrate-7838.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-remo-outlook-backup-migrate-7838.html
</guid><description>
Remo Outlook Backup &amp;amp; Migrate is a safe and simple Utility to restore, backup and migrate your Outlook data without any limitations. Use this tool to automatically back up and migrate specific Outlook properties including settings, notes, attachments, and more.
Features of Remo Outlook Backup &amp;amp; Migrate
	Migrate Outlook data quickly and securely
	Unlimited Outlook Backup and Migration
	Backup Outlook data securely in the cloud
	Complete Outlook backup with just one...
</description></item><item><title>Download Balsamiq Wireframes 4.8.5</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Sep 2025 23:10:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-balsamiq-wireframes-3918.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-balsamiq-wireframes-3918.html
</guid><description>
Balsamiq Wireframes is a tool to create frame user interface fidelity low quickly, reproduces experience sketching on a notepad or white board, but use the computer. Balsamiq Wireframes really force you to focus on structure and content, avoid long discussions about color and detail will come later in the process. Wireframes is FAST: you will create more ideas, so you can throw away the bad ones and discover the best solution.
Balsamiq Wireframes - Create frame app and Website
The...
</description></item><item><title>Download PlayerFab (Ultra HD Player) 7.0.5.4</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Sep 2025 23:10:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dvdfab-player-ultra-68.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dvdfab-player-ultra-68.html
</guid><description>
PlayerFab (DVDFab Player Ultra) is one of the best 4K UHD media players. The software plays DVD, Blu-ray, 4K Ultra HD Blu-ray and also supports online video. It supports native navigation menus, along with HDR10, and supports high-resolution audio output. PlayerFab supports watching videos of a variety of popular streaming platforms such as Amazon, Netflix, Tubi, Peacock, and more.
Video streaming in FHD 1080p video quality and high quality EAC3 audio quality is the prerequisite and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Media Player Classic Black Edition 1.8.7</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Sep 2025 23:09:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-media-player-classic-black-edition-3351.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-media-player-classic-black-edition-3351.html
</guid><description>
Media Player Classic Black Edition is abbreviated as MPC-BE is a free program that can interface black support users to watch movies, listen to music on the computer with the new interface. Media Player Classic - BE is based on the project "Media Player Classic" original (Gabest) and the project "Media Player Classic Home Cinema" (Casimir666), contains additional features and bug fixes.
Both programs are quite similar, because they are based on Media Player Classic original. In fact, MPC...
</description></item><item><title>Download Fast Video Downloader 4.0.0.76</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Sep 2025 23:08:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fast-video-downloader-2619.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fast-video-downloader-2619.html
</guid><description>
Fast Video Downloader is a support program download quick video of genuine FastPcTools. ast Video Downloader is an easy to use program that allows you to download desired videos from a number of sites online storage. I think that I will not reveal secret if they write that most of the sites have video archives do not contain the ability to download videos and sometimes that's very necessary. This is when the same program is rescue, this allows you to save videos from the archive page as...
</description></item><item><title>Download Gilisoft Copy Protect 8.2.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Sep 2025 23:08:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-copy-protect-8047.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-copy-protect-8047.html
</guid><description>
Gilisoft Copy Protect is software that helps you protect audio, video, PDF, DOC, PPT, XLS and image files so that they cannot be copied or distributed by illegal means. Users can play from, video encoded on macOS, android using Gilisoft's GCP reader.
Features of Gilisoft Copy Protect
	A document security tool that creates shareless GCP files to protect your Video, Photo, DOC, PDF, XLS, PPT files from unauthorized sharing, editing, copying or viewing .
	Protect document files from...
</description></item><item><title>Download RizomUV Real &amp;amp; Virtual Space 2025.0.97</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Sep 2025 23:07:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rizomuv-real-virtual-space-1537.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rizomuv-real-virtual-space-1537.html
</guid><description>
RizomUV Real &amp;amp; Virtual Space known as Unold3D ago, is the perfect software to design a package or build texture laser. RizomUV Real Space includes all the features of RizomUV Virtual Space, but use ultraviolet rays to build and control the UV maps to the flat version over of your model will take all the size of it. This program allows you to get the mesh is not perpendicular three-dimensional, not even lasts for a few seconds. Mesh felt is produced with real size and get delivered in...
</description></item><item><title>Download QuickTextPaste 9.31</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Sep 2025 23:06:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quicktextpaste-2905.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quicktextpaste-2905.html
</guid><description>
QuickTextPaste is a mobile application that allows you to add (paste) the text to be predetermined quickly in any Microsoft Windows program through keyboard shortcuts. You can copy the software on any USB flash drive or other portable device and carry it with you whenever you have to automate the task, paste text messages quickly and easily without having to redo the installation steps.
QuickTextPaste - Create shortcut paste text
Although this app seems geared to users who have more...
</description></item><item><title>Download DBF Recovery 4.55</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Sep 2025 23:06:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbf-recovery-7931.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbf-recovery-7931.html
</guid><description>
DBF Recovery is software that gives users the ability to restore a damaged database back to its original condition without the expertise required to complete that task. It fixes headers and data structures in an automated process that doesn't involve user interaction. With DBF Recovery, you will truly have a lean, honest DBF repair machine without any functionality.
Features of DBF Recovery
	Quick and simple to use DBF file repair software.
	Repair almost any DBF...
</description></item><item><title>Download Google Drive (Backup and Sync) 114.0.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Sep 2025 22:35:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-drive-6751.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-drive-6751.html
</guid><description>
Using Google Drive is a great way to store your files safely in secure data centers, where your files will not be lost. Even if your computer, phone or tablet is broken, the files you store in the Google Drive are safe. Download photos, videos, documents, and other files that are important to you up to Google Drive. Continue with the memory up to 15GB. Free. Google Drive helps you access your file faster by recognizing the objects in your image and text in the scanned documents.
Easy to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Java SE Development Kit 25.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Sep 2025 22:35:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-java-se-development-kit-6881.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-java-se-development-kit-6881.html
</guid><description>
Java allows you to play online games, chat with people around the world, and view images in 3D. These applications, written in the Java programming language and accessible from your browser, are called applets. Companies also use Java applications for intranet applications and other e-business solutions.
Java is used by companies in all major industries. Whether deployed on mobile phones, embedded devices, game consoles, laptops, or in data centers, Java provides rich user interfaces,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Media Player Classic Home Cinema 2.5.3</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Sep 2025 22:34:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-media-player-classic-home-cinema-2839.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-media-player-classic-home-cinema-2839.html
</guid><description>
Media Player Classic Home Cinema is a multimedia compact for Microsoft Windows 32 bit and 64 bit. MPC mimics the interface of Windows Media Player 6.4, but provides most options and features available in the modern means. Media Player Classic Home Cinema for free 100% no advertising, so you can directly access content and enjoy media playback without being distracted.
With Media Player Classic Home, you can now change the design a multimedia of the custom toolbar. There is a range to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Free Download Manager 6.30.0 Build 6459</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Sep 2025 22:34:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-download-manager-3105.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-download-manager-3105.html
</guid><description>
Free Download Manager is free application download manager, Free Download Manager will significantly increase downloads by splitting the files into several smaller parts and then downloads at the same time. Speed your download will be significantly increased. Manager download free can also continue to download at broken or not responding, so you don't need start downloading from the beginning after occasionally interrupted.
Free Download Manager - Manage and speed up downloads
You can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Windows 10 Pro Lite 22H2 Build 1904X.6332 Ghost Spectre</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Sep 2025 22:33:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-10-pro-lite-8714.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-10-pro-lite-8714.html
</guid><description>
Windows 10 Pro Lite is a version of the Windows 10 operating system that has been optimized for performance and reduced in size to be lighter and faster than the standard version of Windows 10 Pro. The Lite version of Windows 10 is designed to work well on older or lower-end hardware, making it a good choice for devices with limited resources.
Windows 10 Pro Lite has a smaller install size and uses less system resources than the standard version of Windows 10. This version also includes...
</description></item><item><title>Download Futuremark PCMark Pro 10 v2.2.2737</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Sep 2025 22:32:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-futuremark-pcmark-pro-1275.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-futuremark-pcmark-pro-1275.html
</guid><description>
Futuremark PCMark 10 Professional Edition is a suite of comprehensive test includes multiple tasks to be performed in the work environment modern. With the option of running quick, extended and customized in accordance with your needs, PCMark 10 is a standard PC complete for modern office and is the ideal choice for organizations that buy PC with big volume.
Futuremark PCMark Pro
PCMark 10 easy to install and run, no need for complex configuration. Running the benchmark itself and you...
</description></item><item><title>Download SolidWorks 2025 SP4.0 Full Premium</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Sep 2025 22:32:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-solidworks-01en-6421.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-solidworks-01en-6421.html
</guid><description>
SolidWorks  is 3D design software running on Windows operating system and available since 1997, created by Dassault Systèmes SolidWorks Corp. SolidWorks is a computer-aided design, analysis and preparation system for the manufacture of products of any complexity and purpose. CALS technology, including bidirectional data exchange with other Windows applications and interactive document creation Depending on the type of task to be solved.
SolidWorks's line of analysis and simulation...
</description></item><item><title>Download The Graphics Creator 8 1.4.15</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Sep 2025 22:30:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-the-graphics-creator-6419.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-the-graphics-creator-6419.html
</guid><description>
The Graphics Creator  is this program that allows you to create your own graphics in minutes without any design skills or big budget. Attract attention with stunning graphics. Search hundreds of thousands of high-quality photos and videos. And much more.
Features of The Graphics Creator
	Search hundreds of thousands of high-quality photos and videos
	Choose from 1000+ beautiful fonts from Google
	Erase the background of the image to make it transparent
	Increase Graphics Maker's...
</description></item><item><title>Download Embarcadero RAD Studio 13.0 Florence Architect Version 37.0.57242.3601</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Sep 2025 22:29:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-embarcadero-rad-studio-10661.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-embarcadero-rad-studio-10661.html
</guid><description>
RAD Studio is Embarcadero's integrated development environment (IDE) for software development. It supports application development for various platforms, including Windows, macOS, iOS, Android, and Linux. RAD Studio is known for its emphasis on rapid application development (RAD) and provides many tools and components to streamline the development process.
IDE includes Delphi and C++ Builder, which are programming languages used to build native applications. Delphi is a language based...
</description></item><item><title>Download nTopology 5.30.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Sep 2025 22:28:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ntopology-7887.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ntopology-7887.html
</guid><description>
nTopology is software that enables engineers and designers to create any geometry no matter how complex and meet the requirements of high performance products . Our software is used from research through production to create breakthrough products and processes for the aerospace, automotive, medical and consumer industries. Our customers depend on the general design capabilities of the nTopology to get the most out of new hardware, optimize components where performance is important,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Intel Ethernet Adapter Complete Driver Pack 30.4.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Sep 2025 22:27:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intel-ethernet-adapter-complete-driver-pack-7424.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intel-ethernet-adapter-complete-driver-pack-7424.html
</guid><description>
Intel Ethernet Adapter Complete Driver Pack contains all Intel® Ethernet networking software and drivers for Windows, Linux and FreeBSD versions currently supported for most Intel Ethernet Adapters. Not all Intel Ethernet Adapters and Intel Ethernet Controllers are supported in all versions of Windows, Linux, or FreeBSD.
What's new in this release:
In this point release, NVM Update Package 3.20 has been updated. If you currently have the 3.20 update package installed and are running...
</description></item><item><title>Download ChrisPC Free VPN Connection 4.25.0917</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Sep 2025 22:27:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-free-vpn-connection-2887.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-free-vpn-connection-2887.html
</guid><description>
ChrisPC Free VPN Connection software allows you to create VPN connection (virtual private network) to the server for free from the United States, Germany, Canada, France, Germany, Russia, Singapore, the Netherlands. This will help you to unblock your favorite sites to watch free TV and on-demand television when living abroad, travelling, on business or vacation. In addition, here is the solution to overcome the limited area for the popular websites: Google, YouTube, Facebook, Instagram,...
</description></item><item><title>Download EverNote 10.155.5.14508</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Sep 2025 22:26:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-evernote-3261.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-evernote-3261.html
</guid><description>
EverNote is the all in one tool allows you to track notes, todo items, memos, outlines, excerpts, websites, ideas and other things and automatically synchronize them between multiple computers and mobile devices (iPhone, Android, etc.). You can choose to sort their notes into categories, password protect them, export them to XML and more. EverNote supports a number of pattern notes allow you to add to-do list, spreadsheet like Excel to calculate costs (automatic sum), notes, phone, contact...
</description></item><item><title>Download Windows and Office Genuine ISO Verifier 12.26.50.25</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Sep 2025 22:25:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-and-office-genuine-iso-verifier-542.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-and-office-genuine-iso-verifier-542.html
</guid><description>
Windows and Office Genuine ISO Verifier is a small utility used to check for Microsoft Office and Windows ISO genuine or not by carrying out verification fast SHA-1 and MD5. The software has a friendly interface with the user and not cause you any real trouble whatsoever while navigating.
Users use tool requires to specify the file input and the application will automatically perform the rest of the work. Windows and Office Genuine ISO Verifier can compare the file SHA-1 with the...
</description></item></channel></rss>