<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 13:41:23 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 13:41:23 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Footej Camera - PRO HD Camera 1.2.13</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Sep 2025 16:39:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-footej-camera-pro-hd-camera-10592.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-footej-camera-pro-hd-camera-10592.html
</guid><description>
Footej Camera - Pro HD Camera is a new, attractive, user-friendly and powerful professional camera app that is here, ready to capture, organize and give a new life to your best moments! Improve the quality of your photos with the best camera app! Footej is a unique photo and video camera app that uses Android's Camera 2 API! Professional-grade Camera app that's easy to use, take photos and create a masterpiece.
Experience a whole new level of mobile photography! FUL DSLR Camera, Manual...
</description></item><item><title>Download FV File Pro 1.26.8</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Sep 2025 16:39:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-fv-file-pro-10802.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-fv-file-pro-10802.html
</guid><description>
File Explorer folder. Fast and powerful file manager for Android. Go to /Android/data and on /Android/obb Android 13 without root. Manage your files via HTTP, FTP or SFTP within your LAN without using data cables. It's convenient to transfer documents, images, text files, etc. between computer and mobile phone. Don't have to waste mobile card traffic to share files with colleagues or family members.
Features of FV File Pro
	Supports viewing jpg, png, bmp, tiff, webp, heif, avif, ico,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Shazam: Find Music &amp;amp; Concerts 16.7.0-250826</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Sep 2025 16:38:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-shazam-music-discovery-10763.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-shazam-music-discovery-10763.html
</guid><description>
Shazam will identify any song in seconds. Discover, artists, lyrics, videos &amp;amp; playlists, all for free. Over 1 billion installs and counting. Use Pop-up Shazam to identify music in any app - Instagram, YouTube, TikTok... No connection? No problem! Shazam while offline.
Features of Shazam: Music Discovery
	Find the name of any song in seconds.
	Listen and add to Apple Music playlists.
	Follow along with time-synced lyrics.
	Watch music videos from Apple Music or YouTube.
	Enable...
</description></item><item><title>Download jetAudio+ Hi-Res Music Player 12.3.4</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Sep 2025 16:38:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-jetaudio-hd-music-player-plus-8339.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-jetaudio-hd-music-player-plus-8339.html
</guid><description>
jetAudio is an mp3 player with a 10/20 band graphic equalizer and various sound effects. jetAudio HD Music Player Plus is a mobile music player app for Android devices that offers advanced audio features and customization options. This application is famous for its high-quality sound reproduction and support for many audio formats, including lossless formats such as FLAC and WAV.
Features of jetAudio HD Music Player Plus
	High quality sound reproduction
	Supports many audio formats,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Auto Text: Schedule Messages 5.7.9</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Sep 2025 16:33:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-auto-text-auto-send-message-8447.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-auto-text-auto-send-message-8447.html
</guid><description>
Auto Text: Auto send WA &amp;amp; SMS is a feature or application that allows users to automatically send pre-written text messages at a specific time or in response to a request. specific activation. This feature can be useful in many situations, such as sending reminders, sending messages to loved ones at a specific time, or sending messages in response to certain events, such as calls to or location-based triggers.
Auto Text features: Auto send WA &amp;amp; SMS
	Automatically send happy...
</description></item><item><title>Download Anti Spy Detector: Anti Hack 44.28.8.25</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Sep 2025 16:33:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-anti-spy-detector-firewall-10779.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-anti-spy-detector-firewall-10779.html
</guid><description>
With the powerful built-in firewall in this app, you can monitor every outgoing connection each app makes. If you don't trust the app, you can block it from accessing the internet with a firewall to prevent tracking and analysis. Every outgoing IP or domain will be saved and you can see them, the Firewall will show you the address, organization and information about that IP and if you feel suspicious you can block that domain so that application is no longer accessible. Additionally, you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Busuu: Learn &amp;amp; Speak Languages 32.19.2(1425259)</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Sep 2025 16:32:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-busuu-learn-languages-8400.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-busuu-learn-languages-8400.html
</guid><description>
Busuu: Learn Languages is a mobile application that allows users to learn and practice various languages ​​on their Android devices. It includes various features such as interactive lessons, flashcards, quizzes, and exercises designed to help users learn and practice vocabulary, grammar, and conversation skills. The app also includes many customizable settings, such as the ability to choose between different languages ​​and set learning goals.
Busuu Features: Learn...
</description></item><item><title>Download Network Utilities 8.3.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Sep 2025 16:32:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-network-utilities-8758.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-network-utilities-8758.html
</guid><description>
Network Utilities is an Android application that provides users with a set of tools to analyze and manage their network connections. It is a useful tool for users who want to troubleshoot network problems, monitor network activity, and optimize network performance. It is also available for purchase with additional features such as ad-free browsing, more advanced network tools, and more detailed network analysis.
The following tools are currently available: 
	Network Info will display...
</description></item><item><title>Download Money Manager: Expense Tracker 11.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Sep 2025 16:25:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-money-manager-expense-tracker-8782.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-money-manager-expense-tracker-8782.html
</guid><description>
Money Manager is a simple money management app to manage money and track your daily spending. Find out where you spend the most money with the help of our budgeting system that can help you control your spending and save more money. This free expense tracker app is not only an expense tracker that helps you easily record daily expenses and income, but also has additional features that make it easy to track and manage all types of content. financial content to help make the accounting...
</description></item><item><title>Download 365Scores: Live Scores &amp;amp; News 14.3.3</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Sep 2025 16:25:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-365scores-live-scores-news-8220.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-365scores-live-scores-news-8220.html
</guid><description>
365Scores is a sports app that provides users with real-time scores, statistics, and news for many sports including football, basketball, soccer, and more. Some features of the application include:
	Live scores and notifications: 365Scores provides live scores and push notifications for many sports, including football, soccer, basketball, baseball, etc.
	Match statistics: The app includes detailed match statistics such as ball control, number of shots on goal, etc.
	Latest News:...
</description></item><item><title>Download Knots 3D 10.1.0 beta</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Sep 2025 16:25:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-knots-3d-8500.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-knots-3d-8500.html
</guid><description>
Knots 3D is a mobile application that provides visual and interactive instructions for tying different types of knots. This app can be used to learn and practice different knots, with detailed animations and illustrations showing the correct technique for each knot. Used by arborists, fishermen, firefighters, climbers, military, and boy and girl scouts worldwide, Knots 3D will quickly teach you how to tie even the most difficult knots!
With more than 175 nautical miles, Knots 3D will be...
</description></item><item><title>Download Today Weather: Radar &amp;amp; Widgets 2.4.0-4</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Sep 2025 16:24:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-today-weather-alerts-widgets-8915.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-today-weather-alerts-widgets-8915.html
</guid><description>
Weather Today is a beautiful and easy-to-use weather app that provides the world's most accurate local weather forecasts.
Features of Weather Today for Android
	Displays clear, easy-to-understand weather forecasts.
	Enjoy every moment you open the app with thousands of beautiful photos corresponding to the weather and day.
	Prepare for any situation with 24/7 weather forecasts and chance of rain.
	Protect your health with air quality, UV index and pollen count.
	Capture beautiful...
</description></item><item><title>Download Lifesum: AI Calorie Tracker 19.3.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Sep 2025 16:24:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-lifesum-healthy-eating-diet-8257.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-lifesum-healthy-eating-diet-8257.html
</guid><description>
Lifesum is a health and fitness app that helps users track their diet and exercise. The app allows users to set personalized health goals, such as losing weight or building muscle, and offers suggestions for healthy meals and snacks based on the goals there. Users can also track their water intake, log their workouts, and track their progress over time.
Some key features include:
	Personalized health goals: Users can set specific goals, such as losing weight or building muscle, and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Magnifier Plus with Flashlight 4.8.12</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Sep 2025 16:24:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-magnifier-plus-with-flashlight-8494.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-magnifier-plus-with-flashlight-8494.html
</guid><description>
Are you tired of trying to read labels with small fonts? Now you can use your Android device as the perfect digital magnifier! No need to use a magnifying glass to read small labels - this app lets you see text large and clearly. The magnifier has on-screen zoom and illumination controls for easy operation. You can also use the flash as a light to get a brighter image, and the negative mode inverts the colors so you can see this differently when they're hard to see.
Features of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Drivvo - car management 8.6.6</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Sep 2025 16:23:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-drivvo-car-management-8614.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-drivvo-car-management-8614.html
</guid><description>
Drivvo is a car management app that helps users track and manage expenses related to their vehicles. It provides a platform to record and analyze fuel consumption, maintenance costs and other expenses, making it easier to budget and manage car-related expenses.
Save Money: Manage fuel consumption and economic costs, car maintenance costs and service costs of your car, motorcycle, bus or truck.
Control Finances: Track average KM/liter, monthly costs, average per day, fuel,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Planes Live - Flight Tracker 1.44.4 build 139</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Sep 2025 16:23:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-the-flight-tracker-12198.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-the-flight-tracker-12198.html
</guid><description>
Travel safely and enjoy your flight! Flight Tracker is the most convenient flight app you can find on Google Play. It contains in-depth information on all available flights and airlines; Destinations, Departures, Stations &amp;amp; Gates, Delays, etc.
Main features:
	Track any flight in the world
	Detailed departure and arrival information
	Flight delay information
	Real-time station and gate updates
	Add your boarding pass
	Plan your flights during trips
	Check the local weather at your...
</description></item><item><title>Download Projectivy Launcher 4.68</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Sep 2025 16:22:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-projectivy-launcher-8369.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-projectivy-launcher-8369.html
</guid><description>
Projectivy Launcher is an alternative launcher for Android TV, designed specifically for your TV and projector needs: smooth, clean, customizable and packed with unique features. It's Projectivy Tools on steroids.
Projectivy Launcher Features
	No ads
	Shortcut to change input source (HDMI 1/2/3, AV) and on-screen menu popup
	Autostart directly with any external input or installed application
	Parental controls to prevent HDMI/app use during certain times of day
	Detect inactivity to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Colorimeter 2.25.19</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Sep 2025 16:22:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-colorimeter-13047.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-colorimeter-13047.html
</guid><description>
Discover the ultimate app for professional color capture and analysis, widely used by designers, scientists, architects, artists, personal color consultants, developers, and color enthusiasts.
Key Features
	Smart Capture: Instantly recognize colors through your camera or photo library with scientific-grade accuracy.
	Professional Analysis: Complete convert in RGB, HEX, CMYK, HSV, HSL, XYZ, CIE Lab, LCh, RYB, Luminance, Binary, Wavelength, and more.
	Paint palettes: Extract color...
</description></item><item><title>Download Voice Recorder Plus: Rec Sound 1.13.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Sep 2025 16:22:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sound-recorder-plus-voice-rec-13795.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sound-recorder-plus-voice-rec-13795.html
</guid><description>
Unlock the full potential of your recordings with Sound Recorder Plus &amp;amp; Dictaphone, your solution for perfect audio quality at your fingertips. Designed with a beautiful, intuitive interface, this app is suitable for both beginners and seasoned professionals. Whether it is for working, studying, listening to music or recording the essence of everyday life, Audio Recorder Free is the embodiment of high-quality and flexible audio recording or voice recording.
Key features of Voice...
</description></item><item><title>Download Flymat: Live Flight Tracker 1.0.61</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Sep 2025 16:21:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-flymat-live-flight-tracker-13248.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-flymat-live-flight-tracker-13248.html
</guid><description>
Check the status of the flight you are about to fly or your loved ones are flying. Discover detailed flight information, including but not limited to Airline name, departure city, arrival city, altitude, manufacturer and more.
Features of Flymat
	Track live flights worldwide.
	Search for flights by flight number, route, airline, date and track the flight throughout the entire journey.
	Save the flights and airports you want to track and easily access flight status and flight...
</description></item><item><title>Download WPS Office - PDF, Word, Excel, PPT 18.20.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Sep 2025 13:40:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wps-office-pdf-word-excel-ppt-8244.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wps-office-pdf-word-excel-ppt-8244.html
</guid><description>
WPS Office is a mobile office suite app that allows users to view, edit and create documents, spreadsheets, and presentations on their Android device. The app is available for download from the Google Play Store and is compatible with a wide range of file formats, including Microsoft Office documents.
WPS Office - Free Office suite for Word, PDF, Excel, is an all-in-one office suite that integrates Word, PDF, Excel, PowerPoint, Forms, Cloud Storage, Online Editing, Template library and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Solid Explorer File Manager 3.0.0 beta</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Sep 2025 13:38:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-solid-explorer-file-manager-8924.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-solid-explorer-file-manager-8924.html
</guid><description>
Solid Explorer is a file management application inspired by old file management applications. Solid Explorer is a popular file management app for Android devices that allows users to manage and organize their files and folders in an intuitive and user-friendly interface. It offers many features that make it stand out from other file management apps.
Solid Explorer allows you to navigate to files stored on your device and automatically organize them into collections. You can view,...
</description></item><item><title>Download AI Enlarger: for Photo &amp;amp; Anime 3.4.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Sep 2025 13:36:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ai-enlarger-for-photo-anime-14129.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ai-enlarger-for-photo-anime-14129.html
</guid><description>
Transform your photos and anime images easily with AI Enlarger. Upscale images by 200%, 400% or 800% without losing quality. Fix pixelated or blurry photos and enhance resolution seamlessly.
Using advanced AI photo super resolution technology, AI Enlarger lets you enlarge images, photos and anime images without blurring or losing quality. Easily convert your photos, cartoons and animations into 4k, 8k or even 16k ultra high resolution wallpapers.
Key Features
	User-friendly: Just...
</description></item><item><title>Download ISS Live Now: Live Earth View 8.0.3</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Sep 2025 13:30:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-iss-live-now-live-earth-view-14128.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-iss-live-now-live-earth-view-14128.html
</guid><description>
ISS Live Now: Live Earth View provides a live HD video stream of Earth from the International Space Station (ISS), real-time tracking of the ISS with interactive maps, and notifications to know when the ISS will be visible from your location. The app also features live astronaut missions, spacewalks, rocket launches, and docking events, plus an immersive virtual tour inside the ISS using Google Street View.
	See Earth 24/7 – Live HD streaming from space.
	Follow the ISS in real time...
</description></item><item><title>Download IObit Uninstaller Pro 15.0.0.8</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Sep 2025 22:33:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iobit-uninstaller-pro-339.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iobit-uninstaller-pro-339.html
</guid><description>
IObit Uninstaller Pro is software to delete programs not needed easily even when Windows "Remove Programs" operation not successful. IObit Uninstaller Pro will uninstall the app Windows, browser toolbars, software packages and plug-ins added. It comes with a scan function is powerful and a tool, Force Uninstall, both of which help to easily and completely remove the app stubborn, and the excess useless, to release more disk space.
With IObit Uninstaller Pro you will have peace of mind...
</description></item></channel></rss>