<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 15:39:22 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 15:39:22 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Internet Download Manager (IDM) 6.42 Build 46</title><pubDate> Thu, 25 Sep 2025 18:21:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-inetnet-download-manager-161.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-inetnet-download-manager-161.html
</guid><description>
Internet Download Manager is the download acceleration software, the best download support now, it can help you speed up the download up to five times, continue and schedule downloads. The latest version of IDM adds the compatibility of Windows 10 and Windows 11, it has supported all current popular browsers such as Internet Explorer, Mozilla Firefox, Opera, Google Chrome, ..
Download IDM with the latest version on taiwebs.com making it easy to download and manage your downloaded files...
</description></item><item><title>Download Advanced SystemCare Ultimate 17.6.0.134</title><pubDate> Thu, 25 Sep 2025 18:20:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-systemcare-ultimate-132.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-systemcare-ultimate-132.html
</guid><description>
Advanced SystemCare Ultimate 17: Antivirus software that also helps protect, repair, clean and optimize your PC. Based on BitDefender antivirus technology and IObit anti-malware engine, it is part of IObit antivirus project devoted to providing better and value-added services to our users.
With real-time protection against viruses, spyware and phishing attacks, powerful tuning and cleaning functions, Advanced SystemCare Ultimate provides always-on protection, Automatic and all-in-one...
</description></item><item><title>Download IDM Retail 6.42 Build 46</title><pubDate> Thu, 25 Sep 2025 18:20:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-internet-download-manager-retail-3609.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-internet-download-manager-retail-3609.html
</guid><description>
IDM - Internet Download Manager Retail is a reliable utility and high efficiency will help you to increase your download speed and manage download at better. The program allows you to easily schedule, pause and resume downloads with a single click. Moreover, the application provides error resilience robust and can restart the download at the interrupted or broken. You can restore the download is interrupted due to network problems, lost connections, unexpected power outages, computer...
</description></item><item><title>Download Windows 11 Pro 25H2 v26200.6584 NoTPM Preactivated</title><pubDate> Thu, 25 Sep 2025 18:19:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-11-6618.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-11-6618.html
</guid><description>
Windows 11 is officially leaked to a developer version. Previously, when Windows 10 was released, Microsoft once stated that Windows 10 would be the last version of Windows for users. Clearly, with the arrival of Windows 11, Microsoft needed a major reason to reverse its previous claims and still remove Windows 10 by introducing some new operating systems.
About the interface of Windows 11 is quite similar to Windows 10X (a version of Windows 10 has stopped growing). The logo image of...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube Downloader 3.9.16 (2409)</title><pubDate> Thu, 25 Sep 2025 18:18:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube Downloader  is a dedicated software that helps users  downloading youtube videos  Favorites on PC for offline viewing. With MediaHuman YouTube  Downloader  you can download videos from youtube website to your computer with  fast speed , with special software development technology that automatically receives videos from Websites, in addition to the ability to download videos from software websites, can convert downloaded video formats to various formats for the purpose...
</description></item><item><title>Download grepWin 2.1.12</title><pubDate> Thu, 25 Sep 2025 18:17:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-grepwin-5044.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-grepwin-5044.html
</guid><description>
grepWin is a tool that search and replace can simply use regular expressions to perform his work. This allows to perform the search and replacement much more powerful. In case you're not familiar with the expression, we have a guide to regular expressions is very short for you.
The features of grepWin
	Lightweight and easy to use
	Search and replace text
	Mode advanced search
	Easily detect patterns complex sentences
</description></item><item><title>Download By Click Downloader 2.4.25</title><pubDate> Thu, 25 Sep 2025 18:16:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-by-click-premium-193.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-by-click-premium-193.html
</guid><description>
YouTube By Click Premium is a high quality powerful video downloader including YouTube downloader, YouTube Converter, YouTube Chrome Downloader, Facebook Video Downloader, Downloader Vimeo, Dailymotion Downloader and supports many other video sites.
YouTube By Click
YouTube By Click Features
	YouTube by Click can download and convert files to MP3, MP4, FLV, AVI, WMV, 3GP, WAV and WEBM formats.
	Download all supported qualities, including HD.
	YouTube By Click downloads entire YouTube...
</description></item><item><title>Download Zortam Mp3 Media Studio Pro 33.30</title><pubDate> Thu, 25 Sep 2025 18:16:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zortam-mp3-media-studio-pro-135.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zortam-mp3-media-studio-pro-135.html
</guid><description>
Zortam Mp3 Media Studio Pro brings you rich processing tools music includes extract and convert music from CD to Mp3 format, edit, music cards, music download....You can also create discs CD high-quality music, with Zortam Mp3 Media Studio search music files duplicated to remove them from the system, rename music files, switch back and forth between formats.
Zortam Mp3 Media Studio Pro is rated as perfect software in the processing of the MP3 files on the computer. First of all, you can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Photo Supreme 2025.3.3.8097</title><pubDate> Thu, 25 Sep 2025 18:15:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photo-supreme-430.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photo-supreme-430.html
</guid><description>
Photo Supreme is a software product management professional pictures of idimager. With Photo Supreme you can arrange, manage back stock photo archive of yourself and share them with you here and relatives easily via Email or Facebook. Photo Supreme provides users method to sort images effective, logical, as well as edit and share your photos with friends and relatives in the family. Especially the Photo Supreme allows to work with multiple image formats and support mounting support,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Acrobat Reader DC 2025.001.20744</title><pubDate> Thu, 25 Sep 2025 18:09:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-acrobat-reader-3707.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-acrobat-reader-3707.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Acrobat Reader DC is a system of application software and Web services developed by Adobe Systems to view, create, manipulate, print and manage PDF files. With Adobe Acrobat Reader DC, you can create, export, edit, and track PDF files from anywhere - and maintain connection with the recent set of files on all your devices.
Adobe Acrobat Reader current DC is connected with Adobe Document Cloud - help working on the computers and mobile devices becomes easier than ever before. This is...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDFsam -PDF Split and Merge 5.4.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 25 Sep 2025 18:08:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-split-and-merge-2337.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-split-and-merge-2337.html
</guid><description>
PDF Split and Merge is free software that makes it easy to split PDF files into smaller files or merge them all into one complete PDF file. PDF Split and Merge is considered to be one of the best PDF file merging software available today, the special thing about this PDF file merge software is that it is completely free, this is one of the reasons that make up the attraction of this software.
PDF Split and Merge - Split and merge PDF 
This is a great alternative to the famous ARTS PDF...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter 3.9.16 (2409)</title><pubDate> Thu, 25 Sep 2025 18:08:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-to-mp3-converter-1744.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-to-mp3-converter-1744.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter is the software support download youtube video and convert video to mp3 format fast and most simple. MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter allows you download and convert videos from YouTube and other websites to MP3 format by pasting the YouTube URL into the application. When you paste the URL, the program will display thumbnails for videos and you have the option to customize the title information, artist and album before you begin the process of...
</description></item><item><title>Download iZotope VEA 1.1.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 25 Sep 2025 18:07:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-izotope-vea-11219.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-izotope-vea-11219.html
</guid><description>
Enjoy the sound of your own voice. VEA is an AI audio enhancement engine that processes any voice recording and makes it stronger, sleeker, and more professional. This easy-to-use tool is perfect for podcasters and content creators of all skill sets, whether you're a beginner or a seasoned pro.
Features of iZotope VEA
	Built with industry-leading audio enhancements from RX, Ozone and Nectar, VEA increases clarity, sets levels more consistently and reduces background noise.
	VEA's...
</description></item><item><title>Download Filmworkz Phoenix 2025.2.012</title><pubDate> Thu, 25 Sep 2025 18:06:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-digital-vision-phoenix-6617.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-digital-vision-phoenix-6617.html
</guid><description>
The Phoenix Ministry of products provides world-class restoration tools for the most demanding jobs. With the DVO technology that has won many of our awards, Phoenix is designed to produce great results quickly with fewer handicrave interventions. With a familiar time-based interface, artists and storage houses can easily review and edit things according to the context if required. Each product has been designed around a set of features for specific work and budget.
Features of...
</description></item><item><title>Download EarthTime 6.30.10</title><pubDate> Thu, 25 Sep 2025 18:06:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-earthtime-185.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-earthtime-185.html
</guid><description>
EarthTime is software that displays the time and date local time of any place in the world. This application has database integration good for 3000 city, users can manually add, download at EarthTime if you want to. EarthTime allows you to install for the time zone and current local time.EarthTime displays the Earth according to the view night and day, you can view the map in full screen mode.
EarthTime
The feature on EarthTime
	EarthTime allows users to interact with visualization...
</description></item><item><title>Download Modular InfoTech Shree-Lipi NXT 8.1.9211.21643</title><pubDate> Thu, 25 Sep 2025 18:05:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-modular-infotech-shree-lipi-nxt-8975.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-modular-infotech-shree-lipi-nxt-8975.html
</guid><description>
Modular InfoTech Shree-Lipi NXT is a software application that provides a comprehensive solution for Indian language typing and publishing. It is designed to support multiple languages, including Hindi, Marathi, Gujarati, Punjabi, Bengali, Tamil, Telugu, Kannada, Malayalam, Oriya and Assamese.
The software includes a user-friendly interface and a wide range of features such as Unicode support, spell check, font management and keyboard layout. It also offers a wide range of advanced...
</description></item><item><title>Download Filmworkz Nucoda 2025.2.012</title><pubDate> Thu, 25 Sep 2025 18:04:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-digital-vision-nucoda-4600.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-digital-vision-nucoda-4600.html
</guid><description>
Filmworkz Nucoda is a solution sorting and finishing color high-grade for feature film, advertising and broadcast application. It combines a set of innovative tools and integrated with workflow Avid includes full support for storage devices Avid Interplay and Nexus set new standards with the highest quality. Nucoda supports workflow is color management ACES, HDR and Dolby Vision. With the color tools in the industry, used by customers such as The Farm, The Picture Shop and Pixar Animation...
</description></item><item><title>Download Abelssoft SendMe (Send2Phone) 2025 v1.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 25 Sep 2025 18:04:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-abelssoft-send2phone-2198.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-abelssoft-send2phone-2198.html
</guid><description>
Abelssoft Send2Phone is a program that allows you to send files from personal computer to phone your mobile, you can now easily share links, images, any files from PC to mobile or vice versa. Traffic will be encrypted using AES-256, so the authors assure you that you should not worry about blocking data, but I won't believe in a hundred percent. Thanks to the user interface simple, clear and pleasant. you can send the file just by a click of the mouse, the software can be integrated into...
</description></item><item><title>Download ThunderSoft Video to GIF Converter 5.6.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 25 Sep 2025 18:03:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thundersoft-video-to-gif-converter-2885.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thundersoft-video-to-gif-converter-2885.html
</guid><description>
ThunderSoft Video to GIF Converter is the best software to batch convert gif files into video files and extract serial gif image. Supports all major video formats: avi, wmv, mp4, mkv, flv, Mov, mpeg, etc. Provide gif file by preview frames and setup output rich, including background music, background color, frame rate, bitrate, custom logo,...
ThunderSoft Video to GIF Converter - convert video into GIF
Features of ThunderSoft Video to GIF Converter
	Convert files Gif, Png, Bitmap or...
</description></item><item><title>Download DP Animation Maker 3.5.43</title><pubDate> Thu, 25 Sep 2025 18:02:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dp-animation-maker-2860.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dp-animation-maker-2860.html
</guid><description>
DP Animation Maker - 2D animation software smart allows you to turn static images into motion directly. The world is a living, breathing from your still images with minimal effort. DP Animation Maker lets you make natural scenes burst with vibrancy and bring out the motion to people and objects.
DP Animation Maker - Create and edit animated GIF
Animation Maker has the tools rich that you need to put all the pieces together. When you select pictures of yourself, it's easy to move from...
</description></item><item><title>Download PC Internals Pro 2.002</title><pubDate> Thu, 25 Sep 2025 18:02:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pc-internals-pro-13002.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pc-internals-pro-13002.html
</guid><description>
PC Internals Pro is a new solution that allows Windows users to comprehensively analyze the system components and reliable monitoring of the hard drive. This software is aimed at individual users as well as IT experts and retail agents attach importance to transparency, early detection and data security. PC Internals provides detailed information about the processor, RAM, graphics card, drive and other system components. The chart directly displays the current load, while the specific...
</description></item><item><title>Download XL-Connector 3.6.14.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 25 Sep 2025 18:01:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xl-connector-12415.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xl-connector-12415.html
</guid><description>
XL-Connector is a popular plugin that securely integrates Excel and Salesforce to export, import, refresh and transform data seamlessly with ultra-fast api connection. It provides Salesforce administrators with a comprehensive toolbox that easily performs data and metadata management activities in a familiar Excel environment.
Features
Export from Salesforce to Excel
	Get data from existing Salesforce reports or build your own SOQL queries directly into Excel.
Import data into...
</description></item><item><title>Download DeskSoft EarthView 7.13.10</title><pubDate> Thu, 25 Sep 2025 18:00:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desksoft-earthview-184.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desksoft-earthview-184.html
</guid><description>
With software DeskSoft EarthView you can easily create wallpapers to your computer or select screen saver of your favorite. the program can change day and night, the clouds will also change according to weather conditions current on one or another part of the earth, you can see the lights of the city.
Features of DeskSoft EarthView can be interesting, because of DeskSoft EarthView support for day and night, you can view atmospheric phenomena, light city can see, the cloud is displayed,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Youtube Downloader HD 5.9.9.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 25 Sep 2025 18:00:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-downloader-hd-3122.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-downloader-hd-3122.html
</guid><description>
Youtube Downloader HD is the best application to download and save Youtube videos. And it's completely free :) You can also convert the downloaded video into various formats easily. Youtube Downloader HD is the download at video free. Download at your videos easily and convert to AVI video format or into MP4 video format (compatible with iPad, iPhone). You can download high quality videos, high definition videos and Full HD from YouTube.
Youtube Downloader HD - Download Youtube videos...
</description></item><item><title>Download Personal Backup 6.4.2.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 25 Sep 2025 17:59:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-personal-backup-1117.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-personal-backup-1117.html
</guid><description>
Personal Backup is software to backup data on computer hard drive professional with the ability to copy data on the hard drive and save any folder. Personal Backup is the most optimal solutions to ensure safety for data on avoid computer viruses, malicious code, intrusion and data loss because you can restore lost data at any time if it has to be backed up and stored on the folder of the computer.
Personal Backup - backup computer data
Features of Personal Backup
	Backup cross data...
</description></item></channel></rss>