<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 05:46:09 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 05:46:09 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Topaz Photo Pro 1.3.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 27 Feb 2026 17:06:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-photo-ai-8105.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-photo-ai-8105.html
</guid><description>
What is Topaz Photo AI?
Topaz Photo AI is a professional software that automatically adjusts for your image quality needs. Simply import images into Topaz Photo AI and it will use specially trained AI models to first detect unique details, clarity, and resolution issues before applying the intelligently adjusts to maximize your image quality.
For users experienced with Topaz Labs image quality applications, it combines the functionality of DeNoise AI, Sharpen AI and Gigapixel AI into...
</description></item><item><title>Download NanaZip 6.0.1638.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 27 Feb 2026 17:05:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nanazip-8074.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nanazip-8074.html
</guid><description>
NanaZip is an open source file archiver for the modern Windows experience, forked from the source code of the popular open source file archiver 7-Zip. NanaZip is considered an interesting alternative to WinRAR and WinZip. According to tests, NanaZip provides about 10% better compression ratio than WinRAR and WinZip.
Supported formats:
	Packing/unpacking: 7Z, ZIP, XZ, BZIP2, GZIP, TAR and WIM.
	Extract: RAR, AR, ARJ, CAB, CHM, CPIO, CramFS, DMG, EXT, FAT, GPT, HFS, IHEX, ISO, LZH,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ashampoo Photo Commander 19.0.4</title><pubDate> Fri, 27 Feb 2026 17:04:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-photo-commander-273.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-photo-commander-273.html
</guid><description>
Ashampoo Photo Commander software brings user photo management tool effectively cover view, sort, edit, convert photos and images to the web. Ashampoo Photo Commander 16 will surprise you immediately! Interface modern user will quickly learn the features of your favorite and adjust accordingly for faster access. The slideshow images appear in the mode 4K stunning and the panoramic feature will steals the show.
Ashampoo Photo Commander - photo editing
Software Ashampoo Photo Commander...
</description></item><item><title>Download Dropbox 242.4.5815</title><pubDate> Fri, 27 Feb 2026 17:04:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dropbox-1313.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dropbox-1313.html
</guid><description>
Dropbox on taiwebs.com is free tool, the data synchronization across multiple PC become easier than never before: after installation, all what you have to do is enter your name, email address and password before opening the folder My Dropbox. If you install the software on a different computer, Dropbox will reflect the content of the online storage. So you exchange any data between the different computer is connected to Dropbox account. In addition the client is installed on the computer,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Calibre 9.4.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 27 Feb 2026 17:03:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-calibre-1669.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-calibre-1669.html
</guid><description>
Calibre  is an eBook library management application that allows you to manage your eBook collection, convert eBooks between different formats, Sync with popular e-reading devices and read your e-books with included viewer. You can sort books by author, title, date and other details, download meta information and book covers, add personalized tags and comments, and view your images in the cover display.
Collection of essential tools for adding metadata editing books or managing your...
</description></item><item><title>Download Opera One 128.0.5807.25</title><pubDate> Fri, 27 Feb 2026 17:02:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-972.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-972.html
</guid><description>
Opera is a fast, safe, configurable and compliant intranet web browser, which includes both the reader and the application. The Opera browser supports web browsing, listening to music, watching high speed movies, you can open many tabs on the Opera without affecting your browsing speed. Opera now supports almost all devices and operating systems such as windows, IOS, Android, linux, MacOS ...
Opera is a beautiful interface and many interesting features, operating on both PCs and mobile,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Advanced Installer Architect 23.5.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 27 Feb 2026 17:01:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-installer-128.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-installer-128.html
</guid><description>
Advanced Installer is a Windows utility designed to help you build the package Windows Installer in a working environment clean and intuitive.
Although it has many parameters dedicated but the user interface is very simple and gives users the ability to create new projects by selecting the type, namely installer (for example: application Visual Studio or .NET, pack 32/64-bit mixture), Java , updates, support, mobile devices, and other things.
Advanced Installer - An environment for...
</description></item><item><title>Download CoolUtils Total Doc Converter 5.1.0.377/149</title><pubDate> Fri, 27 Feb 2026 17:00:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-total-doc-converter-84.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-total-doc-converter-84.html
</guid><description>
CoolUtils Total Doc Converter Program that will allow you to document conversion DOC to others, the list can be viewed on the official website or you can watch carefully the screenshot, I think the question would no longer can download CoolUtils Total Doc Converter below. There is batch processing,in general, everything is convenient, I hope you like it.
Total Doc Converter is conversion tools text comprehensive and multi-featured, very necessary when storing or printing the text. It also...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube Downloader 3.9.18 (2602)</title><pubDate> Fri, 27 Feb 2026 16:59:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube Downloader  is a dedicated software that helps users  downloading youtube videos  Favorites on PC for offline viewing. With MediaHuman YouTube  Downloader  you can download videos from youtube website to your computer with  fast speed , with special software development technology that automatically receives videos from Websites, in addition to the ability to download videos from software websites, can convert downloaded video formats to various formats for the purpose...
</description></item><item><title>Download VideoPad Video Editor Pro 18.13 Beta</title><pubDate> Fri, 27 Feb 2026 16:58:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-videopad-video-editor-pro-268.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-videopad-video-editor-pro-268.html
</guid><description>
VideoPad Video Editor Pro is software edit video from any camcorder, DV camcorder, VHS player or webcam for best quality. The interface of this utility is divided into several parts (for example: list of multi-media, Effects, transitions, Files, Clips, video track, audio track, overlay), which makes everything seem difficult to operate. You can capture videos from camcorder or other devices like webcam or capture card TV and after you have added files and sequence clips to the queue, you...
</description></item><item><title>Download LibreOffice 26.2.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 27 Feb 2026 16:57:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-libreoffice-391.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-libreoffice-391.html
</guid><description>
LibreOffice is editor free for office similar to MS Office and OpenOffice includes word processor, spreadsheet application, presentation tool, database and design diagrams. Here is the app code open source, multi-feature, to offer users many tools to draft documents and handle the office documents efficiently.
The program can open or import most Microsoft Office formats popular, including .doc .ppt and .csv as well as many document formats other. LibreOffice is a tool to be more user...
</description></item><item><title>Download Intel Graphics Driver for Windows 10 / 11 32.0.101.8531</title><pubDate> Fri, 27 Feb 2026 16:57:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intel-graphics-driver-for-windows-10-5954.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intel-graphics-driver-for-windows-10-5954.html
</guid><description>
Intel Graphics Driver for Windows 10 supports Intel ' s latest 8th-generation Core processor, introducing the Intel ® UHD graphics, with the ability to immerve in the top 4K UHD entertainment from your laptop for a maximum of 10 hours. Along with some security fixes, this driver also optimised the system's inactivity to reduce power consumption.
Look at the complete new interface of gameplay.intel.com, where you will find the proposed game settings for many of your favorite PC games....
</description></item><item><title>Download PhraseExpress 18.0.62</title><pubDate> Fri, 27 Feb 2026 16:55:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-phraseexpress-41.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-phraseexpress-41.html
</guid><description>
PhraseExpress is a useful application that helps users save time when typing frequently used text or commands. This application allows users to create shortcuts to automatically insert text quickly and conveniently.
With PhraseExpress, users can create "templates" for common commands, regular emails, chat messages, or any text they have to retype frequently. Users only need to set up shortcuts for each template and when needed, just type that shortcut and the text will automatically...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft PIX 2602.25</title><pubDate> Fri, 27 Feb 2026 16:55:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-pix-4100.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-pix-4100.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft PIX is a free program designed for all game developers, professional and amateur, give them reviews, game performance, debugging and tuning applications. Microsoft PIX will optimize the resource consumption is essential, especially for the game that requires high resources. Microsoft PIX can provide insight about the whole process of the production and how it affects the performance of the server system. Therefore, it can prove to be a real asset in the toolbox of developers,...
</description></item><item><title>Download AutoHideMouseCursor 6.16</title><pubDate> Fri, 27 Feb 2026 16:54:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-autohidemousecursor-4104.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-autohidemousecursor-4104.html
</guid><description>
AutoHideMouseCursor is a Microsoft Windows application mobile mini allows you to hide the cursor, if the mouse is not active for a period of time. With AutoHideMouseCursor you can automatically hide the mouse cursor with the timer can be customized this is utility desktop perfect when the cursor is too annoying to them, such as when used with the application handling the text because often when you add pointers, text and cover text.
AutoHideMouseCursor - Hide mouse cursor
User...
</description></item><item><title>Download Resolume Arena 7.24.3 rev 63742</title><pubDate> Fri, 27 Feb 2026 16:53:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-resolume-arena-001-760.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-resolume-arena-001-760.html
</guid><description>
Resolume Arena is software Visual Jockey for DJ help adjust, mix and match image combination screen displayed directly. Software control it from the lighting and synchronize with the DJ via SMPTE time code. Adjust the ratio and position of the clip to suit your needs. Apply effects to change the powerful interface of the video. Everything running on the card screen so you get fast performance and good image quality as possible.
Resolume Arena - software Visual Jockey for DJ
Features of...
</description></item><item><title>Download AutoHideDesktopIcons 6.66</title><pubDate> Fri, 27 Feb 2026 16:51:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-autohidedesktopicons-1747.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-autohidedesktopicons-1747.html
</guid><description>
AutoHideDesktopIcons allows you to automatically hide the icons on his screen after some seconds of inactivity, certain to your screen is not cluttered and your wallpaper in full view. The program works very similar to the screen saver, but instead of making the desktop look your beautiful eyes, it makes it look clean.
AutoHideDesktopIcons - Hides icons on the Desktop
Must say that AutoHideDesktopIcons is software features auto hide and show on the computer screen. It has a lot of apps...
</description></item><item><title>Download Start Everywhere 1.4.3.45</title><pubDate> Fri, 27 Feb 2026 16:51:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-start-everywhere-4897.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-start-everywhere-4897.html
</guid><description>
Start Everywherel is software Start Menu provides a number of unique solutions to allow you to launch the application is installed on the computer and access the documents. The appearance, operation, and management of Start Everywhere can be flexibly customized.
Features of Start Everywhere
	It provides effective access to applications, documents, and computer settings are installed.
	It put the long list in alphabetical order and also allows you to sort them by date.
	System menu of...
</description></item><item><title>Download KeyScrambler Premium 3.19.0.2 + Professional</title><pubDate> Fri, 27 Feb 2026 16:50:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-keyscrambler-premium-professional-143.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-keyscrambler-premium-professional-143.html
</guid><description>
KeyScrambler Premium / Professional allows users to search for and remove the malicious program, the spy program on the computer system. This program support users to handle a number of spy programs send user information to the server by way thoroughly remove them from the system.
KeyScrambler Premium Key key encryption real-time encryption key, every key you type deep in the Windows. It protects the personal information of you against all malware keylog already know and not know on...
</description></item><item><title>Download Systweak PDF Editor 1.0.0.8664</title><pubDate> Fri, 27 Feb 2026 16:49:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-systweak-pdf-editor-11484.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-systweak-pdf-editor-11484.html
</guid><description>
Systweak PDF Editor is a fast and simple solution to edit, convert, sign, protect, compress PDF files and make scanned PDF files searchable and can choose. With Systweak PDF Editor, quickly convert your PDF files into a variety of editable formats. Converting PDF files to and from any MS Office files, images, ebooks, web pages, and other formats just got easier.
For working and editing PDF files, Systweak PDF editor offers many features and tools. Using them, you can mark text for...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ahnenblatt 4.43.0.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 27 Feb 2026 16:49:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ahnenblatt-3844.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ahnenblatt-3844.html
</guid><description>
Ahnenblatt is a genealogy software full-featured, easy to use suitable for beginners and even pedigree has the experience to organize genealogy research by you. Use plausibility checks to find out the inaccuracies in your family and create the chart impressive with just a few mouse clicks.
Ahnenblatt - Create family tree,
Recently, there has been strong increase of the general interest of the public for genealogical tree. Users who desire to track their heritage have many tools at...
</description></item><item><title>Download The Foundry Nuke Studio 16.1v1</title><pubDate> Fri, 27 Feb 2026 16:48:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-the-foundry-nuke-studio-733.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-the-foundry-nuke-studio-733.html
</guid><description>
Nuke®, NukeX® and Nuke Studio offer cutting-edge toolkits for node-based compositing, editorial and review. The Nuke family's unparalleled flexibility and collaborative workflows help you get the highest quality results-fast.
Power and performance
Built to meet the needs of modern production work, the Nuke family offers unparalleled levels of power and performance, whether you're a team with a deadline or tackling a solo project.
Collaborative workflow
Efficient, collaborative...
</description></item><item><title>Download Boris FX Silhouette 2025.5.3</title><pubDate> Fri, 27 Feb 2026 16:47:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-boris-fx-silhouette-4242.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-boris-fx-silhouette-4242.html
</guid><description>
Boris FX Silhouette is a composite application acceleration GPU best-in-class, provides tools roto and paint does not destroy the most powerful in the industry to highlight the group effect movies and images. Since 2005, Silhouette has burn mark in the greatest movies of Hollywood, including Avatar, Black Panther, Avengers: End Game, and many other films. Tools artists for Roto, paint and tracking. Silhouette 2020 beyond roto and made the task cleanup with the tools to complete the photo...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cryptomator 1.18.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 27 Feb 2026 16:46:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cryptomator-1763.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cryptomator-1763.html
</guid><description>
&amp;nbsp;
Cryptomator give you coding client-side free and open source for the cloud file your. It works with any cloud provider of any kind, including Dropbox, Google Drive, OneDrive and any hosting service anywhere else. Cryptomator works by creating a "Vault" is encrypted that you save to wherever you store the files their cloud. Vault can then be opened as a drive letter virtual from interface Cryptomator and you can add files by moving or copying them with Windows File Explorer....
</description></item><item><title>Download MiTeC Task Manager DeLuxe 4.11.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 27 Feb 2026 16:45:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mitec-task-manager-deluxe-145.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mitec-task-manager-deluxe-145.html
</guid><description>
MITEC Task Manager Deluxe is a software indispensable. It allows you to view the running background apps, the apps, the performance of the computer.
It provides a full range of parameters for CPU, memory, speed processing chip,....
You can also close the app when ever it crashes can not turn off as normal.
In addition, you can filter displayed items by keyword, auto-refresh view for update information and also take a snapshot of the current view using the screen capture tool built-in.
</description></item></channel></rss>