<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 20:15:56 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 20:15:56 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Final Draft 13.3.0 Build 105</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 22:39:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-final-draft-1241.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-final-draft-1241.html
</guid><description>
Final Draft is a professional program to write scripts for movies, tv shows and performances. This program is a word processor text window with a lot of ability to script specialized. To use the program, you absolutely do not need to know the rules to design the scenario - draft ultimate will automatically convert scripts you write by world standards.
Final Draft - script Writing professional
The features of Final Draft
	Send a copy of the index cards with the summary directly to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ashampoo Photo Converter 3.0.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 22:39:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-photo-converter-14004.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-photo-converter-14004.html
</guid><description>
Ashampoo Photo Converter is a Windows software tool designed for efficient image conversion and editing. The software supports more than 18 image formats and includes popular formats such as BMP, GIF, JPG, PNG, PDF and many more. The software can process individual photos or entire folders in batch mode, suitable for processing large photo collections.
Ashampoo Photo Converter Features
	Extensive format support allows conversion between multiple file types.
	Batch processing for...
</description></item><item><title>Download Net Monitor for Employees Professional 6.5.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 22:38:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-network-lookout-net-monitor-for-employees-professional-2098.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-network-lookout-net-monitor-for-employees-professional-2098.html
</guid><description>
Network LookOut Net Monitor for Employees Professional is a software platform to help manage user activity, gives the ability to inspect and control computer activities, as well as record activity on the screen as AVI file. Net Monitor for Employees Professional allows access from remote computers. This feature proved particularly useful when you want to see the activity of each user on the computer, or assist them perform the work on the computer with the mouse manipulation or the...
</description></item><item><title>Download JixiPix Pastello 6.0.104</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 22:38:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jixipix-pastello-2660.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jixipix-pastello-2660.html
</guid><description>
JixiPix Pastello is a companion app with completely new Imixi Pro of JixiPix. Pastello take you back in time to the 15th century. Leave brush and big strokes and in the kingdom of means dry with colors just brilliant and exquisite. "Method of color dry" the famous Leonardo da Vinci's very powerful by the simplicity and beauty of it with black chalk and red chalk, yellow highlights. Then, the artist will paint the portrait charm styled blend very smooth. Moving forward a few centuries later...
</description></item><item><title>Download JixiPix Chromatic Edges 1.0.36</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 22:37:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jixipix-chromatic-edges-4997.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jixipix-chromatic-edges-4997.html
</guid><description>
JixiPix Chromatic Edges gives customers more angular and professional to create many photography pop your own way. With JixiPix, customers can create the classic products or flares for your image. The products have the collection of glass, silver and paper help processing your images more easily and create many typical photos with a few taps.
The features of JixiPix Chromatic Edges
	Add an edge image, edge color and edge outside
	Use create edges to create edges
	Save the edge to use...
</description></item><item><title>Download MusConv 4.10.450 Lifetime</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 22:37:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html
</guid><description>
MusConv transfers playlists, albums, followed artists and liked songs across a variety of services – Spotify, Apple Music, Amazon Music, YouTube, YouTube Music, iTunes, Deezer, Tidal, SoundCloud, Pandora and more 125 music services!
Features of MusConv Ultimate
	Transfer playlists, albums, followed artists and liked tracks between over 125 music servicesManage playlists (Delete, Merge, Split, Copy...)
	More than 125 music services supported
	Access DAILY updated music charts on...
</description></item><item><title>Download Classroom Spy Professional 5.5.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 22:37:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-classroom-spy-professional-916.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-classroom-spy-professional-916.html
</guid><description>
Classroom Spy Professional is a software classroom management effective. Manage and track activities of all the computers of students remotely. Plus, you can share your screen with the activity record of the student, the computer controls for performance, limit the use of the Internet, the application blocks and more.
Classroom Spy Professional - software classroom management
The main features of Classroom Spy Professional
	Display live images of the remote computer.
	You can control...
</description></item><item><title>Download Jixipix Premium Pack 1.2.18</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 22:36:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jixipix-premium-pack-2656.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jixipix-premium-pack-2656.html
</guid><description>
Jixipix Premium Pack or the full name is Jixipix Software Premium Pack is a pack of 18 application incredible creative into a powerful package: Aquarella, Artista Haiku, Artista Oil, Artista Sketch, Artoon, Powderspirst, Dramatic Black &amp;amp; White, Grungetastic, Kyoobik Photo Moku Hanga NIR Color Pop Dot Comics Portrait Painter Rainy Daze, romantic Photo, simply HDR, Snow Daze, and classic Landscape. Premium Pack comes wrapped together for convenience - one application, one installation,...
</description></item><item><title>Download JixiPix Spektrel Art 1.1.22</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 22:36:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jixipix-spektrel-art-2657.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jixipix-spektrel-art-2657.html
</guid><description>
JixiPix Spektrel Art is a program convenience and style allows you to easily change the sharpness of the image to highlight motifs and attract the user's attention on the essential elements of the layout. All what we request is to transfer image into main window, select the preset, squeeze the slider to the right, then you can save results and satisfaction. Apply with photo, this medium of artistic form imaginative and magical beyond the ordinary to the extraordinary to create something...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wise Program Uninstaller 3.2.8.272</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 22:35:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wise-program-uninstaller-519.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wise-program-uninstaller-519.html
</guid><description>
Wise Program Uninstaller is a software that manages the application program was installed on the computer and support the user uninstall the application from your computer. Wise Program Uninstaller can fully uninstall applications on the system in just a few seconds. Special tool to completely remove these apps and not leave traces on the system.
Thanks features uninstall, clean the application system of Wise Program Uninstaller, you will be able to cleanup the file data garbage save...
</description></item><item><title>Download JixiPix Artista Impresso Pro 1.8.29</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 22:35:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jixipix-artista-impresso-pro-2659.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jixipix-artista-impresso-pro-2659.html
</guid><description>
JixiPix Artista Impresso Pro is an interesting program that allows you to convert photos into paintings quite beautiful, done in impressive style, they will contain the brushstrokes and color combinations, impressive. Thanks to the presets, integrated attention to the smallest details, you can get a great result in few minutes.
JixiPix Artista Impresso Pro
In addition, the program can operate as a plug-in more for popular programs such as Photoshop, Lightroom and Elements. Among the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Blue Cat Audio 2026.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 22:35:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blue-cat-audio-751.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blue-cat-audio-751.html
</guid><description>
Blue Cat Audio develops and distributes the app and the plug-in real-time audio for PC and Mac platforms, focuses on sound analysis, feedback, image accuracy and flexibility. Check out our software and convert audio workstation digital of a processing environment sounds professional.
Blue Cat Audio - Plugins audio standard
The products Plugins inside Blue Cat Audio
Blue Cat's Axiom v1.1.2
Blue Cat's Destructor v1.4.1
Blue Cat's DP Meter Pro v4.1.0
Blue Cat's Dynamics v4.2.0
Blue Cat's...
</description></item><item><title>Download Zoom Player Max 22.2 Beta 1</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 22:34:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zoom-player-max-104.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zoom-player-max-104.html
</guid><description>
Zoom Player MAX help you to see the film on DVD, Blu-ray, Flash movies and HD format with high quality and the ability to display subtitles in English very well. The advantage of software is that takes up very little system resources to play the movie with quick speed, change the wallpaper options while viewing movies.
Zoom Player MAX is the movies, browse high-quality photos on the computer with the advantages such as compact size, quick start, built-in codec. The application supports...
</description></item><item><title>Download JixiPix Photo Formation 1.0.27</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 22:33:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jixipix-photo-formation-2670.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jixipix-photo-formation-2670.html
</guid><description>
JixiPix Photo Formation is photo effects automatically convert images into paper form super creative then use the lighting tool 3D to create the ball extremely cool. Use it to segment, engage, woven, cut pieces and fold the images into each piece eye-catching appeal, with all the folds, delicate curls, and bent as if carefully assembled by hand.
The software comes with friendly interface with the user and includes dozens of presets. The effects are applied in real time and you will be...
</description></item><item><title>Download iTop Easy Desktop 4.0.0.272</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 22:33:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-itop-easy-desktop-7879.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-itop-easy-desktop-7879.html
</guid><description>
iTop Easy Desktop is a lightweight and easy-to-use desktop manager that organizes desktop icons, files and folders according to your rules, helping you Freed from the tedious arrangement of icons on the screen. It provides various practical features including but not limited to grouping desktop items, awakening live search, and quickly accessing icons and files even across multiple desktop sites. desktop.
Untidy desktop If you're not one to diligently organize your Windows desktop icons...
</description></item><item><title>Download Jixipix Watercolor Studio 1.4.22</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 22:33:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jixipix-watercolor-studio-74.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jixipix-watercolor-studio-74.html
</guid><description>
Jixipix Watercolor Studio Watercolor Studio create water color effect, liquid, matte, natural. Jixipix Watercolor Studio is built on a system of rendering incredible use of practical techniques, this application performs original work, created water colors immediately, then allows you to customize the painting of himself using a series of sliders, Class, brush, Color wash, and Artistic finish . The end result - the colors of water quality in flooded the transparency and sheer...
</description></item><item><title>Download JixiPix Hand Tint Pro 1.0.27</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 22:32:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jixipix-hand-tint-pro-2658.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jixipix-hand-tint-pro-2658.html
</guid><description>
JixiPix Hand Tint Pro is another program by JixiPix Software, popular with the development in the field of graphics processing. Now you will have everything in hand to make color, craft and coloring for the photos of you, and the goal of this event is to give them a vintage style or art.
Hand Tint Pro offers everything you need - the color palette, paper and palm smart - to create the photograph beautiful, hand-painted and timeless. Like all art forms, prepare a good base to color by hand...
</description></item><item><title>Download JWIZARD Cleaner 1.11.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 22:32:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jwizard-cleaner-12853.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jwizard-cleaner-12853.html
</guid><description>
Effective Windows cleaning software to remove unnecessary files from your PC. JWIZARD Cleaner for Windows quickly frees up disk space and keeps your system in an optimal state, ensuring your PC runs stably and efficiently. This application is designed to provide you with a comprehensive tool to analyze and optimize your PC by performing a comprehensive cleanup or a more detailed cleanup, targeting specific areas such as system, browser, mail, etc.
Features of JWIZARD Cleaner
	Clean...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft PowerToys for Windows 10/11 0.97.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 22:31:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-powertoys-for-windows-6014.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-powertoys-for-windows-6014.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft PowerToys is a user-proficiency set to adjust and streamline their Windows experience for higher productivity. Inspired by Windows 95's PowerToys project, this reboot provides users with proficiency in ways to exploit the more efficient Windows 10 and customisable processes it provides for each work process.
Utility of Microsoft PowerToys
	FancyZones is a window manager that allows you to easily create complex windows layout and quickly locate windows in those layout.
	Image...
</description></item><item><title>Download Network LookOut Administrator Pro 5.4.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 22:31:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-network-lookout-administrator-pro-1414.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-network-lookout-administrator-pro-1414.html
</guid><description>
Network LookOut Administrator Pro is application software to control the screen of the computer on the network to help full the right to monitor your computer remotely. Network LookOut Administrator use the most appropriate for LAN network, the benefits that it brought back really great, you can control the computer remotely using the mouse and keyboard , without the need to use these tools other troubles. When employees get into trouble, you only have to help from far away that still...
</description></item><item><title>Download JixiPix Rip Studio Pro 1.1.25</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 22:30:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jixipix-rip-studio-pro-2661.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jixipix-rip-studio-pro-2661.html
</guid><description>
JixiPix Rip Studio Pro is a program that can add beautiful frames to your photos just by few clicks of the mouse, any kind of sticker, how can simulation image is crumpled, in general, you can decorate your own pictures and configure each parameter separately, this will make the photos become unique. Convenient interface, and thus, will not be difficult to find it and all the layers in your photo will be processed smoothly, each layer is separately configurable.
JixiPix Rip Studio Pro -...
</description></item><item><title>Download BitRecover MBOX Viewer 9.3</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 22:30:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bitrecover-mbox-viewer-7635.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bitrecover-mbox-viewer-7635.html
</guid><description>
BitRecover MBOX Viewer is a smartly designed, simple and easy to use free viewer. By using Thunderbird MBOX, users can easily open and view MBOX file contents without extra effort. BitRecover MBOX Viewer is very handy and very useful especially for forensic investigators to investigate evidence from MBOX mailbox files as it allows to export evidence in CSV, Text, HTML, PDF, etc. It has the ability to run without installation via a pen drive so that forensic investigators can investigate...
</description></item><item><title>Download Benthic Golden 8.2.0.830</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 22:30:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-benthic-software-golden-4113.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-benthic-software-golden-4113.html
</guid><description>
Benthic Software Golden is a query tool for Oracle database. It includes the possibility of advanced queries, edit data and ability to import and export powerful, including support for Excel spreadsheet and Calc. It features compatibility closely with sqlplus estimate scenario consists of the variable binding, variable prompting and parameter scripts to go through. Benthic Software Golden can export directly to Excel files xls and xlsx. Exports can be scripted and run automatically using...
</description></item><item><title>Download JixiPix PuzziPix Pro 1.0.25</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 22:29:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jixipix-puzzipix-pro-2705.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jixipix-puzzipix-pro-2705.html
</guid><description>
JixiPix PuzziPix Pro is the software used to turn any photo into a jigsaw puzzle. PuzziPix Pro to combine the photos with the components puzzle fit perfectly for the layout and storytelling great. In Advertising, context and meaning can be in high demand for designers, so having puzzles as a visualization technique can be invaluable. PuzziPix Pro turn any photo into a jigsaw puzzle with the ability to control the creation of the final result.
Each puzzle piece can be moved, change size...
</description></item><item><title>Download Coder Technologies Coder 2.28.8</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 22:28:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coder-oss-enterprise-8726.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coder-oss-enterprise-8726.html
</guid><description>
Coder OSS Enterprise is a development platform that provides a complete cloud-based solution for software development, testing and deployment. It is designed to simplify the software development process by providing developers with a collaborative and streamlined environment.
Coder offloads development from local workstations to your on-premises infrastructure and public cloud. Boost developer productivity with powerful server resources and instant integration. Keep the code and data...
</description></item></channel></rss>