<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 13:50:08 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 13:50:08 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Taskito: To-Do List, Planner 1.1.6 build 1161</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 16:50:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-taskito-to-do-list-planner-8449.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-taskito-to-do-list-planner-8449.html
</guid><description>
Taskito is a simple yet powerful daily organizer app. It helps you organize tasks, events, notes, and reminders in one place by creating a timeline.
Features of Taskito for Android
	Plan your day.
	Get a better overview of your day and week with Timeline.
	Create daily tasks &amp;amp; To-Do Lists to track your progress.
	Gain more control over your schedule by importing Google Calendar to consolidate your events in the timeline..
	Create grocery lists, shopping lists with checklist...
</description></item><item><title>Download Anti Spy Detector - Spyware 6.7.5</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 16:49:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-anti-spy-scanner-spyware-8753.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-anti-spy-scanner-spyware-8753.html
</guid><description>
Anti-spy scanner &amp;amp; Spyware is an Android app that scans your device for spyware and other harmful applications that can compromise your privacy and security. This is a useful tool for users who want to ensure their devices are not infected with spyware or other malware that could collect sensitive information or cause other harm.
Anti Spy has been developed to scan Android devices to detect potential spies effectively. Thanks to artificial intelligence (AI), real-time signature...
</description></item><item><title>Download Rotation | Orientation Manager 29.2.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 16:49:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-rotation-orientation-manager-8332.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-rotation-orientation-manager-8332.html
</guid><description>
Rotate | Orientation Manager is a mobile application for Android devices that allows users to control screen rotation settings on their devices. This app allows users to set custom rotation settings for different apps, and also provides a quick toggle to enable or disable rotation globally.
Rotation feature | Orientation Manager
	Control screen rotation on a per-app basis
	Option to set custom rotation settings for different applications
	Quick toggle switch to enable or disable...
</description></item><item><title>Download Genius Scan Enterprise 7.34.0 build 7130</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 16:49:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-genius-scan-enterprise-8561.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-genius-scan-enterprise-8561.html
</guid><description>
Genius Scan Enterprise: Quickly scan your paper documents on the go and export them as multi-page PDF files. Place any document in front of your device's camera: our scanner app automatically recognizes the paper on the background, crops it and cleans the result. You get sharp, easy-to-read scans. Batch scanning allows you to scan dozens of pages in just a few seconds. Powerful tools help you organize, share or archive your documents.
Features of Genius Scan Enterprise for...
</description></item><item><title>Download AdGuard Ad Blocker 4.14.30 Nightly</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 16:48:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-adguard-block-ads-without-root-8215.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-adguard-block-ads-without-root-8215.html
</guid><description>
AdGuard for Android is the only root-free ad blocker for Android that removes ads in apps and browsers, protects your privacy, and helps you manage your apps. Adguard is designed to block unwanted ads, pop-ups and banners while you browse the web on your device. It uses a combination of local VPN technology and a custom DNS server to block ads, meaning it can block ads in apps as well as in web browsers.
In addition, Adguard also blocks tracking scripts from collecting information about...
</description></item><item><title>Download SnapTube for Android 7.51.1.75172801</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 16:48:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-snaptube-youtube-downloader-hd-video-8351.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-snaptube-youtube-downloader-hd-video-8351.html
</guid><description>
SnapTube is a mobile application that allows users to download videos from various platforms, such as YouTube, Vimeo, and Dailymotion. It provides video resolution in multiple formats 144p, 720p, 1080p HD, 2K HD, 4K HD and audio formats MP3 and M4A. With Snaptube, users can search for content across all their platforms without using multiple apps.
Features of SnapTube for Android
Download in multiple resolutions
	MP4 videos are available in resolutions: choose small 360 pixels or...
</description></item><item><title>Download WiFi Mouse Pro 5.6.6</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 16:48:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wifi-mouse-pro-8925.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wifi-mouse-pro-8925.html
</guid><description>
Convert your phone into a wireless mouse, keyboard and trackpad for your computer, it allows you to control your PC/Mac/Linux easily via local network connection. Media Controller, Presentation Controller and Remote File Explorer are all included in this controller app.
Now you can relax on the sofa and control movies or games in the comfort of your own home, replacing your broken mouse and keyboard with this app.
Features of WiFi Mouse Pro
	Fully simulated mouse
	Built-in support...
</description></item><item><title>Download Map Coordinates 5.8.5</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 16:47:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-map-coordinates-8437.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-map-coordinates-8437.html
</guid><description>
Map coordinates are a set of numerical values ​​that represent a specific location on the Earth's surface. The most common forms of map coordinates are latitude and longitude, which are used to pinpoint a location on a map. Latitude is a measure of a location's distance north or south of the equator, while longitude is a measure of a location's distance east or west of the Prime Meridian. Map coordinates can be used in a variety of applications, including navigation, land surveying,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Universal TV Remote Control 1.7.5 build 64</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 16:47:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-universal-tv-remote-control-9202.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-universal-tv-remote-control-9202.html
</guid><description>
Universal TV Remote Control is an Android app that turns your smartphone or tablet into a remote control for your TV. Your Android device will become a TV remote control for Smart TV, Samsung, LG, Android TV, Roku, Fire TV, Sony, etc. You can control both Smart TV (using Wi-Fi) and Non-Smart TV (using IR Blaster).
Make your life a little easier by installing UniMote. Turn your smartphone into a remote control for your TV. User-friendly interface. It's basically the old remote control...
</description></item><item><title>Download Balance: Meditation &amp;amp; Sleep 1.191.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 16:46:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-balance-meditation-sleep-8559.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-balance-meditation-sleep-8559.html
</guid><description>
Improve stress, sleep and more with the world's first personalized meditation program. Balance is your personal meditation coach. Each day, you will answer questions about your meditation experience, goals, and interests. Using an audio library of thousands of files, Balance puts together the perfect daily meditation for you. The more you share over time, the more personalized and effective your meditation becomes.
Balance's daily meditation sessions are organized according to a 10-Day...
</description></item><item><title>Download Magnifier Plus with Flashlight 4.8.16</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 16:46:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-magnifier-plus-with-flashlight-8494.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-magnifier-plus-with-flashlight-8494.html
</guid><description>
Are you tired of trying to read labels with small fonts? Now you can use your Android device as the perfect digital magnifier! No need to use a magnifying glass to read small labels - this app lets you see text large and clearly. The magnifier has on-screen zoom and illumination controls for easy operation. You can also use the flash as a light to get a brighter image, and the negative mode inverts the colors so you can see this differently when they're hard to see.
Features of...
</description></item><item><title>Download YoWindow Weather - Unlimited 2.54.7</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 16:46:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-yowindow-weather-unlimited-8421.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-yowindow-weather-unlimited-8421.html
</guid><description>
YoWindow is a unique new weather app. The magic of YoWindow is a living landscape that reflects your real-life weather. For example, if it rains - it will rain in YoWindow. Sunset and sunrise in YoWindow take place at the same time as in real life. But the cool thing is you can roll time forward. Just swipe the screen and you'll see how the weather changes throughout the day.
YoWindow Weather Features - Unlimited
	All the weather at your fingertips. You see the current weather,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Multi Timer: Timer + Stopwatch 2.2.16</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 16:45:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-timer-plus-with-stopwatch-10105.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-timer-plus-with-stopwatch-10105.html
</guid><description>
Multi Timer is a comprehensive mobile app designed to revolutionize how you track and manage time. The stopwatch and digital timer are simple, easy -to -use and accurate applications for Android to help you measure the time of all situations, such as sports, cooking, etc. With the time application, you will enjoy the freedom of the time counter and the timer and the full -featured and complete stopwatch with the ring and the clear display function.
Features of Multi Timer
	Easy to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Scientific Calculator Pro 6.10.15</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 16:45:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-scientific-calculator-pro-11445.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-scientific-calculator-pro-11445.html
</guid><description>
Turn your phone into the best scientific calculator you've ever used with this essential app. Basic, advanced, and graphing modes let you use only what you need, when you need it. It's fast, easy to use and looks real.
Main features
	No advertising
	Full-color graph
	Works in landscape and portrait mode
	Trigonometry, log, exponent
	Calculate fractions
	Complex numbers
	Linear equations and polynomials
	Basic statistical functions
	Binary, decimal, hexadecimal operations
	Bitwise...
</description></item><item><title>Download Maple Calculator: Math Solver 4.3.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 16:45:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-maple-calculator-math-solver-13489.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-maple-calculator-math-solver-13489.html
</guid><description>
Powered by Maple, the world's most powerful math engine, this all-in-one calculator solves math problems, creates 2-D and 3-D visualizations, and provides step-by-step solutions to a wide variety of math homework problems encountered in high school and college.
This app is a graphing calculator, scientific calculator, algebra calculator, integral calculator, and calculator integration all rolled into one! Take a picture of your problem with your phone's camera or type it in through the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Map My Run GPS Running Tracker 25.12.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 16:44:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-map-my-run-by-under-armour-8145.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-map-my-run-by-under-armour-8145.html
</guid><description>
Map My Run by Under Armor is a mobile app that allows users to track their running, walking, and other outdoor activities using GPS. The app is available to download from the Google Play Store and Apple App Store. It was developed by Under Armour, a company specializing in sports apparel and equipment. In addition to tracking workouts, the app also provides users with tools to analyze performance and set goals.
Features of Map My Run by Under Armor APK
	GPS tracking: The app uses GPS...
</description></item><item><title>Download Any.do - To do list &amp;amp; Calendar 5.18.15.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 16:44:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-anydo-to-do-list-calendar-8360.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-anydo-to-do-list-calendar-8360.html
</guid><description>
Any.do is a productivity app that combines the features of a to-do list and a calendar. It allows users to create and organize tasks as well as schedule them according to specific dates and times. The app also includes a feature called "My Day" that helps users focus on the most important tasks of the day.
Some of Any.do's other features include the ability to set reminders, create side and recurring tasks, and collaborate on tasks with others. Additionally, Any.do also has a calendar...
</description></item><item><title>Download Swiftly switch Pro 4.3.9</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 16:44:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-swiftly-switch-pro-10045.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-swiftly-switch-pro-10045.html
</guid><description>
Swiftly Switch is an edge app that improves your Android experience by allowing you to use your phone with one hand and multitask faster! Swiftly Switch runs in the background and can be easily accessed from any screen with just a swipe from the edge screen. It's fast, battery-friendly, highly customizable, and ad-free.
Features of Swiftly switch for Android
	Recent apps switcher: Organize your recent apps in a floating circular sidebar. Switch between them with a swipe from the area...
</description></item><item><title>Download Multi Timer StopWatch 2.13.30</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 16:43:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-multi-timer-stopwatch-8914.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-multi-timer-stopwatch-8914.html
</guid><description>
Multi Timer is a beautifully designed time management app. Multiple timers can be set, started and run independently at the same time. Stopwatch results can be stored. Use Multi Timer for cooking, sports, machine washing, studying, working, gaming - whatever you like.
Features of Multi Timer StopWatch
	Multiple timers at once: Store the timers you often use for cooking, sports, studying, working, gaming, whatever you want. Start them with just one tap, anytime you need.
	Timer in...
</description></item><item><title>Download Money Lover - Spending Manager 8.52.0.57</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 16:43:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-money-lover-spending-manager-8349.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-money-lover-spending-manager-8349.html
</guid><description>
Receive personal finance awards &amp;amp; Money management app to manage money now! Track your spending, monitor your transactions, create a monthly budget, motivate yourself to save money, and more. You can also link your Money Lover wallet to your bank account to automatically track your transaction history. Money Lover is a must-have app for personal finance management. Financial management becomes super easy and fast!
Managing personal finances can be difficult for many people. You need...
</description></item><item><title>Download Gaia GPS: Offline Trail Maps 2025.8 build 10275</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 16:42:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-gaia-gps-offroad-hiking-maps-8610.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-gaia-gps-offroad-hiking-maps-8610.html
</guid><description>
Gaia GPS is a navigation app that provides hiking maps, topographic maps, and satellite images for outdoor enthusiasts. It allows users to plan trips, navigate the wilderness, and track their progress. The app is available for both iOS and Android devices, and offers a premium subscription for offline maps, aerial imagery, and advanced features.
Features of Gaia GPS for Android
	Offline maps: Ability to download maps for offline use, ideal for use in areas with limited or no Internet...
</description></item><item><title>Download PeakFinder 4.8.71</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 16:42:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-peakfinder-10050.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-peakfinder-10050.html
</guid><description>
Explore more mountains than any other climber! PeakFinder AR makes it possible… and shows the names of all the mountains and peaks with a 360° panoramic display. This functionality is completely offline - and worldwide! PeakFinder knows more than 650,000 mountain peaks - from Mount Everest to that little hill on the corner.
PeakFinder Features
	Works offline and worldwide
	Includes more than 650,000 peak names
	Install the camera image using a panoramic drawing *
	Display real-time...
</description></item><item><title>Download Overdrop - Weather &amp;amp; Widget 2.4.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 16:41:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-overdrop-weather-widgets-8404.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-overdrop-weather-widgets-8404.html
</guid><description>
Powered by the world's leading source of hyper-local weather data, Overdrop is the perfect companion for life on the go. Stay one step ahead with real-time predictions in an app that won't slow you down.
Overdrop Features - Weather &amp;amp; Widget
	Real-time detailed weather data
	24-hour and 7-day forecast
	Customizable weather notifications
	Severe condition warning
	Optimized for aspects
	5 themes (including Alomed theme)
	Time, weather and battery widgets
	‘At a glance’ widget...
</description></item><item><title>Download Flowx: Weather Map Forecast 4.144</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 16:41:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-flowx-weather-map-forecast-8535.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-flowx-weather-map-forecast-8535.html
</guid><description>
Visualize forecasts anywhere in the world with unique Flowx weather maps and charts. Move your finger across the screen to control the forecast animation over time. Choose data according to your needs from over 30 data types and several forecast models, including GFS, GDPS, NAM, HRRR, ICON, ICON-EU, APERGE, AROME, HIRLAM, COSMO, RDPS &amp;amp; HRDPS. Use Flowx for weather planning, for aviation, fishing, boating, surfing, cycling, hiking, photography, storm tracking, or anyone interested in...
</description></item><item><title>Download Twilight: Blue light filter 14.20 build 598</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 16:40:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-twilight-blue-light-filter-12193.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-twilight-blue-light-filter-12193.html
</guid><description>
Are you having trouble falling asleep? Is your child hyperactive when playing with the tablet before going to bed? The Twilight app helps your device's screen adapt to the time of day. It filters the blue light emitted from your phone or tablet after sunset and protects your eyes with a soft and pleasant red filter. Filter intensity is smoothly adjusted to the solar cycle based on your local sunset and sunrise times.
Get more from Twilight
	- Reading in bed: Twilight is more...
</description></item></channel></rss>