<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 09:01:13 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 09:01:13 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download MSI Center 2.0.59.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 23:35:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-msi-center-12314.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-msi-center-12314.html
</guid><description>
The AI ​​era of computing: MSI laptops are equipped with MSI's exclusive AI technology capable of providing completely new smart features. The AI ​​revolution has arrived on MSI laptops. MSI AI Engine automatically recognizes various user situations, triggering appropriate adjustments in performance, sound effects, display modes and keyboard backlighting. Users do not need to make manual adjustments to achieve optimal situations.
MSI Center combines all of MSI's exclusive...
</description></item><item><title>Download IObit Driver Booster Pro 13.0.0.143</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 23:33:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iobit-driver-booster-102.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iobit-driver-booster-102.html
</guid><description>
IObit Driver Booster Pro is the starting step to avoid hardware errors, the loss of the system and hidden security vulneruses. To update the regular driver is also an effective way to enhance your overall computer performance and maximize your gaming experience. While this process can be dangerous and frustrating if done manually. IObit Driver Booster Pro is introduced to download and update the driver for you automatically with only one click. Based on the cloud library, IObit Driver...
</description></item><item><title>Download Serif Affinity Designer 2.6.4.3634</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 23:32:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-affinity-designer-328.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-affinity-designer-328.html
</guid><description>
Affinity Designer is the design software graphics for premium users, helping you to realize the ideas in his creating project, such as design, user interface, web graphics. Affinity Designer own vector fastest, smoothest, most accurate out there. Whether you are working on branding, concept art, project, print, logo, ui, UX, website, or forged, Affinity Designer will revolutionize the way you work, on macOS and Windows.
Affinity Designer will help you handle the images, allowing zoom...
</description></item><item><title>Download Topaz Gigapixel Pro 1.0.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 23:32:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-ai-gigapixel-1318.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-ai-gigapixel-1318.html
</guid><description>
Topaz ONE Gigapixel is the first app and only use the power of artificial intelligence to enhance your photos, add natural details, for great results. Use technology to learn deep, AIGigapixel ™ can zoom in and fill in the details that the products change in size other are not included. The traditional method this created blurred image, a non-realistic and do not have the detail present in the image have high resolution.
Topaz A.I. Gigapixel - enhance image quality
The content of...
</description></item><item><title>Download OBS Studio 32.0.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 23:32:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-open-broadcaster-software-2451.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-open-broadcaster-software-2451.html
</guid><description>
Open Broadcaster Software is abbreviated as OBS is a program to detect the type of multimedia content to the internet. It is worth noting that a simple interface and the presence of a good tool. You can adjust the quality of the audio and video before starting the broadcast, you can specify the URL, choose the resolution of the screen, etc. With strong desire, videos which you found can be saved to your hard drive.
Open Broadcaster Software - LiveStream on PC
The basic features of Open...
</description></item><item><title>Download Serif Affinity Photo 2.6.4.3634</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 23:31:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-serif-affinity-photo-318.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-serif-affinity-photo-318.html
</guid><description>
Serif Affinity Photo is photo editing software professional provides sophisticated tools to enhance and edit images in a interface is extremely intuitive, with all the power and performance you need. Serif Affinity Photo is built on the foundation of solid rock with the principles of performance, stability and lack of swell, Affinity Photo is a photography tool professional to the core.
Serif Affinity Photo has process work in CMYK from beginning to end with ICC color management and...
</description></item><item><title>Download DaVinci Resolve Studio 20.2.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 23:30:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-davinci-resolve-studio-1072.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-davinci-resolve-studio-1072.html
</guid><description>
DaVinci Resolve Studio is professional video editing and color grading software developed by Blackmagic Design. This is an enhanced version of the free DaVinci Resolve software, providing additional features and capabilities for professional video editing, color correction, and post-production.
One of the outstanding features of DaVinci Resolve Studio is its powerful color correction capabilities. It provides a comprehensive set of tools and features for advanced color correction,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Serif Affinity Publisher 2.6.4.3634</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 23:29:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-serif-affinity-publisher-2165.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-serif-affinity-publisher-2165.html
</guid><description>
Fluid publishing powerhouse. Bring your vision to life with Affinity Publisher, the next generation of professional publishing software. From magazines, books, brochures, posters, reports and stationery to other creations, this incredibly smooth, intuitive app gives you the power to combine your images, graphics and text to make beautiful layouts ready for publication.
Serif Affinity Publisher
Engineered for advanced technology
	Engineered with the same no-compromise vision as our...
</description></item><item><title>Download KMPlayer (KMP) 2025.9.22.12 x64 / 4.2.3.25 x86</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 23:29:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kmplayer-kmp-902.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kmplayer-kmp-902.html
</guid><description>
KMPlayer (KMP) is software watch movies listen to music multi-function for video enthusiasts. KMPlayer development is many types of the format different. KMPlayer has improved on sound quality, images when listening to music and watching movies, the playback speed of video is faster, more codec player is added to the software video decoder is optimized.
KMPlayer also supports a variety of audio formats and video and offers a the interface can be customized with the preview coverflow and...
</description></item><item><title>Download EaseUS ClipAce (ScreenShot) 1.8.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 23:28:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-screenshot-7937.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-screenshot-7937.html
</guid><description>
Capture everything on your screen easily through this tool, EaseUS ScreenShot provides users with a powerful set of screen capture tools to meet all their needs. The app is easy to start and use, and it does exactly what you'd expect: it helps you take screenshots without much effort.
You can capture the entire screen or just an area of ​​it. To help improve usability, double-pressing the Alt key automatically captures the full screen, while pressing Ctrl twice will let you select...
</description></item><item><title>Download Blackmagic Design Fusion Studio 20.2.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 23:28:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blackmagic-design-fusion-studio-2750.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blackmagic-design-fusion-studio-2750.html
</guid><description>
Blackmagic Design Fusion Studio is the world's most advanced compositing software for visual effects artists, broadcast and motion graphics designers, and 3D animators. For the past 30 years, Fusion has been used on thousands of Hollywood blockbuster films and television shows. Fusion features a powerful node-based interface that lets you quickly and easily create sophisticated effects by connecting different types of image processing tools together! You get a wide range of tools,...
</description></item><item><title>Download ExpanDrive 2025.09.18</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 23:28:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-expandrive-609.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-expandrive-609.html
</guid><description>
ExpanDrive is software sync cloud storage strong support BackBlaze B2, Google Team Drive, SMB / CIFS and new interface and easy user search file version, share links and much more.  ExpanDrive mapped network drives for macOS and Micosoft Windows connect with all the provide major cloud storage such as Dropbox, Google Drive, Google Team Drive, Amazon Drive, Box, OneDrive, OneDrive for Business, Sharepoint, Openstack Swift , BackBlaze B2, Amazon S3 or SFTP servers, FTP or WebDAV on your own...
</description></item><item><title>Download Derivative TouchDesigner Pro 2023.12370</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 23:27:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-derivative-touchdesigner-pro-3916.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-derivative-touchdesigner-pro-3916.html
</guid><description>
Derivative TouchDesigner Pro is a development platform visual equip you with the tools you need to create the project real-time stunning user experience and rich. Whether you are creating the system, media interaction, project architecture, photos, live music, or simply rapid-prototyping creative impulses your latest Derivative TouchDesigner Pro is platform can do it all.
Derivative TouchDesigner Pro - creation Support project, application
Derivative TouchDesigner Pro works well with...
</description></item><item><title>Download Nemetschek SCIA Engineer 2025 v25.0.4009.64</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 23:26:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nemetschek-scia-enginee-1960.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nemetschek-scia-enginee-1960.html
</guid><description>
Nemetschek SCIA Enginee software analysis and design, software structures for multiple projects. This software has both the spread of the capabilities of each other. Nemetschek SCIA Enginee can be used for a variety of design projects, office building, plant and equipment and Bridges in user interface easy to use.
Nemetschek SCIA Enginee - 2019 v19.0.1219
The features of Nemetschek SCIA Enginee
	Models like BIM
	Use the mesh &amp;amp; stories
	Wind generator 3D
	Download free
	Meshing...
</description></item><item><title>Download Directory Opus Pro 13.18.5 Beta</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 23:26:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-opus-pro-779.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-opus-pro-779.html
</guid><description>
Directory Opus Pro is a software replacement for Explorer with traditional strength and function more than any manager other files. Directory Opus Pro full support for high DPI screen (for example 4K and 5K) with the rename dialog is redesigned, with new features. Besides being a recording macro only allows you to perform mass renaming complex that don't need regular expressions. In addition, Directory Opus Pro also enhances the ability to script.Better handling of renaming recursive and...
</description></item><item><title>Download RoboTask 10.5.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 23:26:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-robotask-6157.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-robotask-6157.html
</guid><description>
RoboTask is software that allows you to automate any task combination on your computer, from just launching applications, checking your email, moving or backup files to upload or download, email and more. The program allows easy task to create simple tasks, as well as highly complex automation, involving the IF/ELSE statements that have conditions, loops, customization variables, and other advanced options.
Just a few minutes with RoboTask will give you a lot of ideas about how you can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Plex Media Server 1.42.2.10156</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 23:25:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-plexp-media-server-47.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-plexp-media-server-47.html
</guid><description>
Plex Media Server allows you to stream movies, music and photos from PC to Roku devices, Google TV or DLNA compatible (for example PS3, Xbox 360). You can also stream online media his to another computer or mobile device (Android, iOS ...) with the help of the client application available.
Film and television program you are presented with the origin-themed, cover art, overview the plot and cast, cross-link, as well as the technical details.
Content update Plex Media Server...
</description></item><item><title>Download Vivaldi Browser 7.6.3797.55</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 23:25:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vivaldi-159.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vivaldi-159.html
</guid><description>
Vivaldi is a browser designed for users who have power and offer the option to customize high. You can choose the location of the tabs and the address bar, put the hotkeys for the common tasks and many other features. Also, Vivaldi also provides a number of improvements such as Tab Stacks to group multiple open tabs into a tab, leads to interface less cluttered. Can notes and added a screenshot of a web page while browsing, storing an attachment, and add the URL to easily sort and locate...
</description></item><item><title>Download Argente System Repair 1.0.2.7</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 23:24:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-argente-system-repair-13813.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-argente-system-repair-13813.html
</guid><description>
Argente System Repair is a lightweight utility designed to diagnose and fix common Windows system problems. It scans your system to identify errors in operating system components, file systems, installation files, and other system components, and then applies targeted fixes to resolve these problems. The tool provides different scan modes, including simple scan, recommended scan, and custom scan, allowing users to customize the repair process according to their needs.
System Repair...
</description></item><item><title>Download DBF Viewer 2000 8.83</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 23:23:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbf-viewer-2000-7869.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbf-viewer-2000-7869.html
</guid><description>
DBF Viewer 2000 is a fast, efficient solution for viewing and editing all types of DBF files. It can handle files from dBase, Visual dBase, Foxpro, Visual FoxPro and Clipper, just to name a few, with performance that easily rivals expensive professional database utilities. DBF Viewer 2000 is extremely fast, does any task, just one simple query and cleanup copy to export data at lightning speed.
With DBF Editor's simple, dynamically generated visual dialogs, you can easily view the...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDF-XChange Editor Plus 10.7.3.401.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:55:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-xchange-editor-plus-645.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-xchange-editor-plus-645.html
</guid><description>
PDF-XChange Editor Plus is the editor, PDF viewer, compact, fast with many features, add-ons, professional. When using the PDF-XChange Editor Plus, easy for users to create, view, edit, annotate, OCR and digital signing PDF files, plus much more.
PDF-XChange Editor is a PDF editing full-featured. With the help of it, you can edit, fix, add, or delete text easily. Graphics can also be moved, resized or removed.
Features PDF-XChange Editor Plus
Edit documents
	Use a variety of editing...
</description></item><item><title>Download Screenpresso Pro 2.1.39</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:55:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-screenpresso-pro-1362.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-screenpresso-pro-1362.html
</guid><description>
Screenpresso Pro is a program easy to take great photos on your screen! Screenpresso blocked Print Screen key and screen capture the best in a few seconds. Allows you to capture windows and screen area, roll the part of the screen, edit the images obtained, add effects, resize a group of images, send screenshots by email and post them to Web resources.
Screenpresso Pro - Shooting the computer screen
Features of Screenpresso Pro
	Take the window and screen area. Take a partial screen...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDF-XChange Pro 10.7.3.401.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:54:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-xchange-editor-pro-3422.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-xchange-editor-pro-3422.html
</guid><description>
PDF-XChange Editor Pro is an application to manipulate and create PDF versatile, offering a wide range of useful features and powerful will help you to easily work with PDF files. This application is very flexible and allows you to easily create and modify PDF files. PDF-XChange Editor Pro provides a powerful set of tools and flexibility to work with PDF files, such as editor PDF-XChange new, utilities series, OFFice2PDF and the Addin tool Bar allows you to easily convert multiple file...
</description></item><item><title>Download Helium Music Manager Premium 17.4.528</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:54:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-helium-music-manager-premium-164.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-helium-music-manager-premium-164.html
</guid><description>
Helium Music Manager is a music manager that can rip, tag, play, browse, search, rename, burn and synchronize your music with the mobile. You can control your music collection with Helium Music Manager. Stop using time looking for the file on your computer or looking through CDS, vinyl records and tapes - instead, simply enjoy and explore your music! Helium Music Manager can replace the ripper, the player, tag editor and related software to audio your other.
Helium Music Manager...
</description></item><item><title>Download Abelssoft HappyCard 4.05</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:53:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-abelssoft-happycard-3128.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-abelssoft-happycard-3128.html
</guid><description>
Abelssoft HappyCard allows you to create cards, business cards only in few clicks. HappyCard help users to have simple interface to use to create invitation cards in just a few clicks. The card is made creative, without any previous knowledge. No matter if you want to make a invitation card, greeting card or a gift card: HappyCard comes with 50 card templates professional for events such as birthday party, wedding, etc.
Abelssoft HappyCard - Create invitations, business cards
Features...
</description></item></channel></rss>