<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 13:52:42 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 13:52:42 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Zero Install 2.27.3</title><pubDate> Wed, 30 Jul 2025 15:53:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zero-install-1632.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zero-install-1632.html
</guid><description>
Zero Install is a system, install the software distribution cross africa focus. Other features include full support for shared libraries (with the SAT for resolution dependent), share between users, and integration with the package manager original foundation. Zero Install supports both binary packages and source and works on Linux systems , OS X , Unix and Windows. It is completely open source.
Zero Install - System software installation
Zero Install also has a number of interesting...
</description></item><item><title>Download CapCut PC 6.7.0.2661 / 6.8.0.2697 Beta 4</title><pubDate> Wed, 30 Jul 2025 15:52:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capcut-pc-9995.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capcut-pc-9995.html
</guid><description>
CapCut PC is a simple video editing tool that you can freely use anywhere. You can create videos on your browser, desktop and laptop, or on your phone. Versatile editing, magical AI tools, team collaboration, and built-in assets. Create videos in a whole new way.
You can edit videos based on editing the timeline, in the process you can add different elements and effects to the video to give the best effect to your work. It is a simple and intuitive set of editing tools and effects that...
</description></item><item><title>Download GoodSync Enterprise 12.9.2.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 30 Jul 2025 15:50:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-goodsync-enterprise-163.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-goodsync-enterprise-163.html
</guid><description>
GoodSync Enterprise is a software that saves files and files easily and is reliable. It automatically analyts, synchronize and backup your email, family photos, contacts, MP3, financial documentation and other important files-between desktop computers, laptops, servers, external drives and Windows Mobile devices as well as remotely via FTP , SFTP, WebDAV and more. The GoodSync synchronized software combines bulletproof reliability with an extremely easy interface to compare, synchronize...
</description></item><item><title>Download iDownerGo Pro 10.6.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 30 Jul 2025 15:49:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idownergo-12439.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idownergo-12439.html
</guid><description>
iDownerGo is the best tool that allows users to download videos, music and playlists from more than 10,000 streaming sites. It can easily convert videos to MP4, MOV, MKV, 3GP, AAC, WAV, FLAC and other formats on PC and Mac. With this amazing program, users can enjoy their favorite media content without restrictions.
iDownerGo Features
	Download any video up to 8K resolution
	Download 1080p videos online from over 10,000 popular streaming sites easily.
	Save any video in various...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Saver Pro 10.6.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 30 Jul 2025 15:49:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-saver-6830.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-saver-6830.html
</guid><description>
YT Saver is a software that supports downloading Video, Audio, Playlist from 10,000+ websites, Convert Video to MP4, MOV, AAC, WAV and more. YT Saver is a powerful downloader that allows you to save video and audio for free. The output format of the high-speed converter is high-quality MP4, MP3. Fully compatible with iPhone, iPad, iTunes, iMovie, Android Phone and more.
Supported Input Formats:
	Video: MP4, M4V, 3GP, MPEG, DAT, AVI, ASF, WMV, VOB, MKV, FLV, 3GS, 3G2, F4V, WEBM, TS,...
</description></item><item><title>Download 4KSoftware 4K Downloader 5.16.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 30 Jul 2025 15:48:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-downloader-3858.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-downloader-3858.html
</guid><description>
4K Downloader is a Windows application small but powerful to download and convert video in 4K and 8K Ultra HD from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion and thousands of other video-based websites. It speeds up your download by up to 5 times. Consider that most smart phones, TVS, computers, and tablets all support the high definition format, don't be surprised when many users want to enjoy quality content on their device. 4K Downloader is a lightweight software designed to help you grab videos...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cascadeur 2025.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 30 Jul 2025 15:41:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cascadeur-9720.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cascadeur-9720.html
</guid><description>
Cascadeur is a standalone software for 3D keyframe animation of human figures or other characters. Never before has it been so easy and fun to create an animation from scratch or re-edit. Thanks to AI-powered tools, you can perform key poses very quickly, see the physical results immediately, and adjust the secondary movement. All while retaining full control at any point.
Cascadeur uses advanced simulation techniques and algorithms to accurately simulate the movements and interactions...
</description></item><item><title>Download Dropbox 229.4.5197</title><pubDate> Wed, 30 Jul 2025 15:41:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dropbox-1313.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dropbox-1313.html
</guid><description>
Dropbox on taiwebs.com is free tool, the data synchronization across multiple PC become easier than never before: after installation, all what you have to do is enter your name, email address and password before opening the folder My Dropbox. If you install the software on a different computer, Dropbox will reflect the content of the online storage. So you exchange any data between the different computer is connected to Dropbox account. In addition the client is installed on the computer,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Winstep Nexus 25.7</title><pubDate> Wed, 30 Jul 2025 15:40:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winstep-xtreme-447.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winstep-xtreme-447.html
</guid><description>
Winstep Nexus is software that helps you reschedule the icons of apps, prevent a disturbance on the Desktop. Winstep Nexus offers multiple features that are differentiated into different main application groups so you choose to use. Winstep Nexus has the ability to organize icons of applications, frequently used documents on a computer so that your computer will always be in a stack of blocks.
Winstep Nexus helps to enhance your productivity, software that allows you to work better and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Synapse Audio DUNE 3 3.6.4</title><pubDate> Wed, 30 Jul 2025 15:40:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-synapse-audio-dune-1030.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-synapse-audio-dune-1030.html
</guid><description>
Synapse Audio DUNE is the new technology brought the concept of unison fame to new heights. Unison is a feature classic synthesizer developed at the same time many voice when playing a note, usually up to 8. The voice that can be separated and spread in the stereo field. The new thing about DUNE is the ability to do anything with the voice, not that most, or even the phrase the voice.
Synapse Audio DUNE 3
The filter is modified in Dune 3 now has filters multi-dual mode plus effects...
</description></item><item><title>Download Alternate Password DB 3.630</title><pubDate> Wed, 30 Jul 2025 15:39:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-alternate-password-db-2723.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-alternate-password-db-2723.html
</guid><description>
Alternate Password DB is a program to securely store the password and your PIN code. With just one password, you have access to the encrypted data (BLOWFISH 256 bit). The password file can be converted into an executable file, can be transferred on a USB memory stick or other removable drive without the need to install this program.
Alternate Password DB - password storage safe
You can also configure the program locks itself after a period of time (main password will be required...
</description></item><item><title>Download Visual Studio Code 1.102.3</title><pubDate> Wed, 30 Jul 2025 15:36:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-visual-studio-code-3182.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-visual-studio-code-3182.html
</guid><description>
Visual Studio Code is the encryption tool of Microsoft has met most of the needs of the developer. Environment this encoding was introduced to compete with other products such as Sublime and Nodepad ++ . Microsoft, in its new product, has not been released in many years, has provided many features in a simple environment. In addition to the familiar with a dozen programming languages, the syntax and get to know coding language as soon as be encrypted and allows for syntax highlighting, it...
</description></item><item><title>Download Pazu Apple Music Converter 1.8.6</title><pubDate> Wed, 30 Jul 2025 15:35:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pazu-apple-music-converter-11027.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pazu-apple-music-converter-11027.html
</guid><description>
Pazusoft Apple Music Converter for Windows allows you to easily download Apple Music songs, albums and playlists to M4A, MP3, AAC, FLAC, WAV, AIFF. So you can play Apple Music songs offline wherever you want, without the Music app or iTunes.
Pazu Apple Music Converter helps you download songs, albums, and Apple Music playlists to M4A/MP3/AAC/FLAC/WAV/AIFF while preserving the original sound quality (up to 256kbps). Additionally, custom output settings such as audio quality, file name...
</description></item><item><title>Download SysTools NSF Converter 6.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 30 Jul 2025 15:34:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-systools-nsf-converter-9228.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-systools-nsf-converter-9228.html
</guid><description>
SysTools NSF Converter is a software utility designed to help users convert Lotus Notes NSF files to a variety of file formats, including PST, EML, MSG, PDF , HTML and other formats. This software is designed to provide a quick and easy way to convert NSF files to other formats without requiring any technical knowledge or expertise.
Features of SysTools NSF Converter
	Convert NSF files Email, Contacts, Tasks &amp;amp; Calendars in 8+ file formats
	Export NSF to MSG, PDF, MBOX, EML, vCard,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Room Arranger 10.2.0.725 Beta</title><pubDate> Wed, 30 Jul 2025 15:34:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-room-arranger-3779.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-room-arranger-3779.html
</guid><description>
Room Arranger is a 3D application lets you easily plan for the room, office or his apartment just a few mouse clicks. The application comes with a simple interface will significantly simplify your work. You can draw many kinds of objects and items to create furniture of your own. This app also includes a library of object rich.
Software Room Arranger enables you to view your project in 3D form. You can also upload the 3D scene interact on your blog or your website. The application uses...
</description></item><item><title>Download Nobe OmniScope 1.10.166</title><pubDate> Wed, 30 Jul 2025 15:34:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nobe-omniscope-10985.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nobe-omniscope-10985.html
</guid><description>
Nobe OmniScope is a powerful and flexible video monitoring and analysis tool used by professionals in the film, television and post-production industries. It provides a comprehensive set of features and tools for monitoring, analyzing, and editing video footage. Nobe OmniScope is equipped with many powerful features to help classify colors easily. GPU acceleration, HDR support, StreamDeck. Use the benefits of GPU acceleration and monitor your images in real time with virtually no...
</description></item><item><title>Download Muziza YouTube Downloader Converter 8.11.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 30 Jul 2025 15:33:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-muziza-youtube-downloader-converter-3972.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-muziza-youtube-downloader-converter-3972.html
</guid><description>
Muziza YouTube Downloader Converter is a tool to create conditions for an attractive interface and many features to help you to download video clips from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion, Instagram and other sites. Muziza YouTube Downloader Converter can also download the video UHD 8K, 5K, 4K, QHD 2K, HD 1080p and 720p from YouTube. The app allows you download only audio stream from YouTube and save as MP3. You don't need to download the entire video file.
Muziza YouTube Downloader...
</description></item><item><title>Download Karaosoft Karma 2026.0.5</title><pubDate> Wed, 30 Jul 2025 15:32:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-karma-2379.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-karma-2379.html
</guid><description>
Karma is an enhancement program that helps you tune, karaoke can view the text of the files sound different. At first glance, after launch, the layout may seem complicated, unclear where to start. You can customize the display prompts to understand the function of each parameter is highlighted integrated.
Management program your karaoke a easy way. Search no need to click, drag and drop feature and many other unique features designed to bring you the easiest management for the program...
</description></item><item><title>Download Duplicate &amp;amp; Same Files Searcher 10.6.6</title><pubDate> Wed, 30 Jul 2025 15:31:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-duplicate-same-files-searcher-1758.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-duplicate-same-files-searcher-1758.html
</guid><description>
Duplicate &amp;amp; Same Files Searcher is the duplicate search allows you to search for files similar or identical on your computer and help you delete to free up disk space.The interface of the app Duplicate &amp;amp; Same Files Searcher user-friendly. So, you can immediately start the search by setting the destination drive.
Duplicate &amp;amp; Same Files Searcher - Find duplicate files
With software you can include and exclude file types, set file size, minimum and maximum, just find the link...
</description></item><item><title>Download TubeDownload Pro 6.28.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 30 Jul 2025 15:31:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubedownload-pro-12035.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubedownload-pro-12035.html
</guid><description>
TubeDownload Pro is a professional Windows application for downloading your favorite videos from YouTube and hundreds of other video sites. TubeDownload Pro can increase download speed up to 500% or even more.
Features of TubeDownload Pro
	Download your favorite videos from YouTube and hundreds of other video sites.
	Increase download speed up to 500% or even more.
	Download 720p, 1080p, 2K, 4K and 8K HD videos from YouTube.
	Download entire playlists in just a few clicks.
	Download...
</description></item><item><title>Download QOwnNotes 25.7.9</title><pubDate> Wed, 30 Jul 2025 15:30:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qownnotes-3178.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qownnotes-3178.html
</guid><description>
QOwnNotes is notes bookmark file simple text (GPL) open source application for GNU / Linux , Mac OS X and Windows of Patrizio Bekerle ( pbek on GitHub and IRC) (optional) activity along with the notes application of ownCloud or Nextcloud. QOwnNote store your notes as plain text files and can be synchronized with synchronization function file of ownCloud / Nextcloud. You can also use other apps like Syncthing or Dropbox . Just write out your thoughts as they appear, and edit them if...
</description></item><item><title>Download Pixel Sorter Studio Bundle 2025.7</title><pubDate> Wed, 30 Jul 2025 12:47:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pixel-sorter-studio-bundle-13972.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pixel-sorter-studio-bundle-13972.html
</guid><description>
Pixel Sorter Studio Bundle is a set of pixel sorting tools and plugins designed for creative visual effects, mainly glitch and distortion effects, by rearranging pixel data. These tools are built into a variety of platforms, including After Effects, Premiere Pro, Nuke, Fusion, and DaVinci Resolve, and are also available as standalone applications for Windows.
Plugins include:
Ballpoint is a GPU-accelerated plugin for After Effects and Premiere that transforms your footage into dense,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Blender 4.5.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:53:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blender-3017.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blender-3017.html
</guid><description>
Blender has a tool that new and very powerful, whose name is Ciking provides the ability to display extremely impressive and extremely realistic.
Features of Blender
	- Feature button support complete
	- The ball exactly on the physical side, SSS and translucency
	- Support languages open for coding the ball unique
Blender - The software-rendered optical
Tool output integration provides:
	- The GPU and CPU
	- Preview options view real-time
	- Support light HDR
	- The license...
</description></item><item><title>Download balenaEtcher 2.1.4</title><pubDate> Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:53:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-etcher-1748.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-etcher-1748.html
</guid><description>
Etcher help easy and safe to flash the operating system image to the SD card and USB drive, using a 3-step process simple. Just select the image file to the operating system you want to use (.iso, zip, .bin, etc.), specify the drive you want to flash and start the process. Etcher automatically check for SD card or hard drive to ensure that it is not corrupted, verify image file to ensure that it has the ability to launch and also ensure that you don't accidentally wipe the hard drive of...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaInfo 25.07</title><pubDate> Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:52:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediainfo-1456.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediainfo-1456.html
</guid><description>
MediaInfo is a software that provides access to view the information of media files, such as technical information and tags of the video file and bad sound. Software displays detailed information including: format, profile, commercial name of the format, duration, bit rate overall, writing application and library, title, author, director, album, track number, updates.
MediaInfo - View file info media
The features and functions of MediaInfo
	Container: format, profile, commercial name...
</description></item></channel></rss>