<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 03:58:33 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 03:58:33 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Wondershare Recoverit 14.0.18.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 11 Feb 2026 21:07:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-recoverits-374.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-recoverits-374.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare Recoverit is a data recovery software that is easily lost at a rapid rate and is used by many people. You will do what happens if one day your data is suddenly lost due to the virus or deleted it, .. Wondershare Recoverit will provide you with an environment to protect important data.
Wondershare Recoverit has all the scanning processes that are divided into multiple types, from the typical recovery of the deleted files that are deleted to the recovery of missing files due...
</description></item><item><title>Download CalendarTask (formerly DesktopCal) 3.26.267.8501</title><pubDate> Wed, 11 Feb 2026 21:06:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopcal-1831.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopcal-1831.html
</guid><description>
CalendarTask (formerly DesktopCal) is a simple desktop calendar that blends into your desktop without blocking access to your desktop icons. You can double-click on a date to quickly add notes and also jump to specific dates in the past or future.
CalendarTask - Computer calendar
CalendarTask can use your current wallpaper or loop through images from your folder and update your desktop every few minutes. The program helps you make appointments, make plans... Not only that, the Screen...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Illustrator 2026 v30.2.1.1 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Wed, 11 Feb 2026 21:06:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-illustrator-0024-749.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-illustrator-0024-749.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Illustrator is a powerful vector graphics editor developed by Adobe Inc., first released in 1987. It is primarily used by graphic designers, illustrators, and artists to create high-quality illustrations, logos, icons, and digital artwork. Unlike raster graphics editors like Adobe Photoshop, which manipulate images pixel by pixel, Illustrator uses mathematical formulas to create vector graphics. This allows designs to be scaled infinitely without losing quality, making it ideal for...
</description></item><item><title>Download Perfectly Clear WorkBench 5.0.2.3093</title><pubDate> Wed, 11 Feb 2026 21:05:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfectly-clear-workbench-6892.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfectly-clear-workbench-6892.html
</guid><description>
Perfectly Clear Workbench is an application that uses image editing libraries Perfectly Clear by Athentech and is provided to demonstrate the capabilities of the Perfectly Clear processing libraries, which recognize faces and allow quick export of processing settings for use.
One of the key features in Workbench is the ability to "export to API" when saving a Preset. This allows you to make image edits in Workbench and adjust the settings to suit your editing style and needs. You can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Google Chrome 145.0.7632.46</title><pubDate> Wed, 11 Feb 2026 21:05:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-chrome-1012.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-chrome-1012.html
</guid><description>
Google Chrome web browser is the most used today. Support surf the web, listen to music, watch movies, play web game effective no jerky lag with the internet connection stable. When you are surfing the web or performing an important task, whether it is operation big or small, work or entertainment, then Chrome has the smart features and the speed you need to make, create and explore on the net.
The latest version of Google Chrome is the third 114. But we are providing for users Google...
</description></item><item><title>Download RawDigger 1.4.10.845</title><pubDate> Wed, 11 Feb 2026 21:04:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rawdigger-3593.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rawdigger-3593.html
</guid><description>
RawDigger is a tool to visualize and examine raw data true as the camera has recorded. In essence, it is a type of microscope allows you to delve into the raw data. RawDigger does not change the raw data in any way. RawDigger is not a transition rough. Instead, it allows you to see the data that will be used by convertors rough.
RawDigger - Check the raw data the camera recorded
The features of RawDigger
	RawDigger displays a chart of the raw data, differs greatly from the chart and...
</description></item><item><title>Download MEmu Android Emulator 9.3.2.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 11 Feb 2026 21:04:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-memu-2975.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-memu-2975.html
</guid><description>
MEmu or also known as Android Emulator is the Android emulator light and free, allowing Windows users to enjoy Android experience the original on the computer and device Microsoft their. This app provides outstanding performance, allowing you to play on PC a series of games designed to run on Android devices. This app allows you to play the game favorite Android on larger screens, to bring you a better gaming experience.
MEmu - Android emulator, lightweight and free
Software MEmu also...
</description></item><item><title>Download System Mechanic Pro 26.0.1.81 + Standard</title><pubDate> Wed, 11 Feb 2026 21:04:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-system-mechanic-434.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-system-mechanic-434.html
</guid><description>
System Mechanic Pro is tool cleanup and repair errors on the system and restore hard drive and operating speed window.  System Mechanic helps you to clean your entire computer system, delete the unnecessary files, detect and repair the incident occurred due to virus attack or due to mistakenly deleted system files.
System Mechanic offers many useful features such as Registry cleaning, defragmenting computer memory, protect your privacy while accessing the Internet. With programs this...
</description></item><item><title>Download System Mechanic Ultimate Defense 26.0.1.81</title><pubDate> Wed, 11 Feb 2026 21:03:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-system-mechanic-ultimate-defense-1974.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-system-mechanic-ultimate-defense-1974.html
</guid><description>
System Mechanic Ultimate Defense is software provides tracking features anti browser and protect your online privacy, management, encryption and secure password protection, anti-virus certified, VB100, detect and remove malware on demand, technology, erase hard drive military grade, award-winning optimize PC, software, file recovery advanced.
Malware threats is growing fast now because of almost a million new viruses, worms, trojan horses, rootkits and other types of spyware, and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Able2Extract Professional 21.0.4.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 11 Feb 2026 21:02:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-able2extract-professional-3133.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-able2extract-professional-3133.html
</guid><description>
Able2Extract Professional is a PDF conversion only on the market to help increase efficiency, productivity PDF of you on Windows. Convert PDF format to Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Publisher, AutoCAD and CSV. Get photo create perfect PDF with the optional enhanced security and quickly modify text and page PDF. Fill in, edit and create the PDF form can be filled right in the Able2Extract or insert the order number on long PDF documents. All the tasks are performed in a user interface smooth...
</description></item><item><title>Download FX Math Tools Manifest 26.02.11</title><pubDate> Wed, 11 Feb 2026 21:02:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fx-draw-tools-multidocs-8814.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fx-draw-tools-multidocs-8814.html
</guid><description>
MultiDocs is a new way to create self-modifying Word documents. MultiDocs' amazing new document reproduction features allow you to create reproducible tests and quizzes in minutes. Get new numbers, new diagrams and even brand new solutions! MultiDocs combines the power of Word with two leading products: FX Draw and FX Equation in a new and exciting way.
Features of FX Draw Tools MultiDocs
	Create multiple documents: The software allows users to create multiple math and evaluation...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cutting Optimization Pro 5.18.20</title><pubDate> Wed, 11 Feb 2026 21:01:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cutting-optimization-pro-6573.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cutting-optimization-pro-6573.html
</guid><description>
Cutting Optimization Pro is a cutting software used to obtain the optimal cut layout for one-dimensional (1D) and two-dimensional (2D) pieces. The software also allows you to define and process complex products, such as desks, tables, cabinets, cabinets, bookshelves... Cutting Optimization Pro can be used to cut rectangular panels made of glass, wood, metal, plastic or any other material used in industrial applications.
Features of Cutting Optimization Pro
	Optimize 1D and 2D in the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft Office Pro Plus - Online Installer 3.3.11</title><pubDate> Wed, 11 Feb 2026 21:01:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-office-professional-plus-online-installer-7661.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-office-professional-plus-online-installer-7661.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft Office 2021 Professional Plus x86-x64 - Online Installer is a small script that helps users to download and install Microsoft Office 2021 Professional Plus including all updates directly from Microsoft CDN Server.
The version of Office 2021 downloaded and installed on your computer will include the following programs: Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Outlook, OneNote, Publisher, Access, Visio, Project, ProofingTools, OneDrive Desktop.
Usage:
Unzip the downloaded ZIP Archive...
</description></item><item><title>Download VSave 3.0.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 11 Feb 2026 21:00:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vsave-14404.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vsave-14404.html
</guid><description>
VSave is a video saving and editing app that lets you download videos from cloud storage services, import videos from your camera or library, and convert or edit video formats and attributes. It's compatible with major platforms including YouTube, NicoNico, Apple Music, Spotify, TikTok, Twitter, and other video, audio, and social media websites. It supports downloading playlists, shows, channels, individual songs, and entire albums. Save content permanently in high quality without data...
</description></item><item><title>Download EdrawMax Portable 15.1.4.1481 Ultimate</title><pubDate> Wed, 11 Feb 2026 21:00:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-edraw-max-portable-4301.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-edraw-max-portable-4301.html
</guid><description>
Edraw Max Portable is software that diagrams all in one, helping simplify the creation of professional looking diagrams, organizational chart, network diagrams, business presentations, building plans, mind mapping, illustration, science, fashion designs, UML diagrams, workflows, program structure diagrams, web design diagrams, electrical engineering, map orientation, diagram database and much more.
Edraw Max Portable - mapping professional
With the large library is drawing available...
</description></item><item><title>Download SoftPerfect Switch Port Mapper 26.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 11 Feb 2026 20:59:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-softperfect-switch-port-mapper-976.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-softperfect-switch-port-mapper-976.html
</guid><description>
SoftPerfect Switch Port Mapper is a software that manages and reports network connection. Listed MAC address, IP address and host name of the computer is linked. In addition, software SoftPerfect Switch Port Mapper can display supplier network card of each customer, speed ports and timer the frame is defective and discarded for each port. This can be a good support when troubleshooting network connectivity.
SoftPerfect Switch Port Mapper - Manage and report network connection
The main...
</description></item><item><title>Download FX Science Tools Manifest 26.02.11</title><pubDate> Wed, 11 Feb 2026 20:58:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fx-science-tools-3744.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fx-science-tools-3744.html
</guid><description>
FX Science Tools provided to teachers of chemistry and physics the effective means to create equations and chemical structures. Just type and create. FX Chem FX Chem makes writing chemical equations become simple. You just type and FX Chem know enough about chemistry to put all the components of the equation at the right point. FX Chem can even create the chemical equations for nuclear - a very difficult thing in the Word. FX ChemSturation FX ChemSturation made the organic structure, what...
</description></item><item><title>Download Talking Translator - Languages 3.6.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 11 Feb 2026 20:58:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-talking-translator-9776.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-talking-translator-9776.html
</guid><description>
With the instant translation feature, the Talking Translator application will help you communicate in any multilingual environment such as when traveling, going on business trips, meeting buyers or just simple conversations. You can translate into more than 100 languages ​​with just this one app: Talking Translator! You don't know how to read sentences? Nothing! Talking Translator provides handwritten text translation.
Supports more than 100 languages ​​including English,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Calculator Plus 8.1.9</title><pubDate> Wed, 11 Feb 2026 20:57:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-calculator-plus-8135.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-calculator-plus-8135.html
</guid><description>
Calculator Plus is a perfect calculator program for Android that is easy to read and saves you time and effort. It can remember everything you calculate and let you review it at any time, making it perfect for shopping, doing homework, balancing a checkbook, or even helping with taxes. .
Plus Calculator Features
	Calculator Plus displays your calculations in clear, elegant, easy-to-read typeface, with commas in the right places
	You'll never forget where you are in the calculation - I...
</description></item><item><title>Download Peachy - AI Face &amp;amp; Body Editor 1.213.63</title><pubDate> Wed, 11 Feb 2026 20:57:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-peachy-ai-face-body-editor-13805.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-peachy-ai-face-body-editor-13805.html
</guid><description>
Peachy - AI Face &amp;amp; Body Editor is a powerful and user-friendly photo editing app that focuses on enhancing selfies and portraits through advanced body reshaping and editing features. The app helps users get the best look by smoothing skin, whitening teeth, removing blemishes and wrinkles, reshaping facial features and body parts, and applying makeup and lighting effects.
Key Features
	Photo Editing: Smooth skin, remove pimples and wrinkles, brighten eyes, whiten teeth, reduce dark...
</description></item><item><title>Download Video Converter: Compress Video 4.1.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 11 Feb 2026 20:57:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-video-converter-compress-video-13666.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-video-converter-compress-video-13666.html
</guid><description>
Explore the power of ConverterBlack, the ultimate Video Converter app designed to optimize your video files efficiently and easily. Enjoy the convenience of converting your videos while maintaining high quality output. This app is a multi-purpose tool that provides comprehensive functions such as video compression, format conversion, audio extraction, etc.
Features
	Convert Video to MP3: Turn your videos into stunning MP3 background music with MP4 to MP3 Converter today. Convert video...
</description></item><item><title>Download PhotoRoom AI Photo Editor 2026.07.02 build 2274</title><pubDate> Wed, 11 Feb 2026 20:56:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-photoroom-ai-photo-editor-10083.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-photoroom-ai-photo-editor-10083.html
</guid><description>
PhotoRoom is an all-in-one app for great visual content editing, design, and optimization that helps you run your business from your phone. Remove or erase photo backgrounds, use templates, and create your own content. The app will automatically crop objects and people in your photos. With just one tap, you can remove the background and create highlight content that showcases a product or a person. Edit images, add text or logo, stickers, create collages....
What you can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Weather Live Wallpapers 2.26.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 11 Feb 2026 20:56:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-weather-live-wallpapers-11506.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-weather-live-wallpapers-11506.html
</guid><description>
The movement of the sun, rainfall and phases of the moon are realistic animations on the screen with beautifully crafted details. The picturesque landscape reflects the weather with astonishing accuracy. Enjoy the sunrise, the rainbow, the birds singing and all the bright sunshine!
You can use real weather apps as wallpaper on your screen, they will reflect the current weather and you will always know the weather conditions. You can also launch the weather app in a window or install a...
</description></item><item><title>Download Speedtest by Ookla 1.14.198</title><pubDate> Wed, 11 Feb 2026 20:56:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-speedtest-by-ookla-3716.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-speedtest-by-ookla-3716.html
</guid><description>
Speedtest by Ookla is test tool Internet speed fast in real time. Use the Speedtest to check your connection easy, only one click in under 30 seconds - accurate anywhere thanks global network of us. Millions of people every day use the website Speedtest and mobile apps to check their internet speed. Now, the correct way and most convenient way to check the speed of your life on the Windows desktop. Get ping speed, download and upload your in seconds - real time graph showing the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Speedtest by Ookla 6.6.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 11 Feb 2026 20:55:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-speedtest-by-ookla-for-android-8605.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-speedtest-by-ookla-for-android-8605.html
</guid><description>
Speedtest by Ookla is a popular online service that allows users to measure the speed of their internet connection. The service works by sending small amounts of data to a user's device and measuring the time it takes for that data to return to the server. Based on this measurement, the service provides reports on the user's download and upload speeds as well as connection latency.
Features of Ookla Speedtest
	Explore your downloads, uploads, and pings
	The only Internet connection...
</description></item></channel></rss>