<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 09:23:53 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 09:23:53 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download iTop Easy Desktop 4.0.0.231</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 02:30:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-itop-easy-desktop-7879.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-itop-easy-desktop-7879.html
</guid><description>
iTop Easy Desktop is a lightweight and easy-to-use desktop manager that organizes desktop icons, files and folders according to your rules, helping you Freed from the tedious arrangement of icons on the screen. It provides various practical features including but not limited to grouping desktop items, awakening live search, and quickly accessing icons and files even across multiple desktop sites. desktop.
Untidy desktop If you're not one to diligently organize your Windows desktop icons...
</description></item><item><title>Download CalendarTask (formerly DesktopCal) 3.26.261.8274</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 02:29:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopcal-1831.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopcal-1831.html
</guid><description>
CalendarTask (formerly DesktopCal) is a simple desktop calendar that blends into your desktop without blocking access to your desktop icons. You can double-click on a date to quickly add notes and also jump to specific dates in the past or future.
CalendarTask - Computer calendar
CalendarTask can use your current wallpaper or loop through images from your folder and update your desktop every few minutes. The program helps you make appointments, make plans... Not only that, the Screen...
</description></item><item><title>Download MuseScore 4.6.5 + Portable</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 02:29:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musescore-2857.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musescore-2857.html
</guid><description>
MuseScore is the tool score for Windows, macOS and Linux, can compare with Finale and Sibelius, support multiple file formats and input methods. It is released as free software and open source under The GNU general public License.
MuseScore - The application composer
Features of MuseScore
	Design WYSIWYG, notes are entered on a "virtual notice"
	TrueType fonts for printing and display allows split ratio high quality for all sizes
	Enter notes easily and quickly
	Many editing...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare PDFelement Pro 12.1.2.3904</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 02:27:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-pdfelement-pro-105.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-pdfelement-pro-105.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare PDFelement Pro support users to convert PDF to office documents for easier use, modify in every situation. Is one of the software conversion material is rated best today, integrated with many features. We recommend that you should use experience software many useful features this.
Wondershare PDFelement Pro - conversion Fie PDF more features, multi-language
Wondershare PDFelement Pro what?
Convert PDF into Word, Excel, PowerPoint...
• Convert PDF and protected PDF into...
</description></item><item><title>Download XYplorer 28.10.0200</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 02:27:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-533.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-533.html
</guid><description>
XYplorer - File Manager for Windows is software that supports users to manage files on the Window quickly and to arrange the folder tidy. XYplorer features tabbed browsing, search, files, powerful, preview, flexible, highly customizable interface, dual frame options and a variety of unique ways to automate effective tasks often repeat. It's fast, lightweight, and portable.
Features XYplorer
	XYplorer is a file manager mobile. It does not require any settings, store all configuration...
</description></item><item><title>Download Edraw Max Ultimate 15.0.6.1445</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 02:27:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-edraw-max-1121.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-edraw-max-1121.html
</guid><description>
Edraw Max is software draw professional looking diagrams help simplify creating diagrams, organization charts, network diagrams, business presentations, building plans, mind mapping, illustration, science, fashion designs, UML diagrams , workflows, program structure diagrams, web design diagrams, electrical engineering, directional maps, diagrams, databases, and more.
Edraw Max - Draw professional looking diagrams
EdrawSoft Edraw Max use software mapping best suits what you know and...
</description></item><item><title>Download HashTools 4.8.3</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 02:26:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hashtools-3056.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hashtools-3056.html
</guid><description>
HashTools is a program to encode files, hash files with user interface intuitive, which can operate with different algorithms: CRC32, MD5, SHA1, SHA256, SHA384 and SHA512. Archive with HashTools has the mobile version of the program, very convenient and suitable in these days, it's enough to unzip an archive file and you can use right this utility. The interface looks clean and easy to navigate in it, you will not be distracted by any graphic element, which means you can immediately...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ashampoo Backup Pro 27.5.36</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 02:25:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-backup-pro-716.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-backup-pro-716.html
</guid><description>
Ashampoo Backup Pro is software to backup and restore data professional to save the file, the important data for your computer. Ashampoo Backup Pro will remove the fear of viruses, ransomware, or hardware errors. Ashampoo® Backup Pro offers you various options to backup individual files or entire disk partitions on any storage media or on the cloud. User friendly, intuitive, fast. Even in case an error occurs the entire system, application integrated emergency can bring your...
</description></item><item><title>Download GiliSoft Audio Recorder Pro 15.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 02:25:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-audio-recorder-pro-855.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-audio-recorder-pro-855.html
</guid><description>
GiliSoft Audio Recorder Pro is software perfect recorder to record audio and microphone of your computer to AAC, AC3, AIFF, AMR, AU, FLAC, M4A, M4B, M4R, MKA, MP2, MP3, OGG, RA, VOC , WAV Files or WMA files on Windows 7/8. Recording the sound that goes through your sound card is not at all a difficult task, but GiliSoft Audio Recorder Pro promises to make everything a lot easier, even for those who do not have computer knowledge advanced.
GiliSoft Audio Recorder Pro - audio recording...
</description></item><item><title>Download Fast Video Downloader 4.0.0.78</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 02:24:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fast-video-downloader-2619.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fast-video-downloader-2619.html
</guid><description>
Fast Video Downloader is a support program download quick video of genuine FastPcTools. ast Video Downloader is an easy to use program that allows you to download desired videos from a number of sites online storage. I think that I will not reveal secret if they write that most of the sites have video archives do not contain the ability to download videos and sometimes that's very necessary. This is when the same program is rescue, this allows you to save videos from the archive page as...
</description></item><item><title>Download Opera One 125.0.5729.49</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 02:24:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-972.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-972.html
</guid><description>
Opera is a fast, safe, configurable and compliant intranet web browser, which includes both the reader and the application. The Opera browser supports web browsing, listening to music, watching high speed movies, you can open many tabs on the Opera without affecting your browsing speed. Opera now supports almost all devices and operating systems such as windows, IOS, Android, linux, MacOS ...
Opera is a beautiful interface and many interesting features, operating on both PCs and mobile,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Gilisoft DRM Protection 9.3.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 02:18:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-video-drm-protection-5260.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-video-drm-protection-5260.html
</guid><description>
Gilisoft Video DRM Protection is software that helps you can protect your videos and the E-Learning content to another by secure, encrypted the files, your content and distribute them to the target audience authorized of you. Very easy to make video / sound / pictures of you can't see are for anyone except those you allow. Gilisoft Video DRM Protection can encrypt and pack video &amp;amp; codec &amp;amp; player into exe.
Gilisoft Video DRM Protection can easily encode almost any kind of Video...
</description></item><item><title>Download InfoTouch Professional 2.5.7.12195</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 02:17:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-infotouch-professional-5518.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-infotouch-professional-5518.html
</guid><description>
InfoTouch Professional is an innovative and reliable solution for public showcases and self-service kiosks. The software protects public computers against any kind of undesirable end-user actions, monitors kiosk, generates usage statistics, and enables easy and secure display of various types of information in public spaces such as libraries, schools, universities, museums, etc.
InfoTouch Features
	Display web pages in a secure Web browser
	Creates a personalized start page and...
</description></item><item><title>Download AddLEDs 1.3.0.7</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 02:09:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-addleds-3386.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-addleds-3386.html
</guid><description>
AddLEDs is an indicator systray offer the quick view for the scroll, number, caps lock, and more. This utility goes a bit further than a number of important indicators other; it also provides flashing lights for the network (there are five sensitivity levels can be set for network activity) and the activity of the disk, as well as the ability to engage / disconnect the coils / of / your hat through the mouse. Have the ability to engage and disconnect the keyboard input which can be useful...
</description></item><item><title>Download Window Inspector 3.8</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 02:09:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-window-inspector-2921.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-window-inspector-2921.html
</guid><description>
Window Inspector is a lightweight software application but the effect allows you to easily view the attributes and properties of an open window, such as text, window class and many other attributes. This program is very easy to use, allows you to access and view information just by your mouse cursor on the target window.
Window Inspector - Management application on windows
Window Inspector comes with a set of hot keys integrated will help you to freeze the information displayed, save...
</description></item><item><title>Download MEmu Android Emulator 9.3.1.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 01:19:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-memu-2975.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-memu-2975.html
</guid><description>
MEmu or also known as Android Emulator is the Android emulator light and free, allowing Windows users to enjoy Android experience the original on the computer and device Microsoft their. This app provides outstanding performance, allowing you to play on PC a series of games designed to run on Android devices. This app allows you to play the game favorite Android on larger screens, to bring you a better gaming experience.
MEmu - Android emulator, lightweight and free
Software MEmu also...
</description></item><item><title>Download LibreOffice 25.8.4 / 7.6.7</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 01:19:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-libreoffice-391.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-libreoffice-391.html
</guid><description>
LibreOffice is editor free for office similar to MS Office and OpenOffice includes word processor, spreadsheet application, presentation tool, database and design diagrams. Here is the app code open source, multi-feature, to offer users many tools to draft documents and handle the office documents efficiently.
The program can open or import most Microsoft Office formats popular, including .doc .ppt and .csv as well as many document formats other. LibreOffice is a tool to be more user...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinRAR 7.20 Beta 3 / 7.13 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Dec 2025 23:26:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winrar-127.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winrar-127.html
</guid><description>
WinRAR is a compression utility data advanced supports multiple formats including RAR, ZIP, CAB, ARJ, LZH, ACE, TAR, GZip, UUE, ISO, BZIP2, Z and 7-Zip. It allows you to create, organize and manage archives in a comfortable way and quickly. WinRAR naturally are is a leading software currently in the compression and decompression of data. With the enhanced algorithm is applied, the software allows users to compress bulk files in different formats into synthetic 1 single file to facilitate...
</description></item><item><title>Download MicroVision Suite 4.13</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Dec 2025 23:21:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microvision-suite-14380.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microvision-suite-14380.html
</guid><description>
Welcome to MicroVision Suite: Microscope Software, the ultimate microscope software designed for professionals, educators, and enthusiasts. This powerful solution transforms your computer into an advanced analysis station for USB microscope cameras. Whether you're conducting detailed research or exploring the microscopic world for the first time, MicroVision Suite provides a stable and feature-rich environment to help you get the most out of your hardware.
Key Features:
	Particle Size...
</description></item><item><title>Download Roberts Geospatial Engineering ProRaster Scientific 4.0.10</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Dec 2025 23:14:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-roberts-geospatial-engineering-proraster-scientific-14379.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-roberts-geospatial-engineering-proraster-scientific-14379.html
</guid><description>
ProRaster Scientific is the world's most advanced platform for exploring, understanding, and implementing findings in modern raster meshes, raster imagery, and multispectral raster images. ProRaster Scientific includes all the features of ProRaster Essential and ProRaster Premium and offers three additional key capabilities:
	Rendering, processing, and analyzing multispectral satellite imagery, powered by virtual raster technology.
	Raster processing operations powered by virtual raster...
</description></item><item><title>Download IObit Uninstaller Pro 15.2.0.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Dec 2025 23:01:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iobit-uninstaller-pro-339.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iobit-uninstaller-pro-339.html
</guid><description>
IObit Uninstaller Pro is software to delete programs not needed easily even when Windows "Remove Programs" operation not successful. IObit Uninstaller Pro will uninstall the app Windows, browser toolbars, software packages and plug-ins added. It comes with a scan function is powerful and a tool, Force Uninstall, both of which help to easily and completely remove the app stubborn, and the excess useless, to release more disk space.
With IObit Uninstaller Pro you will have peace of mind...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinToUSB Enterprise 10.4</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Dec 2025 23:00:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wintousb-enterprise-32.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wintousb-enterprise-32.html
</guid><description>
WinToUSB is the best software that allows you to install and run the Windows operating system on a USB hard drive or USB flash drive, using an ISO image or a CD/DVD drive as a setting source. With WinToUSB, you can copy the current Windows operating system settings (Windows 7 or more) to the USB drive as the WindowsToGo work space. WinToUSB also supports instalability USB WinPE drives, which can help you move WinPE's content to the USB drive and make the drive to boot.
Features of...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinToUSB Technician 10.4 + Professional</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Dec 2025 23:00:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wintousb-technician-2463.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wintousb-technician-2463.html
</guid><description>
WinToUSB Technician is a handy program that allows you to install Windows on a USB flash or hard drive and run Windows from that drive. The program is easy to use this provide the simple instructions to install the ISO image or CD / DVD into the drive of your USB. After installation, users can easily deploy Windows from the image on the USB drive.
WinToUSB lets you install and run Windows operating system on USB hard drive or USB flash drive, use ISO image or CD / DVD drive as the source...
</description></item><item><title>Download EaseUS Partition Master Technican Edition 19.23.0 Build 202512171740</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Dec 2025 22:59:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-partition-master-350.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-partition-master-350.html
</guid><description>
EaseUS Partition Master is software partition management all-in-one be used to redistribute capacity hard drive with high performance and keep all PC, laptop and server running perfect performance. Engineering software master partition deals with all the task partition in an effective way without loss of data. Just a few clicks to re-partition your hard drive, SSD, USB, flash drive, memory card, SD card, memory card and many other storage devices in Windows 10, 8.1, 8, 7, Vista, XP and...
</description></item><item><title>Download DaVinci Resolve Studio 20.3.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Dec 2025 22:58:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-davinci-resolve-studio-1072.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-davinci-resolve-studio-1072.html
</guid><description>
DaVinci Resolve Studio is professional video editing and color grading software developed by Blackmagic Design. This is an enhanced version of the free DaVinci Resolve software, providing additional features and capabilities for professional video editing, color correction, and post-production.
One of the outstanding features of DaVinci Resolve Studio is its powerful color correction capabilities. It provides a comprehensive set of tools and features for advanced color correction,...
</description></item></channel></rss>