<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 13:46:18 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 13:46:18 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download PDF Viewer Pro 2025.4.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 05 Nov 2025 16:42:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pdf-viewer-pro-9527.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pdf-viewer-pro-9527.html
</guid><description>
Whether you're working alone or collaborating with a team, PDF Viewer Pro maximizes productivity, allowing you to view, search, and annotate PDF documents easily on your phone or tablet. your Android tablet or Chromebook.
Features of PDF Viewer Pro
View documents on the go
	Easily open PDF files from your favorite cloud provider, email, or directly from the website you're browsing.
	Search for the exact text you are looking for in the document.
	Double-tap the screen to Smart Zoom...
</description></item><item><title>Download All world Language Translator 1.36</title><pubDate> Wed, 05 Nov 2025 16:42:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-all-world-language-translator-11009.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-all-world-language-translator-11009.html
</guid><description>
Translate faster and support 132 spoken and listened languages worldwide. Easily learn and speak any other language and support the education system.
Supports translation of the following languages: Afrikaans , Spanish (Español) , Arabic (العربية), Turkish (Türkçe) , Bengali (বাংলা), Bulgarian (Български), Bosnian (Bosanski), Cantonese (粵語繁體中文), Catalan (Català), Simplified Chinese (简体中文), Traditional Chinese (繁體中文), Croatian...
</description></item><item><title>Download Chat AI - AI Chatbot Assistant v217.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 05 Nov 2025 16:42:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-chat-ai-ai-chatbot-assistant-11260.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-chat-ai-ai-chatbot-assistant-11260.html
</guid><description>
AI Chatbot is a smart artificial intelligence interactive application that brings a unique and convenient experience to users. With AI Chatbot, you can communicate and ask questions directly with a powerful AI system that helps you find information, answer questions, and even provide solutions to complex problems.
Main features of Chatbot AI include
	Natural conversation: Chatbot AI uses advanced natural language technology to understand and respond to your questions and requests...
</description></item><item><title>Download TickTick:To Do List &amp;amp; Calendar 7.7.1.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 05 Nov 2025 16:41:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ticktick-to-do-list-tasks-8702.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ticktick-to-do-list-tasks-8702.html
</guid><description>
TickTick is a simple and effective task management and to-do list application that helps you schedule, manage time, remind about deadlines and organize your life at work, at home. home and everywhere else. TickTick is here to help you make the most of your day and get things done (gtd). Whether there's an idea you want to capture, a personal goal to achieve, a job to complete, or collaborating with other colleagues, even create a shopping list (with the help of a list creator). book)....
</description></item><item><title>Download BikeComputer Pro 9.2.4</title><pubDate> Wed, 05 Nov 2025 16:41:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-bikecomputer-pro-8146.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-bikecomputer-pro-8146.html
</guid><description>
BikeComputer Pro is a mobile application that allows users to track their cycling and other outdoor activities using GPS. The app is available to download from the Google Play Store and Apple App Store. It is designed for cycling enthusiasts and offers many features to help users track and improve their performance. Some features of the application include:
	Track distance, speed and route with GPS
	Altitude tracking
	Audible signals for distance and speed
	Personalized training...
</description></item><item><title>Download Drivvo - car management 8.7.4</title><pubDate> Wed, 05 Nov 2025 16:41:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-drivvo-car-management-8614.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-drivvo-car-management-8614.html
</guid><description>
Drivvo is a car management app that helps users track and manage expenses related to their vehicles. It provides a platform to record and analyze fuel consumption, maintenance costs and other expenses, making it easier to budget and manage car-related expenses.
Save Money: Manage fuel consumption and economic costs, car maintenance costs and service costs of your car, motorcycle, bus or truck.
Control Finances: Track average KM/liter, monthly costs, average per day, fuel,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Moviebase: Movies &amp;amp; TV Guide 5.4.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 05 Nov 2025 16:40:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-moviebase-track-tv-shows-8175.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-moviebase-track-tv-shows-8175.html
</guid><description>
Are you looking for a useful movie finder and movie tracker app to help you find movie ratings, movie reviews, movie recommendations, movie trailers and more? Try Moviebase – Movie Manager. Moviebase is the most popular movie finder and movie tracker app where you can find movies, series, seasons, episodes. Movie reviews, movie trailers, movie descriptions and actors from the largest community database TMDB.
Explore the world of movies and series from Movie Tracker
	Explore a huge...
</description></item><item><title>Download Battery HD Pro 1.99.42</title><pubDate> Wed, 05 Nov 2025 16:40:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-battery-hd-pro-8140.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-battery-hd-pro-8140.html
</guid><description>
Battery HD Pro is the perfect battery monitor for your phone or tablet. It's simple, beautiful, and can be specially calibrated for your device. Battery HD Pro is an application designed to help users monitor their device's battery usage and optimize device performance. Some features of this application include:
	Monitor battery usage: The app shows the remaining battery percentage and the estimated time remaining until the battery is depleted.
	Charging History: The app tracks the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Barquode: Barcode &amp;amp; QR Scanner 8.1.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 05 Nov 2025 16:40:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-barquode-matrix-manager-8858.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-barquode-matrix-manager-8858.html
</guid><description>
Barcode is a tool to create, capture and manage many types of matrix codes including Barcodes and QR codes. It is highly customizable with a dynamic theme engine to match your style. Try exploring its other features.
Barcode features
Matrix code
	Codabar
	Code 39
	Code 128
	EAN-8
	EAN-13
	ITF
	UPC-A
	Aztec
	Data matrix
	PDF417
	QR Code
Data format
	URL
	Wi-Fi
	Location
	Email
	Phone
	Message
	Contact
	Event
Get code
	Integrated scanner
	Image
	Device camera
Code...
</description></item><item><title>Download Audiomack: Music Downloader 7.7.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 05 Nov 2025 16:40:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-audiomack-music-downloader-11192.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-audiomack-music-downloader-11192.html
</guid><description>
Stream and download the best new trending music (full tracks offline data-free) and listen to your local MP3s!&amp;nbsp;Browse music from the best artists in top categories like Hip-Hop, Rap, R&amp;amp;B, EDM, Afropop, and Reggae on the Audiomack music app. Download songs and listen offline, without using your data, or listen to your personal MP3 collection! Audiomack provides download access and unlimited streaming to the newest and hottest tracks, right at your fingertips. Our music download...
</description></item><item><title>Download SnapTube for Android 7.49.0.74950410</title><pubDate> Wed, 05 Nov 2025 16:39:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-snaptube-youtube-downloader-hd-video-8351.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-snaptube-youtube-downloader-hd-video-8351.html
</guid><description>
SnapTube is a mobile application that allows users to download videos from various platforms, such as YouTube, Vimeo, and Dailymotion. It provides video resolution in multiple formats 144p, 720p, 1080p HD, 2K HD, 4K HD and audio formats MP3 and M4A. With Snaptube, users can search for content across all their platforms without using multiple apps.
Features of SnapTube for Android
Download in multiple resolutions
	MP4 videos are available in resolutions: choose small 360 pixels or...
</description></item><item><title>Download WiFi Pro FTP Server 2.2.8</title><pubDate> Wed, 05 Nov 2025 16:39:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wifi-pro-ftp-server-8831.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wifi-pro-ftp-server-8831.html
</guid><description>
Convert your Android phone/tablet into an FTP Server! Use this cool app to host your own FTP Server on your phone/tablet. Use FTP Server to transfer files, photos, movies, songs, etc. to/from your Android device using an FTP client like FileZilla.
Features of WiFi Pro FTP Server Pro
	Full-fledged FTP server with configurable port numbers
	Supports FTP over TLS/SSL (FTPS)
	Configurable anonymous access
	Configurable home directory (mount point)
	Configurable username/password
	Avoid...
</description></item><item><title>Download ISS Detector Pro 2.05.43</title><pubDate> Wed, 05 Nov 2025 16:39:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-iss-detector-pro-8393.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-iss-detector-pro-8393.html
</guid><description>
You can actually see it in the night sky. View Starlink satellite ships with Famous Objects (available in the Filter menu). If you like space or astronomy, you will love this ISS tracking app. ISS Detector Pro includes the functionality of ISS Detector (free) with all Extensions and no ads.
ISS Detector Pro will tell you when and where to look for the International Space Station or Iridium flares. You get a warning a few minutes before passing. You'll never miss a pass by the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Podcast Republic - Podcast app 25.10.22R</title><pubDate> Wed, 05 Nov 2025 16:38:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-podcast-republic-podcast-app-8131.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-podcast-republic-podcast-app-8131.html
</guid><description>
Podcast Republic is a podcast app that allows users to discover, download and listen to podcasts on their mobile devices. Podcast Republic is a top quality Podcast App on Android with 4+ million downloads, 76k+ authentic reviews, 600k+ podcasts, and 40+ million episodes worldwide. It offers features like automatic downloading, variable playback speed, and the ability to create and manage playlists. Podcast Republic also supports Android Auto and Chromecast, so you can listen to podcasts...
</description></item><item><title>Download WiFi Direct + 10.0.22</title><pubDate> Wed, 05 Nov 2025 16:38:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wifi-direct-10153.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wifi-direct-10153.html
</guid><description>
Wi-Fi Direct is a Wi-Fi standard for peer-to-peer wireless connections that allows two devices to establish a direct Wi-Fi connection without the need for an intermediate wireless access point, router, or Internet connection.
Features of WiFi Direct +
	Fast
	Completely free, no intrusive ads.
	Supports all file transfers.
	Supports multiple file transfers.
	Supports folder transfer.
	Supports file transfer to and from external sdcard.
	Tested on many devices.
	Advanced file chooser.
</description></item><item><title>Download Fast Photo Gallery Pro: F-Stop 5.5.484 build 484</title><pubDate> Wed, 05 Nov 2025 16:38:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-f-stop-gallery-8357.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-f-stop-gallery-8357.html
</guid><description>
Replace your bulky storage library with a light, fast (even fun) library that helps you organize all the photos and videos on your device. F-Stop is an alternative image library that gives you professional tools and a clean Material Design interface that makes organizing your photos a breeze.
F Stop Library Features
	Fully optimized for Android 7.0+ including material design
	Instantly search through all your photos to find results based on filename and metadata (tags, ratings, camera...
</description></item><item><title>Download System Monitor Cpu Ram Battery 11.10.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 05 Nov 2025 16:37:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-system-monitor-cpu-ram-booster-8783.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-system-monitor-cpu-ram-booster-8783.html
</guid><description>
System Monitor CPU RAM Booster is the most powerful System Monitor for Android, Including: CPU Monitor, Storage Cleaner, Memory Booster, Battery Doctor, Battery Saver. Developed by Andro IX, The App Provides Detailed Information About The Device's CPU, RAM, Storage, Battery, and Network Usage, Allowing Users To Identify and Troubleshoot Performance Issues.
System Monitor Proved many Kinds of Powerful Tools, Including: RAM Booster and Cleaner, Overheating Alarm, Overheating Protection,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Stick - Remote Control For TV 3.14</title><pubDate> Wed, 05 Nov 2025 16:37:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-stick-remote-control-for-tv-12980.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-stick-remote-control-for-tv-12980.html
</guid><description>
Stick is a TV remote control app that turns your phone into a TV remote control! Now you have a universal TV remote that you can connect to TV models like Samsung TV remote, LG TV remote, Sony TV remote, Vizio TV remote, TCL TV remote, Insignia TV remote, Hisense TV remote, Roku TV remote, etc.
Some notable features
	Perfect for LG TV remote, TCL TV remote, Android TV remote and Samsung TV remote: Easily change channels, adjust volume and use menus on LG remote and Samsung TV...
</description></item><item><title>Download Lock Me Out - App/Site Blocker 7.2.5</title><pubDate> Wed, 05 Nov 2025 16:36:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-lock-me-out-appsite-blocker-11314.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-lock-me-out-appsite-blocker-11314.html
</guid><description>
Lock Me Out is a powerful app blocker that locks you out of selected apps when you want to do other things. There are three application blocking modes. The first mode blocks selected applications and allows the remaining applications. The second mode allows selected apps and blocks the rest. The third and strictest mode only allows the use of the lock screen. You can still answer calls or call emergency numbers in this mode.
Usage-based locking: Usage-based locking has rules that...
</description></item><item><title>Download Weather &amp;amp; Radar - Morecast 4.1.44</title><pubDate> Wed, 05 Nov 2025 16:36:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-weather-radar-morecast-8801.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-weather-radar-morecast-8801.html
</guid><description>
Morecast - Weather Forecast with Radar &amp;amp; Widget is your personal weather companion, helping you prepare for upcoming Blizzards, Rain, Heat and other severe weather conditions.
Features of Weather &amp;amp; Radar - Morecast
Determine the weather
	Accurate weather is available with street-level accuracy for your current location or favorite locations anywhere in the United States, Canada, and Mexico. Morecast is powered by global weather forecast data from more than 28,000 weather...
</description></item><item><title>Download IgeBlock - Tube ad blocker 2.0.8 Build 315</title><pubDate> Wed, 05 Nov 2025 16:36:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-igeblock-tube-ad-blocker-11113.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-igeblock-tube-ad-blocker-11113.html
</guid><description>
IgeBlock is an app that allows you to watch videos without ads, watch videos with sound, and watch videos in pop-up player while using other apps.
IgeBlock Features
Block ads
	Automatically skip annoying video ads.
	Automatically skip ads even in sound and pop-up player mode.
Pop-up player (PIP)
	You can play videos in floating mode without additional permissions.
Can be added
	Full screen touch lock function
	looped video
	Bookmark function without logging in
	Timer to turn...
</description></item><item><title>Download DAVx⁵ – CalDAV CardDAV WebDAV 4.5.5-gplay</title><pubDate> Wed, 05 Nov 2025 16:35:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-davx-caldav-carddav-webdav-8633.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-davx-caldav-carddav-webdav-8633.html
</guid><description>
DAVx is the only all-in-one app for everything CalDAV, CardDAV and WebDAV! This is a full-featured synchronization solution for your contacts (CardDAV), calendar (CalDAV), and tasks (based on VTODO). The app is easy to install and integrates seamlessly with your favorite calendar/contacts apps (including default apps). It can also be used separately if you have CalDAV, CardDAV or just Tasks. DAVx can also be used to access your remote WebDAV files.
Features of DAVx for Android
	Sync...
</description></item><item><title>Download FlashLight HD LED Pro 2.10.25</title><pubDate> Wed, 05 Nov 2025 16:35:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-flashlight-hd-led-pro-8446.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-flashlight-hd-led-pro-8446.html
</guid><description>
FlashLight HD LED Pro is a flashlight app for Android devices that provides strong and bright light using the device's camera flash. This app is compatible with most phones, including those where other apps don't work. This includes for example: Sony Xperia, Samsung Galaxy S8, S7 Edge, S6, J7, Xiaomi Redmi Note, Oppo, Huawei, LG, Lenovo,Vivo, HTC, Alcatel, ZTE, Asus ZenFone, Motorola Moto G4, E2. .. and much more.
Features of FlashLight HD LED Pro
	The brightest and strongest light...
</description></item><item><title>Download 3D Modeling App: Sculpt &amp;amp; Draw 1.20.7</title><pubDate> Wed, 05 Nov 2025 16:35:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-3d-modeling-app-sculpt-draw-9081.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-3d-modeling-app-sculpt-draw-9081.html
</guid><description>
3D modeling app allows you to easily create 3D models, objects, art and cgi graphics, paintings, create 3D characters and design 3D games on the go using gestures on your mobile phone or tablet. This is a powerful 3D modeling application, suitable for both beginners and advanced users. With an intuitive interface and powerful feature set, it's a great tool for creating 3D models, animations, and more.
Features of 3D modeling app: Sculpture &amp;amp; Drawing
	Sculpture: Sculpt &amp;amp; Draw...
</description></item><item><title>Download Running Tracker App – FITAPP 8.9.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 05 Nov 2025 16:34:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-fitapp-track-my-run-running-8392.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-fitapp-track-my-run-running-8392.html
</guid><description>
FITAPP Track My Run &amp;amp; Running is a fitness tracking mobile application that allows users to track and analyze their running activities. It often includes features like GPS tracking, allowing users to track their route, distance, speed, and time. It also includes many tools for analyzing performance, such as graphs and charts that display data such as heart rate, calories burned, and elevation.
FITAPP will also help you lose weight, count calories, maintain your target weight or...
</description></item></channel></rss>