<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 17:35:02 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 17:35:02 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Balabolka 2.15.0.904</title><pubDate> Fri, 29 Aug 2025 17:02:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-balaboka-142.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-balaboka-142.html
</guid><description>
Balabolka is a text-to-speech (TTS) program. It can read text on your screen in a human-like voice. You can use Balabolka to listen to text from a variety of file formats, convert text to spoken audio files, and adjust speech parameters such as speed and pitch. It is often used for accessibility purposes, helping people who have difficulty reading or multi-tasking by listening to text while doing other activities. Balabolka supports multiple languages and uses different TTS engines,...
</description></item><item><title>Download pdfFactory Pro 9.16</title><pubDate> Fri, 29 Aug 2025 17:02:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdffactory-pro-277.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdffactory-pro-277.html
</guid><description>
pdfFactory Pro is software to create PDF files according to standards in a simple and secure documents secure. pdfFactory Pro on taiwebs.com that support encryption (40 or 128bit) and control access to the PDF file.
pdfFactory Pro has all the features of pdfFactory and adds bookmarks, job order, title a letter and the email function automatically. Only pdfFactory allows printing to paper or PDF without printing twice. Acrobat is not needed for the printing. Increases the convenience of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Office Installer Plus 1.29</title><pubDate> Fri, 29 Aug 2025 17:01:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-installer-plus-11616.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-installer-plus-11616.html
</guid><description>
Office Installer Plus is the next version of Ratiborus that helps you download, install, update, uninstall, activate office 2024, 2021, 2019, 2016 and it has added an Office activator to the program. submit. Office Installer+ is considered a useful application that helps users install and manage office applications from Microsoft Office easily and quickly. This application is designed to help users save time and effort when installing popular office applications such as Word, Excel,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Perfectly Clear WorkBench 4.8.0.2846</title><pubDate> Fri, 29 Aug 2025 17:01:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfectly-clear-workbench-6892.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfectly-clear-workbench-6892.html
</guid><description>
Perfectly Clear Workbench is an application that uses image editing libraries Perfectly Clear by Athentech and is provided to demonstrate the capabilities of the Perfectly Clear processing libraries, which recognize faces and allow quick export of processing settings for use.
One of the key features in Workbench is the ability to "export to API" when saving a Preset. This allows you to make image edits in Workbench and adjust the settings to suit your editing style and needs. You can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Android Studio 2025.1.2.13</title><pubDate> Fri, 29 Aug 2025 17:00:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-android-studio-3890.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-android-studio-3890.html
</guid><description>
Android Studio is an Android development environment, completely new, provides many improvements and new features compared to Eclipse ADT. This software solution will is IDE the official Android when is finishing. This tool provides many tools and features such as editing, layout, rich set of tools to capture usability, compatibility version, performance and other issues, create a lot APK, build system based on Gradle flexibility, extended support for Google Services, integrated support...
</description></item><item><title>Download StartAllBack 3.9.14.5302</title><pubDate> Fri, 29 Aug 2025 17:00:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-startallback-6857.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-startallback-6857.html
</guid><description>
With the official release of Windows 11, chances are that most of you want to try it out. As the name suggests, StartAllBack is a small, lightweight tool that can help you enjoy the power of the new operating system while keeping the look and feel, especially because main work area, desktop of Windows 7, Windows 10 as taskbars and start menu styles.
StartAllBack is specially designed for Windows 11 and will not work on any older operating systems. If you want to get the start menu back...
</description></item><item><title>Download Office Installer by Ratiborus 1.29</title><pubDate> Fri, 29 Aug 2025 16:59:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-installer-11545.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-installer-11545.html
</guid><description>
Office Installer is a software program by Ratiborus used to install Microsoft Office on computers or devices. Office is a productivity suite that includes programs like Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Outlook, and more. The installer ensures that all required Microsoft Office files and components are installed, properly configured, and ready for use on the user's computer.
Office Installer allows users to choose which Office applications they want to install, select the installation location,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wireshark 4.4.9</title><pubDate> Fri, 29 Aug 2025 16:59:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wireshark-56.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wireshark-56.html
</guid><description>
Wireshark (aka Ethereal) is a network protocol analyzer allows you to capture and examine data from a live network or from a snapshot file on disk.You can browse the captured data in an interactive way and view summary information and details for each package. Wireshark has several powerful features, including a language filter rich display and ability to view flow created back of the TCP.
Wireshark - network protocol analyzer
The program can read the capture file from tcpdump...
</description></item><item><title>Download FinePrint 12.16</title><pubDate> Fri, 29 Aug 2025 16:58:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fineprint-276.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fineprint-276.html
</guid><description>
FinePrint is a software support you work in text saves paper and increases the lifespan of your printer. FinePrint is a software connected printer, you can print 4 or 8 pages file on the computer on a page of paper that still ensure the font is clear, easy to read.
With FinePrint works for you, the incidents of printing annoyances will disappear. Below are just some examples of incidents in which FinePrint can fix. Read more part of our Business for the benefit of the FinePrint in the...
</description></item><item><title>Download 3D Youtube Downloader 1.22.12</title><pubDate> Fri, 29 Aug 2025 16:58:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-3d-youtube-downloader-1631.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-3d-youtube-downloader-1631.html
</guid><description>
3D Youtube Downloader is application support users to download the videos from Youtube website with great quality. The advantage of this software is the ability to download the videos in 3D, make the download process is fully automated and the download speed is extremely fast. In addition to Youtube, this tool also allows to download videos from many other sites, so users can own any favorite videos yet. 3D Youtube Downloader is a downloads simple but powerful from Youtube, Vimeo,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Plex Media Server 1.42.1.10060</title><pubDate> Fri, 29 Aug 2025 16:57:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-plexp-media-server-47.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-plexp-media-server-47.html
</guid><description>
Plex Media Server allows you to stream movies, music and photos from PC to Roku devices, Google TV or DLNA compatible (for example PS3, Xbox 360). You can also stream online media his to another computer or mobile device (Android, iOS ...) with the help of the client application available.
Film and television program you are presented with the origin-themed, cover art, overview the plot and cast, cross-link, as well as the technical details.
Content update Plex Media Server...
</description></item><item><title>Download Avast Ransomware Decryption Tools 1.0.0.781</title><pubDate> Fri, 29 Aug 2025 16:56:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avast-ransomware-decryption-tools-5371.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avast-ransomware-decryption-tools-5371.html
</guid><description>
Avast Ransomware Decryption Tools is a package of ransomware decryption tools to help you get back files from 20 different ransomware encrypted. Avast Ransomware Decryption Tools supports decryption AES_NI, Alcatraz Locker, Apocalypse, BadBlock, Bart, BTCWare, Crypt888, CryptoMix (Offline), CrySiS, EncrypTile, FindZip, Globe HiddenTear, Jigsaw, Legion NoobCrypt, Stampado, SZFLocker, TeslaCrypt, XData.
Features of Avast Ransomware Decryption Tools
	Easily remove ransomware
	Decrypt and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cycling 74 Max 9.0.8</title><pubDate> Fri, 29 Aug 2025 16:56:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cycling-74-max-2543.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cycling-74-max-2543.html
</guid><description>
Cycling 74 Max has released version 8 of Max and company called it "the closest thing to a mind-expanding drug Max has ever had". Programming language visual has launched a series of new improvements in the latest iteration, most notably the introduction of the new MC. object.
Cycling Max make the patch with 100-channel sound look as simple as these can have a channel. The big development in version 8 have focused on performance. Now, Cycling 74 Max announce that will run 20 times faster...
</description></item><item><title>Download Futuremark SystemInfo 5.88.1377</title><pubDate> Fri, 29 Aug 2025 16:55:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-futuremark-systeminfo-2568.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-futuremark-systeminfo-2568.html
</guid><description>
Futuremark SystemInfo is a small program created to conduct diagnostic analysis complete all kinds of processes, as well as equipment used on a personal computer of you. According to the author, you can use this tool as a component reference in the application be supported, it will determine the version of your operating system and other information about the hardware.
Note that Windows XP, 3DMark06, and PCMark05 are no longer be Futuremark support. Function SystemInfo on Windows XP is...
</description></item><item><title>Download WIA-Loader 2.9.6.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 29 Aug 2025 16:51:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wia-loader-6128.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wia-loader-6128.html
</guid><description>
WIA-Loader is a camera program from a camera or a memory card to a computer, and it can change the name of a serial, upload them to the FTP server to create an HTML album, and can add a GPS card to your photo. There are many functions available to name images and folders and edit images. WIA-Loader maps part of the photographer's work process: from camera to computer.
Features of WIA-Loader
	Video streaming and video to the computer quickly and easily
	Create the order in the image...
</description></item><item><title>Download Directory Opus Pro 13.18.1 Beta</title><pubDate> Fri, 29 Aug 2025 16:50:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-opus-pro-779.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-opus-pro-779.html
</guid><description>
Directory Opus Pro is a software replacement for Explorer with traditional strength and function more than any manager other files. Directory Opus Pro full support for high DPI screen (for example 4K and 5K) with the rename dialog is redesigned, with new features. Besides being a recording macro only allows you to perform mass renaming complex that don't need regular expressions. In addition, Directory Opus Pro also enhances the ability to script.Better handling of renaming recursive and...
</description></item><item><title>Download RedNotebook 2.41</title><pubDate> Fri, 29 Aug 2025 16:50:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rednotebook-2884.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rednotebook-2884.html
</guid><description>
RedNotebook is a note-taking app for free. It allows you to format, tag and search your entries. You can also add images, links and templates can customize, check the spelling of your notes and export into plain text, HTML or LaTeX. RedNotebook is free software under the GPL.
RedNotebook - Write notes, edit text
Features of RedNotebook
	Use #hashtags
	Format your text bold , italic or underline
	Insert images, files and links to the website
	Links and email addresses are recognized...
</description></item><item><title>Download myViewBoard Whiteboard 2.74.7</title><pubDate> Fri, 29 Aug 2025 16:49:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-myviewboard-whiteboard-13930.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-myviewboard-whiteboard-13930.html
</guid><description>
myViewBoard Whiteboard is digital whiteboard software developed by ViewSonic, designed for interactive displays and whiteboards, widely used in education and collaboration. The software provides a secure, easy-to-use platform for annotating and creating multimedia content, supporting multiple users at once on unlimited page space.
Key features include:
	Compatibility: Works on any interactive whiteboard or flat panel display, including ViewSonic ViewBoard, Promethean Board, Smart...
</description></item><item><title>Download Black Menu for Google 26.2.0 + Firefox</title><pubDate> Fri, 29 Aug 2025 16:49:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-black-menu-for-google-3231.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-black-menu-for-google-3231.html
</guid><description>
Black Menu for Google (Firefox) gives you fast access to Google services with your favorite drop-down menu conveniently allows you to use Search, Google+ and many other services without leaving the page you are visiting. Click on the menu item to get a preview small window or click the open button to the right to open them in a new tab.
Customize the menu by just entering ‘Add to, and drag / click on the service you want from the list of comprehensive services. To delete a service, drag...
</description></item><item><title>Download Phoenix Customizer 1.1.10.0 Beta</title><pubDate> Fri, 29 Aug 2025 16:44:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-phoenix-customizer-12580.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-phoenix-customizer-12580.html
</guid><description>
Phoenix Customizer provides you with various settings that allow you to customize your Windows 11 or Windows 10 system. You can easily customize Windows folders with various colors and effects, add a custom taskbar that you can change to your liking, have a floating widget with access to shortcuts, and favorites or modify the Windows context menu.
Main features
	Customize Windows folders: Customize your Windows folder icons easily. It's simple, select the Windows folder for which you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Zero Install 2.27.8</title><pubDate> Fri, 29 Aug 2025 16:42:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zero-install-1632.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zero-install-1632.html
</guid><description>
Zero Install is a system, install the software distribution cross africa focus. Other features include full support for shared libraries (with the SAT for resolution dependent), share between users, and integration with the package manager original foundation. Zero Install supports both binary packages and source and works on Linux systems , OS X , Unix and Windows. It is completely open source.
Zero Install - System software installation
Zero Install also has a number of interesting...
</description></item><item><title>Download Syncovery Premium 11.7.6.91</title><pubDate> Fri, 29 Aug 2025 16:41:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncovery-pro-enterprise-232.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncovery-pro-enterprise-232.html
</guid><description>
Syncovery Pro Enterprise is a great application used to back up data and to synchronize personal computers, servers, laptops, notepads and storage online. The software comes with support for FTP and secure FTP servers, SSH, WebDAV, Amazon S3, http, update the part file, ZIP compression, data encryption, and schedule automatic backups.
Syncovery Pro Enterprise have the ability to freely select files and folders across the whole folder hierarchy in tree view and supports email...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cent Browser 5.2.1168.83</title><pubDate> Fri, 29 Aug 2025 16:41:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cent-browser-3301.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cent-browser-3301.html
</guid><description>
Cents Browser is the improved version of web browser Chrome popular integrate countless features, including download the lazy, the tab bar can scroll, optimize memory automatically, mouse gestures and more options the other tab. Application small and efficient, this will significantly improve the browsing experience of your website and make it safer and more comfortable.
Cent Browser - web browser improvements new
This web browser based on the code and tools of Google Chrome and offers...
</description></item><item><title>Download wsltty 3.8.0.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 29 Aug 2025 16:40:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wsltty-3237.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wsltty-3237.html
</guid><description>
wsltty use Mintty do the terminal for WSL (System con Windows for Linux).
wsltty
The composition wsltty:
	The component package wsltty (see below) in the application folder of the users% LOCALAPPDATA%
	a folder configuration wsltty in the application folder in user's% APPDATA% (the configuration file is allocated according to the type of housing from one version to be installed before it will be move to default position new)
	Start Menu shortcuts to start the terminal WSL
	* .bat...
</description></item><item><title>Download NovoNotes 3DX 1.10.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 29 Aug 2025 16:40:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-novonotes-3dx-9037.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-novonotes-3dx-9037.html
</guid><description>
3DX realizes the highest sound quality and enables real-world sound field representation. By integrating functions essential for 3D audio production such as 3D scanning, binaural, and ambient sound into a single plug-in, it provides a complex production workflow.
NovoNotes 3DX uses HPL audio technology (a professional binaural transducer technology researched and developed in Japan) to produce highly appreciated audio quality, featured in the production of high-quality high-resolution...
</description></item></channel></rss>