<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 01:51:21 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 01:51:21 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Privacy Eraser Pro 6.27.0.5500</title><pubDate> Sun, 01 Mar 2026 02:41:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-privacy-eraser-1141.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-privacy-eraser-1141.html
</guid><description>
Privacy Eraser is the cleanup for computer help to clear the tracks, junk files and traces of recent activity of the computer. Privacy Eraser support the popular web browsers like Internet Explorer, Mozilla Firefox, Google Chrome, Safari and Opera. The program can quickly erase the browser cache, cookies, browsing history, website history, website URL entered, form data, auto complete, file index.dat, file swapping, temporary directory and the position in other common.
Privacy Eraser -...
</description></item><item><title>Download Perfectly Clear WorkBench 5.0.3.3125</title><pubDate> Sun, 01 Mar 2026 02:40:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfectly-clear-workbench-6892.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfectly-clear-workbench-6892.html
</guid><description>
Perfectly Clear Workbench is an application that uses image editing libraries Perfectly Clear by Athentech and is provided to demonstrate the capabilities of the Perfectly Clear processing libraries, which recognize faces and allow quick export of processing settings for use.
One of the key features in Workbench is the ability to "export to API" when saving a Preset. This allows you to make image edits in Workbench and adjust the settings to suit your editing style and needs. You can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Privacy Eraser Free 6.27.0.5500</title><pubDate> Sun, 01 Mar 2026 02:40:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-privacy-eraser-free-9160.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-privacy-eraser-free-9160.html
</guid><description>
Privacy Eraser is a software tool that helps protect user privacy by securely erasing or deleting unwanted data from their computer or device. This tool is designed to delete browsing history, cookies, cache, temporary files and other sensitive information that may be stored on the computer.
Privacy Eraser can be used to clear browsing history of popular web browsers such as Google Chrome, Mozilla Firefox and Microsoft Edge. It can also clear the history and cache of other applications,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Topaz Photo Pro 1.3.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 01 Mar 2026 02:39:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-photo-ai-8105.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-photo-ai-8105.html
</guid><description>
What is Topaz Photo AI?
Topaz Photo AI is a professional software that automatically adjusts for your image quality needs. Simply import images into Topaz Photo AI and it will use specially trained AI models to first detect unique details, clarity, and resolution issues before applying the intelligently adjusts to maximize your image quality.
For users experienced with Topaz Labs image quality applications, it combines the functionality of DeNoise AI, Sharpen AI and Gigapixel AI into...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ant Download Manager Pro 2.16.7 Build 92593</title><pubDate> Sun, 01 Mar 2026 02:39:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ant-download-manager-pro-137.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ant-download-manager-pro-137.html
</guid><description>
Ant Download Manager Pro is software support download has the same features as IDM, even it has many prominent features, more user friendly more and have speed download data incredible. Ant Download Manager is a Internet content downloader quickly with support download at video! Function: fully Integrated with the web browsers most popular: Internet Explorer 8+, Mozilla Firefox 32 +, Google Chrome 31+ and the copies of them (Pale Moon, Opera, Vivaldi, Slimjet, ComodoDragon, etc.). you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Advanced Installer Architect 23.5.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 01 Mar 2026 02:38:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-installer-128.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-installer-128.html
</guid><description>
Advanced Installer is a Windows utility designed to help you build the package Windows Installer in a working environment clean and intuitive.
Although it has many parameters dedicated but the user interface is very simple and gives users the ability to create new projects by selecting the type, namely installer (for example: application Visual Studio or .NET, pack 32/64-bit mixture), Java , updates, support, mobile devices, and other things.
Advanced Installer - An environment for...
</description></item><item><title>Download PassFab 4EasyPartition 3.10.1.11</title><pubDate> Sun, 01 Mar 2026 02:37:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-passfab-4easypartition-7983.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-passfab-4easypartition-7983.html
</guid><description>
After using your PC for many years, there are bound to be many files you want to transfer to your new PC. PassFab 4EasyPartition can perform a one-click migration saving you hours of reinstalling operating systems and applications. It has an intuitive interface and step-by-step wizard that makes migrating the system in just a few steps. PassFab 4EasyPartition will effectively solve the problem of low disk space, speed up your computer and make it run faster.
Features of PassFab...
</description></item><item><title>Download Telestream Wirecast Pro 16.5.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 01 Mar 2026 02:36:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-telestream-wirecast-pro-739.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-telestream-wirecast-pro-739.html
</guid><description>
Telestream Wirecast Pro is software to broadcast live video, turn your computer into a tv studio directly. Live streaming with just your webcam or connect multiple cameras, scoreboard, graphics, and guests from far away. Wirecast makes it easy to stream great-looking live and pre-recorded video to Facebook Live, YouTube, Twitter, Periscope and many more.
Telestream Wirecast Pro - live broadcast
Wirecast is used everywhere to transmit online your program to OTT and the social platform....
</description></item><item><title>Download Fast Video Cutter Joiner 7.0.3</title><pubDate> Sun, 01 Mar 2026 02:35:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fast-video-cutter-joiner-7542.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fast-video-cutter-joiner-7542.html
</guid><description>
Fast Video Cutter Joiner is a fast video cutter and joiner with an easy to use interface. It allows users to trim parts of a video quickly while maintaining the quality of the original video. It supports various formats like AVI, MPEG, MP4, WMV, 3GP, FLV...
This tool helps you to cut video files into small parts, to keep only the parts you need and remove unwanted parts like trailers and advertisements in a movie. The clips you cut can then be used for other video productions or for a...
</description></item><item><title>Download Helium Music Manager Premium 18.0.697</title><pubDate> Sun, 01 Mar 2026 02:35:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-helium-music-manager-premium-164.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-helium-music-manager-premium-164.html
</guid><description>
Helium Music Manager is a music manager that can rip, tag, play, browse, search, rename, burn and synchronize your music with the mobile. You can control your music collection with Helium Music Manager. Stop using time looking for the file on your computer or looking through CDS, vinyl records and tapes - instead, simply enjoy and explore your music! Helium Music Manager can replace the ripper, the player, tag editor and related software to audio your other.
Helium Music Manager...
</description></item><item><title>Download 4DDiG Partition Manager 3.10.1.11</title><pubDate> Sun, 01 Mar 2026 02:34:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4ddig-partition-manager-2024-9781.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4ddig-partition-manager-2024-9781.html
</guid><description>
4DDiG Partition Manager is a powerful Windows disk partition software expert in system migration, disk cloning and disk partition management. It can effectively clone your entire disk or partition, providing a reliable solution for data backup.
This is Windows 10 fast system and data transfer solution &amp;amp; 11. 4DDiG Partition Manager can move the system and large files or folders from one disk partition to a larger one with just one click. Or you can use it to move the system and large...
</description></item><item><title>Download Black NotePad 2.3.2.31</title><pubDate> Sun, 01 Mar 2026 02:33:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-black-notepad-1154.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-black-notepad-1154.html
</guid><description>
Black NotePad is software write notes replacement for traditional NotePad with many different color schemes. Black NotePad provides a table of white color on a black background by default and allows you to quickly switch between 5 different color schemes from the toolbar.
Black NotePad - Write notes NotePad
In addition to foreground color and background color, you can also switch between the font type just by the click of a button. The color scheme and font options can be user...
</description></item><item><title>Download MusConv 4.10.454 Lifetime</title><pubDate> Sun, 01 Mar 2026 02:32:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html
</guid><description>
MusConv transfers playlists, albums, followed artists and liked songs across a variety of services – Spotify, Apple Music, Amazon Music, YouTube, YouTube Music, iTunes, Deezer, Tidal, SoundCloud, Pandora and more 125 music services!
Features of MusConv Ultimate
	Transfer playlists, albums, followed artists and liked tracks between over 125 music servicesManage playlists (Delete, Merge, Split, Copy...)
	More than 125 music services supported
	Access DAILY updated music charts on...
</description></item><item><title>Download DISMTools 0.7.3</title><pubDate> Sun, 01 Mar 2026 02:32:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dismtools-12200.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dismtools-12200.html
</guid><description>
Inspired by Visual Studio, DISMTools is a user interface for DISM that allows you to manage Windows Imaging (WIM) files and much more. You can use it to uninstall apps, add driver or tool packages, etc.
DISM: This is a tool used to maintain and repair Windows images. This includes Windows Recovery Environment, Windows Setup, and Windows PE (WinPE). You can also use DISM to repair Windows images locally on your computer.
DISMTools: This is a user-friendly interface that allows you to...
</description></item><item><title>Download HFS: HTTP File Server (version 3) 3.0.5</title><pubDate> Sun, 01 Mar 2026 02:31:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hfs-http-file-server-11851.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hfs-http-file-server-11851.html
</guid><description>
HFS is a web file server to run on your computer. Share a folder or even a file thanks to the virtual file system. Essentially, this application turns your computer into an HTTP server and all users who want to connect and download files can do so by loading a simple website in their browser. HFS includes many configuration settings, so you can basically change each part of the application, starting with how users download files and ending with the appearance of the created website.
HFS...
</description></item><item><title>Download Duplicate File Finder Professional 2026 v412</title><pubDate> Sun, 01 Mar 2026 02:30:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-duplicate-file-finder-professional-4425.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-duplicate-file-finder-professional-4425.html
</guid><description>
Duplicate File Finder Professional is a compact application helps you quickly find and remove files duplicate on the computer. With Duplicate File Finder Professional you can choose any folder on the hard drive or use the folder standard user and our app will analyze the deep content of the selected folder to copy. It will take only a few seconds. The files will be compared by the hash algorithm MD5, which means they will be compared by content, not by name. Then, use our convenient...
</description></item><item><title>Download Secret Disk Pro 2026 v319</title><pubDate> Sun, 01 Mar 2026 02:29:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secret-disk-pro-933.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secret-disk-pro-933.html
</guid><description>
Secret Disk Pro 4 is a software to create a virtual disk can be hidden and password protected to keep your data private and safe. You can store any file and folder on the disk. Disc secret works like a hard disk typically, and is compatible with any any other program that you have installed. You can have more than one disk secret, and you can also choose disk letter.
Secret Disk Pro 4 - Create and secure drive
Secret Disk does not encrypt any files, it just limits access to your files...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter 3.9.18 (2802)</title><pubDate> Sun, 01 Mar 2026 02:28:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-to-mp3-converter-1744.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-to-mp3-converter-1744.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter is the software support download youtube video and convert video to mp3 format fast and most simple. MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter allows you download and convert videos from YouTube and other websites to MP3 format by pasting the YouTube URL into the application. When you paste the URL, the program will display thumbnails for videos and you have the option to customize the title information, artist and album before you begin the process of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Pazu StreamGet All-In-One Video Downloader 2.9.3</title><pubDate> Sun, 01 Mar 2026 02:27:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pazu-streamget-all-in-one-video-downloader-12037.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pazu-streamget-all-in-one-video-downloader-12037.html
</guid><description>
StreamGet All-In-One Video Downloader is the ultimate downloading solution for you. It supports downloading any movies and shows from the most popular streaming sites including Netflix, Prime Video, Disney Plus, Max, Hulu, and Apple TV Plus. The downloader is continuously updated to support more platforms in the future.
Download movies and shows from various streaming platforms to MP4/MKV on your Windows device and enjoy them anywhere you want.
Features of Pazu StreamGet All-In-One...
</description></item><item><title>Download VovSoft Web Platform Identifier 1.6</title><pubDate> Sun, 01 Mar 2026 02:26:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-web-platform-identifier-10234.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-web-platform-identifier-10234.html
</guid><description>
Discover the power of seamless web platform identification with VovSoft Web Platform Identifier, a simple software designed to easily scan and reveal the underlying web platform of any entered URL. Whether you are a web developer, designer, or simply curious about the technologies that power your favorite websites, this tool is the right solution for quick and accurate platform identification. body.
This easy-to-use utility uses advanced algorithms to quickly analyze the structure of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Rainbow Analyst add-in Professional 26.02.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 01 Mar 2026 02:26:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rainbow-analyst-add-in-professional-11122.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rainbow-analyst-add-in-professional-11122.html
</guid><description>
Rainbow Analyst add-in Professional is a powerful tool designed to enhance data analysis in Microsoft Excel. This add-on provides many advanced features and visualizations to help users gain valuable insights from their data.
One of the key features of Rainbow Analyst is the ability to create color-coded reports and charts. Users can assign specific colors to different data values, making it easier to identify patterns, trends, and outliers. This visual representation of data enhances...
</description></item><item><title>Download Vovsoft Link Analyzer 2.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 01 Mar 2026 02:11:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-link-analyzer-5400.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-link-analyzer-5400.html
</guid><description>
Vovsoft Link Analyzer is an easy-to-use hyperlink checker that can efficiently crawl both small and very large websites, while also allowing you to find broken, broken links. analysis results in real time, crawl on-site, differentiate internal and external links, check dofollow and nofollow links, analyze META description and various tags.
Vovsoft Link Analyzer Features
	Simple and easy to use
	Free
	Distinguishes between internal and external links
	Analyze description and meta...
</description></item><item><title>Download Imagine 2.5.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 28 Feb 2026 23:49:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-imagine-7369.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-imagine-7369.html
</guid><description>
Imagine is an application that allows you to view images and animations in a variety of formats, including JPG, BMP, PNG and GIF. With Imagine you can view file properties and EXIF ​​information, copy, move, delete and rename images. Additionally, you can also flip, resize and rotate them, swap colors, set transparency levels, import, export, and edit palettes, and change color depth.
Features of Imagine
	View and save image/animation files at lightning speed
	Multiple...
</description></item><item><title>Download Active Data Studio 26.0.0.4</title><pubDate> Sat, 28 Feb 2026 23:47:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-active-data-studio-306.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-active-data-studio-306.html
</guid><description>
Active Data Studio is software to backup and restore discs, restore documents and deleted photos, delete disks securely, monitor HDD status and can repair PC when Windows can't start normally. Active@ Data Studio is a set of both apps to the desktop with a CD / DVD boot or USB disk to boot any system into the Windows Recovery Environment.
Features Active Data Studio
Active Data Studio perform data recovery
	Active@ File Recovery - recover files and folders deleted, even when deleted,...
</description></item><item><title>Download VideoMeld 1.82</title><pubDate> Sat, 28 Feb 2026 23:47:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-videomeld-5549.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-videomeld-5549.html
</guid><description>
VideoMeld is a brand new multi-path digital audio and video editing program. VideoMeld has one of the most advanced effects editors in its class. Multiple effects can be applied at the same time, creating astonishing variety. Effect settings can be precisely changed over time for detailed animations.
Key features include:
	High quality HD video up to 1920x1080 and save as MPEG 4 H. 264
	High quality 8-channel audio (7.1 surround sound)
	More than 50 video effects, transition effects...
</description></item></channel></rss>