<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 05:52:16 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 05:52:16 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download 7-Zip 26.00</title><pubDate> Fri, 13 Feb 2026 02:21:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-7-zip-446.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-7-zip-446.html
</guid><description>
7Zip is a file storage and open source, provide high compression rate, the most used format f new 7z, bringing compression results are better than 30-50% compared with the ZIP standard. We have tested it with a log file, server is compressed with ZIP had a file size of 18 mb and using 7-Zip was reduced to 8 mb (results may vary, depending on the file type).
In addition, 7Zip also supports the formats 7z, ZIP, CAB, RAR, ARJ, GZIP, BZIP2, TAR, CPIO, RPM and DEB, so it can also be used...
</description></item><item><title>Download CalendarTask (formerly DesktopCal) 3.26.268.8507</title><pubDate> Fri, 13 Feb 2026 02:20:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopcal-1831.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopcal-1831.html
</guid><description>
CalendarTask (formerly DesktopCal) is a simple desktop calendar that blends into your desktop without blocking access to your desktop icons. You can double-click on a date to quickly add notes and also jump to specific dates in the past or future.
CalendarTask - Computer calendar
CalendarTask can use your current wallpaper or loop through images from your folder and update your desktop every few minutes. The program helps you make appointments, make plans... Not only that, the Screen...
</description></item><item><title>Download Apowersoft Video Download Capture 6.6.3.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 13 Feb 2026 02:15:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-apowersoft-video-download-capture-1556.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-apowersoft-video-download-capture-1556.html
</guid><description>
Apowersoft Video Download Capture is a comprehensive tool with advanced technologies for media streaming to choice cost-effective to download videos from YouTube, Dailymotion, Vimeo, Yahoo Screen and Hulu, as well as millions of other websites. Apowersoft Video Download Capture is your download video powerful and effective this can download and save videos, movies, tv episodes and music videos online. It also has the switch function, supports convert any video to MP4, AVI, MKV, WMV and the...
</description></item><item><title>Download XYplorer 28.20.0200</title><pubDate> Fri, 13 Feb 2026 02:14:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-533.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-533.html
</guid><description>
XYplorer - File Manager for Windows is software that supports users to manage files on the Window quickly and to arrange the folder tidy. XYplorer features tabbed browsing, search, files, powerful, preview, flexible, highly customizable interface, dual frame options and a variety of unique ways to automate effective tasks often repeat. It's fast, lightweight, and portable.
Features XYplorer
	XYplorer is a file manager mobile. It does not require any settings, store all configuration...
</description></item><item><title>Download DaVinci Resolve Studio 20.3.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 13 Feb 2026 02:13:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-davinci-resolve-studio-1072.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-davinci-resolve-studio-1072.html
</guid><description>
DaVinci Resolve Studio is professional video editing and color grading software developed by Blackmagic Design. This is an enhanced version of the free DaVinci Resolve software, providing additional features and capabilities for professional video editing, color correction, and post-production.
One of the outstanding features of DaVinci Resolve Studio is its powerful color correction capabilities. It provides a comprehensive set of tools and features for advanced color correction,...
</description></item><item><title>Download XYplorer (32 Bit) 27.20.1000</title><pubDate> Fri, 13 Feb 2026 02:13:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-portable-12066.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-portable-12066.html
</guid><description>
XYplorer Portable is a file management software application that provides a comprehensive set of features for organizing and managing files and folders on your computer. This is a portable version of XYplorer that you can run directly from a portable storage device, such as a USB drive, without installation.
XYplorer Portable Features
	File Management: XYplorer Portable provides a two-window interface, allowing you to view and work with two folders at the same time. It provides easy...
</description></item><item><title>Download Steinberg VST Live Pro 3.0.20</title><pubDate> Fri, 13 Feb 2026 02:12:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-steinberg-vst-live-pro-7557.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-steinberg-vst-live-pro-7557.html
</guid><description>
Steinberg VST Live Pro is a unique, stable software solution designed for musicians who want to deliver a great performance, including sound, light and video, wherever they are. VST Live comes with a wide range of virtual instruments, sync features for music, text and chord symbols showing on other devices, video, Cubase import, MIDI tracks for lighting control Live DMX and more.
Features of Steinberg VST Live Pro
The core of your live production.
Has all the functionality needed to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Geekbench AI Corporate 1.7.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 13 Feb 2026 02:12:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-geekbench-ai-corporate-12385.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-geekbench-ai-corporate-12385.html
</guid><description>
Geekbench AI is a cross-platform AI benchmark that uses real-world machine learning tasks to evaluate the performance of AI workloads. Geekbench AI measures your CPU, GPU, and NPU to determine whether your device is ready for today's and tomorrow's advanced machine learning applications.
Evaluating real-world AI performance:
Real-world AI performance
	Geekbench AI runs ten AI workloads, each with three different types of data, giving you a multidimensional picture of on-device AI...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube Downloader 3.9.18 (1202)</title><pubDate> Fri, 13 Feb 2026 02:12:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube Downloader  is a dedicated software that helps users  downloading youtube videos  Favorites on PC for offline viewing. With MediaHuman YouTube  Downloader  you can download videos from youtube website to your computer with  fast speed , with special software development technology that automatically receives videos from Websites, in addition to the ability to download videos from software websites, can convert downloaded video formats to various formats for the purpose...
</description></item><item><title>Download Blackmagic Design Fusion Studio 20.3.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 13 Feb 2026 02:11:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blackmagic-design-fusion-studio-2750.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blackmagic-design-fusion-studio-2750.html
</guid><description>
Blackmagic Design Fusion Studio is the world's most advanced compositing software for visual effects artists, broadcast and motion graphics designers, and 3D animators. For the past 30 years, Fusion has been used on thousands of Hollywood blockbuster films and television shows. Fusion features a powerful node-based interface that lets you quickly and easily create sophisticated effects by connecting different types of image processing tools together! You get a wide range of tools,...
</description></item><item><title>Download DroidKit 2.3.7.20260212</title><pubDate> Fri, 13 Feb 2026 02:10:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-droidkit-6578.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-droidkit-6578.html
</guid><description>
DroidKit is data recovery software for your mobile device, it will quickly scan your phone memory and save photos, WhatsApp chats and files, messages Messages, contacts and more essential data up to 13 categories, covering almost everything you need every day. All Android phones and tablets are supported. Without rooting your device. No tech skills required. No need to wait many days. You can get back what you've lost with just a few simple clicks, instantly.
Besides, DroidKit also has...
</description></item><item><title>Download Axialis IconVectors Pro 1.30</title><pubDate> Fri, 13 Feb 2026 02:10:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-axialis-iconvectors-pro-14187.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-axialis-iconvectors-pro-14187.html
</guid><description>
Axialis IconVectors is a lightweight and fast SVG icon editor built specifically for developers, providing precise control and quick editing of vector icons. It easily integrates into existing development workflows with real-time code preview (SVG, ReactTS, VueTS, XAML, C++), compatible with Visual Studio, VS Code and Adobe Illustrator. Its developer-focused features remove unnecessary complexity, making vector icon creation efficient and simple.
Features of Axialis IconVectors...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter 3.9.18 (1202)</title><pubDate> Fri, 13 Feb 2026 02:01:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-to-mp3-converter-1744.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-to-mp3-converter-1744.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter is the software support download youtube video and convert video to mp3 format fast and most simple. MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter allows you download and convert videos from YouTube and other websites to MP3 format by pasting the YouTube URL into the application. When you paste the URL, the program will display thumbnails for videos and you have the option to customize the title information, artist and album before you begin the process of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Disk Savvy Ultimate 17.8.16 + Enterprise + Pro</title><pubDate> Fri, 13 Feb 2026 02:00:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-disk-savvy-ultimate-1290.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-disk-savvy-ultimate-1290.html
</guid><description>
Disk Savvy Ultimate is the analysis disk space visualization and powerful reporting, comprehensive operation management file and export options. This is the Disk Savvy Ultimate get bottle service for free on taiwebs.com software is the analyze disk space usage has the ability to analyze disks, network shares, NAS devices and storage systems business. Users are provided with more ability to analyze disk usage and classification of files, allows one to have is the ability to display more in...
</description></item><item><title>Download QuadSpinner Gaea 2.2.9</title><pubDate> Fri, 13 Feb 2026 02:00:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quadspinner-gaea-3870.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quadspinner-gaea-3870.html
</guid><description>
QuadSpinner Gaea is design software terrain, sophisticated and modern for results the top in moments. The top tools of QuadSpinner Gaea makes realism became the basis. Workflows are streamlined, allowing you to easily gain visibility and work in parallel with your team. Interface is extremely modern and our multitude of gadgets stimulate creativity, not limit it. Working at Gaea very interesting and can help you set a performance standard new.
QuadSpinner Gaea - design software...
</description></item><item><title>Download PC Repair Suite 2.0.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 12 Feb 2026 23:06:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pc-repair-suite-14567.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pc-repair-suite-14567.html
</guid><description>
Whether you're experiencing issues like corrupted system files, failed Windows updates, or network problems, this modern utility lets you control and resolve the issue quickly. No complicated installation required. Doesn't run in the background. PC Repair Suite is optimized for speed, uses minimal resources, and is easy to use.
It provides guided access to built-in Windows diagnostic and configuration tools, allowing users to check system integrity, troubleshoot network issues, and manage...
</description></item><item><title>Download Dont Sleep 9.99</title><pubDate> Thu, 12 Feb 2026 19:49:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dont-sleep-89.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dont-sleep-89.html
</guid><description>
Don't Sleep allows you can set the date and custom time that you want to reactivate the feature manager usual sources or you can set a countdown fast to pause the power management in X hours.
Can temporarily disable the protection of your screen or off your computer at a certain time.
The main features of the Dont Sleep:
- Optimal power supply for computer
- Installation time power source according to
- Prevent computer reboot
Content update Dont Sleep 5.66:
The official website...
</description></item><item><title>Download Fender Studio Pro (PreSonus Studio One Pro) 8 v8.0.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 12 Feb 2026 19:46:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-presonus-studio-one-pro-780.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-presonus-studio-one-pro-780.html
</guid><description>
PreSonus Studio One Pro is software production music professional perfect combination between the studio model with the production process according to the beat and loop today so you can bring music ideas to actual sounds. Screen interface, simple, effective contains the number of tracks is not limited to , the editing tools are intuitive and the tools advanced virtual. Spend precious time to create music instead of wondering what to click next. Studio One does not dictate how you work or...
</description></item><item><title>Download Room Arranger 10.3.6.748</title><pubDate> Thu, 12 Feb 2026 19:46:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-room-arranger-3779.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-room-arranger-3779.html
</guid><description>
Room Arranger is a 3D application lets you easily plan for the room, office or his apartment just a few mouse clicks. The application comes with a simple interface will significantly simplify your work. You can draw many kinds of objects and items to create furniture of your own. This app also includes a library of object rich.
Software Room Arranger enables you to view your project in 3D form. You can also upload the 3D scene interact on your blog or your website. The application uses...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Downloader 10.2.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 12 Feb 2026 19:46:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html
</guid><description>
YTD Youtube Downloader is an application that reliable and intuitive, allowing you to quickly download YouTube videos and save them to your computer. You can also convert the media files to the format desired video or extract audio streams and save separately. YTD Youtube Downloader lets you save your favorite clips of yourself from Youtube, Facebook, Vimeo and Dailymotion to your desktop. The software supports URLS from many web site hosting, multimedia and allows you to download desired...
</description></item><item><title>Download Active@ Disk Editor 26.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 12 Feb 2026 16:49:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-active-disk-editor-4606.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-active-disk-editor-4606.html
</guid><description>
Active Disk Editor is the editing tool, disk usage viewer, disk low-level, simple, displays information in the binary mode and text at the same time. You can use this view to analyze the content of the structural components data storage, such as: hard Drives, floppy Drives, partitions, other objects.
The app allows you to quickly navigate to almost all areas, although the whole code is displayed. This can be done through the drop-down menu where you can select the boot sector of NTFS /...
</description></item><item><title>Download Photo Reducer 6.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 12 Feb 2026 16:47:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photo-reducer-10218.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photo-reducer-10218.html
</guid><description>
Photo Reducer is free software that supports image size reduction in various formats by choosing from countless presets or defining values yourself, then sending via email or save locally. In terms of optimization, the app comes with a lot of preset configurations. These are found in a drop-down menu, with options for ideal print size, digital frames, screens for HD TVs and 4K TVs, ideal sizes for the web, as well as customization options. The second choice allows you to adjust quality...
</description></item><item><title>Download Office Tool Plus 11.0.27.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 12 Feb 2026 16:45:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-tool-plus-3664.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-tool-plus-3664.html
</guid><description>
Office Tool Plus based on the Office deployment tool from Microsoft. You can customize configuration files installation and install Office of to install Office without Internet. Configure install Office, as well as customize the product C2R have installed, such as add and remove components, language packs, etc.
Office Tool Plus - Download and install Office
The characteristics of Office Tool Plus
	1. Configure install Office, as well as customize the product C2R have installed, such...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft Office 2024 Professional Plus LTSC v2408 Build 17932.20670 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Thu, 12 Feb 2026 16:40:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-office-2024-professional-plus-64-bit-10679.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-office-2024-professional-plus-64-bit-10679.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft has officially announced the final version of the Office 2024 release for Windows and Mac users. After releasing a preview version in the first half of this year, the product has been finalized and is now available to users. Office 2024 includes updated versions of apps from the Word 2024, Excel 2024, PowerPoint 2024, Outlook 2024, Access 2024, and Publisher 2024 suites.
Office 2024 includes virtually every change that has been added to the suite of programs in Office 365 over...
</description></item><item><title>Download 4K Video Downloader Plus 26.0.3</title><pubDate> Thu, 12 Feb 2026 16:39:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-video-downloader-617.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-video-downloader-617.html
</guid><description>
4K Video Downloader Plus is software support downloads video, audio and subtitles from YouTube with high quality up to 4K. Download process video is very simple: just copy the video link from your browser and click Paste Url. Done! If you want that video on your iPad, iPhone or other device, we have protected you.
The feature on 4K Video Downloader Plus
	Download entire playlists and channels from YouTube and save them in MP4, MKV, M4A, MP3, FLV, 3G, create a file .m3u for...
</description></item></channel></rss>