<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 17:38:12 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 17:38:12 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download IObit Uninstaller Pro Portable 15.0.0.4</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 20:08:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iobit-uninstaller-pro-portable-4487.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iobit-uninstaller-pro-portable-4487.html
</guid><description>
IObit Uninstaller Pro Portable is the portable version has activation available version Pro helps you to uninstall program and remove unwanted software installed on your computer very easily. Even if you have trouble uninstalling and cannot uninstall them from the applet control panel, Programs and features (Add or Remove Programs). IObit Uninstaller Pro Portable is an option faster and more efficient for option Add or Remove Programs in the Windows control Panel. The program is packed...
</description></item><item><title>Download AlfaOBD 2.5.7</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 20:07:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-alfaobd-5977.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-alfaobd-5977.html
</guid><description>
AlfaOBD is a diagnostic software for vehicles produced by the Fiat Chrysler Automobiles Corporation (FCA). Fiat/Alfa Romeo/Lancia car support produced in 1994-2017 and Chrysler/Dodge/Ram/Jeep life 2005-2017. Although this software is primarily targeted for car owners, it offers many of the features of the professional scanner.
AlfaOBD naturally supports the Electronic Controller (ECU) installed on the vehicles of the FCA group. Other original support with AlfaOBD many other diagnostic...
</description></item><item><title>Download Glary Utilities Pro Portable 6.30.0.34</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 20:06:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-utilities-pro-portable-3500.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-utilities-pro-portable-3500.html
</guid><description>
Glary Utilities Pro Portable is a program that provides you with the necessary options to clean and maintain your PC system. The software's interface consists of a small window, simple to use. Newbies shouldn't have any problems getting around the program. So you can scan for problems revolving around incorrect registry entries, dangerous startup entries, invalid shortcuts, Internet history and traces, temporary files, spyware and adware.
Glary Utilities Pro Portable - Optimize and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Winxvideo AI 4.3.0.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 20:06:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winxvideo-ai-10981.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winxvideo-ai-10981.html
</guid><description>
Winxvideo AI is an innovative video editing app that leverages the power of artificial intelligence to provide users with advanced video editing capabilities. With advanced features and a user-friendly interface, Winxvideo AI is designed to streamline the video editing process and empower creators to create professional-quality videos.
Winxvideo AI meets all your audio/video conversion needs and compresses your 4K/8K footage from GB to MB without compromising on quality, powered by...
</description></item><item><title>Download 4K Video Downloader Plus Portable 25.3.0.219</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 20:05:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-video-downloader-plus-portable-12527.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-video-downloader-plus-portable-12527.html
</guid><description>
4K Video Downloader Plus Portable is a cross-platform application that allows you to save high-quality videos from YouTube and other websites in seconds. This app works faster than any free online video downloader — just one click and you can enjoy content anytime, anywhere.
Save private clips and playlists that you have access to. Download private videos not only from YouTube but also from Facebook, Vimeo, Bilibili and many other sites. Access and download login-protected media...
</description></item><item><title>Download EF Commander 25.20</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 20:05:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ef-commander-92.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ef-commander-92.html
</guid><description>
EF Commander is an application specialized software can help you to manage your files effectively can help you full control over the files and folders, suitable for both beginners to experts with interface according to the card format Tab. The application supports ID3 tags, enhanced sound quality and use less resources with the format OGG/ Vorbis, FLAC, WMA and WAV and other formats can be heard on Winamp,...
EF Commander - a file manager effectively 
With EF Commander : When starting...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare Repairit Portable 6.5.13.6</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 20:04:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-repairit-portable-12168.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-repairit-portable-12168.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare Repairit Portable (unofficial portable version) makes it possible to completely restore videos, photos, files, audio, emails, etc. your lost from hard drive, broken computer, NAS &amp;amp; Linux system. It will also repair damaged videos, photos, and other files for you!
Wondershare Repairit uses advanced algorithms to analyze damaged video files and repair them. It can fix a range of issues, including playback lag, freezing, pixelation, missing audio, and more. The software...
</description></item><item><title>Download Allround Automations PL-SQL Developer 16.0.7.2172</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 20:04:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allround-automations-plsql-developer-4730.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allround-automations-plsql-developer-4730.html
</guid><description>
Allround Automations PL/SQL Developer is a development environment integration is specifically targeted at the development application units are stored for the Oracle database. Over time, we have seen the business logic more and move towards the Oracle server, make PL / SQL programming become an important part of the development process overall. This software focuses on ease of use, coding quality and the main advantage in the process of software development, Oracle.
The features of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Desktop Info 3.20.4</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 20:03:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktop-info-11667.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktop-info-11667.html
</guid><description>
Desktop Info is a free application for Windows that allows users to display system information and important parameters directly on their desktop. This application provides a convenient way to monitor parameters such as CPU, memory, hard drive, network, and many other information that users want to monitor continuously.
With a simple and easy-to-use interface, Desktop Info allows users to customize the information displayed according to their wishes. Users can select...
</description></item><item><title>Download 4K YouTube to MP3 Portable 25.3.0.219</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 20:03:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-youtube-to-mp3-portable-12526.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-youtube-to-mp3-portable-12526.html
</guid><description>
4K YouTube to MP3 Portable is a portable, installation-free version specifically created to extract audio from YouTube, Vimeo or Facebook and save it as MP3, M4A, OGG. No need to deal with annoying and complicated settings, just a clean, friendly and functional interface. Downloading is simple and straightforward: just copy the link from your browser and click 'Paste Url'. Done!
No toolbars, no adware, no malware. And best of all it's a FREE YouTube to MP3 converter! Enjoy your audio...
</description></item><item><title>Download SmartCapture 3.22.4</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 20:02:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-smartcapture-1019.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-smartcapture-1019.html
</guid><description>
SmartCapture a product of DeskSoft. This is a screen capture tool for professional window captures entire desktop and holding bowl moments on the computer screen. User interface clear and intuitive, with powerful features make it the ideal utility for everyone who wants to capture any contents of the desktop Windows. It can capture the rectangular area screen, whole objects, windows or screens and it can retrieve images from the imaging device.
SmartCapture - screenshot
The captured...
</description></item><item><title>Download Network Monitor II 31.9</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 20:02:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-network-monitor-ii-3628.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-network-monitor-ii-3628.html
</guid><description>
Network Monitor II is a lightweight utility that lets you quickly view important information about your network connection. The program allows you to view information about IP addresses, network traffic and much more. No extra tools or libraries needed. Network Monitor II comes with a customizable interface can be adjusted according to your wishes. You can choose what information will be displayed, change the interface of the program, change the color of each category are displayed, and...
</description></item><item><title>Download XYplorer Portable 27.10.0600</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 20:01:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-portable-12066.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-portable-12066.html
</guid><description>
XYplorer Portable is a file management software application that provides a comprehensive set of features for organizing and managing files and folders on your computer. This is a portable version of XYplorer that you can run directly from a portable storage device, such as a USB drive, without installation.
XYplorer Portable Features
	File Management: XYplorer Portable provides a two-window interface, allowing you to view and work with two folders at the same time. It provides easy...
</description></item><item><title>Download NPS Image Editor 4.3.4.6951</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 20:01:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nps-image-editor-12735.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nps-image-editor-12735.html
</guid><description>
NPS Image Editor is a unique, free image editor that is perfect for pixel art, drawing, and photo editing. It is lightweight, customizable, and intuitive, yet incredibly powerful. The goal of NPS Image Editor is to provide the world with an easy-to-use image editing application that also allows me (as a developer) to learn new skills and improve my programming knowledge.
In addition, NPS Image Editor also includes an advanced color picker that can run standalone (without opening the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sante FFT Imaging 1.4.4</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 19:59:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sante-fft-imaging-11341.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sante-fft-imaging-11341.html
</guid><description>
Sante FFT Imaging is a program to remove sample noise from DICOM and simple images (jpg, tif, png and bmp). This type of noise is very common in images that have been digitized with a CR digitizer. The program uses a Fast Fourier Transform (FFT), a convolutional low-pass filter in the frequency domain or/and direct frequency deletion to remove sample noise.
Main features:
Fourier transform
	Fourier transform is a mathematical tool used to convert images from the spatial domain to the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Currency Converter Plus 3.1.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 17:09:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-currency-converter-plus-8174.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-currency-converter-plus-8174.html
</guid><description>
Advanced currency converter - With multiple currency fields, historical rate charts, and a built-in calculator for convenience, compare prices wherever you travel abroad to ensure Make sure you get the best deal at today's price. All conversions use live exchange rates from AccuRate™, providing the most accurate rates available in the world. Plus, it still works offline for moves when exchange rate data isn't available. This app even supports Bitcoin!
Features of Currency Converter...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sygic GPS Navigation &amp;amp; Maps 25.3.3-2453</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 17:09:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sygic-gps-navigation-maps-8606.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sygic-gps-navigation-maps-8606.html
</guid><description>
Sygic GPS Navigation &amp;amp; Maps is the most downloaded GPS navigation app in the world, trusted by more than 200 million drivers. Offline 3D maps stored on your phone for GPS navigation without an internet connection. We update our maps for free multiple times each year so you can always rely on Sygic GPS Navigation.
Navigate anywhere, even without an Internet connection
	Offline maps of all the countries in the world, from TomTom and other providers
	Free map updates several times...
</description></item><item><title>Download 3C All-in-One Toolbox 3.1.0f</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 17:09:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-3c-all-in-one-toolbox-8399.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-3c-all-in-one-toolbox-8399.html
</guid><description>
3C All-in-One Toolbox combines many features into one giant toolbox with a modern and easy-to-use interface. All the tools you need to monitor, control and fine-tune all your Android devices. This app uses the Accessibility service to help you stop the app on non-rooted devices but will never collect any information.
Features of 3C All-in-One Toolbox
	Device Manager offers very powerful configurations, task scheduling, and device watchdogs that you can find to optimize performance and...
</description></item><item><title>Download All PDF Editor &amp;amp; Reader | Xodo 10.5.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 17:09:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-xodo-pdf-reader-editor-8451.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-xodo-pdf-reader-editor-8451.html
</guid><description>
Xodo PDF Reader &amp;amp; Editor is a mobile application for reading and editing PDF documents on Android and iOS devices. The app allows users to view, annotate, and edit PDF files using a variety of tools, including highlighting, underlining, and adding notes. With Xodo, you can read, annotate, sign, and share PDFs and fill out PDF forms, all while syncing with Google Drive, Dropbox, and OneDrive.
Xodo PDF Reader &amp;amp; Editor Features
	PDF Viewer: Application that allows users to view...
</description></item><item><title>Download AI Speech to text: Transcribe 1.30</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 17:08:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ai-speech-to-text-transcribe-13800.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ai-speech-to-text-transcribe-13800.html
</guid><description>
Welcome to AI Speech to Text: Audio to Text, an innovative and sophisticated solution designed to enhance your transcription experience. Our AI Speech to Text app sets new standards in speech to text conversion by combining cutting-edge technology with user-friendly features. Whether you are a professional who wants to transcribe real-time conversations, an academic who needs to convert audio files, or a business professional managing important meeting notes, our AI audio to text...
</description></item><item><title>Download µTorrent® Pro - Torrent App 8.2.51</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 17:08:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-utorrent-pro-torrent-app-9897.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-utorrent-pro-torrent-app-9897.html
</guid><description>
µTorrent® Pro - Torrent App downloads files quickly using the BitTorrent P2P file sharing protocol. Multi-threading when seeding helps speed up downloads of music, movies, and videos. The application will help users split files with too heavy data into smaller files. From there, downloading movies will be smoother than ever. Owning this unique application, users will no longer need to worry too much about downloading anything that is too heavy.
Other features of µTorrent® Pro -...
</description></item><item><title>Download Dev Tools Pro (Developer Tools) 9.0.0-gp</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 17:07:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-dev-tools-pro-developer-tools-12197.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-dev-tools-pro-developer-tools-12197.html
</guid><description>
Android Dev Tools Pro is an essential, efficient, powerful, automation Android Development Assistant, It can improve your development productivity. It can be used to decompile another app, view other app's layout details, view screen colors (color sampler or eyedropper), view latest open source projects, view activity history, view manifest of any app, view recently used or installed apps, extract apk or more, debug apps, view hardware and firmware related information phone software,...
</description></item><item><title>Download BitTorrent®- Torrent Downloads 8.2.51</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 17:07:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-bittorrent-pro-torrent-app-9913.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-bittorrent-pro-torrent-app-9913.html
</guid><description>
Find torrents and download them directly to your phone or tablet, WITHOUT ADS, with the official BitTorrent® Pro app for Android -- now with battery saver and auto-shutdown features.
Features of BitTorrent Pro - Torrent App
	Neat, light and beautiful design
	Wi-Fi only mode to save mobile data
	No speed limit and no size limit
	Easy access to your media with integrated music and video libraries
	Select files to download in torrents to minimize your storage space
	Better music and...
</description></item><item><title>Download SnapTube for Android 7.46.1.74603801</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 17:06:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-snaptube-youtube-downloader-hd-video-8351.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-snaptube-youtube-downloader-hd-video-8351.html
</guid><description>
SnapTube is a mobile application that allows users to download videos from various platforms, such as YouTube, Vimeo, and Dailymotion. It provides video resolution in multiple formats 144p, 720p, 1080p HD, 2K HD, 4K HD and audio formats MP3 and M4A. With Snaptube, users can search for content across all their platforms without using multiple apps.
Features of SnapTube for Android
Download in multiple resolutions
	MP4 videos are available in resolutions: choose small 360 pixels or...
</description></item><item><title>Download CALCU Stylish Basic Calculator 4.7.8</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 17:06:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-stylish-calculator-calcu-8716.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-stylish-calculator-calcu-8716.html
</guid><description>
Express your style with a computer made just for you. Choose a stylish, colorful theme to brighten your day while you calculate with ease. CALCU™ is easy to use for everyday calculations, with all the scientific capabilities you need for work and school at a swipe. And for your most demanding needs, CALCU™ lets you add or remove the functions and constants you need to create the perfect calculator you designed for you.
Features of Fashion Calculator - CALCU
	Try our new Material...
</description></item></channel></rss>