<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 23:38:20 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 23:38:20 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Perfect Backup 3.4.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 26 Aug 2025 22:20:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfect-backup-7873.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfect-backup-7873.html
</guid><description>
Perfect Backup is free software to backup your personal and business data to external drives, FTP servers and cloud storages like Google Drive, OneDrive, Box,... It allows you to automate the process of saving your important files to external storage. With it, you can be sure that you never lose your documents, tables, sources and media files.
Features of Perfect Backup
	It's actually freeware. No limits, no adware.
	Back up files and folders to different types of devices: internal...
</description></item><item><title>Download LDPlayer 9.1.60.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 26 Aug 2025 21:25:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ldplayer-2331.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ldplayer-2331.html
</guid><description>
LDPlayer is software that emulates Android, allowing users to play games, run apps on a Windows computer. LDPlayer support play heavy games, run chat applications, photo editing, video and many other Android apps, LDPlayer compatible with Android 5.1 and above, supports multitasking for experience not inferior when used on Mobile.
Installation is a simple process and quickly without the need for special attention from your side, there's more. installed, you can't touch them. This...
</description></item><item><title>Download AnyDesk 9.6</title><pubDate> Tue, 26 Aug 2025 21:25:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anydesk-1321.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anydesk-1321.html
</guid><description>
AnyDesk is software computer control remote, easy connection with remote computer management and manipulation on the computer. After installing the AnyDesk up 2 the computer then you can easily use the software to provide technical support for a friend or family member or you have access to your computer while you away from home or office.
AnyDesk - control your computer remotely
The process of using very simple software, want to allow access to his computer, only need to provide for...
</description></item><item><title>Download Advanced SystemCare Pro 18.5.0.250</title><pubDate> Tue, 26 Aug 2025 21:24:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-systemcare-pro-368.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-systemcare-pro-368.html
</guid><description>
Advanced SystemCare Pro is software that provides features to optimize a PC system professional cleanup, repair, speed up and protect PC.  Advanced SystemCare Pro tab Protect new is added, is designed to provide quick access to protect browsing from being tracked by automatically delete traces of privacy when browser closed and detect and resist the attack of the plugin / malicious toolbar by Browser Anti -Backing and Plugin / toolbar cleaner.
Program speed up pc top
Advanced SystemCare...
</description></item><item><title>Download Serato DJ Pro 3.3.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 26 Aug 2025 21:24:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-serato-dj-pro-169.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-serato-dj-pro-169.html
</guid><description>
Serato DJ Pro is software mix DJ music, professional support, sound effects, and combined to create music, Great DJ. Serato DJ Pro supports the sound effects such as Delay, Reverb, Flanger, Echo, PingPong Delay, Phaser, Distortion, High and Low Pass Filter, as well as combinations of them. Supports MIDI in full, be made in the program, providing the ability to adapt to the controller and program for every need. It allows you to use at the same time from two to four floors. Program Serato...
</description></item><item><title>Download MiniTool ShadowMaker Pro 4.8.0 All Editions</title><pubDate> Tue, 26 Aug 2025 21:23:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minitool-shadowmaker-pro-6105.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minitool-shadowmaker-pro-6105.html
</guid><description>
MiniTool ShadowMaker Pro offers easy file backup, system backup, and disk/partition backup for Windows users. It comes with a clear interface and rapid operation. In addition, this data backup software provides full, different backup copies, increasing and on a real schedule that makes it easier for you to customize the backup plan.
To ensure data safety, this Windows backup software provides backup, backup, and disk/partition backup in case of any incident. In addition, the rescue...
</description></item><item><title>Download DaVinci Resolve Studio 20.1.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 26 Aug 2025 21:23:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-davinci-resolve-studio-1072.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-davinci-resolve-studio-1072.html
</guid><description>
DaVinci Resolve Studio is professional video editing and color grading software developed by Blackmagic Design. This is an enhanced version of the free DaVinci Resolve software, providing additional features and capabilities for professional video editing, color correction, and post-production.
One of the outstanding features of DaVinci Resolve Studio is its powerful color correction capabilities. It provides a comprehensive set of tools and features for advanced color correction,...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDQ Deploy 19.4.108.0 Enterprise</title><pubDate> Tue, 26 Aug 2025 21:22:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdq-deploy-1469.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdq-deploy-1469.html
</guid><description>
PDQ Deploy Enterprise is an application to keep the Windows PC and the programs installed on it. Software PDQ Deploy helps you to connect multiple patch or a windows app (.exe, .msi) with multiple operating systems. The deployment software can be install, delete, run script, reboot, copy the file, sliding mode, send messages, etc.
PDQ Deploy Enterprise
Features of PDQ Deploy Enterprise
	Send notifications (alerts) via email
	Run the script as popular as .vbs, .reg .bat and .ps1
	Run...
</description></item><item><title>Download Argente Malware Cleaner 3.0.2.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 26 Aug 2025 21:21:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-argente-malware-cleaner-13494.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-argente-malware-cleaner-13494.html
</guid><description>
Argente Malware Cleaner is a lightweight utility designed to detect and remove a wide range of malware, including spyware, adware, Trojans and other threats that can compromise your privacy and data. It works as a complementary tool alongside your main antivirus software, helping to detect malware that may slip through the cracks.
Key features of Argente Malware Cleaner include:
	Easy-to-use, clean, and user-friendly interface that suits both casual and advanced users.
	Deep scanning...
</description></item><item><title>Download Coreform Cubit 2025.8.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 26 Aug 2025 21:21:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coreform-cubit-7997.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coreform-cubit-7997.html
</guid><description>
Coreform Cubit preprocessing and Flex IGA modeling with advanced hex meshing and hex mainstream meshing minimizes time spent on model preparation for FEA and CFD while maximizing optimize mesh quality control to get the right mesh for quality solutions, allowing you to maximize your investment in simulation technology. Coreform Cubit helps you maximize the return on your investment in simulation technology.
Features of Coreform Cubit
	Everything you need for CAD import, preprocessing,...
</description></item><item><title>Download GiliSoft Audio Toolbox Suite 13.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 26 Aug 2025 21:20:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-audio-toolbox-suite-856.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-audio-toolbox-suite-856.html
</guid><description>
GiliSoft Audio Toolbox Suite is software that contains 9 program powerful audio like Audio Recorder , Audio Cutter, Audio Joiner, Audio Converter, Video to Mp3,ID3 Tag Editor,Transfer to iTunes,CD Ripper,CD Burner. With GiliSoft Audio Toolbox Suite, you can easily convert and edit any audio file, how to extract, create and copy CD, convert audio files, burn music to CD, rip CD / DVD to the audio file to another, etc.
GiliSoft Audio Toolbox Suite - software sound synthesis
The main...
</description></item><item><title>Download Aescripts Face 3D 1.1.3 for After Effects</title><pubDate> Tue, 26 Aug 2025 21:20:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aescripts-face-3d-12304.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aescripts-face-3d-12304.html
</guid><description>
Aescripts Face 3D is a powerful 3D portrait and photo animation tool that is extremely easy to use, fast and powered by AI. This tool
turn photos into realistic 3D models that can be fully animated!
Important request
	This plugin uses Blender for background processing. To use it, you need to install the completely free Blender application for your operating system.
	System requirements: After Effects v24.2 or higher with Advanced 3D Renderer.
</description></item><item><title>Download Blackmagic Design Fusion Studio 20.1.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 26 Aug 2025 21:19:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blackmagic-design-fusion-studio-2750.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blackmagic-design-fusion-studio-2750.html
</guid><description>
Blackmagic Design Fusion Studio is the world's most advanced compositing software for visual effects artists, broadcast and motion graphics designers, and 3D animators. For the past 30 years, Fusion has been used on thousands of Hollywood blockbuster films and television shows. Fusion features a powerful node-based interface that lets you quickly and easily create sophisticated effects by connecting different types of image processing tools together! You get a wide range of tools,...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube Downloader 3.9.16 (2408)</title><pubDate> Tue, 26 Aug 2025 21:18:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube Downloader  is a dedicated software that helps users  downloading youtube videos  Favorites on PC for offline viewing. With MediaHuman YouTube  Downloader  you can download videos from youtube website to your computer with  fast speed , with special software development technology that automatically receives videos from Websites, in addition to the ability to download videos from software websites, can convert downloaded video formats to various formats for the purpose...
</description></item><item><title>Download BG Renderer MAX for After Effects 1.0.27</title><pubDate> Tue, 26 Aug 2025 21:18:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bg-renderer-max-for-after-effects-10138.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bg-renderer-max-for-after-effects-10138.html
</guid><description>
BG Renderer MAX gives you the ability to render compositions in the background using After Effects' rendering engine while still working on your projects. Set up your render workflow with a variety of post-render options like Slack and Email notifications.
Features of BG Renderer MAX for After Effects
	Easier workflow
	Free Remote Monitoring
	Native Notification System: Send render notifications as Slack messages and emails right from BG Renderer Max.
	Integrating Zapier, Microsoft...
</description></item><item><title>Download Unicodia 2.12.7</title><pubDate> Tue, 26 Aug 2025 21:18:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-unicodia-8521.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-unicodia-8521.html
</guid><description>
Unicodia is free, open source software that can be used as an alternative character map for your Windows machine. The interface contains everything you need, allowing you to easily cycle through all the available ASCII symbols and copy them to the clipboard. Uncicodia is a great alternative to your standard Unicode characters and is filled with symbols/characters that make it useful for a number of different uses.
Features of Unicodia
	In Windows 10/11 — all characters of Unicode 15...
</description></item><item><title>Download ezPaycheck 3.15.19</title><pubDate> Tue, 26 Aug 2025 21:17:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ezpaycheck-5319.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ezpaycheck-5319.html
</guid><description>
ezPaycheck is a payroll software easy to use is designed for the small business: simple, reliable and affordable. The developer of we have designed it to become a solution tax payroll internal for small businesses to calculate taxes, print paychecks for employees and contractors, generate reports and print tax forms.
The features of ezPaycheck
	Calculate payroll federal and state tax / deductions and local taxes (such as SDI tax, occupation tax, city)
	Print paychecks and tax...
</description></item><item><title>Download Argente System Repair 1.0.2.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 26 Aug 2025 21:17:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-argente-system-repair-13813.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-argente-system-repair-13813.html
</guid><description>
Argente System Repair is a lightweight utility designed to diagnose and fix common Windows system problems. It scans your system to identify errors in operating system components, file systems, installation files, and other system components, and then applies targeted fixes to resolve these problems. The tool provides different scan modes, including simple scan, recommended scan, and custom scan, allowing users to customize the repair process according to their needs.
System Repair...
</description></item><item><title>Download SplitCam 10.8.60</title><pubDate> Tue, 26 Aug 2025 21:16:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-splitcam-4754.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-splitcam-4754.html
</guid><description>
SplitCam offers webcam effects great to have more positive emotions during video calls with your friends! Additionally SplitCam is the easiest way to divide the video stream of your webcam. With SplitCam you can video chat with all your friends, SplitCam is also software development, live video - broadcast your video to any ims and video services and all this at the same time.
10.3.78
The features of SplitCam
Software amazing webcam effects
Add our effects to video your webcam in video...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDQ Inventory 19.4.108.0 Enterprise</title><pubDate> Tue, 26 Aug 2025 21:16:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdq-inventory-1468.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdq-inventory-1468.html
</guid><description>
PDQ Inventory is a software application to manage your system. This software will be able to manage your system by scanning the Windows operating system of you to provide information hardware, software, and configuration for the Windows operating system in your your tools. The tools available in this software helps you can scan the computer correctly.
In addition, the software PDQ Inventory can give you very detailed information. This software application is one of the management...
</description></item><item><title>Download Database Tour Pro 11.5.3.701</title><pubDate> Tue, 26 Aug 2025 21:15:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-database-tour-pro-5321.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-database-tour-pro-5321.html
</guid><description>
Database Tour Pro application is a comprehensive software that allows you to organize all the database is connected his. It provides support for Borland Database Engine (BDE) and Microsoft ActiveX Data Objects (ADO), SQL scripts, reports, along with conversion and data export, among others.
It contains a browser object for the function, package, triggers, folders, users, roles, profiles, sequences, work, style, Java, exception, link, database, general properties, table, schema, and...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter 3.9.16 (2408)</title><pubDate> Tue, 26 Aug 2025 21:15:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-to-mp3-converter-1744.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-to-mp3-converter-1744.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter is the software support download youtube video and convert video to mp3 format fast and most simple. MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter allows you download and convert videos from YouTube and other websites to MP3 format by pasting the YouTube URL into the application. When you paste the URL, the program will display thumbnails for videos and you have the option to customize the title information, artist and album before you begin the process of...
</description></item><item><title>Download TeamViewer 15.69.4 + Portable</title><pubDate> Tue, 26 Aug 2025 21:14:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-teamviewer-528.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-teamviewer-528.html
</guid><description>
TeamViewer is software that functions to connect and control the remote computer, the ability to connect with any system anywhere from all over the place. This is a support tool users is very convenient. TeamViewer to help users control remote computer becomes much more simple, help you interact and collaborate with others in the exchange and share of information, instruction manual, application software or fix the computer.
TeamViewer as a revolution of computer science. when you have...
</description></item><item><title>Download FontBase Awesome 2.23.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 26 Aug 2025 21:14:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fontbase-awesome-12674.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fontbase-awesome-12674.html
</guid><description>
FontBase is a modern font manager designed for designers, providing many features to enhance font management across a variety of platforms. With a FontBase Awesome subscription, in addition to all the free features, you'll get a suite of advanced features to improve your font management workflow.
FontBase Awesome Features
	OpenType features: The largest set of supported OpenType features among font software at your fingertips.
	Symbols: View and copy any icon for any language and font...
</description></item><item><title>Download Zoner Photo Studio X 19.2503.2.639</title><pubDate> Tue, 26 Aug 2025 21:14:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zoner-photo-studio-x-95.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zoner-photo-studio-x-95.html
</guid><description>
Zoner Photo Studio X Pro helps you to control your photos. Zoner Photo Studio is a complete toolbox for managing and processing digital photos. Get photos from your camera, organize your archive, and edit and share your photos - never been easier! Zoner Photo Studio is useful for beginners, advanced users and photographers with experience, who can choose one of four different variations. Zoner Photo Studio is made for every user of digital cameras, scanners, and mobile devices. It contains...
</description></item></channel></rss>