<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 03:33:29 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 03:33:29 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download QontrolPanel (QuickSoundSwitcher) 1.10.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 08 Dec 2025 00:37:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quicksoundswitcher-14033.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quicksoundswitcher-14033.html
</guid><description>
QuickSoundSwitcher is a lightweight, open-source Windows utility designed to quickly and easily manage audio input and output devices. It allows users to switch between multiple audio devices (e.g. speakers, headphones, microphones) and control the volume directly from the system tray without navigating to complex Windows settings.
The program also provides an application volume mixer, allowing for volume adjustment and muting for individual programs. This tool is especially useful for...
</description></item><item><title>Download Hypersnap 9.6.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 08 Dec 2025 00:00:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hypersnap-764.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hypersnap-764.html
</guid><description>
Hypersnap is a software screen capture from Windows screen and capture text (TextSnap) from places can't copy normal text. HyperSnap combines the power of screen capture app class with utility image editing advanced is packaged in a easy to use tool! It's perfect for capturing images that you want to put into the help system, online tutorials, manuals, training guides, presentations, marketing materials, website, email, and more. Use HyperSnap to quickly share a picture perfect...
</description></item><item><title>Download Office Timeline Plus 13.11.00.00 Expert / Pro / Pro+ Edition</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 23:59:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-timeline-2106.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-timeline-2106.html
</guid><description>
Office Timeline is an add-on very useful and powerful software for Microsoft PowerPoint. With add-ons, you can create PowerPoint documents look more beautiful. With add-ons, you can add the time Line on the project by yourself. Application time for the composition and different segments of the document, your PowerPoint will not only increase the beauty for your work, but also for customers and your manager. The people who created this product is also believe that add-ons this is the only...
</description></item><item><title>Download TubeMate Downloader 6.0.10</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 23:59:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubemate-downloader-4250.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubemate-downloader-4250.html
</guid><description>
TubeMate Downloader is a smart application that lets you download any clip you want from the website hosting the main video and convert them in when download at or then. If you need a simple and effective tool to download videos, you can give it a try. With TubeMate Downloader, you can directly drag and drop video link from your browser into the drop-down box or application window to start downloading. You don't even need to copy and paste the video URL.
TubeMate Downloader - Support...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinTools.net Professional / Premium / Classic 25.13.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 23:58:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wintoolsnet-304.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wintoolsnet-304.html
</guid><description>
WinTools.net is an optimal tool working performance of the operating system and delete the unnecessary program from the hard drive and control the start-up process of Windows.
WinTools.net integrates many useful tools, to support increased processing speed and ability, stable operation for the computer include: Clean Uninstaller, Scan Files, Scan Registry, Start Up, Tweak UI, Net Tweaker, The Privacy. Scan Files are often used to scan the hard drive periodically, search for junk files or...
</description></item><item><title>Download VCap Downloader Pro 0.1.42.6860</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 23:58:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vcap-downloader-pro-8474.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vcap-downloader-pro-8474.html
</guid><description>
VCap Downloader Pro (VCapDL) is a popular piece of software that allows you to record video and audio from websites on the internet. The interface of the software is similar to a normal browser, making it easy for users to get used to and work with this software. User just need to copy video url from favorite browser and convert it to VCap Downloader Pro. It will capture the video and make the quality available for download. You can also extract the audio track from any video and convert...
</description></item><item><title>Download Renee PassNow Pro 2025.11.09.153</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 23:57:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-renee-passnow-pro-3975.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-renee-passnow-pro-3975.html
</guid><description>
Renee PassNow Pro is the application used to reset BIOS passwords, a feature quite useful when users need to make changes there but can't access the BIOS because the login information is forgotten. Users can take advantage of Renee PassNow to discover the faults of Windows and fix them, as long as they can not boot into the operating system anymore.
Renee PassNow Pro - password Recovery system
This tool can create direct means to recover data with just a few mouse clicks, as it can...
</description></item><item><title>Download TubeDownload Pro 7.0.6</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 23:57:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubedownload-pro-12035.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubedownload-pro-12035.html
</guid><description>
TubeDownload Pro is a professional Windows application for downloading your favorite videos from YouTube and hundreds of other video sites. TubeDownload Pro can increase download speed up to 500% or even more.
Features of TubeDownload Pro
	Download your favorite videos from YouTube and hundreds of other video sites.
	Increase download speed up to 500% or even more.
	Download 720p, 1080p, 2K, 4K and 8K HD videos from YouTube.
	Download entire playlists in just a few clicks.
	Download...
</description></item><item><title>Download DesktopUp 1.5.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 23:51:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopup-10730.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopup-10730.html
</guid><description>
DesktopUp will allow you to optimize your desktop. You can create as many desktops as you like and switch between them. For each desktop, you can choose the programs you want to run when you switch to it.
Features of DesktopUp
	Create an unlimited number of desktops
	Associate to each desktop an unlimited number of programs that will be executed when switched to each desktop
	Delete desktop
	Delete executable files associated with the desktop
	Quick selector
	Theme for the quick...
</description></item><item><title>Download Agisoft Metashape Professional 2.3.0 Build 21751</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 23:50:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-agisoft-metashape-professional-1731.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-agisoft-metashape-professional-1731.html
</guid><description>
Agisoft Metashape (formerly PhotoScan) is a software product independently perform image processing and digital data creation, 3D space used in GIS applications, material cultural heritage and the production visual effects as well as the indirect measurement of the different subjects scale. Technical digital photography is deployed wisely is applied with the method of computer vision led to the system processor, smart auto, on the one hand, can be managed by a new person in the field of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Thimeo ST-Enterprise 10.72</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 23:50:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thimeo-st-enterprise-10422.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thimeo-st-enterprise-10422.html
</guid><description>
Thimeo ST-Enterprise is for larger media groups running multiple stations or channels. It does everything that Stereo Tools does and more! With ST-Enterprise, you can run up to 50(*) FM and/or HD processors on a single computer, with a single interface to control them and an overview screen showing the status of them all. incoming and outgoing signals.
Features of Thimeo ST-Enterprise
	It makes more efficient use of available resources, mainly processing power, and allows you to share...
</description></item><item><title>Download LuBan 3D 02.12.2025</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 23:42:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-luban-3d-10427.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-luban-3d-10427.html
</guid><description>
LuBan 3D is creative design software that helps designers and manufacturers create their innovative products quickly. LuBan automatically creates 3D models in a variety of forms, such as lithophane, stacks, hashes, slabs, reliefs, modules, and wireframes. The resulting model can be fabricated by 3D printing, laser cutting and CNC milling. Model parts can be fabricated using laser cutting and 3D printing. LuBan does not depend on specific fabrication methods; instead, it can communicate...
</description></item><item><title>Download FX Science Tools Manifest 25.12.05</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 23:41:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fx-science-tools-3744.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fx-science-tools-3744.html
</guid><description>
FX Science Tools provided to teachers of chemistry and physics the effective means to create equations and chemical structures. Just type and create. FX Chem FX Chem makes writing chemical equations become simple. You just type and FX Chem know enough about chemistry to put all the components of the equation at the right point. FX Chem can even create the chemical equations for nuclear - a very difficult thing in the Word. FX ChemSturation FX ChemSturation made the organic structure, what...
</description></item><item><title>Download ExamDiff Pro Master Edition 16.0.1.17</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 23:40:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-examdiff-pro-master-312.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-examdiff-pro-master-312.html
</guid><description>
ExamDiff Pro Master is a tool to compare files and folders intuitive and easy to use, intuitive and easy to use for Windows. ExamDiff Pro Master has unique features distinguishes ExamDiff Pro with the program compare other. ExamDiff Pro Master to help perform reviews of code and share other reports with your colleagues and compare local website with FTP server by plug-ins more integrated.
ExamDiff Pro Master can create a snapshot folder for comparison and storage in the future, compare...
</description></item><item><title>Download Thimeo Stereo Tool 10.72</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 23:39:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stereo-tool-4066.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stereo-tool-4066.html
</guid><description>
Stereo Tool is an audio processor based on software, provide sound quality superior and comes with many unique features. It is used by over 1500 FM stations, from the station of the small local to the station 50 - 100 kW and nationwide network with dozens of generators, thousands of stations online and many radio DAB +, HD, AM and TV. Stereo Tool can make recordings sound equal and consistent in volume and sound color, highlight details and increase the stereo effect is there. It can...
</description></item><item><title>Download KS DB Merge Tools for Oracle 1.14</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 23:38:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ks-db-merge-tools-for-oracle-12715.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ks-db-merge-tools-for-oracle-12715.html
</guid><description>
KS DB Merge Tools for Oracle is designed for database comparison and synchronization, allowing you to compare data and schemas within two Oracle databases and merge any possible changes happen. It displays data on two tables, each allowing a direct connection to an Oracle database. Some essential details to get you started: server name and port number, as well as connection credentials. Maybe test the connection to see if everything is working properly.
KS DB Merge Tools for Oracle...
</description></item><item><title>Download FX Math Tools Manifest 25.12.05</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 23:37:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fx-draw-tools-multidocs-8814.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fx-draw-tools-multidocs-8814.html
</guid><description>
MultiDocs is a new way to create self-modifying Word documents. MultiDocs' amazing new document reproduction features allow you to create reproducible tests and quizzes in minutes. Get new numbers, new diagrams and even brand new solutions! MultiDocs combines the power of Word with two leading products: FX Draw and FX Equation in a new and exciting way.
Features of FX Draw Tools MultiDocs
	Create multiple documents: The software allows users to create multiple math and evaluation...
</description></item><item><title>Download Thimeo Relay 10.72</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 23:37:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thimeo-relay-10423.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thimeo-relay-10423.html
</guid><description>
Thimeo Relay uses your sound card (internal or external) as a Relay detector and converts on/off signals into RDS commands that can be sent to most devices. RDS encoders, including those in Stereo Engine and STXtreme.
Features of Thimeo Relay
	It minimizes audio latency, ensuring real-time audio processing and synchronization with video content or virtual instruments.
	It offers multiple connection options to meet different audio needs.
	Use your sound card (internal or external) as a...
</description></item><item><title>Download FonesGo WhatsApp Transfer 8.9.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 20:55:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fonesgo-whatsapp-transfer-14319.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fonesgo-whatsapp-transfer-14319.html
</guid><description>
The Ultimate WhatsApp Transfer, Backup &amp;amp; Restore Solution. Transfer WhatsApp/WhatsApp Business between Android and iOS devices. Backup WhatsApp to PC/Mac without iCloud or Google Drive. Restore WhatsApp backup from Google Drive to iPhone. Transfer GBWhatsApp to WhatsApp/GBWhatsApp. Well support the latest iOS 26 and Android 16.
	Transfer WhatsApp from Android to iPhone
	Transfer WhatsApp from iPhone to Android
	Transfer WhatsApp from Android to Android
	Transfer WhatsApp from...
</description></item><item><title>Download TriloBase 8.8.3</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 20:48:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-trilobase-14318.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-trilobase-14318.html
</guid><description>
TriloBase is a Windows-based database program designed to catalog collections of fossils, minerals, and artifacts. It is aimed at both amateur and professional collectors who need to store detailed information about each specimen, including location, taxonomy, size, and references.
Over the years, your collection will grow to hundreds or even thousands of artifacts. Recording all relevant information is absolutely essential. You can do this in a notebook, in a simple Excel file, or with...
</description></item><item><title>Download FxSound (FxSound Enhancer Premium) 1.2.4 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 17:32:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fxsound-enhancer-premium-2013.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fxsound-enhancer-premium-2013.html
</guid><description>
FxSound Enhancer Premium formerly DFX Audio Enhance, is accessories multimedia software most popular in the world with over 46 million downloads worldwide. FxSound enhances the sound of most of the music content and online video is live streaming on the Web, including the streaming service, YouTube, Pandora, Spotify and Apple Music. FxSound Enhancer Premium also implemented enhanced real-time audio on the player PC multimedia most popular include iTunes, Windows Media Player, Winamp and...
</description></item><item><title>Download OCCT 15.0.11.99</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 17:31:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-occt-perestroika-1680.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-occt-perestroika-1680.html
</guid><description>
OCCT is a free application designed to benchmark and overclock system components. Test tool OverClock includes 4 different tests to assess the stability of your computer. CPU and CPU: Linpack to test the processor, GPU: 3D to check stability of the graphics processor and power supply combination of CPU: Linpack and GPU: 3D to download power of you up to the maximum.
OCCT - Measuring system components
The features of OCCT
	Support is enabled for a maximum of 16 cores.
	All the tests...
</description></item><item><title>Download Irix HDR Pro 2.3.55</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 17:29:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-irix-hdr-pro-10653.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-irix-hdr-pro-10653.html
</guid><description>
Irix HDR Pro is an AI-powered photo editing application for Windows, it is available on Microsoft Store. This program has tons of professional HDR photo editing features including Sky Replacement, Face Sculpting &amp;amp; body, over 200 presets &amp;amp; AI powered tool' and is a Photo Editor in the category of photo &amp;amp; Graphics. It delivers true-to-life HDR photo editing, providing one-click edits for a full-scale professional editing toolkit.
Features of Irix HDR Pro
	Sky Replacement...
</description></item><item><title>Download PrivaZer Pro Donors 4.0.115</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 17:29:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-privazer-donors-198.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-privazer-donors-198.html
</guid><description>
PrivaZer Donors  cleans and removes filth traces from the system. Intensive cleaning of unwanted traces of what you've done, viewed, downloaded, deleted, etc. Take ownership of your security and freedom - Free up disk space. Keep your PC snug and secure !!!
With one click, PrivaZer can safely clean: Internet browsers, Index.dat, Cookies, Tor Cookies, Flash Cookies, Silverlight Cookies, DOM Storing, IndexedDB, AppCache Registry, RAM, Pagefile.sys and Hiberfil.sys files.  PrivaZer  can...
</description></item><item><title>Download FxSound Pro 1.2.4 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 17:29:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fxsound-5966.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fxsound-5966.html
</guid><description>
FxSound Pro is a professional software that helps to enhance the quality of sound, volume, depth, and sound on your PC. FxSound brings you a great sound just with a downloadable download. After using FxSound, you will know if it is for you or not. Most people do n' t know what they ' re missing in their sound until they try their software/sound hardware better. It ' s hard to convey if you do n' t really experience yourself.
Reason to use FxSound Pro:
	The perfect sound on every...
</description></item></channel></rss>