<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 08:58:15 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 08:58:15 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download MobiOffice: Word, Sheets, PDF 15.8.57539</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Sep 2025 01:41:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-officesuite-word-sheets-pdf-8508.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-officesuite-word-sheets-pdf-8508.html
</guid><description>
OfficeSuite allows you to easily view, edit, and create Word, Excel, and PowerPoint documents and perform advanced PDF operations. Our integrated file manager, Chat app with document exchange capabilities, and tons of other handy tools make this the most feature-rich mobile office solution available on Android. Pre-installed by leading manufacturers including Sony, ZTE, Amazon, Sharp, Acer, CAT, Alcatel, Kyocera, Toshiba, etc.
Features of OfficeSuite for Android
	View, create, and...
</description></item><item><title>Download GPS Map Camera 2.1.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Sep 2025 01:40:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-gps-map-camera-9537.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-gps-map-camera-9537.html
</guid><description>
GPS Map Camera will help users save memorable moments with extremely detailed information about where and when they took that photo. Now just by looking at the photo, you can immediately remember when, where and how you took this photo. GPS Map Camera will provide you with an extremely sharp photo capture tool with a very good image processing system, so your photos will be of very high quality. Besides, the photo function of this application can also intelligently identify objects to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Document Scanner - PDF Creator 6.8.18</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Sep 2025 01:39:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-document-scanner-pdf-creator-9783.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-document-scanner-pdf-creator-9783.html
</guid><description>
Sometimes in a day, you need to scan your different documents multiple times. In that situation, if everything is planned, you will definitely not have to suffer any more. But if the need to scan those documents arises one by one, it will definitely be a disaster. To rescue you from that situation CV Infotech brings you a mobile Doc Scanner. This document scanner allows you to scan your documents anytime, anywhere.
The application also has some additional features that help your scanned...
</description></item><item><title>Download Advanced Download Manager Pro 14.0.39</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Sep 2025 01:39:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-advanced-download-manager-8188.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-advanced-download-manager-8188.html
</guid><description>
Advanced download manager (ADM) is a type of application that allows users to download files from the Internet with additional features and functionality beyond what is provided by standard download managers of equipment. ADM is designed to make file downloads faster, more efficient, and more reliable by downloading files in multiple parts at once, which can increase download speeds by up to 500%.
Features of Advanced Download Manager Pro
	Download from the Internet up to three files...
</description></item><item><title>Download SnapEdit - AI photo editor 7.4.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Sep 2025 01:38:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-snapedit-ai-photo-editor-13164.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-snapedit-ai-photo-editor-13164.html
</guid><description>
SnapEdit is one of the best AI photo editing apps with a mission to make your editing easy, smooth and fun. Transform your photos like never before with SnapEdit, the ultimate photo editing app designed to easily remove unwanted objects, enhance image quality and create stunning photo masterpieces. Download SnapEdit now and unlock a world of possibilities for your photos!
KEY FEATURES:
ONE-TAP OBJECT REMOVAL: Say goodbye to photo spoilers, unwanted elements, or distracting objects in...
</description></item><item><title>Download AI Speech to text: Transcribe 1.33</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Sep 2025 01:38:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ai-speech-to-text-transcribe-13800.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ai-speech-to-text-transcribe-13800.html
</guid><description>
Welcome to AI Speech to Text: Audio to Text, an innovative and sophisticated solution designed to enhance your transcription experience. Our AI Speech to Text app sets new standards in speech to text conversion by combining cutting-edge technology with user-friendly features. Whether you are a professional who wants to transcribe real-time conversations, an academic who needs to convert audio files, or a business professional managing important meeting notes, our AI audio to text...
</description></item><item><title>Download Lucky Patcher 11.9.6</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Sep 2025 01:38:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-lucky-patcher-11914.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-lucky-patcher-11914.html
</guid><description>
Lucky Patcher is a free Android app that can modify many apps and games, Block ads, remove unwanted system apps, backup apps before and after modification, Move apps apps to SD card, remove license verification from paid apps and games, etc.
Lucky Patcher features and details:
	Remove or block ads on Android apps and games. You can easily block ads with Lucky Patcher.
	Block in-app purchase verification with the app. You can use premium apps and games for free by removing in-app...
</description></item><item><title>Download Promeo - Story &amp;amp; Reels Maker 8.3.4</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Sep 2025 01:38:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-promeo-story-reels-maker-13060.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-promeo-story-reels-maker-13060.html
</guid><description>
Create stunning designs with minimal effort. Easily customize pre-made templates with simple tools and share them online to get more likes and followers. Choose from over 10,000 optimized, editable, customizable templates with vibrant colors, fonts, effects, and a complete library of premium stock media. No design skills required! Promeo has everything you need to create beautiful and creative social media posts.
Key Features
	Templates: Access over 10,000 ready-to-use templates...
</description></item><item><title>Download AVG Cleaner - Storage Cleaner 25.17.0 build 800011244</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Sep 2025 01:37:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-avg-cleaner-storage-cleaner-9005.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-avg-cleaner-storage-cleaner-9005.html
</guid><description>
AVG Cleaner is a memory cleaning and optimization application developed by AVG Technologies. It is designed to help users reclaim space on their Android devices by deleting unnecessary files and optimizing system performance.
The app can scan your device for junk files, including temporary files, cache files, and outdated APK files, and help you delete them safely. Additionally, AVG Cleaner can analyze your device's battery consumption and provide suggestions on how to improve your...
</description></item><item><title>Download Chat AI - AI Chatbot Assistant v208.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Sep 2025 01:37:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-chat-ai-ai-chatbot-assistant-11260.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-chat-ai-ai-chatbot-assistant-11260.html
</guid><description>
AI Chatbot is a smart artificial intelligence interactive application that brings a unique and convenient experience to users. With AI Chatbot, you can communicate and ask questions directly with a powerful AI system that helps you find information, answer questions, and even provide solutions to complex problems.
Main features of Chatbot AI include
	Natural conversation: Chatbot AI uses advanced natural language technology to understand and respond to your questions and requests...
</description></item><item><title>Download XY VPN - Security Proxy VPN 5.0.753</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Sep 2025 01:37:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-xy-vpn-security-proxy-vpn-11170.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-xy-vpn-security-proxy-vpn-11170.html
</guid><description>
XY VPN is a stable VPN! Stable and worldwide internet security and privacy VPN app for all Android users.It provides secure protection for privacy and security: Military-grade 128-bit AES encryption to secure WiFi hotspots and IPsec protocol and OpenVPN protocol (UDP/TCP) to protect your privacy.
Features:
	Choose the app to use VPN (requires Android 5.0 or later)
	Smart server selection
	No registration or configuration required
	No other permissions required
	One tap to establish a...
</description></item><item><title>Download Video Player All Format 1.2.9.5.90</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Sep 2025 01:36:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-video-player-all-format-10984.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-video-player-all-format-10984.html
</guid><description>
The best Video Player All Format for Android with subtitle support. Listen to music with high quality equalizer. Browse and play songs by genre, album, artist, song and folder.
Features of Video Player All Format
	Select multiple files by pressing and holding.
	Hardware acceleration.
	Video player supports all video formats, including MP4, M4V, AVI, MOV, 3GP, FLV, WMV, RMVB, TS, etc.
	Video queue with reordering.
	Supports subtitles with subtitle delay adjustment.
	Find duplicate...
</description></item><item><title>Download Image to text - Text scanner 1.7.19</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Sep 2025 01:35:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-image-to-text-text-scanner-11903.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-image-to-text-text-scanner-11903.html
</guid><description>
Free online document scanner to text image to copy text program helps you with handwritten text recognition of optical characters and has them converted into characters. This photo to text converter has the function to scan text from image any type of scan and read into offline text located on photo and help you easily extract text from image text scanner scan Word from photo and translator Now you can scan handwriting to text converter free image to text converter program online all...
</description></item><item><title>Download Story Bit | Story Video Maker 2.0.8</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Sep 2025 01:34:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-story-bit-story-video-maker-11696.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-story-bit-story-video-maker-11696.html
</guid><description>
Story Bit makes editing status and story videos surprisingly fun (and simple). Create stunning video collage maker - even if you're not a design expert! Create a Story using templates with music for any social platform. StoryBit allows creating animated statuses, story collages with stylish fonts and Sounds. Stretch out a finger to customize your awesome Insta stories and Instagram posts now!
StoryBit Provides Simple and Stylish Templates that are easily editable and Download now and...
</description></item><item><title>Download DrawNote: Drawing Notepad Memo 8.2.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Sep 2025 01:34:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-drawnote-drawing-notepad-memo-9812.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-drawnote-drawing-notepad-memo-9812.html
</guid><description>
DRAWNOTE is an all-in-one notebook and Notepad that integrates note-taking, mind mapping, to-do lists, handwriting, sketching, drawing and painting. Whether you are a student, teacher, artist, designer, engineer or someone else, Dressote provides powerful tools designed to spark your imagination and creativity.
DRIPROTE Features: Draw Memo Notepad
Infinite Canvas - Create Infinite Possibilities
	Drawote has an infinite canvas, allowing your imagination and creativity to be fully...
</description></item><item><title>Download NokoPrint - Mobile Printing 5.23.6</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Sep 2025 01:33:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-nokoprint-mobile-printing-8528.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-nokoprint-mobile-printing-8528.html
</guid><description>
Print photos and share them with family and friends. Print documents, PDFs, invoices, receipts, boarding passes, and more. at home, at work or on the go! You can print images, photos, web pages, PDF and Microsoft Office documents without downloading any additional apps or printing tools anytime, anywhere on almost any WiFi, Bluetooth or USB printer .
Features of NokoPrint for Android
	Print directly from your Android phone or tablet to almost any inkjet, laser or thermal...
</description></item><item><title>Download Clipboard - Copy Paste &amp;amp;amp; Notes 7.2.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Sep 2025 01:33:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-clipboard-copy-paste-notes-11467.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-clipboard-copy-paste-notes-11467.html
</guid><description>
Are you in need of a smart solution to easily store and access frequently used documents? With Clipboard, every time you copy a piece of text, it's automatically added to your comprehensive and ever-expanding list. Imagine this: you're working on a project and you frequently need to use specific phrases, reply to emails, or even game promo codes. With just a simple copy, Clipboard ensures all your frequently used code snippets are available at your fingertips.
With the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Flexcil Notes &amp;amp; PDF Reader 1.4.0.24</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Sep 2025 01:32:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-flexcil-notes-pdf-reader-11960.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-flexcil-notes-pdf-reader-11960.html
</guid><description>
Whether you need to write notes, read PDF files, edit notes, manage reminders or create a personal planner – Flexcil is always ready! Markup, store text and images; Handwrite notes using touch gestures very easily. The gesture function will help you summarize documents briefly to put into your notepad easily and effectively.
COMBINE NOTES &amp;amp; READ PDF IN ONE APP
	Edit, annotate, and organize content in PDF &amp;amp; Notebooks
	Beautiful handwriting thanks to the vector technology...
</description></item><item><title>Download HiPhone Launcher OS Phone: Fast 1.0.1.5</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Sep 2025 01:32:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-hiphone-launcher-os-phone-fast-13339.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-hiphone-launcher-os-phone-fast-13339.html
</guid><description>
Do you love your phone? Do you want to change your style? Let HiPhone Launcher, MiniOS Launcher change your style
Features:
	Smart search: smart swipe down search screen
	Beautiful wallpapers to decorate your screen
	Support lock screen display with password, pattern lock
	Easily search by swiping down anywhere on the home screen
	Smart switch for silent mode, airplane mode, bluetooth, you can customize more styles, such as size, color, position, vibration.
	Fast, convenient,...
</description></item><item><title>Download UnWX (Severe Weather Alerts) 5.2.13</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Sep 2025 01:32:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-unwx-severe-weather-alerts-14064.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-unwx-severe-weather-alerts-14064.html
</guid><description>
This app will alert you when severe weather is likely. Alerts are issued from official sources when weather conditions are likely to pose a danger to life and property. In addition, the application also integrates a probability indicator (if available).
Depending on the country, the application will warn of weather hazards such as tornadoes, cyclones, thunderstorms, hail, heavy rain, snow, ice, slippery, heat, strong winds, fog, floods or sea warnings.
Features:
	Warnings for all...
</description></item><item><title>Download Logo Maker : Graphic Designer 2.2.7</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Sep 2025 01:32:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-logo-maker-graphic-designer-13419.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-logo-maker-graphic-designer-13419.html
</guid><description>
Are you tired of struggling with complicated graphic design software? Look no further! Introducing Logo Maker Design Creator, the all-in-one solution to quickly create a professional brand. Whether you are a business owner, a gamer, a website developer, or someone who wants to personalize their brand, this logo maker app is the graphic design tool for you. Say goodbye to design challenges and hello to instant branding with Logo Generator: Graphic Designer!
Key Features of Graphic...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ringtone Maker - Music Cutter 1.01.75.0904.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Sep 2025 01:31:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ringtone-maker-music-cutter-11801.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ringtone-maker-music-cutter-11801.html
</guid><description>
Want to create custom ringtones for different contacts or SIM cards? Want to create ringtones from recorded music or audio? Ringtone Maker - Music Cutter is an application that helps users create unique ringtones from music files available on their phone. This application provides users with a set of convenient tools to cut and edit audio files easily and quickly.
When using Ringtone Maker - Music Cutter, users can choose any of their favorite songs from the music library on their phone...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sun Surveyor (Sun &amp;amp; Moon) 2.7.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Sep 2025 01:31:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sun-surveyor-sun-moon-13217.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sun-surveyor-sun-moon-13217.html
</guid><description>
Sun Surveyor helps you uncover the mysteries of sunrise, sunset and moon phases, allowing photographers and filmmakers to find the best locations, plan efficiently and get the perfect shot.
Live camera views, interactive maps (with street view), 3D compass and detailed ephemeris provide a wealth of information about the largest natural light source in the galaxy, as well as the moon and the Milky Way. Ha:
	View augmented reality projections of the sun and moon paths, pinpointing...
</description></item><item><title>Download Daily Planner and Journal 65.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Sep 2025 01:31:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-daily-planner-and-journal-13249.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-daily-planner-and-journal-13249.html
</guid><description>
Welcome to Daily Planner and Journal, your all-in-one solution to seamlessly organize your daily tasks, schedules, and personal reflections. This daily planner and weekly planner app is designed to help you stay on top of your busy life, making it easier than ever to plan your day and capture your thoughts.
Key Features:
	Organize your daily tasks and appointments with our schedule planner.
	Plan your day efficiently with our customizable daily planner.
	Track important meetings and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Hermit - Lite Apps Browser 29.3.6</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Sep 2025 01:30:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-hermit-lite-apps-browser-9896.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-hermit-lite-apps-browser-9896.html
</guid><description>
Hermit APK is a professional web browser with great built-in features that extend users' operations and productivity to new heights by allowing them to explore optimized applications and functions. good optimization. In addition, it automatically helps users search for Lite version specialized applications that they can use in the browser to save a lot of performance. It also includes integration of more extensions to take user personalization to the next level while exploring or...
</description></item></channel></rss>