<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 15:42:59 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 15:42:59 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download RapidRAW 1.4.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Sep 2025 18:03:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rapidraw-13957.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rapidraw-13957.html
</guid><description>
RapidRAW is a modern, high-performance, open-source RAW photo editor, designed to deliver a fast and clean editing experience with a lightweight footprint (under 30MB). Built with performance and usability in mind, the software is aimed at photographers who want a simple, efficient, and fun workflow without compromising performance.
Key Features
	GPU-accelerated processing: Uses a custom WGSL shader to process all image adjustments on the GPU, allowing for smooth, responsive editing...
</description></item><item><title>Download Battery Monitor 10.7</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Sep 2025 18:03:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-battery-monitor-1049.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-battery-monitor-1049.html
</guid><description>
Battery Monitor is a small utility that display on the computer screen the details current battery of laptop your as its name. The interface is based on a small frame can be moved to any location on the screen, with the help of the mouse cursor.
Battery Monitor is not popular and you can quickly get overview of the battery details while working in other apps. The main frame displays the clock and percent level, battery status, remaining time, charging speed and charging current. Battery...
</description></item><item><title>Download miniToggle 1.4.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Sep 2025 18:00:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minitoggle-12243.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minitoggle-12243.html
</guid><description>
miniToggle provides you with a user-friendly application designed to further simplify the process of modifying Explorer settings. With miniToggle, users can conveniently toggle the visibility of hidden files, show or hide file extensions, and empty the trash.
On the extended screen, you will be able to choose one of the three options above to do so by clicking the tray icon. It also has the option to toggle the Windows 11 context menu between the new and classic design.
With...
</description></item><item><title>Download ScreenToGif 2.42</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Sep 2025 17:58:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-screentogif-499.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-screentogif-499.html
</guid><description>
ScreenToGif is a software that allows you to capture anything on your screen and save it as animated GIF. Besides, ScreenToGif allows you can freely move the frame to record a video on your website or activity on the screen on the computer to your desk.
The recording can be paused and resumed and once you finish recording, the program will display a simple editing allows you to preview the recording and delete every frame is not necessary.
The downside is: Because ScreenToGif does not...
</description></item><item><title>Download BackUp Maker Pro 8.316</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Sep 2025 17:57:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-backup-maker-pro-480.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-backup-maker-pro-480.html
</guid><description>
BackUp Maker Pro is software backup, data recovery secure against hazards like virus attack, system error or due to the user mistakenly deleted data... BackUp Maker Pro security of your files regularly so that in case of emergency, data your computer you can still gain access. BackUp Maker automatically stores your data and at the same time provide intuitive operation: select your data, optionally set the automation to backup according to schedules, select the destination and immediately,...
</description></item><item><title>Download NewFileTime 8.11</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Sep 2025 17:56:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-newfiletime-1918.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-newfiletime-1918.html
</guid><description>
NewFileTime is a small utility independence allows you to change date modified, Created and Accessed of any file. You can modify the dates for one or multiple files, even entire folder structures at the same time. The date can be changed to a date and time specific or you can choose to make each file "older" or "younger," according to a certain number of days.
NewFileTime - edit time files
You can add files simply via Drag and Drop or by import from a folder. In any case, it opens...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinPE 11-10-8 Sergei Strelec 2025.09.29</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Sep 2025 17:56:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winpe-10-8-sergei-strelec-8027.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winpe-10-8-sergei-strelec-8027.html
</guid><description>
WinPE 11-10-8 Sergei Strelec is a Windows 11, 10 and 8 PE boot disk for computer maintenance, hard disks and partitions, disk and partition backup and restore, computer diagnostics, data recovery, installation Windows.
Assembly components include:
	WinPE 11 x64
	WinPE 10 x64
	WinPE 10 x86
	WinPE 8 x86
	WinPE 8 x86 (Native)
System Requirements:
1. RAM 1 GB or more
2. PC can boot from CD/DVD or USB drive.
</description></item><item><title>Download reaConverter Pro 8.0.138</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Sep 2025 17:55:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html
</guid><description>
reaConverter Pro is software image processing feature with batch conversion and image editing periodically becomes simple. eaConverter also provide command line utilities allow you to process images automatically, thus helping you shorten the time for other work.
reaConverter Pro integrated powerful tool of Uber with many great features. It provides advanced solutions to process and adjust images. Management of the conversion process the base image with the latest version of...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Downloader 9.17.7</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Sep 2025 17:55:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html
</guid><description>
YTD Youtube Downloader is an application that reliable and intuitive, allowing you to quickly download YouTube videos and save them to your computer. You can also convert the media files to the format desired video or extract audio streams and save separately. YTD Youtube Downloader lets you save your favorite clips of yourself from Youtube, Facebook, Vimeo and Dailymotion to your desktop. The software supports URLS from many web site hosting, multimedia and allows you to download desired...
</description></item><item><title>Download VidCoder 12.10 + Portable</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Sep 2025 17:54:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vidcoder-534.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vidcoder-534.html
</guid><description>
VidCoder is software to convert movies to MKV and MP4, as well as extract video content from DVDS and Blu-ray. This is a software utility to help people extract the video content from the BD and DVD as well as convert the clips specific to MKV and MP4.
VidCoder has an interface that includes a clear design, including a menu bar, several buttons and a panel to display the queue. The file can be added with the help of the file browser or drag and drop-out.
Features VidCoder
	VidCoder...
</description></item><item><title>Download Windows Repair Toolbox 3.0.4.8</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Sep 2025 17:54:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-repair-toolbox-2225.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-repair-toolbox-2225.html
</guid><description>
Windows Repair Toolbox is a development that will solve almost all the problems with Windows. There is a mobile version in the repository, after the folder launch of it will be created in program files, but after you close it, everything will be deleted.
Windows Repair Toolbox - diagnose the problem on windows
Utilities can diagnose and solve a number of problems about your video Windows at the same time. All the tools are divided into categories. In The tools section, you can view a...
</description></item><item><title>Download Dassault Systemes DraftSight Enterprise Plus 2025 SP4</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Sep 2025 17:53:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-draftsight-enterprise-plus-4057.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-draftsight-enterprise-plus-4057.html
</guid><description>
DraftSight Enterprise Plus solution is a 2D and 3D CAD feature-rich for architects, engineers and suppliers of construction services, as well as user professional CAD designers, educators and hobbyists. Options, options and tools consistent with the needs and specific interests of you. Freedom of design is really lets you work the way you want to work. It is the ability to easily switch from 2D sketch to 3D models and back to optimize and maximize the design.
DraftSight Enterprise Plus...
</description></item><item><title>Download Desktop Info 3.21.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Sep 2025 17:53:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktop-info-11667.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktop-info-11667.html
</guid><description>
Desktop Info is a free application for Windows that allows users to display system information and important parameters directly on their desktop. This application provides a convenient way to monitor parameters such as CPU, memory, hard drive, network, and many other information that users want to monitor continuously.
With a simple and easy-to-use interface, Desktop Info allows users to customize the information displayed according to their wishes. Users can select...
</description></item><item><title>Download AnyTrans for iOS 8.9.12.20250928</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Sep 2025 17:52:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anytrans-for-ios-755.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anytrans-for-ios-755.html
</guid><description>
AnyTrans for iOS is content manager essential fully managed iPhone, Android and content of your cloud. Including all mobile devices, all cloud drives from your iPhone, iPad, iPod touch to phones and tablets. From local disk to cloud storage. AnyTrans has protected them all, providing you convenient management for all data and your files, regardless of whether they are stored where.
AnyTrans is the one stop solution to meet all the management needs of your data. For the first time, you can...
</description></item><item><title>Download AppCheck Anti-Ransomware 3.1.43.10</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Sep 2025 17:52:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-appcheck-anti-ransomware-1776.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-appcheck-anti-ransomware-1776.html
</guid><description>
"AppCheck Anti-Virus" is a software that is designed to prevent attacks ransomware file encryption of your files. Program monitoring your system and automatically blocked most of the software ransomware encryption while backup the original files in your folder are protected by drivers, lets you undo any changes have been made.
"AppCheck Anti-Virus" - Blocked Attack Ransomware
Other features include a warning if execution is blocked, automatic updates, the free Version will protect your...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sure Cuts A Lot Pro 6.077</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Sep 2025 17:51:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sure-cuts-a-lot-pro-2614.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sure-cuts-a-lot-pro-2614.html
</guid><description>
Sure Cuts A Lot Pro is this program offers you a set of drawing tools and you get a work environment, comprehensive, where you can create interesting shapes and cut them by a special electronic. The intelligent combination of fonts OpenType and TrueType in your system, in conjunction with the library program rich text, photos, and other input, will help you create everything you can imagine.
This app is compatible with hundreds of font style and provide support for various cutting...
</description></item><item><title>Download 4KSoftware 4K Downloader 5.18.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Sep 2025 17:51:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-downloader-3858.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-downloader-3858.html
</guid><description>
4K Downloader is a Windows application small but powerful to download and convert video in 4K and 8K Ultra HD from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion and thousands of other video-based websites. It speeds up your download by up to 5 times. Consider that most smart phones, TVS, computers, and tablets all support the high definition format, don't be surprised when many users want to enjoy quality content on their device. 4K Downloader is a lightweight software designed to help you grab videos...
</description></item><item><title>Download App Builder 2025.34</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Sep 2025 17:50:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-app-builder-241.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-app-builder-241.html
</guid><description>
App Builder is a software application developer to help create and design apps, HTML5, web app, web app PWA on both platforms mobile and desktop. App Builder is professional software supports users to create the program HTML5 without writing code. It is very easy to use, suitable with all users who lack of professional knowledge in the field of programming and application design.
App Builder brings to 22 different themes that users can use to design for your app. You can choose 1 or a...
</description></item><item><title>Download Psiphon 186.20250928</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Sep 2025 17:50:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-psiphon-7347.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-psiphon-7347.html
</guid><description>
Psiphon is a firewall bypass tool by Psiphon Inc. Uses VPN, SSH and HTTP Proxy technology to give you uncensored access to Internet content. Your Psiphon app automatically learns about new hotspots to maximize your chances of bypassing censorship.
The way the software works is that Psiphon constantly changes the proxy, so the user's IP address is also constantly changing, the server will not detect the user's real address, so you can feel free. roof. access to websites and software...
</description></item><item><title>Download AppleWin 1.31.0.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Sep 2025 17:49:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-applewin-10785.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-applewin-10785.html
</guid><description>
AppleWin is a full-featured emulator that supports various Apple II clones and models. Supports a variety of peripheral cards and video display modes (e.g. NTSC, RGB); and has an extensive built-in symbolic debugger.
Supported peripheral cards and additional hardware:
	Mockingboard, Phasor and SAM sound cards
	Disk II interface for floppy drives
	Hard disk controller
	Super Serial Card (SSC)
	Parallel printer card
	Mouse interface
	Apple IIe and RamWorks III 80-column expanded text...
</description></item><item><title>Download Argente Registry Cleaner 4.0.3.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Sep 2025 17:49:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-argente-registry-cleaner-13814.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-argente-registry-cleaner-13814.html
</guid><description>
Argente Registry Cleaner is a free Windows utility designed to scan, clean and repair invalid or obsolete entries in the Windows Registry, helping to improve system stability and performance. This utility quickly analyzes the entire Registry for errors such as invalid entries left by uninstalled programs, missing keys, broken references, and other junk that can cause system crashes.
Key Features:
	Fast and Thorough Scan: Provides multiple scan modes including Safe (fastest), Normal...
</description></item><item><title>Download Argente System Repair 1.0.2.8</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Sep 2025 17:49:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-argente-system-repair-13813.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-argente-system-repair-13813.html
</guid><description>
Argente System Repair is a lightweight utility designed to diagnose and fix common Windows system problems. It scans your system to identify errors in operating system components, file systems, installation files, and other system components, and then applies targeted fixes to resolve these problems. The tool provides different scan modes, including simple scan, recommended scan, and custom scan, allowing users to customize the repair process according to their needs.
System Repair...
</description></item><item><title>Download GnuCash 5.13</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Sep 2025 17:48:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gnucash-1312.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gnucash-1312.html
</guid><description>
GnuCash is an accounting application, powerful financial is designed to help you to perform all tasks related to finance. The application can be used to track all activities of your finances from bank accounts, shares and income and other costs.
GnuCash supports databases including PostgreSQL, SQLite3 and MySQL (XML backend). Note, memory is the default XML file is compressed and use the SQL database replace is optional. Note, memory is the default XML file is compressed and use the SQL...
</description></item><item><title>Download GiliSoft File Lock Pro 15.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Sep 2025 17:48:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-file-lock-pro-858.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-file-lock-pro-858.html
</guid><description>
GiliSoft File Lock Pro is program encryption software file power can lock and hide fast and secure files, folders and drives, and it can use AES 256 bit encryption (encryption standard is the government of The United States apply) protect your files located on HDD or any portable media drive such as USB.
GiliSoft File Lock Pro - file encryption
Features of GiliSoft File Lock Pro
	GiliSoft File Lock Pro can hide the folders and drives of your private
	The file / folder / drive locking...
</description></item><item><title>Download Glary Tracks Eraser 6.0.1.26</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Sep 2025 17:47:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-tracks-eraser-1342.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-tracks-eraser-1342.html
</guid><description>
Glary Tracks Eraser is security software privacy when browsing the web, allows you to delete all traces of network access and trace number, including browser cache, cookies, the website is already open, the URL has been entered, the document new mines, temporary files,... Glary Tracks Eraser that helps you free up space in hard disk drives, scan entire junk files in the drive with the speed of processing is extremely fast. Data deleted by Glary Tracks Eraser will not be able to restore,...
</description></item></channel></rss>