<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 18:03:45 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 18:03:45 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Revo Registry Cleaner Pro 2.0.7</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 20:45:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-revo-registry-cleaner-pro-12750.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-revo-registry-cleaner-pro-12750.html
</guid><description>
Revo Registry Cleaner Pro provides complete solutions to advanced Registry cleaning. It uses more than 15 separate scanning categories to identify and completely delete invaluable and redundant registry items that can slow down your system performance. You can customize the cleaning process by specifying the items including and the main exclusion, allowing a more appropriate approach to maintain the integrity of the registration book. In addition, Revo Registry Cleaner has four flexible...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinRAR 7.20 Final</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 20:43:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winrar-127.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winrar-127.html
</guid><description>
WinRAR is a compression utility data advanced supports multiple formats including RAR, ZIP, CAB, ARJ, LZH, ACE, TAR, GZip, UUE, ISO, BZIP2, Z and 7-Zip. It allows you to create, organize and manage archives in a comfortable way and quickly. WinRAR naturally are is a leading software currently in the compression and decompression of data. With the enhanced algorithm is applied, the software allows users to compress bulk files in different formats into synthetic 1 single file to facilitate...
</description></item><item><title>Download GiliSoft Video Editor Pro 18.5</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 20:42:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-video-editor-pro-7065.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-video-editor-pro-7065.html
</guid><description>
GiliSoft Video Editor Pro is the pro version that makes it easy to edit your video files in your own Hollywood style with stunning cinematic quality. With GiliSoft Video Editor Pro you simply select your own video clip, edit it with titles, text, filters, overlays, effects and your videos will come to life.
This software allows you to preview the video before, during and at the end so you can make sure your movie looks good from start to finish, and then export the project file as: MP4,...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDF Annotator 10.0.0.1008</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 20:42:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-annotator-178.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-annotator-178.html
</guid><description>
PDF Annotator software user open any PDF file and add annotations, using the mouse or pen Tablet PC, directly on the Page of the PDF file. PDF Annotator allows users to perform editing operations on PDF files such as: add notes, edit signature, highlight, insert images or text... From the this useful tool, you can completely modify PDF files as you like in order to meet the different work.
PDF Annotator
With the PDF Annotator the document has annotations can then be saved directly back...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ashampoo Burning Studio 26.0.4</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 20:41:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-burning-studio-266.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-burning-studio-266.html
</guid><description>
Ashampoo Burning Studio 19 recording files, movies and music to any disc CD, DVD, or Blu-ray any. It's easy, fast and secure! Record data, create audio CDS, create backups, or create your own movie - the possibilities are endless! Even the senior project as a DVD video with the menu and the scene selection screen is only a few minutes. Get the total solution for the drive recorder of you!
Ashampoo Burning Studio
Features Ashampoo Burning Studio
	Fast, clear and powerful - now with...
</description></item><item><title>Download Psiphon 186.20260204</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 20:40:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-psiphon-7347.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-psiphon-7347.html
</guid><description>
Psiphon is a firewall bypass tool by Psiphon Inc. Uses VPN, SSH and HTTP Proxy technology to give you uncensored access to Internet content. Your Psiphon app automatically learns about new hotspots to maximize your chances of bypassing censorship.
The way the software works is that Psiphon constantly changes the proxy, so the user's IP address is also constantly changing, the server will not detect the user's real address, so you can feel free. roof. access to websites and software...
</description></item><item><title>Download AssistMyTeam PDF Converter 7.2.301.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 20:40:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-assistmyteam-pdf-converter-7856.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-assistmyteam-pdf-converter-7856.html
</guid><description>
AssistMyTeam PDF Converter is a software to convert files to PDF, it is used to save all kinds of documents, such as Word, Excel, PowerPoint, web pages, images, emails. or even ZIP to PDF files. Best of all, Windows Explorer Shell Integration makes this significantly easier, with one-click instant PDF.
Features of AssistMyTeam PDF Converter
	Convert different types of documents to PDF quickly.
	Support to convert 120+ file types to PDF.
	Save the compressed ZIP file to PDF.
	Convert...
</description></item><item><title>Download AweEraser Enterprise 5.3</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 20:40:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aweeraser-449.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aweeraser-449.html
</guid><description>
AweEraser Enterprise is specialized software used to delete data securely and permanently to prevent the possibility of recovery by the other software. As you know, on the computer if there is data that we don't want to let others see and want to delete it. But if you only deleted according to the conventional, then others can easily recover them. So you need to use to AweEraser Enterprise, a software to delete data permanently and can't be recovered.
AweEraser Enterprise has a modern...
</description></item><item><title>Download True Burner 10.7</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 20:39:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-true-burner-3876.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-true-burner-3876.html
</guid><description>
True burner is software burn and copy CD, DVD, Blu-ray free. It is ideal for users wishing to record the disc usually as backup, creating or copying data, audio, MP3 music, DVD-Video and burn disc images. Free, easy to install, it allows you to save your files to disc quickly and provides flexible interface, clean to help you complete the task scored much faster.
True Burner - Burn and copy CD, DVD
The features of True Burner
	Free for personal use and commercial
	File size install...
</description></item><item><title>Download Magoshare Data Recovery Enterprise 4.6 Technician / AdvancedPE</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 20:39:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-magoshare-data-recovery-enterprise-5838.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-magoshare-data-recovery-enterprise-5838.html
</guid><description>
Magoshare Data Recovery Enterprise provides comprehensive data recovery solutions to restore ease and complete data lost due to various disasters. The deep scan technology will scan the hard drive/device and find every file that can be restored in the hard drive/device. You'll completely retrieve all the missing files. This comprehensive hard drive data recovery software provides a safe and effective 100% solution to fully recover lost data from the hard drive or storage...
</description></item><item><title>Download MusConv 4.10.452 Lifetime</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 20:38:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html
</guid><description>
MusConv transfers playlists, albums, followed artists and liked songs across a variety of services – Spotify, Apple Music, Amazon Music, YouTube, YouTube Music, iTunes, Deezer, Tidal, SoundCloud, Pandora and more 125 music services!
Features of MusConv Ultimate
	Transfer playlists, albums, followed artists and liked tracks between over 125 music servicesManage playlists (Delete, Merge, Split, Copy...)
	More than 125 music services supported
	Access DAILY updated music charts on...
</description></item><item><title>Download O&amp;amp;O DiskCommander Premium 5.1.1020</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 20:37:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-diskcommander-premium-14518.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-diskcommander-premium-14518.html
</guid><description>
DiskCommander is a digital detective that helps you solve memory-intensive problems – an advanced analysis tool that helps you understand and optimize your storage structure. With just a few clicks, you'll get a clear, reliable overview of disk usage, along with insights into your hard drive, partitions, and file systems like NTFS or FAT. It's perfect not only for freeing up space but also for diagnosing complex data storage layouts and tricky allocation issues.
Designed with a...
</description></item><item><title>Download Revo Registry Cleaner Free 2.0.7 + Portable</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 20:37:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-revo-registry-cleaner-free-12717.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-revo-registry-cleaner-free-12717.html
</guid><description>
Revo Registry Cleaner Free is a powerful tool designed to clean, tune and optimize the Windows Registry. Explore the powerful Registry Cleaner with over 15 scanning categories to find and remove invalid and unnecessary Registry entries. Customize your cleaning routine with custom key inclusions/exclusions and 4 different deep scan modes.
In addition, it also supports custom backups for user-specified keys as well as full Registry backups providing peace of mind as they ensure the safety...
</description></item><item><title>Download Yellow Leads Extractor 9.3.3</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 20:36:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yellow-leads-extractor-3729.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yellow-leads-extractor-3729.html
</guid><description>
Yellow Leads Extractor is the software that allows users to make 100% custom search in the browser. When you have this program then you don't need to do more work to retrieve information from the yellow pages. You just need to enter the category and location. After entering the information when you will click on the option data get then all the information will be extracted.
Yellow Leads Extractor - custom Search on the browser
The features of the Yellow Leads Extractor
	You can save...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wing FTP Server Corporate 8.1.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 20:36:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wing-ftp-server-corporate-2752.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wing-ftp-server-corporate-2752.html
</guid><description>
Wing FTP Server Corporate is a highly functional, easy and safe can be used in the operating system Windows, Linux, Mac and Solaris are used. The software supports a number of file transfer protocol such as FTP, HTTP, FTPS, HTTPS and SFTP. Wing FTP Server provides web-based interface to manage the server at any time. You can also get performance server and the online and even send email notifications about various events happening on the server.
Management server multi-function
Wing FTP...
</description></item><item><title>Download VidMasta 30.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 20:36:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vidmasta-6803.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vidmasta-6803.html
</guid><description>
VidMasta is a free and open source online movie downloading and viewing software. It allows you to easily watch or download movie/TV titles in any format with just a few clicks. VidMasta gives full control over downloading, searching, reading about, previewing and watching any movie or TV show title currently being shared online.
In addition, VidMasta provides you with solid anonymity through automatic filtering of untrusted IPs, the use of proxies and encryption, as well as the "Best...
</description></item><item><title>Download Icecream Photo Editor Pro 1.53</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 20:35:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-icecream-photo-editor-8993.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-icecream-photo-editor-8993.html
</guid><description>
Icecream Photo Editor is a software application that allows users to edit and enhance their photos. The program provides many tools and features for editing, such as adjusting brightness and contrast, cropping and resizing, adding text, applying filters and effects, and more.
Some of the key features of Icecream Photo Editor include the ability to work with a variety of image formats, including JPG, BMP, and PNG, as well as the ability to export images in a variety of formats, such as...
</description></item><item><title>Download yt-dlp 2026.02.04</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 20:35:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-dlp-6802.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-dlp-6802.html
</guid><description>
yt-dlp is a youtube-dl branch based on youtube-dlc currently not working. The main focus of this project is the addition of new features and patches while still updating the original project.
</description></item><item><title>Download Magoshare AweClone Enterprise 3.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 20:34:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-magoshare-aweclone-enterprise-6913.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-magoshare-aweclone-enterprise-6913.html
</guid><description>
AweClone is a reliable, powerful and fast program for hard disk cloning. AweClone provides state-of-the-art technology to clone hard disks, system disks and external devices easily and securely. You can easily transfer your data and content from one hard drive to another without any loss. You just need to select the resource hard drive and the destination hard drive. After that, AweClone will move all the content from the hard disk resources to the destination hard disk without any...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sante PACS Server 4.4.5</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 20:34:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sante-pacs-server-7541.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sante-pacs-server-7541.html
</guid><description>
Sante PACS Server is an HTTP (web) server for DICOM files and a CD/DVD Burn and Print server that offers high performance and reliability at an affordable price. It provides connectivity to all DICOM methods (CT, MR, US, CR, NM, XA, MG, DX, etc.). Reviewing of DICOM images can be done using the Sante PACS Viewer (the system's built-in, full-featured DICOM Viewer). The built-in web server can be used as a free cloud server for DICOM files!
Tools of Sante PACS Server
	The Migration Tool...
</description></item><item><title>Download Rainbow Analyst add-in Professional 26.02.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 20:34:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rainbow-analyst-add-in-professional-11122.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rainbow-analyst-add-in-professional-11122.html
</guid><description>
Rainbow Analyst add-in Professional is a powerful tool designed to enhance data analysis in Microsoft Excel. This add-on provides many advanced features and visualizations to help users gain valuable insights from their data.
One of the key features of Rainbow Analyst is the ability to create color-coded reports and charts. Users can assign specific colors to different data values, making it easier to identify patterns, trends, and outliers. This visual representation of data enhances...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sante PACS Server PG 4.4.5</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 20:33:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sante-pacs-server-pg-7540.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sante-pacs-server-pg-7540.html
</guid><description>
Sante PACS Server PG is an HTTP server (web) for DICOM files and a recorder and In CD/DVD with high performance and reliability. It provides connectivity with all the DICOM (CT, MR, US, CR, NM, XA, MG, DX, etc.). The review of the DICOM image can be done with the Sante PACS Viewer.
Integrated web servers can be used as a free cloud server for DICOM files!
</description></item><item><title>Download Google Chrome 144.0.7559.133</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 17:03:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-chrome-1012.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-chrome-1012.html
</guid><description>
Google Chrome web browser is the most used today. Support surf the web, listen to music, watch movies, play web game effective no jerky lag with the internet connection stable. When you are surfing the web or performing an important task, whether it is operation big or small, work or entertainment, then Chrome has the smart features and the speed you need to make, create and explore on the net.
The latest version of Google Chrome is the third 114. But we are providing for users Google...
</description></item><item><title>Download CapCut PC 8.0.1.3366</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 17:03:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capcut-pc-9995.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capcut-pc-9995.html
</guid><description>
CapCut PC is a simple video editing tool that you can freely use anywhere. You can create videos on your browser, desktop and laptop, or on your phone. Versatile editing, magical AI tools, team collaboration, and built-in assets. Create videos in a whole new way.
You can edit videos based on editing the timeline, in the process you can add different elements and effects to the video to give the best effect to your work. It is a simple and intuitive set of editing tools and effects that...
</description></item><item><title>Download Find.Same.Images.OK 5.91</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 17:02:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-find-same-images-ok-113.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-find-same-images-ok-113.html
</guid><description>
Find.Same.Images.OK lets find the images identical or similar in the folder of you, even if they were to rotate, change size or change.
Just select one or more folders that you want the program to scan and it will return a list of all the duplicate images or very similar, as indicated by the percent the same and the preview is built.Then, you can select images from the list and then copy, move or delete them.
Find.Same.Images.OK
In addition, there are other options smart option allows...
</description></item></channel></rss>