<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 10:31:38 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 10:31:38 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Revo Uninstaller Pro 5.4.7</title><pubDate> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 21:00:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-revo-uninstaller-pro-35.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-revo-uninstaller-pro-35.html
</guid><description>
Revo Uninstaller Pro is software that helps you to uninstall unnecessary software and easily remove unwanted programs installed on your personal computer. Revo Uninstaller Pro gives you the convenience to optimize your device, as well as get rid of all the program files you don't need and slow down your computer.
Traces such as registry entries or program files and folders may remain. Now with Revo Uninstaller Pro, you can be sure that you can clean your system of all these residues,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Revo Uninstaller Pro Portable 5.4.7</title><pubDate> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:59:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-revo-uninstaller-pro-portable-4370.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-revo-uninstaller-pro-portable-4370.html
</guid><description>
Revo Uninstaller Pro Portable helps you to uninstall the program and delete the unwanted program is installed on your PC the easy way! Even if you have problems uninstalling and cannot uninstall them from control panel, Programs and features of Windows. Revo Uninstaller is an alternative agile and stronger for optional Programs and features of Windows. It has the very powerful feature to uninstall and remove programs.
Revo Uninstaller Pro Portable - Uninstall software
With complex...
</description></item><item><title>Download Olympia Graphic Design 1.7.7.60</title><pubDate> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:59:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-olympia-graphic-design-9607.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-olympia-graphic-design-9607.html
</guid><description>
Olympia Graphic Design is an intuitive yet powerful illustration and design software application. With Olympia Graphic Design, you'll have access to advanced tools, filters, effects, and more, giving you the arsenal you need to take your projects to the next level.
Olympia Graphic Design comes with 2000 royalty-free vector graphics and images to complete your work. You can even access over 100 professional design ideas to inspire and motivate you! It allows users to create flyers,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Musify 5.3.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:58:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musify-4422.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musify-4422.html
</guid><description>
Musify is the convert YouTube Music best can download music from more than 1000 website share music to listen to offline without reducing sound quality. Such as: YouTube, Spotify, SoundCloud, Facebook, Instragram, and more. Easily convert music files mp3 to iPhone, iPad, iPod, Samsung and iOS devices and other Android. High speed and high quality. Musify is a YouTube converter is very efficient and fast, support format converting YouTube to MP3. You can batch convert mp3 files at the same...
</description></item><item><title>Download Glary Malware Hunter PRO 1.212.0.845</title><pubDate> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:58:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-malware-hunter-pro-77.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-malware-hunter-pro-77.html
</guid><description>
Glary Malware Hunter PRO - detection of file malware on your computer and delete dangerous content, allowing you to run on-demand scan of the area, important system or specific files. As suggested by its name, Malware Hunter is designed to find and remove the files and components potential danger on your computer, keep it out of the virus and the type of threat other.
Glary Malware Hunter PRO - perfect protection of your equipment
Features Glary Malware Hunter PRO
- Scan ultrasound...
</description></item><item><title>Download ResumeMaker Professional Deluxe 20.4.1.7050</title><pubDate> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:58:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-resumemaker-professional-deluxe-720.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-resumemaker-professional-deluxe-720.html
</guid><description>
ResumeMaker Professional Deluxe is a software that support creating a resume professional demonstrating experience, skills, and your ability to apply for the position your work and share it on the social media network to get better jobs.
ResumeMaker Professional Deluxe - Create resume, professional resume
The features of ResumeMaker Professional Deluxe
	Choose from 60 styles and custom fonts, graphics and colors to reflect the skills and unique experience of you.
	Get the script...
</description></item><item><title>Download Glarysoft Malware Hunter Pro 1.212.0.845</title><pubDate> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:50:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glarysoft-malware-hunter-pro-235.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glarysoft-malware-hunter-pro-235.html
</guid><description>
Glarysoft Malware Hunter capabilities, comprehensive protection against threats, data protection and privacy, ensure the computer is no longer virus. It allows you against many types of viruses, trojans with the ability to super fast scanning to detect and remove the malware quickly. Glarysoft Malware Hunter has a simple design of the interface, but the pace of new work is the most important problem of this software.
Features Glarysoft Malware Hunter Pro
	Automatically search, detect,...
</description></item><item><title>Download iDefender 5.4.1.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:50:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idefender-13959.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idefender-13959.html
</guid><description>
iDefender is an advanced security solution designed for the home, providing both a High-Performance Intrusion Prevention System (HIPS) and Real-Time Endpoint Detection and Response (EDR). This integrated system protects against potential threats, ensuring the safety and integrity of your devices by proactively monitoring and responding to suspicious activity.
Why iDefender?
Ransomware Prevention
	Detects and blocks ransomware in real time to protect important files from malicious...
</description></item><item><title>Download PhotoCHAT AI 0.4.0.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:49:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photochat-ai-14302.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photochat-ai-14302.html
</guid><description>
PhotoCHAT AI is a Windows app that instantly searches your entire photo library using AI, allowing you to quickly recall and rediscover memories from your photo collection with natural language search features. The app runs entirely on your computer, no uploading, no account and no registration required, prioritizing privacy and ease of use.
Features of PhotoCHAT AI
	Natural Language Search: Describe the moment in plain English and get instant results.
	Voice Search: Just say your...
</description></item><item><title>Download Pazu StreamGet All-In-One Video Downloader 2.9.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:48:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pazu-streamget-all-in-one-video-downloader-12037.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pazu-streamget-all-in-one-video-downloader-12037.html
</guid><description>
StreamGet All-In-One Video Downloader is the ultimate downloading solution for you. It supports downloading any movies and shows from the most popular streaming sites including Netflix, Prime Video, Disney Plus, Max, Hulu, and Apple TV Plus. The downloader is continuously updated to support more platforms in the future.
Download movies and shows from various streaming platforms to MP4/MKV on your Windows device and enjoy them anywhere you want.
Features of Pazu StreamGet All-In-One...
</description></item><item><title>Download Olympia Logo Creation 1.7.7.60</title><pubDate> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:48:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-olympia-logo-creation-9609.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-olympia-logo-creation-9609.html
</guid><description>
Olympia Logo Creation is an ideal solution for creating a logo for your business, brand or event with thousands of templates available to choose from. A good logo will be a visual representation of your company or business. Easily create your logo from scratch or modify any professionally designed logo template into your own unique design. Modify colors, fonts, graphics, etc until you are completely satisfied and you have your perfect logo.
Very unique built-in vector graphics and tools...
</description></item><item><title>Download Markdown Monster 4.1.4.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:47:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-markdown-monster-2640.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-markdown-monster-2640.html
</guid><description>
Markdown Monster is the edit and view Markdown allows you to edit Markdown by syntax highlighting and fast text input. Live preview can collapse, synchronized allows you to see the output of when you enter. You can easily embed images, links, emoticons and code in text form or by using the support UI lightness of we to simplify many operations. You can also paste and drag images directly into the editor.
Markdown Monster is a solution comprehensive software designed to solve almost any...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaMonkey Gold 2024.2.1.3209 RC2</title><pubDate> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:47:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediamonkey-gold-231.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediamonkey-gold-231.html
</guid><description>
MediaMonkey Gold is music manager and music player multimedia for the music collection and iPod users. MediaMonkey lists the audio file of you as CD, OGG, WMA, MPC, FLAC, APE, WAV and MP3 and includes the edit smart card and an automatic file and folder to arrange your music library.
MediaMonkey Gold also has CD ripper, CD / DVD Burner, and audio converter for saving music, and manual or editor list automatically to create mixed music.
Features MediaMonkey Gold
	Automatically find...
</description></item><item><title>Download SysGauge Ultimate 12.5.18 + Pro + Server</title><pubDate> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:46:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sysgauge-1296.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sysgauge-1296.html
</guid><description>
SysGauge Ultimate / Server is software that provides the ability to display the chart type monitoring system, hosted report monitoring systems and results of monitoring system to a number of standard formats including HTML, PDF, Excel, text, CSV and XML. Advanced users and IT administrators are provided the ability to save recurring reports system status, set a limit specified by the user for the timer monitoring the system and then displayed error message or alert, play sound...
</description></item><item><title>Download AI Video to SRT 1.1.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 17:56:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ai-video-to-srt-14564.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ai-video-to-srt-14564.html
</guid><description>
VideoToSRT uses advanced on-premise artificial intelligence (AI) to convert video and audio files into SRT, VTT, and TXT formats. No cloud upload required, no registration needed, and absolute privacy guaranteed for your content.
Features of AI Video to SRT
	Offline speech-to-text conversion using AI technology.
	Batch processing queue for multiple files in sequence.
	NVIDIA GPU acceleration for ultra-fast speeds.
	Supports input formats MP4, MOV, MKV, MP3, WAV, and M4A.
	Export to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Glary Utilities Pro 6.38.0.42</title><pubDate> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 17:25:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-utilities-pro-76.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-utilities-pro-76.html
</guid><description>
Glary Utilities Pro is a collection of tools and system utilities to fix, speed up, maintain and protect your computer. Glary Utilities Pro allows you to clean junk files, system downloads, as well as the subscriptions are not valid and Internet traces (that support the plug-in more for the 45+ program outside). You can also manage and delete add-ons of the browser, analyze the use of disk and find the file duplicate.
Glary Utilities Pro - optimized system
Key features Glary Utilities...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare UniConverter 17.2.1.497</title><pubDate> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 17:25:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-uniconverter-4808.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-uniconverter-4808.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare UniConverter ( old name is Wondershare Video Converter Ultimate) which allows you to convert the video format. You can cut, splice, move, or add effects, subtitles a easy way. When using software you easily cut, splice, move, as well as add the effects, the subtitles to the video.... Or can switch the clods SD, HD video to any format popular for use with iPod (Classic, Nano and Touch), iPhone, Apple TV, Zune, PSP, Pocket PC...
Wondershare UniConverter helps convert formats...
</description></item><item><title>Download Directory Opus Pro 13.21.2 Beta</title><pubDate> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 17:24:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-opus-pro-779.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-opus-pro-779.html
</guid><description>
Directory Opus Pro is a software replacement for Explorer with traditional strength and function more than any manager other files. Directory Opus Pro full support for high DPI screen (for example 4K and 5K) with the rename dialog is redesigned, with new features. Besides being a recording macro only allows you to perform mass renaming complex that don't need regular expressions. In addition, Directory Opus Pro also enhances the ability to script.Better handling of renaming recursive and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare Filmora 15.2.5.17803</title><pubDate> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 17:13:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-filmora-2025-31.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-filmora-2025-31.html
</guid><description>
In early November 2020 Wondershare came up with a new version called Wondershare Filmora 13 with two new ways to edit: Action Cam Tool (Lens distortion correction, Clean up your audio, Control speed new) and Instant Cutter (Cut or merge clips quickly, Export instantly).
Wondershare Filmora 13  allows you to add your favorite tracks to your videos, creating a more stylish, romantic film reel, with a rich music library besides Users can manually add their favorite songs to the editing...
</description></item><item><title>Download Absolute Uninstaller 6.0.1.19</title><pubDate> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 17:12:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-absolute-uninstaller-6676.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-absolute-uninstaller-6676.html
</guid><description>
Absolute Uninstaller is a free software that provides a more friendly way with users to delete unneeded applications and improve your computer efficiency. With Absolute Uninstaller, you can remove multiple programs at the same time, search for the app, delete the entries or restore them, change the program attribute, check the program support information, see the command line, automatically correct the unvalid entries, backup and restore the installation information and publish the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Glary Quick Startup 6.0.1.19</title><pubDate> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 17:12:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-startup-manager-1340.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-startup-manager-1340.html
</guid><description>
Quick StartUp is software that helps you track and control programs and automated services that run when the computer system starts. StartUp Manager brings a simple solution to removing programs that do not need to run with your system and your system resources.
Startup Delayer is also software that allows you to monitor and control startup processes with windows, from which optimizing and reducing the launch time of the PC. When you use this software, users easily shut down the...
</description></item><item><title>Download LINQPad Premium 9.6.6</title><pubDate> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 17:12:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-linqpad-premium-7181.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-linqpad-premium-7181.html
</guid><description>
LINQPad is a software utility targeting .NET Framework and .NET Core development. It is used to interactively query SQL databases using LINQ, as well as to write C# code interactively without an IDE. LINQPad will be where C# code can be rapidly prototyped outside of Visual Studio. It can also be used to code in VB.NET, SQL and F#.
With LINQPad, you can interactively query databases using a modern query language: LINQ. LINQPad includes a tool optimized for on-the-fly context creation of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Dll Export Finder 1.5.9</title><pubDate> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 17:11:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dll-export-finder-11579.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dll-export-finder-11579.html
</guid><description>
Dll Export Finder will find functions exported by dll in a specified directory. This is the tool you need if you don't remember which dll contains the export function you're looking for. Created from a standard window with a classic interface, the interface allows you to create a scan scope by including any drive or folder, apply file filters by type as well as enter the required file name. take into account.
The results reveal the function, filename, and undecorated filename, along...
</description></item><item><title>Download LieberLieber Software LemonTree 4.2.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 17:10:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lieberlieber-software-lemontree-12724.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lieberlieber-software-lemontree-12724.html
</guid><description>
LieberLieber Software has expanded its LemonTree product into a comprehensive family of tools designed for model management and version control, especially for teams working with Enterprise Architect. This evolution reflects the growing demand for advanced model management solutions.
LemonTree Overview
LemonTree was launched over six years ago and has since evolved into a product family consisting of several key components:
	LemonTree.Desktop: Provides diff/merge functionality for...
</description></item><item><title>Download Chief Architect Premier X17 v27.3.2.5</title><pubDate> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 16:31:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chief-architect-premier-1243.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chief-architect-premier-1243.html
</guid><description>
Chief Architect Premier is a program that is almost ideal for interior design, successfully combined interface, user friendly, easy to use and library cliparts rich. After download at on taiwebs.com you will not need to draw each line in a long time and tedious, and is a master in the mouse only exact - thanks to the option to connect the walls, foundation and frame of home appear in just a few seconds.
Chief Architect Premier - interior design
The program Chief Architect Premier...
</description></item></channel></rss>