<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 14:17:16 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 14:17:16 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Calibre 9.3.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 20 Feb 2026 17:16:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-calibre-1669.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-calibre-1669.html
</guid><description>
Calibre  is an eBook library management application that allows you to manage your eBook collection, convert eBooks between different formats, Sync with popular e-reading devices and read your e-books with included viewer. You can sort books by author, title, date and other details, download meta information and book covers, add personalized tags and comments, and view your images in the cover display.
Collection of essential tools for adding metadata editing books or managing your...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube Downloader 3.9.18 (1902)</title><pubDate> Fri, 20 Feb 2026 17:15:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube Downloader  is a dedicated software that helps users  downloading youtube videos  Favorites on PC for offline viewing. With MediaHuman YouTube  Downloader  you can download videos from youtube website to your computer with  fast speed , with special software development technology that automatically receives videos from Websites, in addition to the ability to download videos from software websites, can convert downloaded video formats to various formats for the purpose...
</description></item><item><title>Download AVS4YOU Software AIO Installation Package 26.0.2.17</title><pubDate> Fri, 20 Feb 2026 17:14:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs4you-software-aio-installation-package-1200.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs4you-software-aio-installation-package-1200.html
</guid><description>
AVS4YOU Software AIO Installation Package is the package includes programs to work with video, audio, graphics, documents, and system cleaning. You can install as a complete package, or separate. Which program are presented: AVS Video Editor, AVS Video Converter, AVS Video ReMaker, AVS Media Player, AVS Audio Editor, AVS Audio Converter, AVS Disc Converter, AVS Image Converter, AVS Document Converter, AVS Registry Cleaner.
AVS4YOU Software AIO Installation Package - Full set of tools,...
</description></item><item><title>Download IsMyHdOK 4.48</title><pubDate> Fri, 20 Feb 2026 17:14:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ismyhdok-3225.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ismyhdok-3225.html
</guid><description>
IsMyHdOK is a small program but effective solution to easily check the performance of the volume of Windows, ex. Septum! There are many similar programs, but feel free and check free, start program IsMyHdOK. The first time you use, the program will show you screen license. Free program and license info is only displayed the first time (on each PC). Please select the Drive and Test Time and then the Start button!
IsMyHdOK - Check performance Windows
IsMyHdOK is not installed and can be...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cyberduck 9.4.0.44341</title><pubDate> Fri, 20 Feb 2026 17:13:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberduck-2637.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberduck-2637.html
</guid><description>
Cyberduck is a browser, file open-source and the client transferred to the hosting account FTP, SFTP, WebDAV, Cloud Files, Google Docs and Amazon S3. In addition to file transfers it offers features account management includes installing ACL, version group S3 configuration, Akamai and CloudFront, and more.
In addition, the Cyberduck also helps you can create bookmarks to quickly access favorite locations, edit files remotely using the editor you choose, import bookmarks from popular...
</description></item><item><title>Download Resolume Arena 7.24.2 rev 62935</title><pubDate> Fri, 20 Feb 2026 17:12:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-resolume-arena-001-760.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-resolume-arena-001-760.html
</guid><description>
Resolume Arena is software Visual Jockey for DJ help adjust, mix and match image combination screen displayed directly. Software control it from the lighting and synchronize with the DJ via SMPTE time code. Adjust the ratio and position of the clip to suit your needs. Apply effects to change the powerful interface of the video. Everything running on the card screen so you get fast performance and good image quality as possible.
Resolume Arena - software Visual Jockey for DJ
Features of...
</description></item><item><title>Download QOwnNotes 26.2.7</title><pubDate> Fri, 20 Feb 2026 17:12:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qownnotes-3178.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qownnotes-3178.html
</guid><description>
QOwnNotes is notes bookmark file simple text (GPL) open source application for GNU / Linux , Mac OS X and Windows of Patrizio Bekerle ( pbek on GitHub and IRC) (optional) activity along with the notes application of ownCloud or Nextcloud. QOwnNote store your notes as plain text files and can be synchronized with synchronization function file of ownCloud / Nextcloud. You can also use other apps like Syncthing or Dropbox . Just write out your thoughts as they appear, and edit them if...
</description></item><item><title>Download ExifTool 13.51</title><pubDate> Fri, 20 Feb 2026 17:11:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-exiftool-1685.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-exiftool-1685.html
</guid><description>
ExifTool is a library of Perl platform-independent plus a command line application for reading, writing, and editing meta information in various file types. ExifTool supports many metadata formats including EXIF , GPS , IPTC , XMP , JFIF , GeoTIFF , ICC Profile , Photoshop IRB , FlashPix , AFCP and ID3 , as well as notes of the manufacturer of many digital cameras by Canon , Casio , DJI , FLIR , FujiFilm , GE , GoPro , HP , JVC / Victor , Kodak , Leaf , Minolta / Konica-Minolta , Motorola...
</description></item><item><title>Download AntiPlagiarism.NET 4.155</title><pubDate> Fri, 20 Feb 2026 17:11:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-antiplagiarismnet-2457.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-antiplagiarismnet-2457.html
</guid><description>
AntiPlagiarism NET is software to check the originality of some given text, most people find a section of text on the Internet, often the search engines quickly put out the answer to this question. Sometimes the results can be wrong, because not all results are accurate, a hundred percent. Fortunately, there are other solutions to the problem, for example, AntiPlagiarism.NET it can help you determine the originality of some given text. Application to operate correctly, you need to install...
</description></item><item><title>Download NetSpot Unlimited Enterprise 5.1.0.707</title><pubDate> Fri, 20 Feb 2026 17:10:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-netspot-unlimited-enterprise-3952.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-netspot-unlimited-enterprise-3952.html
</guid><description>
NetSpot Unlimited Enterprise is a professional application only to the site survey, wireless, Wi-Fi and troubleshooting on Mac OS X and Windows. It is a analysis, FREE Wi-Fi. No need to be an expert network to improve the Wi-Fi at home or your office today! All you need is your MacBook running Mac OS X 10.10+, or any laptop with Windows 7/8/10 and NetSpot Unlimited Enterprise that operates on any 802.11 network.
NetSpot Unlimited Enterprise - Wifi network analysis
When working on a...
</description></item><item><title>Download AVS Audio Converter 26.0.2.17</title><pubDate> Fri, 20 Feb 2026 17:09:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs-audio-converter-1195.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs-audio-converter-1195.html
</guid><description>
AVS Audio Converter is a program that convert audio files from this format to other formats support many different formats. Support converting WAV, OGG Vorbis, MP3, MP2, Microsoft ADPCM, WMA, VOX, AAC, M4A, AMR and other audio formats. Before transition, the program determines the frequency, number of channels and other parameters of audio files. In addition, the AVS Audio Converter allows you to make settings for the format MP3 and OGG formats when converting audio files and change the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Brave Browser 1.87.190</title><pubDate> Fri, 20 Feb 2026 17:03:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-brave-browser-2874.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-brave-browser-2874.html
</guid><description>
Brave Browser is a browser based on Chromium, the basic principle is that operation fast and privacy of users. The program can block pop-up windows and other ads, plus it blocked the mechanism for monitoring the online activities of your. Therefore, you can purchase and safely browse the website you are interested in without having to worry about the fact that your activity will be monitored and then you will be shown the necessary advertising or service provider of parties...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter 3.9.18 (1902)</title><pubDate> Fri, 20 Feb 2026 17:02:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-to-mp3-converter-1744.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-to-mp3-converter-1744.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter is the software support download youtube video and convert video to mp3 format fast and most simple. MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter allows you download and convert videos from YouTube and other websites to MP3 format by pasting the YouTube URL into the application. When you paste the URL, the program will display thumbnails for videos and you have the option to customize the title information, artist and album before you begin the process of...
</description></item><item><title>Download FastFlix 6.1.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 20 Feb 2026 17:02:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fastflix-10169.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fastflix-10169.html
</guid><description>
FastFlix is a simple and user-friendly GUI for video encoding. The application has a user-friendly GUI that includes all the necessary tools and configuration options for video encoding. FastFlix provides support for a variety of formats, including MP4, MKV, MOV, M4V, AVI, DIVX, WebM, MPG, MP2, MPEG, OGG, MOV, M4P, FLV, and more. HEVC and YUV videos are also among the compatible formats.
You can choose the output format through a simple drop-down menu in the main window. FastFlix can...
</description></item><item><title>Download AVS Audio Editor 26.0.2.17</title><pubDate> Fri, 20 Feb 2026 17:01:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs-audio-editor-1194.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs-audio-editor-1194.html
</guid><description>
AVS Audio Editor is editor audio professional allows you to edit, record and encode music. The program has more than 20 effects and filters built in, including delay, flanger, chorus, reverb, filters to remove irritating sounds such as "vuvuzelas", new sound effects, strange, unique.
AVS Audio Editor - audio editing
Features of AVS Audio Editor
Save to all major formats
	Edit and save audio files into MP3, FLAC, WAV, M4A, WMA, AAC, MP2, AMR, OGG and other files with the help of AVS...
</description></item><item><title>Download Trillian 6.6 Build 13</title><pubDate> Fri, 20 Feb 2026 17:00:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-trillian-2638.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-trillian-2638.html
</guid><description>
Trillian is the chat help you sign in to more the registered name of a certain service or you can log on at the same time many services in a working window. It integrates multiple services such as Yahoo! MSN, IRC, AIM and ICQ. In addition, you can manage Email accounts, Facebook and Twitter friends - all in just one application.
Login is easy; just click on the network or the appropriate website and log in as normal. Trillian requires access your data (accepted) and post to friends...
</description></item><item><title>Download Picture Window Pro 8.0.552</title><pubDate> Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:59:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-picture-window-pro-7452.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-picture-window-pro-7452.html
</guid><description>
Picture Window Pro is a powerful image editing tool designed for serious photographers with strict creative and quality standards. Its comprehensive set of photo editing and editing tools let you control and shape every aspect of your images.
Picture Window Pro 8 is a complete rewrite of Picture Window Pro 7. It features non-destructive image editing through a novel interface based on an image tree. It also fully supports large, high-resolution displays and can be used in dual monitor...
</description></item><item><title>Download MiniMeters 1.0.23.166</title><pubDate> Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:59:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minimeters-9410.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minimeters-9410.html
</guid><description>
MiniMeters is a simple standalone sound meter application for Windows. Monitor your System Audio*, Any Input, or insert the MiniMeter Server Plug-in (VST3/AU/CLAP) at the end of your main channel in the DAW of your choice. Customize the layout in a horizontal bar (perfect for above or below the audio engine of your choice) or pop out into modules to create custom layouts.
Features of MiniMeters
	6 modules to choose from to build your perfect metering setup: Spectrogram, Waveform,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Directory Opus Pro 13.21.5 Beta</title><pubDate> Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:58:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-opus-pro-779.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-opus-pro-779.html
</guid><description>
Directory Opus Pro is a software replacement for Explorer with traditional strength and function more than any manager other files. Directory Opus Pro full support for high DPI screen (for example 4K and 5K) with the rename dialog is redesigned, with new features. Besides being a recording macro only allows you to perform mass renaming complex that don't need regular expressions. In addition, Directory Opus Pro also enhances the ability to script.Better handling of renaming recursive and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Vivaldi Browser 7.8.3925.70</title><pubDate> Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:57:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vivaldi-159.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vivaldi-159.html
</guid><description>
Vivaldi is a browser designed for users who have power and offer the option to customize high. You can choose the location of the tabs and the address bar, put the hotkeys for the common tasks and many other features. Also, Vivaldi also provides a number of improvements such as Tab Stacks to group multiple open tabs into a tab, leads to interface less cluttered. Can notes and added a screenshot of a web page while browsing, storing an attachment, and add the URL to easily sort and locate...
</description></item><item><title>Download AVS Video Converter 26.0.2.17</title><pubDate> Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:57:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs-video-converter-427.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs-video-converter-427.html
</guid><description>
AVS Video Converter is a software to convert video format, burn VCD, SVCD, DVD, editor video raise.  AVS Video Converter can convert the formats AVI, MPEG, WMV, DVD to the formats AVI, MPEG, WMV, RM, burn DVD, SVCD or VCD, package conversion, editing, effects and filters, video overlay, extract audio from video and save in a file, separate audio, extract a frame (frame) and save as images, split into segments and connect video, rotate video, more in the form of text, banners, logos,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Advanced CSV Converter 7.92</title><pubDate> Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:56:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-csv-converter-4508.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-csv-converter-4508.html
</guid><description>
Advanced CSV Converter is a conversion tool CSV to DBF, Excel (XLS, XLSX), TXT, HTML, PRG, XML, SQL, RTF. To convert a file, the program provides an interface controlled by the wizard, guides you step by step conversion. Use the wizard, you select file input, select the format and destination folder. If necessary, you can set the filter switch according to the example and select columns you want to exclude from the process. When the conversion process is started, the program will extract...
</description></item><item><title>Download ASBYTE Syncing NET 6.5.0.3979</title><pubDate> Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:55:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-asbyte-syncing-net-9468.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-asbyte-syncing-net-9468.html
</guid><description>
ASBYTE Syncing NET provides a unique and powerful Outlook, Exchange and document synchronization tool for companies and professionals from all sectors, as well as any individual need to sync multiple PCs without using a server Real-time, automatic synchronization for Outlook, Exchange and documents anytime, anywhere.
Features of ASBYTE Syncing NET
	The combination of Outlook and Files synchronization in one powerful tool for companies, professionals and individuals who need to sync...
</description></item><item><title>Download OpenVPN 2.7.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:46:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-openvpn-4245.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-openvpn-4245.html
</guid><description>
OpenVPN provides the VPN solution flexible to secure communication of your data, whether it is the right to privacy on the Internet, remote access for employees, security, IoT, or for the data center cloud. Solution VPN software, our Server can be deployed in place by standard server or virtual device or on the cloud.
OpenVPN - VPN Solution flexible
Though built with the open source OpenVPN, the solution of our additional functionality to meet the needs of business customers, the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Inno Setup Unpacker 2.2.4</title><pubDate> Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:45:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-inno-setup-unpacker-12546.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-inno-setup-unpacker-12546.html
</guid><description>
Inno Setup is a popular and reliable application that creates program installers by helping you create scripts. Extracting the installation files from their container, resulting from compiling code with Inno Setup, can only be done through self-extracting files. In other words, you need to create a self-extracting executable to shell the installation documents.
Inno Setup Unpacker can help you avoid such actions, which is especially useful because some system security protocols block...
</description></item></channel></rss>