<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 20:00:13 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 20:00:13 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download MKVToolnix 97.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 03 Jan 2026 17:01:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mkvtoolnix-1129.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mkvtoolnix-1129.html
</guid><description>
MKVToolnix is software that supports video editing, such as cutting or splicing the videos together to create a complete video and unique. MKVToolnix to help you cut the interesting scenes in the video to create the short clips impress others. In addition, you can also stitch multiple videos together to create a single video quality, get big interest from viewers.
MKVToolnix - Cut and connect video
MKVToolnix allows you to customize and manage up the MKV file had to be cut or connect...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sandboxie 5.71.9</title><pubDate> Sat, 03 Jan 2026 17:01:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sandboxie-818.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sandboxie-818.html
</guid><description>
Sandboxie software to browse the Web securely while still keeping all the functionality your browser for content works against harmful agents such as sanbox up your computer. You may not know, when you browse the Web, the change will occur with the system of your computer. When you use Sandboxie, the software will protect the web browser of their own.
Sandboxie - web protection, safe browsing
The main features of Sandboxie
Stay safe on the Internet with Sandboxie
	Run the program in...
</description></item><item><title>Download BirdFont 6.15.4</title><pubDate> Sat, 03 Jan 2026 17:00:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-birdfont-233.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-birdfont-233.html
</guid><description>
BirdFont is software editing font allows you to create vector graphics and export them to font TTF, EOT and SVG to be able to use in any program, text or graphics.
With editor, BirdFont, you can create vector graphics for each letter of the alphabet as well as numbers and characters. Or is draw them completely free by hand or based on the background image. BirdFont create font own from scratch using numerous drawing tools let you design the vectors for each letter or you can trace...
</description></item><item><title>Download PointerStick 6.88</title><pubDate> Sat, 03 Jan 2026 17:00:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pointerstick-1743.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pointerstick-1743.html
</guid><description>
PulumStick is a presentation tool, mobile simple to turn your mouse pointer into a pointer larger. The software is designed to be used with presentations on a large screen, it allows to emphasize the operation of the computer desktop and helps users easily track the cursor over. You can adjust the size of the pointer, choose from a number of cursor interface, and can also move the mouse cursor usually your through mouse click or keyboard hotkeys.
PointerStick - virtual cursor
This is a...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sandboxie Plus 1.16.9</title><pubDate> Sat, 03 Jan 2026 16:59:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sandboxie-plus-4962.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sandboxie-plus-4962.html
</guid><description>
Sandboxie Plus is an application version of the open source project on Github, equipped with software to protect your information while browsing the web or running valuable software. doubt. Web browsing, downloading or running software can affect system security. To prevent this from happening, a high user experience and strong layers of protection are needed to prevent malware from spreading to the system. For example, by opening an unknown application, malware in flash memory can...
</description></item><item><title>Download IntraWEB Ultimate 16.1.9</title><pubDate> Sat, 03 Jan 2026 16:39:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intraweb-ultimate-2007.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intraweb-ultimate-2007.html
</guid><description>
IntraWEB Ultimate is a tool to build the website. With this tool, the developer can create the page using the same method used to build the Windows program. Because the HTML page directly from the concept design to the user's computer does not download a bit more complicated and in fact is required from web server. So, the template IntraWeb on the server and download server and displays them to the user. Things technology direction of the IntraWEB Ultimate provides part flexibility and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Software Companions GerbView 11.33.0.637</title><pubDate> Sat, 03 Jan 2026 16:38:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-software-companions-gerbview-1484.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-software-companions-gerbview-1484.html
</guid><description>
GerbView is a file, advanced, but easy to use, convert, print, and view files HPGL, HPGL / 2, Excellon and raster. It supports both RS274D and RS274X. You can use this software to convert the old format and RS274D standard to the new RS274X have default data. Gerbview is used to represent and illustrate the intricate design of you.
Software Companions GerbView - conversion, printing, and viewing HPGL, HPGL / 2, Excellon
You don't need to wait for rendered images to see the picture of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Executor 2.2.1.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 03 Jan 2026 16:38:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-executor-271.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-executor-271.html
</guid><description>
Executor for windows is a software alternative premium customization features for the Windows "Run" and "Search Programs". When you press WIN + Z and provides the search results instant, as-you-type for any keywords you enter. By default, Executor will index all the Desktop and Start Menu and you can easily expand the search range by adding the folder location additional.
Executor for windows
The program comes with a list of commands built in which you can use to quickly access many...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cockos REAPER 7.58</title><pubDate> Sat, 03 Jan 2026 16:37:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cockos-reaper-889.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cockos-reaper-889.html
</guid><description>
Cockos REAPER is a powerful software for for windows, chp lets you record, arrange, edit, and display the audio waveform multi-track. Cockos REAPER offers an extensive feature set includes many effects and a sample project. REAPER supports ASIO, Kernel Streaming, WaveOut, and DirectSound for playback and recording. It reads the files in WAV, OGG and MP3 files and records WAV files. You can arrange any number of items in any number of tracks and use plug-in sound processing (DirectX and...
</description></item><item><title>Download DVDFab 13.0.5.4</title><pubDate> Sat, 03 Jan 2026 16:36:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dvdfab-67.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dvdfab-67.html
</guid><description>
DVDFab All-In-One is a multi-purpose combo of nearly all powerful DVDFab products-DVD replication, Ripper DVD, Blu-ray Ripper, Blu-ray Ripper, Copy UHD, Blu-ray to DVD, DVD to Blu-ray Transaction, DVD Creator, Blu-ray Creator, video conversion, Cinavia DVD removal, Windows DVD removal, DRM elimination for Apple, Screen Recorder and Editor for iOS, Hi-Fi Sound and File Transfer. It provides a complete solution to all of your DVD/Blu-ray/video problems and the perfect execution.
DvDFab -...
</description></item><item><title>Download GetPixelColor 3.49</title><pubDate> Sat, 03 Jan 2026 16:36:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-getpixelcolor-4502.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-getpixelcolor-4502.html
</guid><description>
GetPixelColor is the right tool for Windows if you want to determine the color value of a pixel on the screen background. GetPixelColor very suitable for the graphic designer, webmaster and those who want to become one, to determine the pixel color of the desktop. But even if you have no need to determine the color value, you can get to know and understand RGB color space in a playful way, especially suitable for school or other purposes. Likewise, to be able to find out what kind of color...
</description></item><item><title>Download Kalmuri 4.1.7</title><pubDate> Sat, 03 Jan 2026 16:36:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kalmuri-12521.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kalmuri-12521.html
</guid><description>
Kalmuri provides one of the simplest means of recording screen activity, working as both a snapshot utility and a screen recorder. It requires no installation and is ready to go at any time, waiting for your action quietly in the tray area, thus not disturbing your work.
Features of Kalmuri
	Supports video recording (specify entire screen and area)
	Entire screen, active program, window control, application area
	Supports PNG, JPG, BMP, GIF, MP4 file formats
	Supports saving documents...
</description></item><item><title>Download QOwnNotes 26.1.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 03 Jan 2026 16:35:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qownnotes-3178.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qownnotes-3178.html
</guid><description>
QOwnNotes is notes bookmark file simple text (GPL) open source application for GNU / Linux , Mac OS X and Windows of Patrizio Bekerle ( pbek on GitHub and IRC) (optional) activity along with the notes application of ownCloud or Nextcloud. QOwnNote store your notes as plain text files and can be synchronized with synchronization function file of ownCloud / Nextcloud. You can also use other apps like Syncthing or Dropbox . Just write out your thoughts as they appear, and edit them if...
</description></item><item><title>Download Social Media Downloader 8.1.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 03 Jan 2026 16:35:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-socialmediaapps-facebook-video-downloader-3742.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-socialmediaapps-facebook-video-downloader-3742.html
</guid><description>
SocialVideo Downloader (formerly SocialMediaApps Facebook Video Downloader) is a Windows application to download and convert your favorite videos from Facebook and hundreds of other video sharing sites. It increases your loading speed by up to 500%, or even more! The application has a simple and intuitive user interface, its main functions and features are quite obvious to anyone. , regardless of prior experience with similar purpose tools.
&amp;nbsp;
SocialVideo Downloader
The main...
</description></item><item><title>Download Digital Clock 5.1.9</title><pubDate> Sat, 03 Jan 2026 16:34:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-digital-clock-3723.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-digital-clock-3723.html
</guid><description>
Digital Clock is a screen saver small and simple application that allows you to view the date, time and current day of the week. In addition, you can set the clock mode 12 or 24 hours, change the font color, display day of the week, current date, separators flash or seconds. hi it boots, outdoor clock, tray icon appear (if available in the system tray). Color tray icon depends on the operating system, in most cases, it is black, but on Windows 10, Windows and macOS with the dark theme,...
</description></item><item><title>Download ToneBoosters Plugin Bundle 2.1.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 03 Jan 2026 16:28:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-toneboosters-plugin-bundle-3675.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-toneboosters-plugin-bundle-3675.html
</guid><description>
ToneBoosters Plugin Bundle is a package tool sound is to combine the digital signal processing advanced and deployed multi-platform is optimized with the easy to use interface to optimize workflow of you. We combine the digital signal processing advanced and highly optimized deployment platform interface with simple-to-use to optimize your work.
ToneBoosters Plugin Bundle - audio tools
ToneBoosters Plugin Bundle includes:
	Barricade: True-peak mastering limiter.
	BitJuggler: The...
</description></item><item><title>Download Withdata DBToFile 2.9.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 03 Jan 2026 13:33:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-withdata-dbtofile-14432.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-withdata-dbtofile-14432.html
</guid><description>
DBToFile is data conversion software that helps data engineers export data from databases to files. DBToFile can export database data to TXT, CSV, TSV, SQL, XML, JSON, HTML, Excel, and many other formats. Supports multiple relational databases, including Access, DB2, DBF, MySQL, Oracle, PostgreSQL, SQLite, SQL Server, Amazon Redshift, AZURE SQL, and more.
Features of DBToFile
	Export Table - Export data from a table in the database to a file.
	Export Query - Export the data returned...
</description></item><item><title>Download CalendarTask (formerly DesktopCal) 3.26.262.8332</title><pubDate> Sat, 03 Jan 2026 00:05:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopcal-1831.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopcal-1831.html
</guid><description>
CalendarTask (formerly DesktopCal) is a simple desktop calendar that blends into your desktop without blocking access to your desktop icons. You can double-click on a date to quickly add notes and also jump to specific dates in the past or future.
CalendarTask - Computer calendar
CalendarTask can use your current wallpaper or loop through images from your folder and update your desktop every few minutes. The program helps you make appointments, make plans... Not only that, the Screen...
</description></item><item><title>Download ImageGlass 9.4.1.15</title><pubDate> Sat, 03 Jan 2026 00:04:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-imageglass-4396.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-imageglass-4396.html
</guid><description>
ImageGlass is a software free image viewer open source. With a beautiful interface, simple and works in a gentle way is the advantages first thing that users notice in ImageGlass. Software ImageGlass is also a tool that helps users to view photos with support for many popular formats, including animations GIF, image transparent PNG. Imageglass allows users to view photos in zoom mode and zoom very flexible and easy. With this utility, you can browse the photo series with the same Zoom...
</description></item><item><title>Download HFS: HTTP File Server (version 3) 3.0.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 03 Jan 2026 00:03:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hfs-http-file-server-11851.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hfs-http-file-server-11851.html
</guid><description>
HFS is a web file server to run on your computer. Share a folder or even a file thanks to the virtual file system. Essentially, this application turns your computer into an HTTP server and all users who want to connect and download files can do so by loading a simple website in their browser. HFS includes many configuration settings, so you can basically change each part of the application, starting with how users download files and ending with the appearance of the created website.
HFS...
</description></item><item><title>Download KiCad 9.0.7</title><pubDate> Sat, 03 Jan 2026 00:03:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kicad-10384.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kicad-10384.html
</guid><description>
KiCad is a unique software product that allows you to open, create and develop electronic circuits for subsequent visualization of printed circuit board designs in interactive views . It allows you to develop complex circuit diagrams using an electronic components database and test signal integrity. It includes free applications, facilities, templates, and open libraries.
Using KiCad, users will be able to create truly professional printed circuit board layouts, beautifully designed...
</description></item><item><title>Download ArmorTools Professional / Home 26.0.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 02 Jan 2026 23:46:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-armortools-7726.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-armortools-7726.html
</guid><description>
ArmorTools is a set of tools that extend the capabilities of the MS Windows operating system in the field of security and protection of user confidential information. ArmorTools allows you to create secure virtual disks encrypted with AES128/AES256 algorithms, encrypting files and folder contents using any file as a password.
ArmorTools erases the user's work traces on the computer, deletes the history of accessing websites, deletes confidential information without the possibility of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Advanced SystemCare Pro Portable 19.1.0.176</title><pubDate> Fri, 02 Jan 2026 23:46:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-systemcare-pro-portable-8964.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-systemcare-pro-portable-8964.html
</guid><description>
Advanced SystemCare Pro Portable (a portable version) is system optimization and maintenance software developed by IObit. It is designed to help users improve the performance and speed of their Windows computers by cleaning junk files, optimizing system settings, and fixing various system errors.
It specializes in ONE-Click solutions to detect, clean, repair, speed up and ultimately protect PC. With new system technology, Advanced SystemCare Pro lets you run your computer faster....
</description></item><item><title>Download O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro 22.1.231 / Server</title><pubDate> Fri, 02 Jan 2026 23:45:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-diskimage-pro-218.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-diskimage-pro-218.html
</guid><description>
O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro is software backup data comprehensive and effective is provided to protect the data of the computer system, it creates images for individual drives or the entire system that still does not affect your system.
O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro allows the user to backup the entire computer or drive, the and files whenever you want even while the computer is being used. Or can use O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro to create a copy chinh sac of computer disk drives, can be used instead of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download ButterScroll 1.3.4</title><pubDate> Fri, 02 Jan 2026 23:45:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-butterscroll-13824.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-butterscroll-13824.html
</guid><description>
Smooth scrolling on Windows just got better. Smooth scrolling for Windows is what ButterScroll is all about. It improves the way your mouse scrolls using customizable speed and ease settings.
Smooth scrolling for all types of mice.
ButterScroll improves your everyday scrolling experience with smooth scrolling precision, customizable controls, and a satisfying feel across all your Windows apps — from browsers to spreadsheets.
ButterScroll Features
	Easy to set up and use
	Smooth,...
</description></item></channel></rss>