<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 23:37:41 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 23:37:41 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download KILHO AutoClick 1.4.6</title><pubDate> Sat, 22 Nov 2025 02:37:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kilho-autoclick-12515.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kilho-autoclick-12515.html
</guid><description>
AutoClick is a software or script designed to automate mouse clicking tasks, especially useful for repetitive actions in a variety of applications, including gaming and data entry. It allows users to define specific click points and automatically click at those locations. This tool is user-friendly and supports recording click sequences for repeated use.
AutoClick allows users to set precise time intervals and geographic coordinates for various click patterns. Additionally, AutoClick...
</description></item><item><title>Download ExpanDrive 2025.11.12</title><pubDate> Sat, 22 Nov 2025 02:36:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-expandrive-609.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-expandrive-609.html
</guid><description>
ExpanDrive is software sync cloud storage strong support BackBlaze B2, Google Team Drive, SMB / CIFS and new interface and easy user search file version, share links and much more.  ExpanDrive mapped network drives for macOS and Micosoft Windows connect with all the provide major cloud storage such as Dropbox, Google Drive, Google Team Drive, Amazon Drive, Box, OneDrive, OneDrive for Business, Sharepoint, Openstack Swift , BackBlaze B2, Amazon S3 or SFTP servers, FTP or WebDAV on your own...
</description></item><item><title>Download Rainlendar Pro 2.23.0 Build 183</title><pubDate> Sat, 22 Nov 2025 02:36:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rainlendar-pro-3123.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rainlendar-pro-3123.html
</guid><description>
Rainlendar is a calendar that is personal and powerful and will help you to easily manage and view all your tasks and important events of you. The program allows you to keep the mission and events of yourself in the separate list, allowing you to keep your own life organized better. This app will also inform you about the mission and upcoming events.
Rainlendar will store your information in the format iCalWiki compatible with the majority of the calendar widget. This means you can easily...
</description></item><item><title>Download MP3Studio YouTube Downloader 2.0.29.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 22 Nov 2025 02:35:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mp3studio-youtube-downloader-6778.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mp3studio-youtube-downloader-6778.html
</guid><description>
MP3Studio YouTube Downloader is an efficient and user-friendly software developed to provide you with an easy means of getting all your favorite videos from the web and store them on your PC, in one of the available formats. With MP3Studio YouTube Downloader, you can download up to 99 songs at once in the background as you start your business.
Use this media editor to preload various songs via YouTube and other services. It will provide you with good quality music that you can listen to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Geometric Glovius Prime 6.7.0.95</title><pubDate> Sat, 22 Nov 2025 02:35:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-geometric-glovius-pro-754.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-geometric-glovius-pro-754.html
</guid><description>
Geometric Glovius Pro is viewer CAD 3D modern for files CATIA, NX, STEP, IGES, Pro/ENGINEER and Creo, SolidWorks, Inventor and Solid Edge. The work of Geometric Glovius Pro is made exact measurements, cut dynamic sections, compare differences between models and export to 3D PDF, STL and Glovius Mobile.
Geometric Glovius Pro - manager, and view CAD 3D
The features of Geometric Glovius Pro
	Modern interface, simple, easy to use
	Mobile app for free for iOS &amp;amp; Android powerful...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaMonkey Gold 2024.2.0.3178 RC3</title><pubDate> Sat, 22 Nov 2025 02:34:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediamonkey-gold-231.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediamonkey-gold-231.html
</guid><description>
MediaMonkey Gold is music manager and music player multimedia for the music collection and iPod users. MediaMonkey lists the audio file of you as CD, OGG, WMA, MPC, FLAC, APE, WAV and MP3 and includes the edit smart card and an automatic file and folder to arrange your music library.
MediaMonkey Gold also has CD ripper, CD / DVD Burner, and audio converter for saving music, and manual or editor list automatically to create mixed music.
Features MediaMonkey Gold
	Automatically find...
</description></item><item><title>Download Spybot Anti-Beacon 5.4</title><pubDate> Sat, 22 Nov 2025 02:34:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-spybot-anti-beacon-2274.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-spybot-anti-beacon-2274.html
</guid><description>
Spybot Anti-Beacon is a small utility to prevent and stop the method of tracking different (e.g., remote) in Windows 10. Developer writes that he just saw a series of such programs, but they are all unfinished or unfinished workers, plus have the program install the type of ads and other junk into the system.
Spybot Anti-Beacon - Block and stop the service in windows 10
Features disabled:
	This tool will disable as follows:
	Remote server
	Remote service
	The program improves the...
</description></item><item><title>Download SysTools SQL Server Recovery Manager 7.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 22 Nov 2025 02:33:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-systools-sql-server-recovery-manager-12420.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-systools-sql-server-recovery-manager-12420.html
</guid><description>
The software gives you the option to recover corrupted database files. You can open and restore both SQL Primary Database (MDF) files as well as Secondary Database (NDF) files. Additionally, the tool can restore deleted Tables, Stored Procedures, Functions, Triggers, etc.
Features
	Restore &amp;amp; Export SQL Database: Primary File (MDF), Secondary File (NDF) and Backup (BAK)
	Analyze SQL Server LOG database transactions
	Export MDF, LDF and BAK Files to SQL Server Located on the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cash Register Pro 4.0.4</title><pubDate> Sat, 22 Nov 2025 02:33:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cash-register-pro-3853.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cash-register-pro-3853.html
</guid><description>
Cash Register Pro a software cash register full of features and creative for a Windows computer, it will help you to better handle all the activities of the computer money. The application comes with the user interface logical and user friendly allows you to work quickly and do not commit the common error. The program can be used on a number of computers and offers a wide range of authorization secure and reliable. Cash Register Pro will help you track products and goods remain...
</description></item><item><title>Download ThinkAutomation Studio Professional 5.1.1096.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 22 Nov 2025 02:32:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thinkautomation-studio-professional-9635.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thinkautomation-studio-professional-9635.html
</guid><description>
ThinkAutomation Studio Professional is software that automates on-premises and cloud-based business processes to cut costs and save time. Automate incoming communication channels, monitor databases, react to incoming webhooks, web forms and chat bots. Handles documents, attachments, local files, and other message sources.
Parse and extract data from incoming messages and take actions in business processes, such as outbound communications, updating on-premises and cloud databases,...
</description></item><item><title>Download VovSoft Collect URL 3.5</title><pubDate> Sat, 22 Nov 2025 02:27:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-collect-url-7395.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-collect-url-7395.html
</guid><description>
VovSoft Collect URL is an internet scanner like a search engine bot. Starting from the URL the user entered, it lists all the links on the URL. Then it recursively scans all the links in the list. Users can limit URL Crawl to only one domain name. The file extension ignore list can be edited. Connection and response timeout values ​​are editable. Additionally, the user can change the user agent value for HTTP and HTTPS connections.
Features of VovSoft Collect URL
	Scan the...
</description></item><item><title>Download EKIO - Loudspeaker Management Application 1.0.8.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 23:30:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ekio-loudspeaker-management-application-14305.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ekio-loudspeaker-management-application-14305.html
</guid><description>
EKIO is a loudspeaker management application that allows you to customize the sound of your loudspeaker system for optimal performance. The application provides the ability to easily create crossovers for full-range speakers, integrate subwoofers, and equalize your sound system. Additionally, EKIO can import loudspeaker measurements to achieve the best settings and achieve the best audio performance.
EKIO is a Windows application that works with the ASIO audio interface. However, if...
</description></item><item><title>Download Inno Setup Compiler 6.6.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 20:22:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-inno-setup-compiler-2655.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-inno-setup-compiler-2655.html
</guid><description>
Inno Setup Compiler is a system installed based on free software created by Delphi by Jordan Russell. The first version was released in 1997. QuickStart of Inno Setup include main Inno Setup and also includes an option to install the script editor Inno Script Studio. The script editor is not official and is not mandatory for general use, but help Inno Setup easier to use.
Inno Setup Compiler - software create file setup.exe
The features of Inno Setup Compiler
	Support for every...
</description></item><item><title>Download PicPick Pro 7.4.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 20:20:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-picpick-pro-2003.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-picpick-pro-2003.html
</guid><description>
PicPick Pro is a premium version paid free of PicPick. PicPick Pro is a screen capturing tool included editing has taken with many built-in tools available as measurement tool on the screen, including a color picker, color palette, protractor pixel, protractor, cross and many more. The program allows you to capture the entire desktop, active window, selected area or window control just by the click of a button or via keyboard shortcut.
PicPick Pro - Take a screenshot
PicPick Pro has an...
</description></item><item><title>Download PicPick 7.4.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 20:19:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-picpick-1323.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-picpick-1323.html
</guid><description>
PicPick is an application that captures the screen including the editing the photo has been taken with many built-in tools available as measurement tool on the screen, including a color picker, color palette, protractor pixel, protractor, cross and many more. The program allows you to capture the entire desktop, active window, selected area or window control just by the click of a button or via keyboard shortcut.
PicPick - Take a screenshot
Can load the captured image into the image...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tiny11 25H2 Build 26200.7171 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 20:19:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tiny11-8649.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tiny11-8649.html
</guid><description>
Tiny11 is a compact Windows operating system based on Windows 11 Pro 22H2, Tiny11 has everything you need for a comfortable, hassle-free computing experience. cumbersome and messy like a standard Windows installation. The operating system requires only 8GB of disk space and 2GB of RAM, and requires no TPM (Trusted Platform Module) and Secure Boot support.
The main goal of Tiny11 is to extend the reach of systems that can access Windows 11. The custom edition can run on any system...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare Filmora 15.0.11.16306</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 20:18:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-filmora-2025-31.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-filmora-2025-31.html
</guid><description>
In early November 2020 Wondershare came up with a new version called Wondershare Filmora 13 with two new ways to edit: Action Cam Tool (Lens distortion correction, Clean up your audio, Control speed new) and Instant Cutter (Cut or merge clips quickly, Export instantly).
Wondershare Filmora 13  allows you to add your favorite tracks to your videos, creating a more stylish, romantic film reel, with a rich music library besides Users can manually add their favorite songs to the editing...
</description></item><item><title>Download Boris FX Sapphire Plug-ins for OFX 2026.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 20:17:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-genarts-sapphire-839.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-genarts-sapphire-839.html
</guid><description>
GenArts Sapphire is the latest upgrade for the plugin VFX. The application includes LensFlare and Flare Designer been refurbished and completely revamped effects , digital art, new and is optimized for performance, CPU and GPU maximum. The current GenArts Sapphire is supported for Adobe, Avid, them Autodesk Flame and OFX as Resolve, Fusion, NUKE, Baselight (only version 4.3 and 4.4), VEGAS Pro and Harmony.
GenArts Sapphire - edit, add visual effects
The main features of GenArts...
</description></item><item><title>Download EaseUS Partition Master Technican Edition 19.23.0 Build 202510091552</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 20:16:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-partition-master-350.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-partition-master-350.html
</guid><description>
EaseUS Partition Master is software partition management all-in-one be used to redistribute capacity hard drive with high performance and keep all PC, laptop and server running perfect performance. Engineering software master partition deals with all the task partition in an effective way without loss of data. Just a few clicks to re-partition your hard drive, SSD, USB, flash drive, memory card, SD card, memory card and many other storage devices in Windows 10, 8.1, 8, 7, Vista, XP and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Boris FX Sapphire Plug-ins for After Effects 2026.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 20:16:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-boris-fx-sapphire-plug-ins-for-adobe-5314.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-boris-fx-sapphire-plug-ins-for-adobe-5314.html
</guid><description>
Boris FX, Sapphire Plug-ins for Adobe is a collection of very useful gadgets with additional powerful, as well as the effects to create the effect of the attractive images in the movies and video files. The film today is not complete without photo effects and include a number of photo effects to increase the beauty for their film. To add effect, clip to your movie, you can use a number of different applications and BorisFX Genarts Sapphire is one of them.
Boris FX, Sapphire Plug-ins for...
</description></item><item><title>Download TreeSize Free 4.8.1.609</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 20:16:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-treesize-free-10656.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-treesize-free-10656.html
</guid><description>
TreeSize Free is a free disk space manager for Windows, it will show you the size of folders including its subfolders in a similar fashion like Explorer. Large folders can be identified at a glance thanks to the gradient bar displayed in the background. All scan results can be detailed at the file level and filters, e.g. for files of a certain type, can be applied.
Features of TreeSize Free
	Search space: clean up hard drive space
	Break down hard drive space usage to file level:...
</description></item><item><title>Download EASEUS Partition Master Server Edition 19.23.0 Build 202510091552</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 20:15:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-partition-master-server-edition-3457.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-partition-master-server-edition-3457.html
</guid><description>
EASEUS Partition Master Server Edition is a powerful program that allows you to solution delete, create, merge, resize / move, split the partition to use better the full capacity of the hard drive. EasUS Partition Master Server Edition is the partition manager packed full of features and includes three main functions: The recovery guide partition manager partition and wizard restore partition.
These tools will enhance the management of your hard drive and will help you to use disk space...
</description></item><item><title>Download AndroidDrive 2.4.13</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 20:15:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-androiddrive-10400.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-androiddrive-10400.html
</guid><description>
AndroidDrive is a program that allows mounting Android smartphones/tablets as drives on Windows. When AndroidDrive is running and you connect an Android device, AndroidDrive automatically mounts the drive containing that device's internal storage (files, folders).
Once you have started AndroidDrive, the connected Android smartphone/tablet will be recognized as a new drive in Windows Explorer. This way, any files, photos, or other media can be moved back and forth between your Windows...
</description></item><item><title>Download EASEUS Partition Master WinPE Edition 19.23.0 Build 202510091552</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 20:15:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-partition-master-winpe-edition-3460.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-partition-master-winpe-edition-3460.html
</guid><description>
EASEUS Partition Master WinPE Edition is a version plugins help you to create a disk partition on WinPE for you to easily recover hard drive partition computer if not may broken or error. Boot disk EasUS Partition Master WinPE, format software mobile, you can:
	Works well in Windows, such as extend system partition or settling low disk space and managing disk space, recovery partition deleted , rebuild MBR, restore partition GPT, etc.
	You are allowed to resize the primary drive to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Boris FX Sapphire Plug-ins for Photoshop 2026.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 20:14:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-boris-fx-sapphire-plug-ins-for-photoshop-7185.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-boris-fx-sapphire-plug-ins-for-photoshop-7185.html
</guid><description>
Sapphire 2022 adds new host support for Adobe Photoshop. Featuring 270+ resolution independent and non-destructive effects built into a one-of-a-kind nodal based effects compositor. Photoshop artists will delight at 3000+ easily searchable presets organized by name, type, or intended use. Sapphire Photoshop has the same extensive parameter set as Sapphire plugins, giving artists complete control over every aspect of an effect.
Anything created with Sapphire Photoshop can be shared with...
</description></item></channel></rss>