<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 20:01:52 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 20:01:52 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download VSCO: Photo &amp;amp; Video Editor v448</title><pubDate> Mon, 17 Nov 2025 21:52:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-vsco-photo-video-editor-8163.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-vsco-photo-video-editor-8163.html
</guid><description>
VSCO is the leading photo and video editor, nurturing the creative journey with our library of over 200 high-quality tools and presets. We also offer an easy-to-use video editor and a curated collection of photos across every genre, style and aesthetic from our global community of talented creators.
This application offers many tools and features that can be used to adjust color, exposure, and other aspects of the image. It also includes many filters that can be applied to give photos a...
</description></item><item><title>Download SnapTube for Android 7.50.1.75070501</title><pubDate> Mon, 17 Nov 2025 21:51:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-snaptube-youtube-downloader-hd-video-8351.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-snaptube-youtube-downloader-hd-video-8351.html
</guid><description>
SnapTube is a mobile application that allows users to download videos from various platforms, such as YouTube, Vimeo, and Dailymotion. It provides video resolution in multiple formats 144p, 720p, 1080p HD, 2K HD, 4K HD and audio formats MP3 and M4A. With Snaptube, users can search for content across all their platforms without using multiple apps.
Features of SnapTube for Android
Download in multiple resolutions
	MP4 videos are available in resolutions: choose small 360 pixels or...
</description></item><item><title>Download Chat AI - AI Chatbot Assistant v227.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 17 Nov 2025 21:51:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-chat-ai-ai-chatbot-assistant-11260.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-chat-ai-ai-chatbot-assistant-11260.html
</guid><description>
AI Chatbot is a smart artificial intelligence interactive application that brings a unique and convenient experience to users. With AI Chatbot, you can communicate and ask questions directly with a powerful AI system that helps you find information, answer questions, and even provide solutions to complex problems.
Main features of Chatbot AI include
	Natural conversation: Chatbot AI uses advanced natural language technology to understand and respond to your questions and requests...
</description></item><item><title>Download PhotoDirector: AI Photo Editor 20.7.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 17 Nov 2025 21:51:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-photodirector-photo-editor-8144.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-photodirector-photo-editor-8144.html
</guid><description>
PhotoDirector is a photo editing app for Android devices that allows you to edit and enhance your photos with a variety of tools and effects. With PhotoDirector, you can adjust your photo's color and lighting, remove blemishes and other imperfections, and apply filters to give your photos a unique look. You can also use PhotoDirector to create photo collages and slideshows, add text and stickers to photos, and share your edited photos on social networks or through other sharing...
</description></item><item><title>Download 1Weather: Forecast &amp;amp; Radar 11.7.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 17 Nov 2025 21:50:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-1weather-forecast-radar-8846.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-1weather-forecast-radar-8846.html
</guid><description>
1Weather is the most popular weather application on Google Play. Whether you want to check temperatures, forecast precipitation, Doppler radar, or simply track the current phases of the sun and moon, 1Weather has you covered. Plus, it's got an outstanding design that makes getting your weather information easy and fun.
Track current conditions and forecasts for your location and up to 12 locations of your choice. Access charts, precipitation forecasts, maps, weather information and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Any.do - To do list &amp;amp; Calendar 5.18.14.6</title><pubDate> Mon, 17 Nov 2025 21:50:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-anydo-to-do-list-calendar-8360.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-anydo-to-do-list-calendar-8360.html
</guid><description>
Any.do is a productivity app that combines the features of a to-do list and a calendar. It allows users to create and organize tasks as well as schedule them according to specific dates and times. The app also includes a feature called "My Day" that helps users focus on the most important tasks of the day.
Some of Any.do's other features include the ability to set reminders, create side and recurring tasks, and collaborate on tasks with others. Additionally, Any.do also has a calendar...
</description></item><item><title>Download FolderSync Pro 4.8.1 build 2020100187</title><pubDate> Mon, 17 Nov 2025 21:49:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-foldersync-pro-8221.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-foldersync-pro-8221.html
</guid><description>
FolderSync Pro allows users to synchronize files and folders between their mobile devices and various cloud storage services, such as Dropbox, Google Drive and OneDrive. Back up music, pictures, and other important files from your phone to your cloud storage, or vice versa. It has never been easier. Automation support with Tasker and similar programs allows granular control over your synchronization process.
FolderSync contains a full file manager, allowing you to manage your files...
</description></item><item><title>Download SMS Backup &amp;amp; Restore Pro 10.24.001</title><pubDate> Mon, 17 Nov 2025 21:49:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sms-backup-restore-pro-8277.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sms-backup-restore-pro-8277.html
</guid><description>
SMS Backup &amp;amp; Restore Pro is an Android application that allows users to backup and restore text messages (SMS) and multimedia messages (MMS). This application can be useful for those who want to keep their text messages safe or for those who want to transfer text messages from one device to another.
Features of SMS Backup &amp;amp; Restore Pro Restore Pro
	Backup SMS (Text) Messages, MMS and Call Logs in XML format.
	Local device backup with options to automatically upload to Google...
</description></item><item><title>Download Glitch! (glitch4ndroid) 4.6.4</title><pubDate> Mon, 17 Nov 2025 21:49:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-glitch-glitch4ndroid-8777.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-glitch-glitch4ndroid-8777.html
</guid><description>
Quickly create your digital artwork with the best glitch photo editing app. Become a digital artist, create real and completely random glitches to add that "nerdy" touch to your photos!
	Upload your photos and edit with 26 unique effects including Pixelsort, Datamosh, JPEG|PNG|WEBP glitch.
	Export your artwork in Jpg format or record an Mp4 or GIF animation
HOW TO USE: You just need to swipe the screen multiple times to create errors in your photo.
Imperfections create uniqueness in...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sleep Monitor: Sleep Tracker 2.9.26</title><pubDate> Mon, 17 Nov 2025 21:48:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sleep-monitor-sleep-tracker-11480.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sleep-monitor-sleep-tracker-11480.html
</guid><description>
Sleep Monitor helps you track and record detailed sleep cycles. Sleep Monitor also has a smart alarm clock to remind you to sleep early at night and wake you gently in the morning. In addition, Sleep Monitor also provides relaxing, soothing music to help you sleep better.
New feature: Write notes about sleep
	Take brief notes about your sleep. Write down anything you want so you will never forget them.
Record snoring or talking in your dreams
	The sleep tracker will record snoring...
</description></item><item><title>Download TickTick:To Do List &amp;amp; Calendar 7.7.2.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 17 Nov 2025 21:48:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ticktick-to-do-list-tasks-8702.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ticktick-to-do-list-tasks-8702.html
</guid><description>
TickTick is a simple and effective task management and to-do list application that helps you schedule, manage time, remind about deadlines and organize your life at work, at home. home and everywhere else. TickTick is here to help you make the most of your day and get things done (gtd). Whether there's an idea you want to capture, a personal goal to achieve, a job to complete, or collaborating with other colleagues, even create a shopping list (with the help of a list creator). book)....
</description></item><item><title>Download Battery Guru: Battery Info 2.4.3 build 641</title><pubDate> Mon, 17 Nov 2025 21:48:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-battery-guru-battery-health-8651.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-battery-guru-battery-health-8651.html
</guid><description>
Battery Guru displays battery usage information, measures battery capacity (mAh), shows estimates, and helps you change your charging habits with helpful tips to extend battery life and increase battery life up 200%.
Features of Battery Guru for Android
	Batteries have a limited lifespan, each time you charge your device, the battery wears out, reducing its total (design) capacity.
	Now you can reduce wear and tear, spend less time tethering your device to the charger, and get the...
</description></item><item><title>Download QuickEdit Text Editor Pro 1.12.1 build 252</title><pubDate> Mon, 17 Nov 2025 21:48:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-quickedit-text-editor-pro-9059.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-quickedit-text-editor-pro-9059.html
</guid><description>
QuickEdit is a fast, stable and full-featured text editor for Android devices. It has been optimized for both phones and tablets. This app is designed to provide a variety of features and tools that make editing and formatting text on mobile devices as easy and efficient as possible.
QuickEdit Text Editor Pro Features
	Advanced notepad application with many improvements.
	Code editor and syntax highlighting for over 40 languages ​​(C++, C#, Java, XML, Javascript, Markdown, PHP,...
</description></item><item><title>Download StbEmu (Pro) 2.0.17.05</title><pubDate> Mon, 17 Nov 2025 21:47:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-stbemu-pro-9840.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-stbemu-pro-9840.html
</guid><description>
StbEmu is an application for Android 5.0+, allowing downloading IPTV web portals, designed to run on IPTV STB (Set-Top-Box), on devices running Android, such as phones, tablets tablets and TV boxes. Currently, the application supports simulation of many STBs created by the Ukrainian company Infomir, such as MAG 250, MAG 270 or MAG 322.
StbEmu (Pro) for IPTV: Remember that this application is configured for a demo IPTV portal for testing purposes. If you want to use the app, you must...
</description></item><item><title>Download Learn Coding/Programming: Mimo 6.13</title><pubDate> Mon, 17 Nov 2025 21:47:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-learn-codingprogramming-mimo-11634.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-learn-codingprogramming-mimo-11634.html
</guid><description>
Code in Python, JavaScript, HTML, CSS or SQL and start your career in Technology in 5 minutes a day! Whether you're an aspiring developer or just starting your journey Code in HTML, JavaScript, or other programming languages, the Mimo programming and coding app is designed to make learning to code accessible, engaging, and effective. Learn to code in these languages popular programming languages ​​like Python, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, SQL, etc. With Mimo coding app, you can learn...
</description></item><item><title>Download WiFi Analyzer 6.8</title><pubDate> Mon, 17 Nov 2025 21:47:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wifi-analyzer-10225.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wifi-analyzer-10225.html
</guid><description>
Introducing a new way to analyze and optimize your WiFi, Turn your Android device into a WiFi Analyzer! WiFi Analyzer Recommends the best channels and locations for your network. WiFi Analyzer gives you the most useful optimization information to help reduce interference and increase connection speed and stability.
WiFi Analyzer Features
	WiFi optimizer for interference issues
	Channel analyzer for neighboring APs
	Real-time data and distance calculation.
	Signal strength...
</description></item><item><title>Download BeSoccer - Soccer Live Score 5.6.3</title><pubDate> Mon, 17 Nov 2025 21:46:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-besoccer-soccer-live-score-8800.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-besoccer-soccer-live-score-8800.html
</guid><description>
All the football in the world at the click of a button. BeSoccer is the best live soccer app with soccer news, results and statistics. We cover over 10,000 competitions: you'll be able to follow all the matches live, receive goal notifications, line-ups, news, signings and today's televised matches . Explore the best database in the world of football with all the statistics about your team, favorite players around the world, comparisons, team form and the latest transfer rumours.&amp;lt;...
</description></item><item><title>Download Rotation | Orientation Manager 29.1.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 17 Nov 2025 21:46:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-rotation-orientation-manager-8332.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-rotation-orientation-manager-8332.html
</guid><description>
Rotate | Orientation Manager is a mobile application for Android devices that allows users to control screen rotation settings on their devices. This app allows users to set custom rotation settings for different apps, and also provides a quick toggle to enable or disable rotation globally.
Rotation feature | Orientation Manager
	Control screen rotation on a per-app basis
	Option to set custom rotation settings for different applications
	Quick toggle switch to enable or disable...
</description></item><item><title>Download Smart Launcher 6 ‧ Home Screen 6.5 build 053</title><pubDate> Mon, 17 Nov 2025 21:46:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-smart-launcher-8412.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-smart-launcher-8412.html
</guid><description>
Smart Launcher is a mobile app that provides users with a customized home screen and app launcher on their Android devices. It includes features like minimalist interface, automatic app sorting, and gesture controls. The app also includes many customizable settings, such as the ability to change the theme, icon size, and screen layout, as well as the ability to create custom categories for the app.
Smart Launcher Features
	Ambient theme: Smart launcher automatically changes theme...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mobizen Screen Recorder 3.10.15.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 17 Nov 2025 21:45:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-mobizen-screen-recorder-13298.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-mobizen-screen-recorder-13298.html
</guid><description>
Mobizen Screen Recorder is a popular and feature-rich screen recorder app for Android and iOS devices, designed for easy and high-quality screen recording, especially for gaming, tutorials, live broadcasting and video calling.
The Screen Recorder You're Looking For
	The Screen Recorder Chosen by 200 Million Global Users.
	Featured in many countries such as Korea, the United States, Europe, Japan, North and South America
	Free screen recording, capture and editing functions.
	Videos...
</description></item><item><title>Download Today Weather: Radar &amp;amp; Widgets 2.4.0-13</title><pubDate> Mon, 17 Nov 2025 21:44:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-today-weather-alerts-widgets-8915.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-today-weather-alerts-widgets-8915.html
</guid><description>
Weather Today is a beautiful and easy-to-use weather app that provides the world's most accurate local weather forecasts.
Features of Weather Today for Android
	Displays clear, easy-to-understand weather forecasts.
	Enjoy every moment you open the app with thousands of beautiful photos corresponding to the weather and day.
	Prepare for any situation with 24/7 weather forecasts and chance of rain.
	Protect your health with air quality, UV index and pollen count.
	Capture beautiful...
</description></item><item><title>Download Calendar Widget: Month/Agenda 2025.11.07-304</title><pubDate> Mon, 17 Nov 2025 21:44:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-calendar-widget-monthagenda-12188.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-calendar-widget-monthagenda-12188.html
</guid><description>
Two minimalist, fully customizable and resizable widgets - agenda (list) and month (grid) help you see your daily schedule at a glance right on your home screen. Widget can display events from facebook, google or company calendar.
Can also set custom reminders for events from the calendar - so you'll never miss a thing again!
</description></item><item><title>Download Easy Voice Recorder Pro 2.9.4</title><pubDate> Mon, 17 Nov 2025 21:44:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-easy-voice-recorder-pro-8778.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-easy-voice-recorder-pro-8778.html
</guid><description>
Easy Voice Recorder Pro is a popular voice recorder app for Android devices. It allows users to record audio using the device's built-in microphone or an external microphone and save the recordings in various audio formats, including MP3, WAV, AAC, and FLAC.
Easy Voice Recorder Pro is your daily companion for recording important moments. Capture meetings, personal notes, classes, songs, and more, with no time limits or ads!
Easy Voice Recorder Pro also offers a number of customizable...
</description></item><item><title>Download Elevate - Brain Training Games 5.214.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 17 Nov 2025 21:44:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-elevate-brain-training-games-8564.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-elevate-brain-training-games-8564.html
</guid><description>
Elevate is a brain training program designed to improve speech, processing speed, memory skills, mental math, and more. Each person is provided with their own personalized learning program, which is adjusted over time to maximize results.
The more you practice with Elevate, the more you'll improve key cognitive skills proven to increase productivity, earning potential, and confidence. More than 90% said their vocabulary, memory, math skills and overall acuity improved when they...
</description></item><item><title>Download Podcast Addict: Podcast player 2025.10</title><pubDate> Mon, 17 Nov 2025 21:43:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-podcast-addict-podcast-player-8373.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-podcast-addict-podcast-player-8373.html
</guid><description>
Podcast Addict is a popular podcast streaming application for Android devices. It allows users to listen to and manage their favorite podcasts, audiobooks, live streams, and YouTube channels. The app provides an easy way to discover and subscribe to new podcasts, while also allowing users to create playlists and customize the listening experience. Podcast Addict allows you to manage your Podcast, Radio, Audiobook, Live streaming, YouTube, SoundCloud channels and RSS News feeds from a...
</description></item></channel></rss>