<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 09:22:06 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 09:22:06 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Media Player Classic Black Edition 1.8.8</title><pubDate> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 01:54:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-media-player-classic-black-edition-3351.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-media-player-classic-black-edition-3351.html
</guid><description>
Media Player Classic Black Edition is abbreviated as MPC-BE is a free program that can interface black support users to watch movies, listen to music on the computer with the new interface. Media Player Classic - BE is based on the project "Media Player Classic" original (Gabest) and the project "Media Player Classic Home Cinema" (Casimir666), contains additional features and bug fixes.
Both programs are quite similar, because they are based on Media Player Classic original. In fact, MPC...
</description></item><item><title>Download PMAS - PowerShell Multi Activation System 7.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 01:52:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-powershell-tsf-activation-13584.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-powershell-tsf-activation-13584.html
</guid><description>
This advanced PowerShell script is a flexible and modular solution designed for licensing Windows and Office products. It runs a custom .NET library called LibTSforge.dll directly from memory to license Office. It can work in GUI mode or silent mode.
Features
	License management for both Windows and Office products
	Generate product keys with the help of LibTSforge.dll
	User-friendly graphical options with Out-GridView
	Compatible with KMS, MAK, RETAIL, OEM, AVMA license types
	In...
</description></item><item><title>Download R-Wipe &amp;amp; Clean 20.0 Build 2532</title><pubDate> Sun, 26 Oct 2025 17:41:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-wipe-clean-891.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-wipe-clean-891.html
</guid><description>
R-Wipe &amp;amp; Clean is software to delete junk files, unnecessary files from your computer to release the storage space and speed up your computer. In addition, R-Wipe &amp;amp; Clean also unleash the capacity of your drive and delete information invasion of privacy on different operations online and offline including your internet history and cookies, the list of downloaded files and documents were open, buffer different data, temporary files and many other items, created by the operating...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare UniConverter 17.0.0.418</title><pubDate> Sun, 26 Oct 2025 17:41:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-uniconverter-4808.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-uniconverter-4808.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare UniConverter ( old name is Wondershare Video Converter Ultimate) which allows you to convert the video format. You can cut, splice, move, or add effects, subtitles a easy way. When using software you easily cut, splice, move, as well as add the effects, the subtitles to the video.... Or can switch the clods SD, HD video to any format popular for use with iPod (Classic, Nano and Touch), iPhone, Apple TV, Zune, PSP, Pocket PC...
Wondershare UniConverter helps convert formats...
</description></item><item><title>Download Classroom Spy Professional 5.4.11</title><pubDate> Sun, 26 Oct 2025 17:40:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-classroom-spy-professional-916.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-classroom-spy-professional-916.html
</guid><description>
Classroom Spy Professional is a software classroom management effective. Manage and track activities of all the computers of students remotely. Plus, you can share your screen with the activity record of the student, the computer controls for performance, limit the use of the Internet, the application blocks and more.
Classroom Spy Professional - software classroom management
The main features of Classroom Spy Professional
	Display live images of the remote computer.
	You can control...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Downloader 9.17.15</title><pubDate> Sun, 26 Oct 2025 17:39:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html
</guid><description>
YTD Youtube Downloader is an application that reliable and intuitive, allowing you to quickly download YouTube videos and save them to your computer. You can also convert the media files to the format desired video or extract audio streams and save separately. YTD Youtube Downloader lets you save your favorite clips of yourself from Youtube, Facebook, Vimeo and Dailymotion to your desktop. The software supports URLS from many web site hosting, multimedia and allows you to download desired...
</description></item><item><title>Download Remote Desktop Manager Enterprise 2025.3.20</title><pubDate> Sun, 26 Oct 2025 17:38:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-remote-desktop-manager-enterprise-242.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-remote-desktop-manager-enterprise-242.html
</guid><description>
Remote Desktop Manager Enterprise software is the complete management of remote connections and virtual machines from a single location, at the same time access support data online and cloud storage. Remote Desktop Manager supports multiple types of connections, not only connections for the protocol connect remote computer Remote Desktop Protocol (RDP).
Remote Desktop Manager easily add, edit, delete, share, organize and find your remote connection of you quickly. Compatible with...
</description></item><item><title>Download HardCopy Pro 4.18.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 26 Oct 2025 17:38:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hardcopy-pro-1018.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hardcopy-pro-1018.html
</guid><description>
HardCopy Pro is the screen capture utility, multipurpose, easy-to-use for Windows. Easy screen capture desktop and save easy.  DeskSoft HardCopy Pro can capture the screen area rectangle and the entire window. Images can be printed, saved, copied to clipboard, emailed, edited with any editing program, photos, etc. Many options allow the customization of all these actions with the needs of individual users.
HardCopy Pro - screen Capture Desktop
In addition, The captured images can be...
</description></item><item><title>Download Garden Planner 3.8.77</title><pubDate> Sun, 26 Oct 2025 17:37:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-garden-planner-186.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-garden-planner-186.html
</guid><description>
Garden Planner : If you want to create a garden plan, create a landscape by activity or simply be curious, then you can download Garden Planner .   Garden Planner is a program that helps the user to design a dream garden through the layout and arrangement of plants, plants, buildings and objects, creating living spaces. style is consistent with the user's criteria and standards.
Garden Planner application is very simple, just select bushes, other plants, trees, pond and drag them into...
</description></item><item><title>Download Full Convert Ultimate 25.08.1688</title><pubDate> Sun, 26 Oct 2025 17:36:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-full-convert-enterprise-997.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-full-convert-enterprise-997.html
</guid><description>
Full Convert Enterprise is a conversion software database. Full Convert Enterprise create all the tables, copy all of your data. Full Convert Enterprise has the custom features and mapped powerful at your disposal, your data will be moved out of the box without custom. Full Convert automatically adjusted the basis of your data and use copy modes optimized for each separate table to achieve information best possible quality.
Full Convert Enterprise - convert data base
Full Convert...
</description></item><item><title>Download Minimal Firewall 2.5.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 26 Oct 2025 17:33:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minimal-firewall-13877.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minimal-firewall-13877.html
</guid><description>
Minimal Firewall works in conjunction with Windows Firewall to block all unknown connections by default, prompting you to create application-based rules to mitigate malware, telemetry, and data leaks. Completely eliminate applications that call home without your knowledge. Minimal Firewall provides a more secure and integrated approach by interacting directly with the native Windows Firewall, eliminating the need for risky system modifications.
Core Features
	Lockdown Mode: The core...
</description></item><item><title>Download FastFolders 5.14.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 26 Oct 2025 17:33:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fastfolders-2968.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fastfolders-2968.html
</guid><description>
FastFolders is a simple application and reliable, allowing for quick access and easy to all content and files in your folders to increase productivity and improve the workflow of you. The app allows you to browse the entire folder structure without the need to open the folder and help you easily find the files needed. The utility will add a new item to the context menu of you, provides an overview of the directory structure of you. You can perform various actions, such as move or copy the...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaMonkey Gold 2024.2.0.3172 Beta</title><pubDate> Sun, 26 Oct 2025 17:32:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediamonkey-gold-231.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediamonkey-gold-231.html
</guid><description>
MediaMonkey Gold is music manager and music player multimedia for the music collection and iPod users. MediaMonkey lists the audio file of you as CD, OGG, WMA, MPC, FLAC, APE, WAV and MP3 and includes the edit smart card and an automatic file and folder to arrange your music library.
MediaMonkey Gold also has CD ripper, CD / DVD Burner, and audio converter for saving music, and manual or editor list automatically to create mixed music.
Features MediaMonkey Gold
	Automatically find...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cyber Privacy Suite 4.4.7</title><pubDate> Sun, 26 Oct 2025 17:32:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyber-privacy-suite-3944.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyber-privacy-suite-3944.html
</guid><description>
Cyber Privacy Suite software supports you protect the data privacy of their own. This comprehensive software helps you and your family stay safe at all times when using equipment or surfing the web. Cyber Privacy Suite against the threat of private harmful and actively determine where your information vulnerable or exposed. Cyber Privacy Suite protection, webcam, microphone, and the documentation required of you from the prying eyes and prevent information from your most precious into the...
</description></item><item><title>Download WindowManager 10.23.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 26 Oct 2025 17:32:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desksoft-windowmanager-573.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desksoft-windowmanager-573.html
</guid><description>
WindowManager is a software by DeskSoft dedicated to providing software utilities for windows. DeskSoft WindowManager is the window manager window to ensure your windows are placed exactly where you want. Software will help you to help you improve your work flow by remembering and restoring the position and size of the program and your window. The processing window can completely customize and you can set the special rules for the windows favorite or used most often.
WindowManager send...
</description></item><item><title>Download ScrollNavigator 5.16.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 26 Oct 2025 17:25:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-scrollnavigator-982.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-scrollnavigator-982.html
</guid><description>
ScrollNavigator is an application to create the custom profiles to help easy navigation for each application or the whole computer with the custom settings. ScrollNavigator helps you to scroll your documents horizontally and vertically. Just click and hold the right mouse button (or middle) anywhere in the window and move the mouse to scroll the window contents.
ScrollNavigator - navigation scroll button in mouse
ScrollNavigator also adds the ability to increase the speed for scroll...
</description></item><item><title>Download NirLauncher Package 1.30.21</title><pubDate> Sun, 26 Oct 2025 17:24:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nirlauncher-152.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nirlauncher-152.html
</guid><description>
NirLauncher is a package of more than 200 freeware utilities developed by Nirsoft, the NirLauncher application is provided free of charge for easy selection, use by feature classification. . Popular Nirsoft Utilities (many of them listed separately on taiwebs.com) NirLauncher includes network tools, password recovery tools, security cleaners, system utilities, programming tools, command line utilities and more.
NirLauncher's Versatile Utility
With this NirLauncher utility, users can...
</description></item><item><title>Download K-Lite Codec Pack Update 19.2.9</title><pubDate> Sun, 26 Oct 2025 17:24:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-update-5145.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-update-5145.html
</guid><description>
K-Lite Codec Pack Update is the update of the set of codecs and related tools. Codec stands for Compressor-decompressor. Codec is necessary to encode and decode (play) audio and video. K-Lite Codec Pack Update is designed as a user-friendly solution with users to play all movie files your. With Codec Pack K-Lite, you can play 99% of all the movies found on your computer. A number of packages codec is not friendly with computers, as they tend to slow down Windows, break down multimedia...
</description></item><item><title>Download ProcessKO 6.55</title><pubDate> Sun, 26 Oct 2025 17:23:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-processko-2977.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-processko-2977.html
</guid><description>
ProcessKO is a lightweight app, but strong will give you full control over your computer. This app allows you to quickly and easily kill all processes and programs hanging or running. This app is mainly targeted to experienced users and experts.
ProcessKO - control machine operation
ProcessKO allows you to stop any process quickly and efficiently, with just a few mouse clicks. You can also restart any process or any application in this program. The application does not require...
</description></item><item><title>Download TypeButler 1.13.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 26 Oct 2025 17:22:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-typebutler-7056.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-typebutler-7056.html
</guid><description>
TypeButler helps you type frequently used documents, from single words to entire sentences, paragraphs, emails, and more. This not only reduces the time required for text entry, but also eliminates the risk of typos. You can arrange your text blocks in a clear menu structure and select them with one click. TypeButler can input texts into any program, it can simulate complex keystrokes, and it can replace entered texts on the fly.
It can also be used to replace keystrokes with any other...
</description></item><item><title>Download CameraBag Pro 2026.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 26 Oct 2025 17:22:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-camerabag-pro-3504.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-camerabag-pro-3504.html
</guid><description>
CameraBag Pro is a photo editing tool and adjust the advanced and more than 250 filters once, click on your photo. CameraBag Pro has been the expert reviews more powerful photo-editing program conventional and less complex business software complex. Create photos and movies, engaging with the professional filters just by one click, or tweak and adjust the image settings to impress your friends, colleagues and your customers easier than ever.
CameraBag Pro - image editing...
</description></item><item><title>Download SmartCapture 3.22.5</title><pubDate> Sun, 26 Oct 2025 17:21:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-smartcapture-1019.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-smartcapture-1019.html
</guid><description>
SmartCapture a product of DeskSoft. This is a screen capture tool for professional window captures entire desktop and holding bowl moments on the computer screen. User interface clear and intuitive, with powerful features make it the ideal utility for everyone who wants to capture any contents of the desktop Windows. It can capture the rectangular area screen, whole objects, windows or screens and it can retrieve images from the imaging device.
SmartCapture - screenshot
The captured...
</description></item><item><title>Download 4KSoftware 4K Downloader 5.18.7</title><pubDate> Sun, 26 Oct 2025 17:21:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-downloader-3858.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-downloader-3858.html
</guid><description>
4K Downloader is a Windows application small but powerful to download and convert video in 4K and 8K Ultra HD from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion and thousands of other video-based websites. It speeds up your download by up to 5 times. Consider that most smart phones, TVS, computers, and tablets all support the high definition format, don't be surprised when many users want to enjoy quality content on their device. 4K Downloader is a lightweight software designed to help you grab videos...
</description></item><item><title>Download Imagine 2.3.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 26 Oct 2025 17:20:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-imagine-7369.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-imagine-7369.html
</guid><description>
Imagine is an application that allows you to view images and animations in a variety of formats, including JPG, BMP, PNG and GIF. With Imagine you can view file properties and EXIF ​​information, copy, move, delete and rename images. Additionally, you can also flip, resize and rotate them, swap colors, set transparency levels, import, export, and edit palettes, and change color depth.
Features of Imagine
	View and save image/animation files at lightning speed
	Multiple...
</description></item><item><title>Download Kalmuri 4.1.4</title><pubDate> Sun, 26 Oct 2025 17:20:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kalmuri-12521.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kalmuri-12521.html
</guid><description>
Kalmuri provides one of the simplest means of recording screen activity, working as both a snapshot utility and a screen recorder. It requires no installation and is ready to go at any time, waiting for your action quietly in the tray area, thus not disturbing your work.
Features of Kalmuri
	Supports video recording (specify entire screen and area)
	Entire screen, active program, window control, application area
	Supports PNG, JPG, BMP, GIF, MP4 file formats
	Supports saving documents...
</description></item></channel></rss>