<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 18:15:29 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 18:15:29 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download AnyDesk 9.6.10</title><pubDate> Tue, 10 Feb 2026 21:02:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anydesk-1321.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anydesk-1321.html
</guid><description>
AnyDesk is software computer control remote, easy connection with remote computer management and manipulation on the computer. After installing the AnyDesk up 2 the computer then you can easily use the software to provide technical support for a friend or family member or you have access to your computer while you away from home or office.
AnyDesk - control your computer remotely
The process of using very simple software, want to allow access to his computer, only need to provide for...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare PDFelement Pro 12.1.11.4032</title><pubDate> Tue, 10 Feb 2026 21:02:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-pdfelement-pro-105.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-pdfelement-pro-105.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare PDFelement Pro support users to convert PDF to office documents for easier use, modify in every situation. Is one of the software conversion material is rated best today, integrated with many features. We recommend that you should use experience software many useful features this.
Wondershare PDFelement Pro - conversion Fie PDF more features, multi-language
Wondershare PDFelement Pro what?
Convert PDF into Word, Excel, PowerPoint...
• Convert PDF and protected PDF into...
</description></item><item><title>Download Abelssoft YouTube Song Downloader Plus 2026 v26.06</title><pubDate> Tue, 10 Feb 2026 21:02:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-abelssoft-youtube-song-downloader-plus-111.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-abelssoft-youtube-song-downloader-plus-111.html
</guid><description>
Abelssoft YouTube Song Downloader Plus 2018.18.17 Program YouTube Song Downloader Plus will help you search the music and video files from YouTube, after you can download them at. To search for music you just need to enter song name in the required field and you will get results, then you can download all videos and audio files. The program can search the entire album, this function will help to find individual songs from separate albums, because of this we specify the name of the artist...
</description></item><item><title>Download HiBit Uninstaller 4.0.10 + Portable</title><pubDate> Tue, 10 Feb 2026 21:01:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hibit-uninstaller-3897.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hibit-uninstaller-3897.html
</guid><description>
HiBit Uninstaller offer alternative solution for applet "Programs and features" standard of Windows allows you to uninstall software.
Software HiBit Uninstaller offer you a list of all the programs currently installed and allows you to uninstall any item that does not leave any rest whatsoever. HiBit Uninstaller will first launch the application uninstall comes standard with software and after removal is complete, it will provide you scan every file, directory and registry entries left by...
</description></item><item><title>Download SeekFast 6.3 Build 2</title><pubDate> Tue, 10 Feb 2026 21:00:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-seekfast-7524.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-seekfast-7524.html
</guid><description>
SeekFast has the ability to quickly search for specific text in all documents on your computer. SeekFast then sorts the results in a way that makes it easy to find the text you're looking for, see its context, and open the file that contains it. All you have to do is select a folder to search for and enter search words or phrases - you'll get all the sentences they appear in within seconds. This is especially useful if you need to find something quickly.
SeekFast uses state-of-the-art...
</description></item><item><title>Download Syncios WhatsApp Transfer 2.5</title><pubDate> Tue, 10 Feb 2026 21:00:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncios-whatsapp-transfer-5944.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncios-whatsapp-transfer-5944.html
</guid><description>
Syncios WhatsApp Transfer helps to backup your WhatsApp history more easily than ever before. It allows you to backup and restore your WhatsApp iPhone/iPad/Android data in just one click. Syncios WhatsApp Transfer can meet all your needs for publishing WhatsApp conversations.
You can export and print the WhatsaS conversations; publish WhatsApp messages, photos, videos and audio files selectively or by a click.
The features of Syncios WhatsApp Transfer
	Why saves all WhatsApp content...
</description></item><item><title>Download PVS-Studio 7.41.103095.2136</title><pubDate> Tue, 10 Feb 2026 20:59:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pvs-studio-1480.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pvs-studio-1480.html
</guid><description>
PVS-Studio is software that performs static code analysis and generate a report to help programmers find and fix bugs. PVS-Studio implements a series of check code, it is also useful to search the prints wrong error and Copy-Paste. Examples of such errors: V501, V517, V522, V523, V3001.
The main value of static analysis is in regular use, hence the error is identified and corrected at the earliest stages. There's no point of wasting 50 hours to search for a fault can be found with static...
</description></item><item><title>Download Zoom Player Max 22.2 Beta 3</title><pubDate> Tue, 10 Feb 2026 20:59:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zoom-player-max-104.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zoom-player-max-104.html
</guid><description>
Zoom Player MAX help you to see the film on DVD, Blu-ray, Flash movies and HD format with high quality and the ability to display subtitles in English very well. The advantage of software is that takes up very little system resources to play the movie with quick speed, change the wallpaper options while viewing movies.
Zoom Player MAX is the movies, browse high-quality photos on the computer with the advantages such as compact size, quick start, built-in codec. The application supports...
</description></item><item><title>Download PanFone WhatsApp Transfer 2.5.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 10 Feb 2026 20:58:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-panfone-whatsapp-transfer-5580.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-panfone-whatsapp-transfer-5580.html
</guid><description>
PanFone WhatsApp Transfer is the best solution to backup, restore and transfer WhatsApp iOS / Android messages as well as export WhatsApp messages to HTML and CSV files. This PanFone WhatsApp Transfer easily and securely transferred iOS to Android WhatsApp can be a useful tool to help you backup and restore WhatsApp data. It will not overwrite or delete previous backups. You can restore WhatsApp backups to your phone any time you want.
Seamlessly transfer all WhatsApp chat history,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Disk Sorter Ultimate 17.8.12 + Server + Pro</title><pubDate> Tue, 10 Feb 2026 20:58:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-disk-sorter-ultimate-1464.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-disk-sorter-ultimate-1464.html
</guid><description>
Disk Sorter Ultimate is the utility classification file lightweight and simple helps people detect files on most types of drives, as well as manage them according to many different criteria to create more capacity on the disc. This app allows you to search through the 500,000 files, have storage capacity of 2TB. To start sorting, all what you have to do is select a directory, drive or server and click the button "Classification". You should know that you can search for the type specific...
</description></item><item><title>Download MobiPDF: PDF Editor &amp;amp; Scanner 11.12.270246</title><pubDate> Tue, 10 Feb 2026 20:57:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pdf-extra-scan-edit-sign-8390.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pdf-extra-scan-edit-sign-8390.html
</guid><description>
PDF Extra PDF Editor &amp;amp; Scanner is a mobile application that allows users to create, edit and sign PDF documents on their Android or iOS devices. It includes many tools and features that make it easy to work with PDF files, including scanning, editing, and signing. This application also allows users to combine multiple PDF files into a single document and export PDF files in various file formats, such as JPEG, PNG, and Microsoft Word.
Features of PDF Extra PDF Editor &amp;amp;...
</description></item><item><title>Download All in One Unit Converter Pro 4.5.9</title><pubDate> Tue, 10 Feb 2026 20:56:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-all-in-one-unit-converter-tool-9570.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-all-in-one-unit-converter-tool-9570.html
</guid><description>
Most of us need to convert different units and do some scientific calculations like to convert Length units we may need to convert inches to mm, convert inches to cm, convert inches to feet, convert cm to inches and convert Weight units like convert kg to lbs, convert lbs to kg or convert Farenheit to Celcius etc.
So, for scientific calculations and to help you easily convert units, the All-in-One Multi-Unit Conversion Calculator is an engineering Unit conversion calculator that...
</description></item><item><title>Download Compass and GPS tools 30.0.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 10 Feb 2026 20:56:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-compass-and-gps-tools-8300.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-compass-and-gps-tools-8300.html
</guid><description>
Compass and GPS tool is a compass and GPS tool. There are many apps available on the Google Play Store or other app stores that provide compass and GPS functionality for Android devices.
Compass and GPS tool features
	GPS Essentials: This app provides many GPS-related tools such as compass, speedometer, and waypoint navigation.
	GPS Navigation &amp;amp; Maps: This app offers turn-by-turn voice navigation, offline maps, and real-time traffic updates.
	Compass: This app provides a simple...
</description></item><item><title>Download Twilight: Blue light filter 14.24 build 605</title><pubDate> Tue, 10 Feb 2026 20:56:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-twilight-blue-light-filter-12193.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-twilight-blue-light-filter-12193.html
</guid><description>
Are you having trouble falling asleep? Is your child hyperactive when playing with the tablet before going to bed? The Twilight app helps your device's screen adapt to the time of day. It filters the blue light emitted from your phone or tablet after sunset and protects your eyes with a soft and pleasant red filter. Filter intensity is smoothly adjusted to the solar cycle based on your local sunset and sunrise times.
Get more from Twilight
	- Reading in bed: Twilight is more...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Photoshop Express Photo Editor 17.9.22 build 1996</title><pubDate> Tue, 10 Feb 2026 20:56:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-photoshop-express-photo-editor-02en-8249.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-photoshop-express-photo-editor-02en-8249.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Photoshop Express is a mobile photo editing app that allows users to edit photos quickly and easily on their Android devices. Join millions of creators who trust and use Adobe Photoshop Express, one of the best photo editors and collage makers on Android for fast, easy, and powerful editing on mobile devices.
Premium version / No Adobe ID account required
Features of Adobe Photoshop Express APK
	Basic photo editing: Users can crop, rotate, adjust brightness, contrast and...
</description></item><item><title>Download PhotoRoom AI Photo Editor 2026.07.01 build 2273</title><pubDate> Tue, 10 Feb 2026 20:55:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-photoroom-ai-photo-editor-10083.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-photoroom-ai-photo-editor-10083.html
</guid><description>
PhotoRoom is an all-in-one app for great visual content editing, design, and optimization that helps you run your business from your phone. Remove or erase photo backgrounds, use templates, and create your own content. The app will automatically crop objects and people in your photos. With just one tap, you can remove the background and create highlight content that showcases a product or a person. Edit images, add text or logo, stickers, create collages....
What you can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Smart Tools mini 1.3.4 build 48</title><pubDate> Tue, 10 Feb 2026 20:54:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-smart-tools-mini-9669.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-smart-tools-mini-9669.html
</guid><description>
Smart Tools mini is a new package optimized for devices without a magnetometer. Half of new Android devices do not have a compass sensor (Moto G4, Galaxy J, Galaxy Tab4...). Surely this application will work well on all Android devices.
It includes 5 professional sets with a total of 15 tools
	Set 1. Length, Angle, Slope, Level, Thread: Smart Ruler Pro
	Set 2. Sound meter, Vibration meter: Sound Meter Pro
	Set of 3. Flashlight, Magnifier, Mirror: Smart Light Pro
	Set 4. Unit,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Duolingo: language lessons 6.65.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 10 Feb 2026 20:54:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-duolingo-language-lessons-8265.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-duolingo-language-lessons-8265.html
</guid><description>
Duolingo is a popular language learning app that offers interactive lessons to help users learn new languages. This application offers many languages for you to choose from, including Spanish, French, German, Italian, Portuguese, Chinese, Japanese and many more.
This app offers an gamified learning experience with interactive lessons, exercises, and quizzes designed to help users learn new words, phrases, and grammar rules. This app is designed to be easy to use and suitable for people...
</description></item><item><title>Download StbEmu (Pro) 2.0.20</title><pubDate> Tue, 10 Feb 2026 20:54:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-stbemu-pro-9840.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-stbemu-pro-9840.html
</guid><description>
StbEmu is an application for Android 5.0+, allowing downloading IPTV web portals, designed to run on IPTV STB (Set-Top-Box), on devices running Android, such as phones, tablets tablets and TV boxes. Currently, the application supports simulation of many STBs created by the Ukrainian company Infomir, such as MAG 250, MAG 270 or MAG 322.
StbEmu (Pro) for IPTV: Remember that this application is configured for a demo IPTV portal for testing purposes. If you want to use the app, you must...
</description></item><item><title>Download Bluelight Filter for Eye Care 6.6.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 10 Feb 2026 20:53:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-bluelight-filter-for-eye-care-8192.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-bluelight-filter-for-eye-care-8192.html
</guid><description>
Blue light from smartphones or tablets causes eye strain and makes it difficult to sleep at night. This app adjusts your screen color to reduce blue light and relax your eyes, helping you sleep better.
Features of Blue Light Filter for Eye Care
	Free screen filter app to protect your eyes
	Screen filter with natural colors
	Easy operation
	Turn on or off quickly and easily
	Automatic start
	Eye care on your smartphone or tablet
	This app works on most smartphones like Samsung Galaxy,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Unit Converter 2.2.66</title><pubDate> Tue, 10 Feb 2026 20:53:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-unit-converter-8436.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-unit-converter-8436.html
</guid><description>
Unit converter is a simple, smart and elegant tool with more than 44 types of units used in daily life. This is the only unit converter app in Google Play Store that has such a wide range of unit conversion features with a very simple and easy to use interface.
Features of Unit Converter for Android
	Built-in real-time currency conversion with 150+ world currencies and their latest exchange rates.
	44 Unit Categories, 12700+ Unit Conversions
	Smart Tools - Bubble Level, Compass,...
</description></item><item><title>Download AppKiller: close apps 26.2.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 10 Feb 2026 20:53:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-appkiller-close-apps-11977.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-appkiller-close-apps-11977.html
</guid><description>
AppKiller: close apps allows users to quickly and effectively kill background applications that are consuming system resources, such as RAM and CPU, which can help improve overall speed and performance. device responsiveness. By freeing up system resources, users can also see increased battery life because their devices are no longer consuming power on unnecessary background processes. This can be especially beneficial for users who use their devices throughout the day and need to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Calculator Plus with History 8.1.9</title><pubDate> Tue, 10 Feb 2026 20:52:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-calculator-plus-with-history-10531.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-calculator-plus-with-history-10531.html
</guid><description>
Plus Calculator with History is the perfect calculator for Android. It remembers everything you calculate and allows you to review it at any time, which is perfect for me when shopping, doing homework, balancing my checkbook, or even helping with taxes. And if you need to quit your job and go do something else, I'll have it all ready for you when you get back. You'll never need to re-enter the same calculation twice.
Features of Calculator Plus with History
	Show your calculations in...
</description></item><item><title>Download Windy.app - Enhanced forecast 87.2.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 10 Feb 2026 20:52:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-windyapp-windy-weather-map-10522.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-windyapp-windy-weather-map-10522.html
</guid><description>
WINDY - wind, wave and weather forecast app for surfers, kitesurfers, windsurfers and sailors.
Features
	Wind reports, forecasts and statistics: wind compass, wind map, wind speed meter, wind gusts and wind direction. It is very useful for extreme wind sports.
	Weather history (archived) 2012-2016: view wind data, temperature (day and night) and atmospheric pressure. The weather archive will help you choose the best month to go to that location.
	Local forecast from NOAA: temperature...
</description></item><item><title>Download Moviebase: Movies &amp;amp; TV Guide 5.7.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 10 Feb 2026 20:52:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-moviebase-track-tv-shows-8175.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-moviebase-track-tv-shows-8175.html
</guid><description>
Are you looking for a useful movie finder and movie tracker app to help you find movie ratings, movie reviews, movie recommendations, movie trailers and more? Try Moviebase – Movie Manager. Moviebase is the most popular movie finder and movie tracker app where you can find movies, series, seasons, episodes. Movie reviews, movie trailers, movie descriptions and actors from the largest community database TMDB.
Explore the world of movies and series from Movie Tracker
	Explore a huge...
</description></item></channel></rss>