<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 19:56:08 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 19:56:08 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download LobbyBrowser 4.5</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Sep 2025 18:06:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lobbybrowser-14137.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lobbybrowser-14137.html
</guid><description>
LobbyBrowser is a lightweight, user-friendly web browser based on Chromium with a minimalist design, focusing on simplicity and accessibility. The download size is less than 1 MB and it is free to use, with no ads or hidden updates. The browser supports more than 10 search engines, allowing users to easily switch between them to compare results. Colorful browsing history helps to quickly identify different types of URLs or search strings.
Features of LobbyBrowser
	Use anonymously and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Reuschtools CopyWin 4.66</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Sep 2025 18:00:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reuschtools-copywin-14136.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reuschtools-copywin-14136.html
</guid><description>
Reuschtools CopyWin is a versatile program designed to copy the contents of your Windows drive, including all files and programs, to another drive, USB or MicroSD card. This is especially useful for upgrading or replacing storage hardware, as it simplifies the migration process. The tool does not require installation; it can be used by running the executable file, but requires administrative rights to operate. CopyWin also offers features like incremental backups after the initial backup,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Bulk Image Downloader 6.59</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Sep 2025 16:47:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bulk-image-downloader-121.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bulk-image-downloader-121.html
</guid><description>
Bulk Image Downloader is an application specially developed to help you download the images in full size from the Bulk Image Downloader most of the web gallery or web forum.
Bulk Image Downloader what?
Support image storage - BID works with almost every archive page popular images, such as flickr, imagevenue, imagefap, imagebam, etc.
Social networking sites - BID supports downloading from sites such as facebook, myspace, and twitter as tweetphoto.com, twitpic.com, yfrog.com
Images are...
</description></item><item><title>Download StartAllBack 3.9.15.5310</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Sep 2025 16:46:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-startallback-6857.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-startallback-6857.html
</guid><description>
With the official release of Windows 11, chances are that most of you want to try it out. As the name suggests, StartAllBack is a small, lightweight tool that can help you enjoy the power of the new operating system while keeping the look and feel, especially because main work area, desktop of Windows 7, Windows 10 as taskbars and start menu styles.
StartAllBack is specially designed for Windows 11 and will not work on any older operating systems. If you want to get the start menu back...
</description></item><item><title>Download MedCalc 23.3.7</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Sep 2025 16:45:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-medcalc-1536.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-medcalc-1536.html
</guid><description>
MedCalc is a statistical software for biomedical research can analyze many performance curve system with a set of rich functionality, chart types and advanced module. MedCalc was designed to meet the needs and requirements of the study nature and aims to analyze the statistical calculations of the project. This software provides the tools and means essential to analyze the characteristic curve of the system (ROC), drawing data and perform the statistical calculations.
MedCalc -...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cutting Optimization Pro 5.18.14</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Sep 2025 16:45:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cutting-optimization-pro-6573.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cutting-optimization-pro-6573.html
</guid><description>
Cutting Optimization Pro is a cutting software used to obtain the optimal cut layout for one-dimensional (1D) and two-dimensional (2D) pieces. The software also allows you to define and process complex products, such as desks, tables, cabinets, cabinets, bookshelves... Cutting Optimization Pro can be used to cut rectangular panels made of glass, wood, metal, plastic or any other material used in industrial applications.
Features of Cutting Optimization Pro
	Optimize 1D and 2D in the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Auslogics File Recovery Pro 12.1.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Sep 2025 16:45:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-auslogics-file-recovery-pro-1893.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-auslogics-file-recovery-pro-1893.html
</guid><description>
Auslogics File Recovery Pro is an effective program and easy to use will recover files accidentally deleted quickly and the most simple. Auslogics File Recovery Pro is the most advanced version, it contains all the basic features of version Auslogics File Recovery Free upgrades and enhancements add a number of new features for users who pay a fee. Often we delete a file, then clear the recycle bin, and files lost. Software programs sometimes encounter problems while dealing with a file and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Geekbench AI Corporate 1.5.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Sep 2025 16:44:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-geekbench-ai-corporate-12385.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-geekbench-ai-corporate-12385.html
</guid><description>
Geekbench AI is a cross-platform AI benchmark that uses real-world machine learning tasks to evaluate the performance of AI workloads. Geekbench AI measures your CPU, GPU, and NPU to determine whether your device is ready for today's and tomorrow's advanced machine learning applications.
Evaluating real-world AI performance:
Real-world AI performance
	Geekbench AI runs ten AI workloads, each with three different types of data, giving you a multidimensional picture of on-device AI...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Acrobat Pro DC 2025.001.20672 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Sep 2025 16:44:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-001en-adobe-acrobat-pro-458.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-001en-adobe-acrobat-pro-458.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Acrobat Pro DC is a comprehensive software that helps you create and edit the PDF&amp;nbsp;document, or create form, sign, protect PDF, connect, split PDF, export PDF to various formats. The Acrobat Pro DC is the latest version of Adobe with improvements in the interface with the polished ribbon bar and the ability to create and handle pdf files as well as its male versions.
The highlight of the Acrobat Pro DC is probably the ability to connect, store documents on the cloud, you can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Viber for PC 26.1.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Sep 2025 16:42:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-viber-2406.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-viber-2406.html
</guid><description>
Viber is a software of instant messaging, based on VoIP protocols, multi-platform due to the Viber Media development for smart phones used to send sms and make calls over the internet. Along with text messaging, users can exchange images, video and audio.
Viber - software news message, chat online
This is a program that is quite popular is mainly designed for mobile phones, but now we are talking about the version for Windows, so immediately. It will allow you to send messages to other...
</description></item><item><title>Download ZebraDesigner Professional 3.3.0.89</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Sep 2025 16:41:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zebradesigner-pro-7203.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zebradesigner-pro-7203.html
</guid><description>
ZebraDesigner Pro is an easy-to-use disc label design software that helps users create high-quality barcode labels quickly. With ZebraDesigner Pro software, you can easily create a variety of labels, whether simple or complex. Thanks to its user-friendly, Windows-based interface, no training or technical know-how is required. Another benefit is that design and editing is done in one window.
ZebraDesigner Pro provides users with the most used disc label design features, and includes a...
</description></item><item><title>Download Auslogics Duplicate File Finder Professional 11.1.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Sep 2025 16:41:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-auslogics-duplicate-file-finder-professional-12706.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-auslogics-duplicate-file-finder-professional-12706.html
</guid><description>
Auslogics Duplicate File Finder Professional is a software tool designed to help users identify and remove duplicate files from their systems effectively. When disk space starts to run out, you need a tool that allows you to clear memory in addition to regular trash cleaning. A duplicate finder is one of the best options that can often delete gigabytes on any computer.
Features of Auslogics Duplicate File Finder Professional
	Scan most types of drives for duplicates: With Duplicate...
</description></item><item><title>Download Directory Opus Pro 13.18.2 Beta</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Sep 2025 16:40:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-opus-pro-779.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-opus-pro-779.html
</guid><description>
Directory Opus Pro is a software replacement for Explorer with traditional strength and function more than any manager other files. Directory Opus Pro full support for high DPI screen (for example 4K and 5K) with the rename dialog is redesigned, with new features. Besides being a recording macro only allows you to perform mass renaming complex that don't need regular expressions. In addition, Directory Opus Pro also enhances the ability to script.Better handling of renaming recursive and...
</description></item><item><title>Download WizFlow Flowcharter Professional 7.45.2215</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Sep 2025 16:40:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wizflow-flowcharter-professional-3604.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wizflow-flowcharter-professional-3604.html
</guid><description>
WizFlow Flowcharter Professional is a tool for drawing diagrams and diagram easy-to-use, feature-rich, abundant for Windows. WizFlow lets you define "styles" shape using more than a hundred shapes and arrow heads to be determined first. Save your styles in the template to set the method of mapping your own. WizFlow comes with the template complete diagram to help you get started. WizFlow can create flowcharts and diagrams similar with minimal effort. When you draw a diagram of WizFlow...
</description></item><item><title>Download FileLocator Pro 2022 Build 3530</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Sep 2025 16:39:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-filelocator-pro-1056.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-filelocator-pro-1056.html
</guid><description>
FileLocator Pro is software manage files and search function the file quickly the software and data. FileLocator Pro helps you find things quickly. The unique feature of it allows the extraction of information in all file formats the most obscure.
FileLocator Pro - file Manager
The features of FileLocator Pro
	Search algorithm based on the C ++ multi-threading for ultra-fast
	Search for network drive by mapped drive or UNC paths
	Support regular expressions for file name and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Auslogics Duplicate File Finder 11.1.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Sep 2025 16:39:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-auslogics-duplicate-file-finder-1248.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-auslogics-duplicate-file-finder-1248.html
</guid><description>
Auslogics Duplicate File Finder is an application completely free on taiwebs.com user support, Windows search and delete the duplicate files due to the process of copying and storage for long days on your computer. The first thing the user sees is the software interface is very simple and easy to use. After process launch, Auslogics Duplicate File Finder will find and delete duplicate files from it will liberate space on the hard drive of your computer by finding and eliminate the...
</description></item><item><title>Download QuadSpinner Gaea 2.2.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Sep 2025 16:38:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quadspinner-gaea-3870.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quadspinner-gaea-3870.html
</guid><description>
QuadSpinner Gaea is design software terrain, sophisticated and modern for results the top in moments. The top tools of QuadSpinner Gaea makes realism became the basis. Workflows are streamlined, allowing you to easily gain visibility and work in parallel with your team. Interface is extremely modern and our multitude of gadgets stimulate creativity, not limit it. Working at Gaea very interesting and can help you set a performance standard new.
QuadSpinner Gaea - design software...
</description></item><item><title>Download EDGE Diagrammer 7.45.2215</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Sep 2025 16:38:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-edge-diagrammer-9462.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-edge-diagrammer-9462.html
</guid><description>
EDGE Diagrammer is a software application used to create graphical diagrams, especially in the field of systems engineering. The term "EDGE" stands for "Enhanced Diagram Graphics Environment". It provides a user-friendly interface and a set of tools for designing and documenting complex systems, processes, and workflows.
EDGE Diagrammer is all you need for block diagrams, flowcharts, organization charts, family trees, data flow diagrams and more. Free extension packs are available to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Geekbench Pro 6.5</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Sep 2025 15:46:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-geekbench-pro-606.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-geekbench-pro-606.html
</guid><description>
Geekbench Pro 4 gauge power your system and let you know whether your computer is ready to roar up. Mobile device or computer to your desk how strong? Each workload CPU model a task or application in the real world, to ensure meaningful results. The trial is very complex, avoid the incidents with simple patterns, memory access, simple and push the limits of your system.
Features Geekbench Pro
Calculate the benchmark
	Measuring the calculation performance of your GPU with benchmark...
</description></item><item><title>Download IK Multimedia Tonex Max 1.10.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Sep 2025 15:45:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ik-multimedia-tonex-max-7877.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ik-multimedia-tonex-max-7877.html
</guid><description>
TONEX software uses groundbreaking AI Machine Modeling technology to let you model the sound of any amp, cabinet, or combo and turn it into a plug-in, all with precision sounds are almost indistinguishable from reality. You can instantly play up to the more than 1,000 already available Melody Models along with browsing, performing, and downloading more and more Melody Models available on TONEX in ToneNET.
Features of IK Multimedia Tonex Max
	Modeled tone generator, player,...
</description></item><item><title>Download MusConv 4.10.414 Lifetime</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Sep 2025 15:45:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html
</guid><description>
MusConv transfers playlists, albums, followed artists and liked songs across a variety of services – Spotify, Apple Music, Amazon Music, YouTube, YouTube Music, iTunes, Deezer, Tidal, SoundCloud, Pandora and more 125 music services!
Features of MusConv Ultimate
	Transfer playlists, albums, followed artists and liked tracks between over 125 music servicesManage playlists (Delete, Merge, Split, Copy...)
	More than 125 music services supported
	Access DAILY updated music charts on...
</description></item><item><title>Download Calibre 8.10.0 + Portable</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Sep 2025 15:44:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-calibre-1669.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-calibre-1669.html
</guid><description>
Calibre  is an eBook library management application that allows you to manage your eBook collection, convert eBooks between different formats, Sync with popular e-reading devices and read your e-books with included viewer. You can sort books by author, title, date and other details, download meta information and book covers, add personalized tags and comments, and view your images in the cover display.
Collection of essential tools for adding metadata editing books or managing your...
</description></item><item><title>Download VovSoft AI Requester 4.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Sep 2025 15:43:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-ai-requester-8997.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-ai-requester-8997.html
</guid><description>
Vovsoft AI Requester is a program that can connect to OpenAI API easily. The software provides users with a reliable and easy-to-use interface that seamlessly integrates with the latest AI technologies, including GPT-3.5 and GPT-4.
Just like ChatGPT, you can connect to the OpenAI platform and start chatting with powerful AI bots capable of giving intelligent responses to a variety of queries and questions. The software is designed to be user-friendly and intuitive, allowing even...
</description></item><item><title>Download AutoHideMouseCursor 5.85</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Sep 2025 15:43:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-autohidemousecursor-4104.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-autohidemousecursor-4104.html
</guid><description>
AutoHideMouseCursor is a Microsoft Windows application mobile mini allows you to hide the cursor, if the mouse is not active for a period of time. With AutoHideMouseCursor you can automatically hide the mouse cursor with the timer can be customized this is utility desktop perfect when the cursor is too annoying to them, such as when used with the application handling the text because often when you add pointers, text and cover text.
AutoHideMouseCursor - Hide mouse cursor
User...
</description></item><item><title>Download Brave Browser 1.82.161</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Sep 2025 15:42:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-brave-browser-2874.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-brave-browser-2874.html
</guid><description>
Brave Browser is a browser based on Chromium, the basic principle is that operation fast and privacy of users. The program can block pop-up windows and other ads, plus it blocked the mechanism for monitoring the online activities of your. Therefore, you can purchase and safely browse the website you are interested in without having to worry about the fact that your activity will be monitored and then you will be shown the necessary advertising or service provider of parties...
</description></item></channel></rss>