<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 15:37:23 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 15:37:23 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Wondershare PDFelement Pro 12.0.2.3719</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 17:44:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-pdfelement-pro-105.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-pdfelement-pro-105.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare PDFelement Pro support users to convert PDF to office documents for easier use, modify in every situation. Is one of the software conversion material is rated best today, integrated with many features. We recommend that you should use experience software many useful features this.
Wondershare PDFelement Pro - conversion Fie PDF more features, multi-language
Wondershare PDFelement Pro what?
Convert PDF into Word, Excel, PowerPoint...
• Convert PDF and protected PDF into...
</description></item><item><title>Download VueScan Pro 9.8.47</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 17:44:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vuescan-pro-75.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vuescan-pro-75.html
</guid><description>
VueScan Pro l  is one of the software  Scan quality pictures  First and appeared quite soon,  VueScan Pro  always asserted its No. 1 position on the technology pages, awards as well as user reviews. Through many versions, VueScan Pro 9 is greatly improved in terms of interface and features. Supporting most popular image formats today, this software will help you scan images quickly, easy to use and high quality output. With the color balance mode, you won't have to worry about blurring the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Active Partition Recovery Ultimate 25.1.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 17:43:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-active-partition-recovery-ultimate-611.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-active-partition-recovery-ultimate-611.html
</guid><description>
Active@ Partition Recovery Ultimate is a data recovery tool in the end. In addition to the Professional features, it also contains an ISO image that can boot (based on WinPE Active @ Boot Disk Lite) that you can burn to CD-ROM or write to a USB Flash drive and boot Windows from CD-ROM / USB to recover partitions (including the system) as well as to restore files and special folder from within the Windows environment familiar.
The final version includes Active@ LiveCD (recovery...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft Office 2021-2024 Professional Plus VL (64-bit) 2508 Build 19127.20222 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 17:43:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-office-2021-6670.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-office-2021-6670.html
</guid><description>
Since the end of February 2021, Microsoft has announced two new versions of Office 2021 including: Office 2021 and Office LTSC. Reportedly, Office 2021 is the next version of Office 2019, promising to bring users a better experience in the new Word, Excel or PowerPoint tools.
With each office user, the Microsoft Office toolkit is essential and indispensable software in the job. Microsoft Office has undergone numerous editions from Office 2010, 2013, 2016, 2019 to Microsoft 365 developed...
</description></item><item><title>Download AVS Video Editor 11.1.2.42</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 17:42:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs-video-editor-426.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs-video-editor-426.html
</guid><description>
AVS Video Editor is software professional video editing for windows with full features useful, easy-to-use.  When using AVS Video Editor you can record a video, to impose various effects, create and burn DVD, export movies to various video formats, convert video to iPod, PSP, mobile phones and the other portable device.
Features AVS Video Editor
Format support
	AVS Video Editor supports all major video formats. Edit and save the video file in the codec AVI, VOB, MP4, DVD, WMV, 3GP,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft Office 2024 Professional Plus LTSC v2408 Build 17932.20540 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 17:41:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-office-2024-professional-plus-64-bit-10679.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-office-2024-professional-plus-64-bit-10679.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft has officially announced the final version of the Office 2024 release for Windows and Mac users. After releasing a preview version in the first half of this year, the product has been finalized and is now available to users. Office 2024 includes updated versions of apps from the Word 2024, Excel 2024, PowerPoint 2024, Outlook 2024, Access 2024, and Publisher 2024 suites.
Office 2024 includes virtually every change that has been added to the suite of programs in Office 365 over...
</description></item><item><title>Download Advanced Installer Architect 23.0.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 17:40:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-installer-128.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-installer-128.html
</guid><description>
Advanced Installer is a Windows utility designed to help you build the package Windows Installer in a working environment clean and intuitive.
Although it has many parameters dedicated but the user interface is very simple and gives users the ability to create new projects by selecting the type, namely installer (for example: application Visual Studio or .NET, pack 32/64-bit mixture), Java , updates, support, mobile devices, and other things.
Advanced Installer - An environment for...
</description></item><item><title>Download vMix Pro 28.0.0.42</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 17:40:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vmix-pro-930.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vmix-pro-930.html
</guid><description>
vMix Pro is software production, recording and streaming live events. Create the products professional video in HD, SD and even 4K. vMix is a software Video Mixer and Switcher that utilizes the latest advances in computer hardware to provide live mix HD video, a task previously only possible on hardware mixers expensive dedicated.
vMix Pro - Production, create video
The features of vMix Pro
	Has the ability to create 4K videos, HD and SD.
	Support for webcam and capture card.
	NDITM...
</description></item><item><title>Download DaVinci Resolve Studio 20.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 17:39:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-davinci-resolve-studio-1072.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-davinci-resolve-studio-1072.html
</guid><description>
DaVinci Resolve Studio is professional video editing and color grading software developed by Blackmagic Design. This is an enhanced version of the free DaVinci Resolve software, providing additional features and capabilities for professional video editing, color correction, and post-production.
One of the outstanding features of DaVinci Resolve Studio is its powerful color correction capabilities. It provides a comprehensive set of tools and features for advanced color correction,...
</description></item><item><title>Download AVS Video Converter 14.1.2.42</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 17:39:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs-video-converter-427.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs-video-converter-427.html
</guid><description>
AVS Video Converter is a software to convert video format, burn VCD, SVCD, DVD, editor video raise.  AVS Video Converter can convert the formats AVI, MPEG, WMV, DVD to the formats AVI, MPEG, WMV, RM, burn DVD, SVCD or VCD, package conversion, editing, effects and filters, video overlay, extract audio from video and save in a file, separate audio, extract a frame (frame) and save as images, split into segments and connect video, rotate video, more in the form of text, banners, logos,...
</description></item><item><title>Download CLO Standalone OnlineAuth 2025.1.166</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 17:38:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-clo-standalone-2806.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-clo-standalone-2806.html
</guid><description>
CLO Standalone is a powerful software to design 3D clothes and outfits. Nowadays, computer plays a prominent role in the industry and the different industries use a variety of techniques and computer techniques to increase the quality and quantity of their products. In the garment industry, it is important to design new templates for clothing to meet the needs of customers and diversify. Aware of this demand, programmers and software companies have launched many products to help the...
</description></item><item><title>Download AllMapSoft Offline Map Maker 8.350</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 17:37:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-offline-map-maker-656.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-offline-map-maker-656.html
</guid><description>
AllMapSoft Offline Map Maker is software create, organize, offline map from Google Maps, Yahoo maps, Bing maps and Openstreetmap. You can view offline maps downloaded with map viewer offline. And you can zoom out or zoom in the offline map or export map under the file format .BMP with file world xxx.bpw, and can output files xxx.map for OziExplorer. If you want to make a offline map of your city by yourself, it is very useful for you.
Features AllMapSoft Offline Map Maker
	You can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Windows PowerShell 7.5.3</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 17:37:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-powershell-4734.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-powershell-4734.html
</guid><description>
Windows PowerShell is a tool / framework to configure and automate multi-platform works well with the existing tools and is optimized to handle structured data (e.g. JSON, CSV, XML, etc.), REST API and object model. This software has more than 130 commands (cmdlets), the command dedicated is designed to use the specific function, can perform many types of work, from service or administration process to the task manipulation book or object.
You can easily manage locally or remotely,...
</description></item><item><title>Download AVS Audio Converter 11.1.2.42</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 17:36:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs-audio-converter-1195.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs-audio-converter-1195.html
</guid><description>
AVS Audio Converter is a program that convert audio files from this format to other formats support many different formats. Support converting WAV, OGG Vorbis, MP3, MP2, Microsoft ADPCM, WMA, VOX, AAC, M4A, AMR and other audio formats. Before transition, the program determines the frequency, number of channels and other parameters of audio files. In addition, the AVS Audio Converter allows you to make settings for the format MP3 and OGG formats when converting audio files and change the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Bandizip Enterprise 7.40</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 17:36:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bandizip-enterprise-4146.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bandizip-enterprise-4146.html
</guid><description>
Bandizip Enterprise is a hosted application intuitive and fast supports WinZip, 7-Zip, and WinRAR, as well as other archive formats. Bandizip Enterprise supported archive files ZIP, 7Z, RAR, ALZ, EGG, TAR, BH, LZH, GZ, BZ2, ISO, CAB, WIM, XZ, ARJ, and Z and user can create files self-extracting (.EXE) and archive files multi-volume (split). Bandizip Enterprise has very fast Zip algorithm for compression &amp;amp; extraction by "fast drag and drop" and "High Speed Archiving"...
</description></item><item><title>Download Boot-US 4.2.3</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 17:35:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-boot-us-4428.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-boot-us-4428.html
</guid><description>
Boot-US is an application powerful and effective to boot manager, allowing you to easily make use of all the operating system is installed on the hard drive without any effort. You can use all its system independently with each other without any interference whatsoever. This application can be installed in MS Windows.
Boot-US - boot Manager
Boot-US is integrated with many features, giving you the ability to use the different operating system without hassle. Application will fit all of...
</description></item><item><title>Download DesktopOK 12.12</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 17:34:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopok-1635.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopok-1635.html
</guid><description>
DesktopOK is software save and restore the positions of icons. DesktopOK also offers a solution small but effective for the user to change the screen resolution often. DesktopOK is not installed and can be executed easily from the desktop, and can be carried on a small USB or memory device to another. Start of the program. The first time you use the program, the program will show you screen license. Free program and license info is only displayed the first time (on each PC).
DesktopOK -...
</description></item><item><title>Download dslrBooth Photo Booth Software Pro 7.48.0910.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 17:34:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dslrbooth-photo-booth-software-666.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dslrbooth-photo-booth-software-666.html
</guid><description>
Photo Booth Software is a software to create, list and combine the images back together in the same theme as travel, haloween. Created by the professional photographer for the operator photo booth at all skill levels, photo booth software dslrBooth built from scratch with the sole purpose of running the photo booth. The software uses the latest technology to provide you and your guests, high quality prints and the ability to share photos and GIF on the means of social media including...
</description></item><item><title>Download AutoPowerOptionsOK 6.21</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 17:33:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-autopoweroptionsok-1820.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-autopoweroptionsok-1820.html
</guid><description>
AutoPowerOptionsOK is a small program that can automatically turn off your screen, put your computer in sleep mode or switch between the power options. Each action can be triggered based on the absence of events keyboard and / or mouse for a specified time interval. For example, you can automatically turn off the screen if the mouse or keyboard has not been used in 10 minutes.
AutoPowerOptionsOK - power Management automatically
AutoPowerOptionsOK is a compact tool designed to help you...
</description></item><item><title>Download XL-Connector 3.6.10.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 17:33:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xl-connector-12415.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xl-connector-12415.html
</guid><description>
XL-Connector is a popular plugin that securely integrates Excel and Salesforce to export, import, refresh and transform data seamlessly with ultra-fast api connection. It provides Salesforce administrators with a comprehensive toolbox that easily performs data and metadata management activities in a familiar Excel environment.
Features
Export from Salesforce to Excel
	Get data from existing Salesforce reports or build your own SOQL queries directly into Excel.
Import data into...
</description></item><item><title>Download Office 2021 Professional Plus (64-bit) LTSC v2108 Build 14334.20296 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 17:33:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-office-professional-plus-2021-64-bit-7187.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-office-professional-plus-2021-64-bit-7187.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft 365 is a subscription that comes with premium apps like Word, Excel, PowerPoint, OneNote, Outlook, Publisher, and Access (Publisher and Access are available on PC only). Applications can be installed on a variety of devices, including PCs, Macs, iPads, iPhones, tablets, and Android phones. Microsoft 365 also comes with services like 1 TB OneDrive storage, 60 Skype minutes per month, and Microsoft support by phone and chat. When you're on a subscription, you'll receive the...
</description></item><item><title>Download MusConv 4.10.416 Lifetime</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 17:31:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html
</guid><description>
MusConv transfers playlists, albums, followed artists and liked songs across a variety of services – Spotify, Apple Music, Amazon Music, YouTube, YouTube Music, iTunes, Deezer, Tidal, SoundCloud, Pandora and more 125 music services!
Features of MusConv Ultimate
	Transfer playlists, albums, followed artists and liked tracks between over 125 music servicesManage playlists (Delete, Merge, Split, Copy...)
	More than 125 music services supported
	Access DAILY updated music charts on...
</description></item><item><title>Download XMedia Recode 3.6.1.7</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 17:31:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xmedia-recode-919.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xmedia-recode-919.html
</guid><description>
XMedia Recode is software to change the quality for video files on windows operating system, it has the ability to change quality, video format. XMedia Recode supports the format conversion such as 3GP, 3GPP, 3GPP2, AAC, AC3, AIFF, AMR, ASF, AU, AVI, DIVX, DTS, DVR-MS, FLV, H. 261, H. 263, H. 264, M4A, M1V, M2V, M4V, MKV.
Parameters advanced
The user can step into the more advanced and modify bitrate, frame interval the frame rate, modes, speed control and many other settings regarding...
</description></item><item><title>Download K-Lite Codec Tweak Tool 6.7.6</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 17:30:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-tweak-tool-6992.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-tweak-tool-6992.html
</guid><description>
K-Lite Codec Tweak Tool is a utility designed to search for broken filters and codecs, showing the user a list of all codecs installed on the computer. . K-Lite Codec Tweak Tool has a very compact capacity of less than 1MB, and possesses a lot of attractive features to help users fix all error codecs quickly.
K-Lite Codec Tweak Tool is capable of working with 250 encoders and filters installed on the user's computer. In addition, K Lite Codec Tweak Tool supports users to repair...
</description></item><item><title>Download Superluminal Performance 1.0.7050.1287</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 17:30:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-superluminal-performance-12585.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-superluminal-performance-12585.html
</guid><description>
Superluminal is a sophisticated sampling analyzer designed to enhance the performance analysis of applications, especially in environments using C++, C# and Rust. Its unique features enable developers to efficiently visualize performance data without intrusive code modifications.
Features
	The best visualization technology allows you to discover and identify performance issues with minimal effort.
	Commenting your code is meant to be biased towards where you think the problem is,...
</description></item></channel></rss>