<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 23:44:15 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 23:44:15 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Monkeys Audio 11.81</title><pubDate> Thu, 06 Nov 2025 00:34:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-monkeys-audio-949.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-monkeys-audio-949.html
</guid><description>
Monkey\'s Audio is software that compresses digital music without loss of quality. Supports high quality WAV files and CD ripping. Monkeys Audio will compress .wav tracks into .ape files to reduce their size without loss of sound quality, decompress .ape, convert files, check file integrity and manage tags.
Unlike traditional methods like MP3 and OGG, which permanently remove quality to save space, Monkey\'s Audio only creates perfect copies with the same sound quality as the originals....
</description></item><item><title>Download ApowerREC 1.8.3.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 06 Nov 2025 00:33:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-apowerrec-592.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-apowerrec-592.html
</guid><description>
ApowerREC is software video, screen capture computer to record the live program stream. ApowerREC can record everything on the screen of you, include the active desktop, video streaming meetings on the web, etc., You can record their activities in full screen or in an area to be customized are placed separately on the screen along with sound and it has great ability to keep the video synced with audio. Besides this, recorded, webcam, or screen capture, along with webcam also feasible and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Hot Door CADtools 2026 v30.1.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 06 Nov 2025 00:32:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hot-door-cadtools-5031.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hot-door-cadtools-5031.html
</guid><description>
Hot Door CADtools is a plug-in add features to Illustrator, the program will add 92 drawing tools, editing, labeling, sizing, conversion, create, and utilities are organized in 10 groups tool in the tool palette in Adobe Illustrator. New tools recently added include: Scale, Line, Repeat, Repeat Along the Path, Scaled Type, Grid, and Wave tools.
The main features of Hot Door CADtools
	Improved table and tools
	Preview label and size
	Compression table by hiding the parts you don't...
</description></item><item><title>Download Enfocus PitStop Pro 2025 v25.11.1637955</title><pubDate> Thu, 06 Nov 2025 00:31:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-enfocus-pitstop-pro-3106.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-enfocus-pitstop-pro-3106.html
</guid><description>
Enfocus PitStop Pro is a powerful tool for work, office, fix bug when printing PDF data. PitStop Pro automatically detects quite a lot of possible errors in the PDF file. Not only detect errors of PitStop Pro, it also gives you the ability to self-repair them or automatically performed.
Enfocus PitStop Pro - test, fix bugs in the PDF file
PitStop Pro also allows you to edit the craft almost everything in a PDF file without leaving Adobe Acrobat.
PitStop Pro. PDF file ready to print....
</description></item><item><title>Download Stellar Repair for Video 6.8.2.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 06 Nov 2025 00:30:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stellar-repair-for-video-2551.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stellar-repair-for-video-2551.html
</guid><description>
Stellar Repair for Video is video repair tool most powerful way to fix the broken video while recording, when performed, file transfer, while editing, switch or handle. This program easily installed on your computer, because it does not require any additional program how. The maximum needs to be done is to accept the license agreement, indicate the correct path where it will be installed. Stellar Repair for Video comes with an intuitive interface and user-friendly, includes a number of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Zoom Player Max 22.0 Beta 4</title><pubDate> Thu, 06 Nov 2025 00:29:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zoom-player-max-104.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zoom-player-max-104.html
</guid><description>
Zoom Player MAX help you to see the film on DVD, Blu-ray, Flash movies and HD format with high quality and the ability to display subtitles in English very well. The advantage of software is that takes up very little system resources to play the movie with quick speed, change the wallpaper options while viewing movies.
Zoom Player MAX is the movies, browse high-quality photos on the computer with the advantages such as compact size, quick start, built-in codec. The application supports...
</description></item><item><title>Download PhoneRescue for iOS 4.3.1.20251105</title><pubDate> Thu, 06 Nov 2025 00:29:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-phonerescue-for-ios-2851.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-phonerescue-for-ios-2851.html
</guid><description>
PhoneRescue for iOS is the solution to restore lost data of iOS devices such as iPhone, iPad with the ability to work quickly find back all the data on the device such as music, videos, photos, call logs, contacts, or even sms. With PhoneRescue is that you don't need to connect iPhone device with the computer directly, the software works through the index and account, now you can completely assured when using data on the iPhone, by all user's data are lost, you can restore back...
</description></item><item><title>Download DBF Viewer 2000 v8.89</title><pubDate> Thu, 06 Nov 2025 00:27:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbf-viewer-2000-7869.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbf-viewer-2000-7869.html
</guid><description>
DBF Viewer 2000 is a fast, efficient solution for viewing and editing all types of DBF files. It can handle files from dBase, Visual dBase, Foxpro, Visual FoxPro and Clipper, just to name a few, with performance that easily rivals expensive professional database utilities. DBF Viewer 2000 is extremely fast, does any task, just one simple query and cleanup copy to export data at lightning speed.
With DBF Editor's simple, dynamically generated visual dialogs, you can easily view the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Calcpad 7.5.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 06 Nov 2025 00:27:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-calcpad-12576.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-calcpad-12576.html
</guid><description>
Calcpad is free software for mathematical and engineering calculations. It is a flexible and modern programmable calculator with Html report generator. Calcpad uses a simple programming language that is fast and easy to learn. It does not require any special programming skills, which makes it suitable for engineers without any computer programming background. You can create calculation notes simply by writing your formula and text, enclosed in 'quotation marks'.
The program includes...
</description></item><item><title>Download Opera One 123.0.5669.47</title><pubDate> Thu, 06 Nov 2025 00:27:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-972.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-972.html
</guid><description>
Opera is a fast, safe, configurable and compliant intranet web browser, which includes both the reader and the application. The Opera browser supports web browsing, listening to music, watching high speed movies, you can open many tabs on the Opera without affecting your browsing speed. Opera now supports almost all devices and operating systems such as windows, IOS, Android, linux, MacOS ...
Opera is a beautiful interface and many interesting features, operating on both PCs and mobile,...
</description></item><item><title>Download TubeMate Downloader 5.25</title><pubDate> Thu, 06 Nov 2025 00:26:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubemate-downloader-4250.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubemate-downloader-4250.html
</guid><description>
TubeMate Downloader is a smart application that lets you download any clip you want from the website hosting the main video and convert them in when download at or then. If you need a simple and effective tool to download videos, you can give it a try. With TubeMate Downloader, you can directly drag and drop video link from your browser into the drop-down box or application window to start downloading. You don't even need to copy and paste the video URL.
TubeMate Downloader - Support...
</description></item><item><title>Download TickTick Premium 6.4.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 06 Nov 2025 00:25:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ticktick-premium-7770.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ticktick-premium-7770.html
</guid><description>
TickTick Premium is a task management application that helps users stay organized, it is very suitable for educators and students with many incentives. TickTick turns your Windows PC device into a flexible, easy-to-use and highly efficient office platform. Join millions of people to capture ideas, organize their lives, and do something creative every day.
Whether there are work related tasks or personal goals, TickTick is here to help you manage all your to-dos. With five different...
</description></item><item><title>Download Muziza YouTube Downloader Converter 8.16</title><pubDate> Thu, 06 Nov 2025 00:25:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-muziza-youtube-downloader-converter-3972.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-muziza-youtube-downloader-converter-3972.html
</guid><description>
Muziza YouTube Downloader Converter is a tool to create conditions for an attractive interface and many features to help you to download video clips from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion, Instagram and other sites. Muziza YouTube Downloader Converter can also download the video UHD 8K, 5K, 4K, QHD 2K, HD 1080p and 720p from YouTube. The app allows you download only audio stream from YouTube and save as MP3. You don't need to download the entire video file.
Muziza YouTube Downloader...
</description></item><item><title>Download Vovsoft QR Code and Barcode Reader 1.5</title><pubDate> Thu, 06 Nov 2025 00:25:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-qr-code-and-barcode-reader-9714.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-qr-code-and-barcode-reader-9714.html
</guid><description>
Vovsoft QR Code and Barcode Reader is a user-friendly software designed specifically for the Windows operating system. This application allows users to easily scan and decode different types of barcodes and QR codes from a file or webcam.
The software's intelligent scanning technology automatically detects the type of code. Whether you need to decode product information or access website links, this tool is the software for Windows users looking for a reliable solution to scan and read...
</description></item><item><title>Download MobiKin Eraser for iOS 2.1.20</title><pubDate> Thu, 06 Nov 2025 00:24:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mobikin-eraser-for-ios-5373.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mobikin-eraser-for-ios-5373.html
</guid><description>
MobiKin Eraser for iOS is one of the top deletion programs that gives you the functionality to delete all deleted files, private data, system settings and other files on your iOS device without have a chance to recover. When you decide to give up your old iDevice, you need to delete all the data on it. Otherwise, your personal data such as bank accounts and passwords, contact information, chat records or other information will be at high risk of disclosure. Luckily, you have MobiKin Eraser...
</description></item><item><title>Download Internet Video Downloader 7.10</title><pubDate> Thu, 06 Nov 2025 00:24:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hdapplications-hd-downloader-6041.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hdapplications-hd-downloader-6041.html
</guid><description>
Internet Video Downloader is a small tool designed to help you download video clips from YouTube, Dailymotion and many other similar sites with high quality that can easily run on smartphones, tablets or the latest Xbox devices. After the quick and simple installation process, you will be welcomed by a user-friendly interface without the ability to cause any problems for you.
Although you can set the app start to download immediately, but you can also create a download list that can be...
</description></item><item><title>Download TubeDownload Pro 6.31</title><pubDate> Thu, 06 Nov 2025 00:23:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubedownload-pro-12035.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubedownload-pro-12035.html
</guid><description>
TubeDownload Pro is a professional Windows application for downloading your favorite videos from YouTube and hundreds of other video sites. TubeDownload Pro can increase download speed up to 500% or even more.
Features of TubeDownload Pro
	Download your favorite videos from YouTube and hundreds of other video sites.
	Increase download speed up to 500% or even more.
	Download 720p, 1080p, 2K, 4K and 8K HD videos from YouTube.
	Download entire playlists in just a few clicks.
	Download...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sante PACS Server 4.3.3</title><pubDate> Thu, 06 Nov 2025 00:23:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sante-pacs-server-7541.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sante-pacs-server-7541.html
</guid><description>
Sante PACS Server is an HTTP (web) server for DICOM files and a CD/DVD Burn and Print server that offers high performance and reliability at an affordable price. It provides connectivity to all DICOM methods (CT, MR, US, CR, NM, XA, MG, DX, etc.). Reviewing of DICOM images can be done using the Sante PACS Viewer (the system's built-in, full-featured DICOM Viewer). The built-in web server can be used as a free cloud server for DICOM files!
Tools of Sante PACS Server
	The Migration Tool...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sante PACS Server PG 4.3.3</title><pubDate> Thu, 06 Nov 2025 00:17:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sante-pacs-server-pg-7540.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sante-pacs-server-pg-7540.html
</guid><description>
Sante PACS Server PG is an HTTP server (web) for DICOM files and a recorder and In CD/DVD with high performance and reliability. It provides connectivity with all the DICOM (CT, MR, US, CR, NM, XA, MG, DX, etc.). The review of the DICOM image can be done with the Sante PACS Viewer.
Integrated web servers can be used as a free cloud server for DICOM files!
</description></item><item><title>Download Cubase Pro 15.0.5</title><pubDate> Wed, 05 Nov 2025 21:32:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-steinberg-cubase-pro-3528.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-steinberg-cubase-pro-3528.html
</guid><description>
Steinberg Cubase Pro - The highest and most professional from the publisher Steinberg. Current program Steinberg Cubase Pro is priced near$ 600. But we will provide versions completely free for you. Can you might also like more simple versions, you can download version Cubase Elements at our website.
Steinberg Cubase Pro - music Production professional
Steinberg Cubase Pro is one of the pack music creation software, the most powerful in the world. With a variety of tools, unparalleled...
</description></item><item><title>Download DaVinci Resolve Studio 20.2.3</title><pubDate> Wed, 05 Nov 2025 21:30:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-davinci-resolve-studio-1072.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-davinci-resolve-studio-1072.html
</guid><description>
DaVinci Resolve Studio is professional video editing and color grading software developed by Blackmagic Design. This is an enhanced version of the free DaVinci Resolve software, providing additional features and capabilities for professional video editing, color correction, and post-production.
One of the outstanding features of DaVinci Resolve Studio is its powerful color correction capabilities. It provides a comprehensive set of tools and features for advanced color correction,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Blackmagic Design Fusion Studio 20.2.3</title><pubDate> Wed, 05 Nov 2025 21:28:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blackmagic-design-fusion-studio-2750.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blackmagic-design-fusion-studio-2750.html
</guid><description>
Blackmagic Design Fusion Studio is the world's most advanced compositing software for visual effects artists, broadcast and motion graphics designers, and 3D animators. For the past 30 years, Fusion has been used on thousands of Hollywood blockbuster films and television shows. Fusion features a powerful node-based interface that lets you quickly and easily create sophisticated effects by connecting different types of image processing tools together! You get a wide range of tools,...
</description></item><item><title>Download SwapVoice 1.0.14</title><pubDate> Wed, 05 Nov 2025 18:22:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-swapvoice-14126.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-swapvoice-14126.html
</guid><description>
Convert your voice into instant, actionable text with SwapVoice's intelligent trigger recognition system, for just a one-time subscription fee instead of the monthly licensing fees of other similar tools. Perfect for professionals, content creators, and anyone who wants to work faster and smarter.
SwapVoice Features
	Offline Speech Recognition - Cloud-Independent, Absolutely Secure
	Multilingual Support - 15 languages ​​including English, Dutch, German, French, Spanish, Italian,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Duplicate Cleaner Pro 5.26.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 05 Nov 2025 18:21:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-duplicate-cleaner-pro-1591.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-duplicate-cleaner-pro-1591.html
</guid><description>
Duplicate Cleaner Pro is software scan and sort content in hard drive to find and remove files duplicate do not use. The special of Duplicate Cleaner Pro is that it will deep scan all file types photos, music, movies, videos, documents Word, presentation PowerPoint, text files-you name it, if it appears twice on your computer then Duplicate Cleaner will find it. When these files are found, you are provided with helpful tools to allow you to select copies to delete or move. These files can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Gilisoft Copy Protect 8.3.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 05 Nov 2025 18:21:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-copy-protect-8047.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-copy-protect-8047.html
</guid><description>
Gilisoft Copy Protect is software that helps you protect audio, video, PDF, DOC, PPT, XLS and image files so that they cannot be copied or distributed by illegal means. Users can play from, video encoded on macOS, android using Gilisoft's GCP reader.
Features of Gilisoft Copy Protect
	A document security tool that creates shareless GCP files to protect your Video, Photo, DOC, PDF, XLS, PPT files from unauthorized sharing, editing, copying or viewing .
	Protect document files from...
</description></item></channel></rss>