<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 20:10:05 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 20:10:05 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Visual Studio Code 1.108.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 15 Jan 2026 16:53:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-visual-studio-code-3182.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-visual-studio-code-3182.html
</guid><description>
Visual Studio Code is the encryption tool of Microsoft has met most of the needs of the developer. Environment this encoding was introduced to compete with other products such as Sublime and Nodepad ++ . Microsoft, in its new product, has not been released in many years, has provided many features in a simple environment. In addition to the familiar with a dozen programming languages, the syntax and get to know coding language as soon as be encrypted and allows for syntax highlighting, it...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft Office 2024 Professional Plus LTSC v2408 Build 17932.20638 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Thu, 15 Jan 2026 16:47:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-office-2024-professional-plus-64-bit-10679.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-office-2024-professional-plus-64-bit-10679.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft has officially announced the final version of the Office 2024 release for Windows and Mac users. After releasing a preview version in the first half of this year, the product has been finalized and is now available to users. Office 2024 includes updated versions of apps from the Word 2024, Excel 2024, PowerPoint 2024, Outlook 2024, Access 2024, and Publisher 2024 suites.
Office 2024 includes virtually every change that has been added to the suite of programs in Office 365 over...
</description></item><item><title>Download Active File Recovery 26.0.3</title><pubDate> Thu, 15 Jan 2026 16:46:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-active-file-recovery-354.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-active-file-recovery-354.html
</guid><description>
Active File Recovery is a recovery tool for files deleted or lost, damaged or reformatted volume even when your PC does not boot. Active File Recovery will help you recover NTFS, ReFS, FAT, exFAT, HFS +, XFS, JFS, UFS, Ext2 / 3 / 4, BtrFS. Recovery software provides the ability to detect and recover files, drives and disks lost due to deleted, formatted, damaged, physical virus.
Features Active File Recovery:
Basic features Active File Recovery
	Active File Recovery helps to restore...
</description></item><item><title>Download Windows 11 Pro 25H2 v26200.7623 NoTPM Multilingual Preactivated</title><pubDate> Thu, 15 Jan 2026 16:45:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-11-6618.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-11-6618.html
</guid><description>
Windows 11 is officially leaked to a developer version. Previously, when Windows 10 was released, Microsoft once stated that Windows 10 would be the last version of Windows for users. Clearly, with the arrival of Windows 11, Microsoft needed a major reason to reverse its previous claims and still remove Windows 10 by introducing some new operating systems.
About the interface of Windows 11 is quite similar to Windows 10X (a version of Windows 10 has stopped growing). The logo image of...
</description></item><item><title>Download XYplorer 28.10.0400</title><pubDate> Thu, 15 Jan 2026 16:45:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-533.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-533.html
</guid><description>
XYplorer - File Manager for Windows is software that supports users to manage files on the Window quickly and to arrange the folder tidy. XYplorer features tabbed browsing, search, files, powerful, preview, flexible, highly customizable interface, dual frame options and a variety of unique ways to automate effective tasks often repeat. It's fast, lightweight, and portable.
Features XYplorer
	XYplorer is a file manager mobile. It does not require any settings, store all configuration...
</description></item><item><title>Download reaConverter Pro 8.0.181</title><pubDate> Thu, 15 Jan 2026 16:44:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html
</guid><description>
reaConverter Pro is software image processing feature with batch conversion and image editing periodically becomes simple. eaConverter also provide command line utilities allow you to process images automatically, thus helping you shorten the time for other work.
reaConverter Pro integrated powerful tool of Uber with many great features. It provides advanced solutions to process and adjust images. Management of the conversion process the base image with the latest version of...
</description></item><item><title>Download VoiceMaster (English) 1.0.3</title><pubDate> Thu, 15 Jan 2026 16:44:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-voicemaster-13831.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-voicemaster-13831.html
</guid><description>
Voice Master is a powerful offline transcription software that converts audio and video content into text, supporting all popular media formats (MP3, MP4, MKV, AVI, MOV, FLV, etc.). It creates easy-to-edit docx files from recordings and videos, and runs offline to ensure maximum data privacy. Voice Master is ideal for businesses and individuals who need secure, private, and accurate transcription services.
Key Features
	High-Accuracy Transcription: Using advanced AI-powered speech...
</description></item><item><title>Download Intel Ethernet Adapter Complete Driver Pack 31.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 15 Jan 2026 16:43:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intel-ethernet-adapter-complete-driver-pack-7424.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intel-ethernet-adapter-complete-driver-pack-7424.html
</guid><description>
Intel Ethernet Adapter Complete Driver Pack contains all Intel® Ethernet networking software and drivers for Windows, Linux and FreeBSD versions currently supported for most Intel Ethernet Adapters. Not all Intel Ethernet Adapters and Intel Ethernet Controllers are supported in all versions of Windows, Linux, or FreeBSD.
What's new in this release:
In this point release, NVM Update Package 3.20 has been updated. If you currently have the 3.20 update package installed and are running...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tails 7.4</title><pubDate> Thu, 15 Jan 2026 16:43:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tails-3241.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tails-3241.html
</guid><description>
Tails is a live operating system that you can boot on almost any computer from a USB memory stick or DVD. Tails does this by using the distribution classic Gnome of Linux. The top navigation bar allows you quick access to "Applications" and "Places" so you can easily access what you need quickly and easily and not lost.
Tails - independent operating System for security
Menu "apps" provide shortcuts for bundled software, including graphics, audio and video, office, system tools, and...
</description></item><item><title>Download DesktopPic 2.0.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 15 Jan 2026 16:42:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktoppic-7444.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktoppic-7444.html
</guid><description>
DesktopPic allows you to display or watermark images on your Windows desktop wallpaper. Display one or more pictures in a resizable, movable window with no borders or captions, so all you see is the photo. This will give the illusion of the image being part of your wallpaper, but it's really just another window. Any icons on the desktop in the same area as the image will be masked. Bitmap image formats, such as PNG (recommended), JPG, BMP and animated GIF are supported.
Features of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Topaz Video AI Pro 7.1.6 / 1.1.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 15 Jan 2026 16:42:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-video-enhance-ai-3733.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-video-enhance-ai-3733.html
</guid><description>
Topaz Video Enhance AI is a tool to increase video quality with this great technology ONE. Topaz Video Enhance WHO wide open your video to resolutions up to 8K with the details and consistency of motion. Until the present, there is no way to re-create a perfect high resolution video from the footage is low resolution. From the family film to SD low quality to DVD quality and more than that, Video Enhance WHO will convert your video into the footage is upgrade clear with resolutions up to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Gpg4win 5.0.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 15 Jan 2026 16:34:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gpg4win-7031.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gpg4win-7031.html
</guid><description>
Gpg4win is a security software program that can encrypt and attach digital signatures to your emails and files when you upload or send them online, to prevent people from unauthorized use of your personal information. Gpg4win allows users to securely transmit emails and files with the help of encryption and digital signatures. Encryption protects content from an unwanted party reading it. A digital signature ensures that it has not been modified and comes from a specific sender.
The...
</description></item><item><title>Download System Utilities 1.4.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 15 Jan 2026 16:34:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-system-utilities-10394.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-system-utilities-10394.html
</guid><description>
System Utilities as its name suggests, contains a collection of tools that can help you maintain your system easily. It can scan your drive for storage, help you quickly uninstall programs, as well as manage startup applications and clean up unnecessary data.
Features of System Utilities
	Scan and organize all the folders on your PC to create more space.
	Uninstall all programs that you do not use. Get rid of data junk on your computer.
	Determine which programs should start...
</description></item><item><title>Download TrayStatus Pro 5.1.4</title><pubDate> Thu, 15 Jan 2026 16:33:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-traystatus-pro-1597.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-traystatus-pro-1597.html
</guid><description>
TrayStatus Pro is professional software to help display the status of the keys Caps Lock, Num Lock, Scroll Lock, Kana, Alt, Ctrl, Shift in the system tray. In addition, the software TrayStatus this Pro also displays CPU, memory or operation of the hard drive or use performance counters to track things like the queue length, disk, network activity, requires IIS and more.
TrayStatus Pro - Show keyboard status and parameters of the computer
The features and functions TrayStatus...
</description></item><item><title>Download MatchWare MindView 9.0.60114</title><pubDate> Thu, 15 Jan 2026 16:33:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mindview-5965.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mindview-5965.html
</guid><description>
MindView is a professional thinking mapping software that allows you to brainpower, organize and present an intuitive idea. Known for the integration of the MS Office that once won the award, the software mapping software allows you to work more efficiently, turning the idea into action faster than ever! With six interchangable viewing modes, unique project management features and strong collaboration options; MindView has become a leading company in the software mapping software...
</description></item><item><title>Download UpdatePack7R2 26.1.15</title><pubDate> Thu, 15 Jan 2026 16:33:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-updatepack7r2-6614.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-updatepack7r2-6614.html
</guid><description>
UpdatePack7R2 is software that allows you to update a working system and integrate software updates in the distribution. Can be installed on any version of Windows 7 and Server 2008 R2, any digit and any language. Includes updates for all versions of Internet Explorer, all critical, recommended, and security updates.
How to use UpdatePack7R2 software:
	The system must have at least 10 GB of free space on the hard drive and preferably no less than 1 GB of free RAM.
	Key / Reboot to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Minimal Firewall 2.6.5</title><pubDate> Thu, 15 Jan 2026 16:32:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minimal-firewall-13877.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minimal-firewall-13877.html
</guid><description>
Minimal Firewall works in conjunction with Windows Firewall to block all unknown connections by default, prompting you to create application-based rules to mitigate malware, telemetry, and data leaks. Completely eliminate applications that call home without your knowledge. Minimal Firewall provides a more secure and integrated approach by interacting directly with the native Windows Firewall, eliminating the need for risky system modifications.
Core Features
	Lockdown Mode: The core...
</description></item><item><title>Download EasyUEFI Winpe 6.2.0 Technician</title><pubDate> Thu, 15 Jan 2026 16:31:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easyuefi-enterprise-winpe-4996.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easyuefi-enterprise-winpe-4996.html
</guid><description>
EasyUEFI Enterprise Winpe is a tool to manage boot option EFI / UEFI is easy to use, allows you to create, delete, edit, clean up, backup and restore the boot option EFI / UEFI. The program allows you to manage the startup items, the properties and the options available on the system based on UEFI or EFI. EasyUEFI Enterprise Winpe provides improved functionality for the end user. It displays the item is discovered, owns the management functions boot options comprehensive and more. EasyUEFI...
</description></item><item><title>Download SIV System Information Viewer 5.85</title><pubDate> Thu, 15 Jan 2026 16:26:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-siv-system-information-viewer-1803.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-siv-system-information-viewer-1803.html
</guid><description>
SIV System Information Viewer is advanced tool that provides in depth information for many components, Windows, hardware and different networks, including information for CPU info, PCI info, PCMCIA info, USB SMBus information SPD, the method ACPI, information , machine, hardware sensors, and more.
SIV System Information Viewer - viewer system information advanced
The original interface can be somewhat overwhelming and perhaps you will have to take a bit of effort to familiarize...
</description></item><item><title>Download Diffchecker 6.7.6</title><pubDate> Thu, 15 Jan 2026 16:26:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-diffchecker-5025.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-diffchecker-5025.html
</guid><description>
Diffchecker is a application compare text, images and powerful file to desktop of your. Available for Windows, macOS. Compare text files, documents, PDF. Compare photos, graphics. Because Diffchecker Desktop running entirely on your computer, so it does not have to communicate with our servers to create your difference. This means that there is no other way in addition you can view your sensitive data, you.
Diffchecker Desktop run offline, that means you can use it anytime, anywhere and...
</description></item><item><title>Download MailWasher Pro 8.0.97</title><pubDate> Thu, 15 Jan 2026 16:20:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-firetrust-mailwasher-pro-825.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-firetrust-mailwasher-pro-825.html
</guid><description>
MailWasher Pro software is ready to filter all of your email accounts and blocked, remove the spam from the list of email. MailWasher allows you to preview all your email before to your computer or your mobile device, you allows you to read all your email securely, and instantly delete any unwanted emails or suspicious. Email good rest of you is download at PC or mobile devices, to help you not get any virus, spam or any email.
Firetrust MailWasher Pro - Blocker remove spam
The...
</description></item><item><title>Download Moneyspire 2026 v26.0.8</title><pubDate> Thu, 15 Jan 2026 16:19:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-moneyspire-14310.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-moneyspire-14310.html
</guid><description>
Moneyspire is a personal and small business finance management program that lets you track your basic accounts, budgets, bills, loans, and investments. Categorize your spending and income into customizable categories. Track bills so you never forget to pay and avoid late fees. Set budgets to track spending and avoid overspending in specific categories like eating out. Forecast account balances to avoid overdrafts and cash shortages. Balance your checkbook and compare it to your bank...
</description></item><item><title>Download QuickMemoryTestOK 5.31</title><pubDate> Thu, 15 Jan 2026 16:19:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quickmemorytestok-3327.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quickmemorytestok-3327.html
</guid><description>
QuickMemoryTestOK is a free utility to check RAM of your PC. QuickMemoryTestOK will be useful when you buy a PC have 16, 32, 64, 128, etc., RAM GB. For example, for most users, the part of this often never be used or handled. For this reason, should undergo a test to ensure that no area is error in main memory. QuickMemoryTestOK can also be used to check your Windows PC if there is any behavior in high memory that may be the cause of a system error other serious not.
QuickMemoryTestOK -...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wireshark 4.6.3</title><pubDate> Thu, 15 Jan 2026 16:18:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wireshark-56.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wireshark-56.html
</guid><description>
Wireshark (aka Ethereal) is a network protocol analyzer allows you to capture and examine data from a live network or from a snapshot file on disk.You can browse the captured data in an interactive way and view summary information and details for each package. Wireshark has several powerful features, including a language filter rich display and ability to view flow created back of the TCP.
Wireshark - network protocol analyzer
The program can read the capture file from tcpdump...
</description></item><item><title>Download NoScript 13.5.9 Chrome + Firefox</title><pubDate> Thu, 15 Jan 2026 16:18:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-noscript-116.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-noscript-116.html
</guid><description>
NoScript is an add-ons extension Firefox , Google Chrome allows you to interactively block Java, JavaScript, Flash a one-click button.
You can choose to temporary block or allow scripts on the current web page and also allows the reliable site by you is excluded from any action to block any.
Whenever you visit a website, all content scripts potential invasive are blocked by default and you can select it on the basis of each script from the status bar of browsers like Google Chrome,...
</description></item></channel></rss>