<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 23:42:35 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 23:42:35 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download ImageMagick 7.1.2-8</title><pubDate> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 01:01:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-imagemagick-1319.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-imagemagick-1319.html
</guid><description>
ImageMagick is software image processing command line to create, edit, compose, or convert bitmap images. ImageMagick is completely free for users and you easily download it on taiwebs.com. Typical functions most of software is able to read and write images in many formats (over 100) including DPX, EXR, GIF, JPEG, JPEG-2000, PDF, PhotoCD, PNG, Postcript, SVG, and TIFF.
ImageMagick - image Processing
The Windows version of ImageMagick is installed. Just click on the appropriate version...
</description></item><item><title>Download CapCut PC 7.3.0.2974</title><pubDate> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 01:00:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capcut-pc-9995.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capcut-pc-9995.html
</guid><description>
CapCut PC is a simple video editing tool that you can freely use anywhere. You can create videos on your browser, desktop and laptop, or on your phone. Versatile editing, magical AI tools, team collaboration, and built-in assets. Create videos in a whole new way.
You can edit videos based on editing the timeline, in the process you can add different elements and effects to the video to give the best effect to your work. It is a simple and intuitive set of editing tools and effects that...
</description></item><item><title>Download Serif Affinity Designer 2.6.5.3782</title><pubDate> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 00:55:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-affinity-designer-328.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-affinity-designer-328.html
</guid><description>
Affinity Designer is the design software graphics for premium users, helping you to realize the ideas in his creating project, such as design, user interface, web graphics. Affinity Designer own vector fastest, smoothest, most accurate out there. Whether you are working on branding, concept art, project, print, logo, ui, UX, website, or forged, Affinity Designer will revolutionize the way you work, on macOS and Windows.
Affinity Designer will help you handle the images, allowing zoom...
</description></item><item><title>Download Serif Affinity Photo 2.6.5.3782</title><pubDate> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 00:54:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-serif-affinity-photo-318.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-serif-affinity-photo-318.html
</guid><description>
Serif Affinity Photo is photo editing software professional provides sophisticated tools to enhance and edit images in a interface is extremely intuitive, with all the power and performance you need. Serif Affinity Photo is built on the foundation of solid rock with the principles of performance, stability and lack of swell, Affinity Photo is a photography tool professional to the core.
Serif Affinity Photo has process work in CMYK from beginning to end with ICC color management and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Free YouTube Download 4.4.43.1025 Premium</title><pubDate> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 00:49:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-download-1177.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-download-1177.html
</guid><description>
Free YouTube Download Premium is the most popular application to download videos from YouTube. The program was released in 2006 and regularly updated since then. Use the program to download and convert YouTube videos to view offline anytime.
Free YouTube Download - added Support to download youtube
Download more videos! Save whole playlists and YouTube channels, videos from a playlist individually (history, video be favorite, favourites, Watch later), videos from many different...
</description></item><item><title>Download PureSync 8.0.4</title><pubDate> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 00:48:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-puresync-380.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-puresync-380.html
</guid><description>
PureSync is software backup and sync file can automatically keep backup files of your important. This is a Windows program to synchronize files and folders and to perform backups e.g. automatically in the background. PureSync will import files from a digital camera and synchronize the contents of multiple folders.
The program provides a step by step guide to configure the task to backup and synchronize your and set the advanced options such as exclude files, manage conflict, compare the...
</description></item><item><title>Download GiliSoft PDF Editor 8.1.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 00:48:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-pdf-editor-13719.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-pdf-editor-13719.html
</guid><description>
GiliSoft PDF Editor is a user-friendly and feature-rich PDF editor that simplifies the process of editing PDF files. With a comprehensive set of features, it helps users improve their office work efficiency. Text editing capabilities allow users to make quick changes to PDF documents by selecting, editing, and formatting text with ease.
Advanced image editing tools allow users to manipulate images in PDF files, including resizing, cropping, rotating, and applying various image...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinMerge 2.16.52</title><pubDate> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 00:47:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winmerge-2028.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winmerge-2028.html
</guid><description>
WinMerge is a tool to merge and distinguish open source for Windows. WinMerge can compare and folders and files, presenting differences in a visual text easy to understand or manipulate. WinMerge is very useful for determining what has changed between the version of the project and merge the changes between the versions. WinMerge can be used as a tool to compare / merge, external or as a standalone application.
In addition, Winmerge has many helpful features helps to compare, synchronize...
</description></item><item><title>Download Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium 4.4.43.1025</title><pubDate> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 00:47:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-to-mp3-converter-premium-844.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-to-mp3-converter-premium-844.html
</guid><description>
Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium version is a software used to convert YouTube to MP3, extract audio from playlists YouTube, show listings, charts, video responses, channels, favorites of the user. With Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium, you can download and convert playlists, channels, stream original tv series and get them into iTunes at the same time.
Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium - convert YouTube to MP3
Features Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium from the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Renee PDF Aide 2025.10.27.185</title><pubDate> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 00:46:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-renee-pdf-aide-2042.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-renee-pdf-aide-2042.html
</guid><description>
Renee PDF Aide is versatile software support to convert and edit PDF like you are edit Word, Excel, Power Point (PPT), Image, HTML,. PDF is the file format most popular commercial but difficult to edit. That's how Renee PDF support: it helps users to convert PDF documents into files that can edit like Word, Excel, Power Point (PPT), Image, HTML, EPUB and txt document. In addition, Renee PDF Aide is equipped with cutting-edge OCR technology can recognize the characters in image PDF or...
</description></item><item><title>Download Qalculate! 5.8.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 00:42:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qalculate-7213.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qalculate-7213.html
</guid><description>
Qalculate! is a versatile cross-platform desktop calculator. It's simple to use but offers the power and flexibility typically reserved for complex math packages, as well as useful tools for everyday needs (such as currency converters and fractional calculations). hundred). Features include a large library of customizable functions, unit calculations and conversions, physical constants, symbol calculations (including integrals and equations), arbitrary precision, uncertainty transfer,...
</description></item><item><title>Download LrToolbox 0.9.8.9</title><pubDate> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 00:41:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lrtoolbox-13054.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lrtoolbox-13054.html
</guid><description>
LrToolbox is a comprehensive Windows software designed to handle your Lightroom catalog with ease. Whether you are a professional photographer or an amateur, this tool will help you streamline your workflow and increase your productivity. Whether you need to extract previews from a catalog, convert your photo ratings to sidecar files, or convert RAW images to JPG, LrToolbox is here to help you with just a few clicks.
Key Features
	Compatible with Adobe Lightroom Classic 14.2 (February...
</description></item><item><title>Download Serif Affinity Publisher 2.6.5.3782</title><pubDate> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 00:41:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-serif-affinity-publisher-2165.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-serif-affinity-publisher-2165.html
</guid><description>
Fluid publishing powerhouse. Bring your vision to life with Affinity Publisher, the next generation of professional publishing software. From magazines, books, brochures, posters, reports and stationery to other creations, this incredibly smooth, intuitive app gives you the power to combine your images, graphics and text to make beautiful layouts ready for publication.
Serif Affinity Publisher
Engineered for advanced technology
	Engineered with the same no-compromise vision as our...
</description></item><item><title>Download ExpanDrive 2025.10.08</title><pubDate> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 00:40:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-expandrive-609.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-expandrive-609.html
</guid><description>
ExpanDrive is software sync cloud storage strong support BackBlaze B2, Google Team Drive, SMB / CIFS and new interface and easy user search file version, share links and much more.  ExpanDrive mapped network drives for macOS and Micosoft Windows connect with all the provide major cloud storage such as Dropbox, Google Drive, Google Team Drive, Amazon Drive, Box, OneDrive, OneDrive for Business, Sharepoint, Openstack Swift , BackBlaze B2, Amazon S3 or SFTP servers, FTP or WebDAV on your own...
</description></item><item><title>Download LastPass Password Manager 5.2.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 00:40:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lastpass-269.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lastpass-269.html
</guid><description>
LastPass is a free software to help manage passwords allows you to store all the login information of your site in a warehouse password cross-platform compatibility only. Instead of remember the user name and personal password, you only need to remember the main password to open the lock the password of his safe.
LastPass
LastPass can automatically fill in the login box for all the account website is your hosting. Whenever you log into a website has stored your vault, the program will...
</description></item><item><title>Download WishPlayer 0.1.7</title><pubDate> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 00:39:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wishplayer-10885.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wishplayer-10885.html
</guid><description>
WishPlayer allows you to enter a song name in the input field of the player and press the play button, it will find and play that song. WishPlayer supports global hotkeys for convenient and fast song playback from anywhere, including chat windows, web pages, and text editors.
With the ability to play audio files offline and it supports a variety of formats, including asf, wma, wmv, wm, asx, Wax, wvx, wmx, wpl, avi, mid, midi, rmi , aif, aifc, aiff, wav, cda, aac, adt, adts, flac, m4a,...
</description></item><item><title>Download SysTools PDF Watermark 5.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 00:39:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-systools-pdf-watermark-6233.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-systools-pdf-watermark-6233.html
</guid><description>
SysTools PDF Watermark  is an advanced tool for adding text or image watermarks across multiple PDFs without Adobe Acrobat. Use this utility to batch insert watermark into PDF documents on Windows Operating System. If you want to protect your confidential PDF file copyright to a higher level, obscure it with this software. This tool allows you to insert any type of watermark on the PDF file and allows to customize it accordingly.
When users add text watermark in PDF, this software...
</description></item><item><title>Download Pianoteq Pro 8.4.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 00:38:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pianoteq-pro-14244.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pianoteq-pro-14244.html
</guid><description>
Pianoteq 8 is a virtual instrument from Modartt, which uses physical modeling to recreate the sound and behavior of pianos and other instruments. Unlike sampled instruments, it takes up very little disk space, while delivering high realism and a wide dynamic range.
	Dual Polarity: An advanced physics engine simulates the vibration of strings in multiple directions, resulting in a more complex and realistic sound, especially in the low range.
	Reproduced Sounds: All modern acoustic...
</description></item><item><title>Download HE - Hardware Read and Write Utility 1.25.10.27</title><pubDate> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 00:38:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-he-hardware-read-and-write-utility-4287.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-he-hardware-read-and-write-utility-4287.html
</guid><description>
HE - Hardware Read and Write Utility is a powerful utility intended for hardware engineer, engineer, BIOS developer, driver, engineer, QA engineers, performance test engineers, diagnostic, etc., this utility access almost all the computer hardware, including PCI (PCI Express), index / Data, PCI, memory, index memory / Data space I / O, Index I / O / Data, Super I / O, DIMM SPD, CPU The registers MSR, screen, SMART, physical area of the hard drive identification data, ATA, dump tables ACPI...
</description></item><item><title>Download DBF Viewer 2000 v8.87</title><pubDate> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 00:37:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbf-viewer-2000-7869.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbf-viewer-2000-7869.html
</guid><description>
DBF Viewer 2000 is a fast, efficient solution for viewing and editing all types of DBF files. It can handle files from dBase, Visual dBase, Foxpro, Visual FoxPro and Clipper, just to name a few, with performance that easily rivals expensive professional database utilities. DBF Viewer 2000 is extremely fast, does any task, just one simple query and cleanup copy to export data at lightning speed.
With DBF Editor's simple, dynamically generated visual dialogs, you can easily view the...
</description></item><item><title>Download DeskSoft EarthView 7.13.13</title><pubDate> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 00:37:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desksoft-earthview-184.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desksoft-earthview-184.html
</guid><description>
With software DeskSoft EarthView you can easily create wallpapers to your computer or select screen saver of your favorite. the program can change day and night, the clouds will also change according to weather conditions current on one or another part of the earth, you can see the lights of the city.
Features of DeskSoft EarthView can be interesting, because of DeskSoft EarthView support for day and night, you can view atmospheric phenomena, light city can see, the cloud is displayed,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Easy Backup 2026 v14.0.0.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 00:36:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easy-backup-9970.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easy-backup-9970.html
</guid><description>
Easy Backup is a free backup solution for your files or the entire system with wizards and video tutorials to assist you through the process. Once configured, the software automatically backs up your data and allows you to store different versions of your files or even your deleted files
Recovering data is very easy. You can restore the integrity of your data or just some files at the desired date and time. For advanced users, restoring can be done manually from the backup media via...
</description></item><item><title>Download Run-Command 6.31</title><pubDate> Tue, 28 Oct 2025 00:29:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-run-command-1816.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-run-command-1816.html
</guid><description>
Run-Command is an alternative to Windows dialog Run standard. Dialog Run-Command looks similar to the Windows dialog but offers the button "Run as Administrator" convenient, as well as the option to save and schedule the Run command on your menu Favorites for quick access in the future.
You may not know, this Command works more or less like command line interface a line. In the Gnome , the command Run is used to run applications through the command terminal. It can be accessed by pressing...
</description></item><item><title>Download AI Voice Changer 5.5.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 21:52:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ai-voice-changer-14258.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ai-voice-changer-14258.html
</guid><description>
AI Voice Changer is a real-time voice changer powered by artificial intelligence technology. It allows users to easily change their voice style, tone, and intonation to create a unique voice experience. Whether it's gaming, live entertainment, voice chat, or content creation, AI Voice Changer delivers natural, smooth, intelligent, and accurate voice changing effects.
Features of AI Voice Changer
	Dual Recording Mode
	Recording Mode: Record first, then apply effects and...
</description></item><item><title>Download TapoPanel 1.0.0.7</title><pubDate> Mon, 27 Oct 2025 21:45:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tapopanel-14257.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tapopanel-14257.html
</guid><description>
Monitor Tapo plug power consumption in real time on Windows PC. TapoPanel displays current power usage and trend graphs of recent activities. No need for complicated Home Assistant setup. Easily monitor power consumption directly from Tp-link plug. Use it to monitor solar panel output or your heater during the winter.
Key Features
	Currently compatible with the following Tapo plugs: P110, P115, P110M for Matter networks.
	Customize fonts and colors
	Works on Windows 8, Windows 10, and...
</description></item></channel></rss>