<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 14:19:18 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 14:19:18 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Waterfox 6.6.9 / 2022.11</title><pubDate> Wed, 25 Feb 2026 16:51:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-waterfox-114.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-waterfox-114.html
</guid><description>
Waterfox is a 64-bit version of the foundation Firefox was built and the compiler Intel is optimized for speed and performance on Windows systems.Waterfox does not add any additional features or bling, in fact, it will automatically import all the gadgets and install is have of you, so you will feel like at home when you run it the first time.All the add-on your Firefox will work with Waterfox, however, only support the plug-in more 64-bit, is includes Adobe Flash, Oracle Java and...
</description></item><item><title>Download ON1 Resize AI 2026.3 v20.3.0.18187</title><pubDate> Wed, 25 Feb 2026 16:49:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-on1-resize-2055.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-on1-resize-2055.html
</guid><description>
ON1 Resize 2019 is the edited final image when you need to zoom in the highest quality - with technology genuine Fractals® - to resize your photo to print. You can quickly change the image size without losing sharpness or detail. ON1 Resize also includes one of the fastest ways to view, remove and edit photos.
ON1 Resize - Zoom, change photo size
The features of ON1 Resize
	ON1 Resize using interpolation algorithm based on fractal - helps quickly change the image size without losing...
</description></item><item><title>Download ON1 Photo RAW MAX 2026.3 v20.3.0.18187</title><pubDate> Wed, 25 Feb 2026 16:48:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-on1-photo-raw-max-10717.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-on1-photo-raw-max-10717.html
</guid><description>
ON1 Photo RAW MAX 2024 is powerful photo editing software that provides photographers with many tools and features to enhance and edit their images. With a user-friendly interface, it offers advanced editing capabilities, including non-destructive editing, AI-powered adjustments, and precise control over color and tone. It also supports raw files from over 800 cameras and works with JPEG, TIF, PSD, PSB, PNG and DNG files. Additionally, it also includes photo organization tools to manage...
</description></item><item><title>Download ON1 Photo RAW 2026.3 v20.3.0.18187</title><pubDate> Wed, 25 Feb 2026 16:47:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-on1-photo-raw-1791.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-on1-photo-raw-1791.html
</guid><description>
ON1 Photo RAW 2023  includes the essential tools and features every photographer needs in their workflow. Our state-of-the-art, super-fast, non-destructive processing engine gives you an extremely smooth and efficient editing experience.
ON1 Photo RAW focuses on letting you get the most out of every photo. Photographers now have a quick photo management engine, hundreds of customizable photo effects, fast and beautiful HDR, masking and selection tools, layers and more in one app. Quickly...
</description></item><item><title>Download XYplorer 28.20.0300</title><pubDate> Wed, 25 Feb 2026 16:47:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-533.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-533.html
</guid><description>
XYplorer - File Manager for Windows is software that supports users to manage files on the Window quickly and to arrange the folder tidy. XYplorer features tabbed browsing, search, files, powerful, preview, flexible, highly customizable interface, dual frame options and a variety of unique ways to automate effective tasks often repeat. It's fast, lightweight, and portable.
Features XYplorer
	XYplorer is a file manager mobile. It does not require any settings, store all configuration...
</description></item><item><title>Download iTop Data Recovery Pro 6.1.0.936</title><pubDate> Wed, 25 Feb 2026 16:46:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-itop-data-recovery-pro-7139.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-itop-data-recovery-pro-7139.html
</guid><description>
iTop Data Recovery Pro is a powerful data recovery tool that speeds up scanning and data recovery processes due to iTop's unique recovery algorithm. In just a few minutes, you can get your deleted files back perfectly as expected. Besides, Scan options are diverse for different needs. You can quickly find your lost data by Location and File Type.
iTop Data Recovery allows you to easily perform file recovery without limitations. More than 1000 file formats are supported. Meanwhile, this...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ashampoo Driver Updater 2.5.0.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 25 Feb 2026 16:45:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-driver-updater-4608.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-driver-updater-4608.html
</guid><description>
Ashampoo Driver Updater is software that helps you to search, download and install the version latest drivers for the cluster of PC computer and external devices and keyboard. Ashampoo Driver Updater operates on the basis of Internet database maintained by the manufacturer of the program. The database has more than 400,000 controller for more than 150,000 devices. Ashampoo Driver Updater is also equipped with the ability to create and restore a backup (backup) of drivers and driver updates...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mozilla Thunderbird 148.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 25 Feb 2026 16:45:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thunderbird-1788.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thunderbird-1788.html
</guid><description>
Thunderbird is an email program full featured with controls spam integration, mail filter, address book, news groups and more. It provides a clean interface and easy to use (customizable). Thunderbird also provides the security features such as S / MIME, digital signing, message encryption, support for certificates and security devices.
Before using this feature, you should review the settings IMAP, SMTP, and SSL/TLS his. Now, what all you need to do is provide your name, email address,...
</description></item><item><title>Download AIDA64 Business / Network Audit 8.25.8200</title><pubDate> Wed, 25 Feb 2026 16:44:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aida64-business-5689.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aida64-business-5689.html
</guid><description>
AIDA64 Business can gather a very detailed arsenal of hardware and software from Windows clients connected to the corporate network. Since it supports command line switching, inventory creation can be fully automated, while reports collected from a PC can be saved in open formats ready for further processing. , as well as into SQL databases. Changes between network test snapshots taken at different times can be tracked in the built-in change manager. It can notify network administrators in...
</description></item><item><title>Download ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro 15.26.0224</title><pubDate> Wed, 25 Feb 2026 16:43:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-videotube-downloader-pro-1276.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-videotube-downloader-pro-1276.html
</guid><description>
ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro is the professional version support download videos and playlists from YouTube, videos from Dailymotion, BBC iPlayer, ITV Player, ABC,  FOX,CBS.com Vimeo, Prosieben, Metacafe, Blip.tv CBC.ca many more video sites. After the video is downloaded, you can convert them to the formats compatible with iPad, iPhone, iPod, MPEG-4, H. 264, MP3, AC3.
ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro - Download videos on Youtube
This is one of the software download the most...
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 8.0.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 25 Feb 2026 16:43:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-11-7760.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-11-7760.html
</guid><description>
TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 is a program that allows users to discover hidden settings in Windows 11. This application is specially designed for Windows 11, groups many registry settings and distribute them from the easy and secure user interface. With TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 you can move the Windows taskbar to the top and resize the taskbar by editing the registry value. With any application that modifies the registry, we recommend that you have a backup copy...
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 8.0.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 25 Feb 2026 16:42:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-10-7759.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-10-7759.html
</guid><description>
TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 is a utility that allows users to discover hidden settings in Windows 10. This application is specially designed for Windows 10, groups many registry settings and provide them from an easy and secure user interface. With TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 you can move the Windows taskbar to the top and resize the taskbar by editing the registry value. With any application that modifies the registry, we recommend that you have a backup copy to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tor Browser 15.0.7</title><pubDate> Wed, 25 Feb 2026 16:42:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tor-browser-1833.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tor-browser-1833.html
</guid><description>
Tor Browser also has full name is Tor Browser Bundle is a web browser give you ability to access the internet safety and security your personal information as well as sensitive documents absolutely. By Tor Browser Bundle will automatically change the IP address on the machine to hide the identity when surfing the web. Tor Browser is free web browser full-featured basic and advanced allows you to leverage the Tor network anonymously without need to make any configuration changes or install...
</description></item><item><title>Download ON1 Effects 2026.3 v20.3.0.18187</title><pubDate> Wed, 25 Feb 2026 16:41:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-on1-effects-1430.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-on1-effects-1430.html
</guid><description>
ON1 Effects is a collection of photo effects includes hundreds of effects, photo filters, LUT, borders, textures and presets and all can be fully customized according to your style. The ability to create endless Effects with ON1. Most popular our included HDR Look, B &amp;amp; W, Lens Blur (tilt-shift), Glows, Color Enhancer, Tone Enhancer, Textures, B Border, Film Look, Split Tone,...
ON1 Effects 2019 - The visual effects
ON1 Effects 2019 includes everything you need to create any style...
</description></item><item><title>Download R-Drive Image 7.3 Build 7314</title><pubDate> Wed, 25 Feb 2026 16:40:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-drive-image-1971.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-drive-image-1971.html
</guid><description>
R-Drive Image is a powerful utility provides create a file disk image for backup purposes, or copy. File disk image contains the exact copy each and every byte of hard drive, partition or logical disk and can be created with various levels compression without stopping Windows os and therefore without interrupting your work. The image file this drive can then be stored in many places, including various removable media as different as a CD-R (W) / DVD, Iomega Zip or Jazz, etc.
R-Drive...
</description></item><item><title>Download HiDownload Phoenix 12.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 25 Feb 2026 16:39:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hidownload-platinum-1225.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hidownload-platinum-1225.html
</guid><description>
HiDownload Platinum is software support download data and videos from the website with many skin formats stream different. HiDownload Platinum can help users Get link live stream as .pm4, .m3u8 to play a video online stability limit error disconnect when Live Stream.
HiDownload Platinum - Download video multi-threaded
The interface of the program is very simple and does not provide much direction. A number of features quite easy to figure out, but what other features do we are...
</description></item><item><title>Download Youtube Downloader HD 5.9.9.8</title><pubDate> Wed, 25 Feb 2026 16:39:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-downloader-hd-3122.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-downloader-hd-3122.html
</guid><description>
Youtube Downloader HD is the best application to download and save Youtube videos. And it's completely free :) You can also convert the downloaded video into various formats easily. Youtube Downloader HD is the download at video free. Download at your videos easily and convert to AVI video format or into MP4 video format (compatible with iPad, iPhone). You can download high quality videos, high definition videos and Full HD from YouTube.
Youtube Downloader HD - Download Youtube videos...
</description></item><item><title>Download NXPowerLite Desktop 11.0.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 25 Feb 2026 16:36:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nxpowerlite-desktop-3719.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nxpowerlite-desktop-3719.html
</guid><description>
NXPowerLite Desktop is a handy, reliable and comprehensive, will help you to compress MS Office documents, PDF files, or JPEG picture of yourself to send them as attachments to e-mail. This program is very useful for the different file can't be compressed in ZIP archive. The application provides integration with e-mail account, your can automatically compress files attached to e-mail sent by you. If you are using MS Outlook, the program will also compress the attachments in the messages...
</description></item><item><title>Download MiniTool Partition Wizard Technician WinPE ISO 13.6</title><pubDate> Wed, 25 Feb 2026 16:34:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minitool-partition-wizard-technician-winpe-iso-5115.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minitool-partition-wizard-technician-winpe-iso-5115.html
</guid><description>
MiniTool Partition Wizard Technician WinPE ISO is a magic partition have feature-rich, designed to optimize disk usage and to protect your data. It comes with many powerful features that you can completely control the hard disk and partitions by yourself. With interface, user friendly, and simple instructions, you can resize partition, copy disk, scan the lost partition and move OS to SSD easily and safely.
Features of MiniTool Partition Wizard Technician WinPE ISO
	Is manager best...
</description></item><item><title>Download TeamViewer 15.75.4 + Portable</title><pubDate> Wed, 25 Feb 2026 16:10:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-teamviewer-528.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-teamviewer-528.html
</guid><description>
TeamViewer is software that functions to connect and control the remote computer, the ability to connect with any system anywhere from all over the place. This is a support tool users is very convenient. TeamViewer to help users control remote computer becomes much more simple, help you interact and collaborate with others in the exchange and share of information, instruction manual, application software or fix the computer.
TeamViewer as a revolution of computer science. when you have...
</description></item><item><title>Download TeamViewer QuickSupport 15.75.4</title><pubDate> Wed, 25 Feb 2026 16:10:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-teamviewer-quicksupport-1933.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-teamviewer-quicksupport-1933.html
</guid><description>
A different version of TeamViewer is TeamViewer QuickSupport is a solution easy to use allows you to share your desktop with a users TeamViewer other to receive technical support or other support. All what you need to do is run the TeamViewer QuickSupport and provides for the remote user ID and your password to grant access to the computer to your desk. Only people you trust can connect to your computer and access password will automatically change after each session.
The software also...
</description></item><item><title>Download VovSoft Text Edit Plus 15.8</title><pubDate> Wed, 25 Feb 2026 16:09:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-text-edit-plus-2872.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-text-edit-plus-2872.html
</guid><description>
VovSoft Text Edit Plus is app designed replacement for Notepad by offering a feature set wider. Text Edit Plus is a lightweight tool that allows users to easily create new text document or edit the existing document. This app is designed replacement for Notepad by offering a feature set wider.
VovSoft Text Edit Plus - text editing
A number of features: dark Mode. Add date and time. The change of the background color and the font. Encrypt and decrypt text. Combine the lines. System...
</description></item><item><title>Download MemoryCleaner 1.9.5</title><pubDate> Wed, 25 Feb 2026 16:08:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-memorycleaner-12469.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-memorycleaner-12469.html
</guid><description>
MemoryCleaner is a tool to free up memory on your computer. This is a free app with a simple user interface that makes it easy for users of all skill levels to use. MemoryCleaner uses many functions built into Windows to free up memory without affecting your system. You can also access Memory Cleaner's functions right from the system tray without having to open the program. The cleaning processes are silent and the only time you see a warning is to briefly display the amount of RAM...
</description></item><item><title>Download Perfect Backup 3.6.0.000</title><pubDate> Wed, 25 Feb 2026 16:07:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfect-backup-7873.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfect-backup-7873.html
</guid><description>
Perfect Backup is free software to backup your personal and business data to external drives, FTP servers and cloud storages like Google Drive, OneDrive, Box,... It allows you to automate the process of saving your important files to external storage. With it, you can be sure that you never lose your documents, tables, sources and media files.
Features of Perfect Backup
	It's actually freeware. No limits, no adware.
	Back up files and folders to different types of devices: internal...
</description></item><item><title>Download Abelssoft AntiLogger 2026 v10.0.70465</title><pubDate> Wed, 25 Feb 2026 16:07:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-abelssoft-antilogger-2772.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-abelssoft-antilogger-2772.html
</guid><description>
Abelssoft AntiLogger is a software to help you easily detect spyware resides in your PC. Find and disable the spy software sneaky're recording the keyboard operations and display your. The background to notify you about the suspicious application. Suspicious application can stop a time or even be blocked permanently.
Abelssoft AntiLogger - Blocking software spy 
Features Abelssoft AntiLogger
	Find and disable the spy software sneaky're recording the keyboard operations and display...
</description></item></channel></rss>