<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 20:01:01 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 20:01:01 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Realtek High Definition Audio Drivers 6.0.9879.1 WHQL</title><pubDate> Thu, 16 Oct 2025 17:29:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-realtek-high-definition-audio-drivers-r282-32bit-64bit-442.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-realtek-high-definition-audio-drivers-r282-32bit-64bit-442.html
</guid><description>
Realtek High Definition Audio Drivers is audio drivers Realtek high-quality latest for windows operating systems, virgin audio controller is based on Realtek for Windows 7/8/8.1/10. When the window is integrated this Driver will make the sound of computer, laptop, your back up crisp, and the sound output for the highest quality possible.
Realtek High Definition Audio Drivers and devices are supported :
ALC880, ALC882, ALC883, ALC885, ALC888, ALC889, ALC861VC, ALC861VD, ALC892, ALC663,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Internet Download Manager (IDM) 6.42 Build 51</title><pubDate> Thu, 16 Oct 2025 17:28:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-inetnet-download-manager-161.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-inetnet-download-manager-161.html
</guid><description>
Internet Download Manager is the download acceleration software, the best download support now, it can help you speed up the download up to five times, continue and schedule downloads. The latest version of IDM adds the compatibility of Windows 10 and Windows 11, it has supported all current popular browsers such as Internet Explorer, Mozilla Firefox, Opera, Google Chrome, ..
Download IDM with the latest version on taiwebs.com making it easy to download and manage your downloaded files...
</description></item><item><title>Download 4K Video Downloader Plus 25.3.3</title><pubDate> Thu, 16 Oct 2025 17:28:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-video-downloader-617.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-video-downloader-617.html
</guid><description>
4K Video Downloader Plus is software support downloads video, audio and subtitles from YouTube with high quality up to 4K. Download process video is very simple: just copy the video link from your browser and click Paste Url. Done! If you want that video on your iPad, iPhone or other device, we have protected you.
The feature on 4K Video Downloader Plus
	Download entire playlists and channels from YouTube and save them in MP4, MKV, M4A, MP3, FLV, 3G, create a file .m3u for...
</description></item><item><title>Download IDM Retail 6.42 Build 51</title><pubDate> Thu, 16 Oct 2025 17:27:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-internet-download-manager-retail-3609.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-internet-download-manager-retail-3609.html
</guid><description>
IDM - Internet Download Manager Retail is a reliable utility and high efficiency will help you to increase your download speed and manage download at better. The program allows you to easily schedule, pause and resume downloads with a single click. Moreover, the application provides error resilience robust and can restart the download at the interrupted or broken. You can restore the download is interrupted due to network problems, lost connections, unexpected power outages, computer...
</description></item><item><title>Download VMware Workstation Pro 25H2 25.0.0.24995812</title><pubDate> Thu, 16 Oct 2025 17:26:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vmware-workstation-pro-29.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vmware-workstation-pro-29.html
</guid><description>
VMware Workstation Pro can change significantly the way of working with the virtual machine, and extremely useful to the developer.Workstation Pro has won many awards, user support when their operating system is not compatible, bringing experience use, feature-rich and efficient operation smoother.
VMware Workstation Pro help you leverage the tablet the latest Intel sensor tablet virtual Workstation. Used Microsoft Surface tablet with the accelerometer, gyroscope, compass and light...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinScan2PDF 9.44 + Portable</title><pubDate> Thu, 16 Oct 2025 17:26:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winscan2pdf-2117.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winscan2pdf-2117.html
</guid><description>
WinScan2PDF is a simple tool that allows you to scan documents from scanner and save them as PDF files. The program also supports multi-page scanning, then will be combined into one PDF document. Useful if your scanning software does not provide PDF conversion.
WinScan2PDF - Scan document to computer
WinScan2PDF allows users to perform scans the entire text or document at the same time to serve for the saved PDF format. Not only that, you also can choose the page any of a text to...
</description></item><item><title>Download CyberLink PowerDirector Ultimate 2026 v24.0.1014.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 16 Oct 2025 17:26:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-powerdirector-ultimate-425.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-powerdirector-ultimate-425.html
</guid><description>
CyberLink PowerDirector Ultimate is software editor, edit video and make movies on the computer from a variety of templates are made available, complete with effects, transitions, animations, and music. CyberLink PowerDirector 17 is a combination of video editing software with advanced video editing features powerful. Cblowing need to add your clips into the time line and click on 'Production'!
The tool design video in CyberLink PowerDirector have the ability to customize helps you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Perfectly Clear WorkBench 4.8.0.2860</title><pubDate> Thu, 16 Oct 2025 17:25:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfectly-clear-workbench-6892.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfectly-clear-workbench-6892.html
</guid><description>
Perfectly Clear Workbench is an application that uses image editing libraries Perfectly Clear by Athentech and is provided to demonstrate the capabilities of the Perfectly Clear processing libraries, which recognize faces and allow quick export of processing settings for use.
One of the key features in Workbench is the ability to "export to API" when saving a Preset. This allows you to make image edits in Workbench and adjust the settings to suit your editing style and needs. You can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Visual Studio Code 1.105.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 16 Oct 2025 17:25:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-visual-studio-code-3182.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-visual-studio-code-3182.html
</guid><description>
Visual Studio Code is the encryption tool of Microsoft has met most of the needs of the developer. Environment this encoding was introduced to compete with other products such as Sublime and Nodepad ++ . Microsoft, in its new product, has not been released in many years, has provided many features in a simple environment. In addition to the familiar with a dozen programming languages, the syntax and get to know coding language as soon as be encrypted and allows for syntax highlighting, it...
</description></item><item><title>Download ExifTool 13.39</title><pubDate> Thu, 16 Oct 2025 17:24:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-exiftool-1685.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-exiftool-1685.html
</guid><description>
ExifTool is a library of Perl platform-independent plus a command line application for reading, writing, and editing meta information in various file types. ExifTool supports many metadata formats including EXIF , GPS , IPTC , XMP , JFIF , GeoTIFF , ICC Profile , Photoshop IRB , FlashPix , AFCP and ID3 , as well as notes of the manufacturer of many digital cameras by Canon , Casio , DJI , FLIR , FujiFilm , GE , GoPro , HP , JVC / Victor , Kodak , Leaf , Minolta / Konica-Minolta , Motorola...
</description></item><item><title>Download Readiris PDF Corporate / Business 25.2.25.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 16 Oct 2025 17:24:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iris-readiris-corporate-120.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iris-readiris-corporate-120.html
</guid><description>
Readiris PDF v22 is a powerful PDF management software that allows file input from various formats to compose, edit, annotate, split, sort, modify, zip, digitally sign and share your own build of one or more secured PDFs. It supports you for daily tasks such as assisting you to work with contracts, text documents, JPG files, Excel spreadsheets, blueprints, Tender projects, Meeting minutes, document conversion PDF documents, edit text documents,...
Readiris Pro converts documents to eBooks...
</description></item><item><title>Download SRWare Iron 141.0.7150.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 16 Oct 2025 17:23:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-srware-iron-6304.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-srware-iron-6304.html
</guid><description>
SRWare Iron  is a Chromium-based web browser developed by the German company SRWare. It is mainly intended to remove usage tracking and other privacy-infringing functionality that Google Chrome browser includes. SRWare Iron Browser is an exact copy of Google Chrome, but it does not have features for collecting personal information. This ensures you can still take advantage of the power of Google Chrome, while being completely assured of your personal information.
A useful feature...
</description></item><item><title>Download 4K YouTube to MP3 25.3.3</title><pubDate> Thu, 16 Oct 2025 17:23:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-youtube-to-mp3-622.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-youtube-to-mp3-622.html
</guid><description>
4K YouTube to MP3 is a software to convert video youtube to mp3 quickly and easily by the manipulation drag-and-drop simple. With 4K YouTube to MP3 you just drag and drop the link to the favorite songs of you and get the MP3 files to your computer, as easy as that. Transfer songs directly to iPod, iPhone and iPad everywhere you go. No install annoying and complex to solve, just a clean interface, user friendly and functional.
When using 4K YouTube to MP3, users will get the playlists,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Auslogics Duplicate File Finder Professional 11.1.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 16 Oct 2025 17:22:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-auslogics-duplicate-file-finder-professional-12706.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-auslogics-duplicate-file-finder-professional-12706.html
</guid><description>
Auslogics Duplicate File Finder Professional is a software tool designed to help users identify and remove duplicate files from their systems effectively. When disk space starts to run out, you need a tool that allows you to clear memory in addition to regular trash cleaning. A duplicate finder is one of the best options that can often delete gigabytes on any computer.
Features of Auslogics Duplicate File Finder Professional
	Scan most types of drives for duplicates: With Duplicate...
</description></item><item><title>Download Total Network Inventory 6.6.0.7114</title><pubDate> Thu, 16 Oct 2025 17:22:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-total-network-inventory-professional-4729.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-total-network-inventory-professional-4729.html
</guid><description>
Computers and servers based on Windows, OS X, Linux, FreeBSD and ESX / ESXi can be scanned without the agent is pre-installed - you just need to know the password of the administrator. Scan the button menu, address range or network structure of Active Directory. Every computer only takes up a few tens of kilobytes in storage TNI concentration. Property group, add comments to them, and attach additional information. It will show your network in all its beauty!
Total Network Inventory...
</description></item><item><title>Download Auslogics Duplicate File Finder 11.1.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 16 Oct 2025 17:22:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-auslogics-duplicate-file-finder-1248.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-auslogics-duplicate-file-finder-1248.html
</guid><description>
Auslogics Duplicate File Finder is an application completely free on taiwebs.com user support, Windows search and delete the duplicate files due to the process of copying and storage for long days on your computer. The first thing the user sees is the software interface is very simple and easy to use. After process launch, Auslogics Duplicate File Finder will find and delete duplicate files from it will liberate space on the hard drive of your computer by finding and eliminate the...
</description></item><item><title>Download ExpanDrive 2025.10.03</title><pubDate> Thu, 16 Oct 2025 17:21:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-expandrive-609.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-expandrive-609.html
</guid><description>
ExpanDrive is software sync cloud storage strong support BackBlaze B2, Google Team Drive, SMB / CIFS and new interface and easy user search file version, share links and much more.  ExpanDrive mapped network drives for macOS and Micosoft Windows connect with all the provide major cloud storage such as Dropbox, Google Drive, Google Team Drive, Amazon Drive, Box, OneDrive, OneDrive for Business, Sharepoint, Openstack Swift , BackBlaze B2, Amazon S3 or SFTP servers, FTP or WebDAV on your own...
</description></item><item><title>Download SIW Technicians 2025 v15.9.1009</title><pubDate> Thu, 16 Oct 2025 17:21:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-siw-technicians-3584.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-siw-technicians-3584.html
</guid><description>
SIW Technicians is an information tool complex system, for Microsoft Windows, check your PC and collect detailed data about the properties and system settings and displays it in a way very easy to understand. SIW Technicians can create a report file (JSON, HTML, TXT, CSV or XML) and you can use that file in batch mode (for Inventory computer inventory of hardware and software, asset inventory, security audit, license Management software, configuration Management server).
SIW Technicians...
</description></item><item><title>Download Auslogics File Recovery Pro 12.1.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 16 Oct 2025 17:20:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-auslogics-file-recovery-pro-1893.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-auslogics-file-recovery-pro-1893.html
</guid><description>
Auslogics File Recovery Pro is an effective program and easy to use will recover files accidentally deleted quickly and the most simple. Auslogics File Recovery Pro is the most advanced version, it contains all the basic features of version Auslogics File Recovery Free upgrades and enhancements add a number of new features for users who pay a fee. Often we delete a file, then clear the recycle bin, and files lost. Software programs sometimes encounter problems while dealing with a file and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wipe Pro 2025.12</title><pubDate> Thu, 16 Oct 2025 17:20:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wipe-pro-710.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wipe-pro-710.html
</guid><description>
Wipe Pro is software that helps clean up litter, increase in hard drive space besides also protect your privacy on the Internet, it removes records about personal activity on the computer. You will be able to delete browser history and the cache, the file index.dat, registry, files, cookies, internet history, auto complete, temporary internet files and many other items. This program also delete all activities other individuals that you made when using the PC and regardless of which...
</description></item><item><title>Download MatchWare MindView 9.0.51011</title><pubDate> Thu, 16 Oct 2025 17:14:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mindview-5965.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mindview-5965.html
</guid><description>
MindView is a professional thinking mapping software that allows you to brainpower, organize and present an intuitive idea. Known for the integration of the MS Office that once won the award, the software mapping software allows you to work more efficiently, turning the idea into action faster than ever! With six interchangable viewing modes, unique project management features and strong collaboration options; MindView has become a leading company in the software mapping software...
</description></item><item><title>Download Picture Window Pro 8.0.533</title><pubDate> Thu, 16 Oct 2025 17:14:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-picture-window-pro-7452.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-picture-window-pro-7452.html
</guid><description>
Picture Window Pro is a powerful image editing tool designed for serious photographers with strict creative and quality standards. Its comprehensive set of photo editing and editing tools let you control and shape every aspect of your images.
Picture Window Pro 8 is a complete rewrite of Picture Window Pro 7. It features non-destructive image editing through a novel interface based on an image tree. It also fully supports large, high-resolution displays and can be used in dual monitor...
</description></item><item><title>Download Auslogics File Recovery 12.1.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 16 Oct 2025 17:13:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-auslogics-file-recovery-649.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-auslogics-file-recovery-649.html
</guid><description>
Auslogics File Recovery is a recovery tool most effective for files you may lose by accident or due to virus attack. When using Auslogics File Recovery you can configure a search filter when it comes to file types (photos, music, videos, documents and software), last modification date, file name and search type (perform deep scan, skip files with the size no, skip temporary and system files).
Auslogics File Recovery - file recovery safe, effective
Auslogics File Recovery works with...
</description></item><item><title>Download All Remixes 1.5.4</title><pubDate> Thu, 16 Oct 2025 17:12:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-all-remixes-7512.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-all-remixes-7512.html
</guid><description>
All Remixes is software to discover all the remixes of your favorite artists and songs! Listen to every remix your favorite artist has ever made! Filter remixes by song title or artist in one click.
Features of All Remixes
	Discover all remixes of your favorite artists and songs!
	Listen to every remix your favorite artist has ever done!
	Filter remixes by song title or artist in one click.
	Find 100s of remixes quickly.
	Discover all the missing mixes from your music collection.
	Get...
</description></item><item><title>Download Room Arranger 10.3.0.735</title><pubDate> Thu, 16 Oct 2025 17:11:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-room-arranger-3779.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-room-arranger-3779.html
</guid><description>
Room Arranger is a 3D application lets you easily plan for the room, office or his apartment just a few mouse clicks. The application comes with a simple interface will significantly simplify your work. You can draw many kinds of objects and items to create furniture of your own. This app also includes a library of object rich.
Software Room Arranger enables you to view your project in 3D form. You can also upload the 3D scene interact on your blog or your website. The application uses...
</description></item></channel></rss>