<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 08:59:46 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 08:59:46 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download K-Lite Codec Pack Full 19.2.5</title><pubDate> Thu, 02 Oct 2025 19:50:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-115.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-115.html
</guid><description>
K Lite Codec Pack Full brings pc users an optimal solution for watching movies, listening to music, support most popular format today by using collection codec rich. This software also allows you to refine the quality of videos and music to enjoy, create a list of music and video to comfortable enjoy.
Prompt to software, listen to music, watch movies, currently, part, user will prompt to programs like VLC or KMP ... With VLC, it was too familiar with users, not just watch videos, listen...
</description></item><item><title>Download K-Lite Codec Pack Mega 19.2.5</title><pubDate> Thu, 02 Oct 2025 19:50:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-mega-3202.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-mega-3202.html
</guid><description>
K-Lite Mega Codec Pack is a collection of components needed for audio playback and the video in the player DirectShow like Windows Media Player, Media Center, and Media Player Classic. This is the latest beta version, Pack Codec K-Lite latest stable. The Mega variant is the biggest of the four variants of the codec pack. It provides everything you need to play all audio and video files. In addition, it also contains some codecs ACM / VFW can be used by the application coding / video...
</description></item><item><title>Download Allavsoft Video Downloader Converter 3.28.4.9401</title><pubDate> Thu, 02 Oct 2025 19:49:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allavsoft-video-downloader-converter-248.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allavsoft-video-downloader-converter-248.html
</guid><description>
Allavsoft Video Downloader Converter software supports download movies, music videos, playlist, sport videos from video sharing website for free like Facebook, Youtube and over 100 video sharing sites.
Allavsoft is many users favorite thanks to the combined features simultaneous transmission of multiple videos and speed limit download video. Besides, the program also supports pause and resume data transmission, to help you interfere with the process of transmitting download data to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Kingston SSD Manager 1.5.6.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 02 Oct 2025 19:48:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kingston-ssd-manager-2810.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kingston-ssd-manager-2810.html
</guid><description>
Kingston SSD Manager is an application that gives users the ability to track and manage the various aspects of solid state drives Kingston® his.
Kingston SSD Manager - track, manage, drive SSD
&amp;nbsp;
The feature of Kingston SSD Manager
	Monitor the status and use of drive
	View the identification information drives, such as model name, serial number, firmware version and other related information
	Using The technology Self-monitoring analysis and report (SMART), and the detailed...
</description></item><item><title>Download Daum PotPlayer 1.7.22619</title><pubDate> Thu, 02 Oct 2025 19:48:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-daum-potplayer-1015.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-daum-potplayer-1015.html
</guid><description>
Daum PotPlayer is a multimedia player has almost all the functions and interface similar, but improved markedly with KMP. Software Daum PotPlayer Stable have the special feature is the high quality playback, support for all video formats and audio modern and the presence of video codecs DXVA integration. Has a modern design, easy to install, have the ability to assign and change the hot keys, record sound to play, display subtitles, connect the plug-in DSP that allows visual display when...
</description></item><item><title>Download Certificate Manager 18.28</title><pubDate> Thu, 02 Oct 2025 19:47:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-certificate-manager-13958.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-certificate-manager-13958.html
</guid><description>
Certificate Manager provides an in-depth overview of your current certificates, allowing you to easily access detailed information. It also provides functions for both exporting existing certificates and importing new certificates, enhancing your certificate management capabilities.
Application certificates are often overlooked by most users until problems arise during application installation. For the average end user, there is little reason to focus on application certificates....
</description></item><item><title>Download Chris-PC RAM Booster 7.25.1001</title><pubDate> Thu, 02 Oct 2025 19:47:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chris-pc-ram-booster-1181.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chris-pc-ram-booster-1181.html
</guid><description>
ChrisPC RAM Booster is software speed up your system by managing and acceleration of the RAM in the operating system. RAM Booster will monitor the RAM usage (memory random access) and upon reaching the threshold memory certain low, it will trigger the process of freeing up memory for the new program open while moving at the same time the old programs from the RAM memory into virtual memory on disk.
Chris-PC RAM Booster - speed up processing RAM
Certainly this is a slower process...
</description></item><item><title>Download Omidsoft System Information 18.28</title><pubDate> Thu, 02 Oct 2025 19:47:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-omidsoft-system-information-12255.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-omidsoft-system-information-12255.html
</guid><description>
System Information is a general Windows utility to display many useful information about Windows, Network and hardware - CPU information, PCI information, PCMCIA information, USB information, SMBus information, SPD information , ACPI method, machine information, hardware sensors, networked computer, operating system information, etc.
System Information is a simple yet highly effective tool designed for individuals who want to gain comprehensive insight into their computer systems. While...
</description></item><item><title>Download PC Timer 18.28</title><pubDate> Thu, 02 Oct 2025 19:46:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pc-timer-7519.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pc-timer-7519.html
</guid><description>
PC Timer is a simple tool to automatically shut down, log out, restart or lock your PC based on your scheduled time. A handy feature of the app is its ability to prevent unauthorized cancellation of a scheduled task. To do so, PC Timer .NET allows you to set a password that the user must provide to cancel the operation.
The advantage of the application is its simplicity, small footprint on the system and the fact that it does not require installation. Thanks to the ability to set tasks...
</description></item><item><title>Download Soft Organizer Pro 10.30</title><pubDate> Thu, 02 Oct 2025 19:46:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-soft-organizer-498.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-soft-organizer-498.html
</guid><description>
Soft Organizer is versatile software just install the software to help uninstall software quickly and safely to release the hard drive or restore when necessary.  That side, Soft Organizer also keep track of the changes made to the system during installation of new utilities or help test the new version of the software on the computer to update timely, classification, and management of programs for users to follow easily.
Soft Organizer has a modern interface with simple manipulation to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Edge Remover 18.28</title><pubDate> Thu, 02 Oct 2025 19:45:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-edge-remover-7689.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-edge-remover-7689.html
</guid><description>
Edge Remover is our mini user interfaceless tool to permanently remove Microsoft Edge from your system. Easily remove Microsoft Edge browser from your system, with just one click, with this simple, no UI app.
Features of Edge Remover
	Remove MSEdge and its components
	Prevent reinstalling MSEdge on your system
Requirements:
Operating System: Microsoft Windows 7 or later
Framework: Microsoft .NET Framework 4.0
</description></item><item><title>Download BoostPing 1.6.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 02 Oct 2025 19:45:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-boostping-12519.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-boostping-12519.html
</guid><description>
BoostPing helps optimize your online gaming experience by modifying the network throttling index and disabling the Nagle algorithm. By turning this feature off, you can achieve more instantaneous data transfer speeds, potentially reducing latency.
What is Nagle's algorithm?
The Nagle algorithm is designed to improve network efficiency by combining small data packets into larger packets, which can cause lag in online games. Disabling it can result in more responsive gameplay. On the...
</description></item><item><title>Download ExamDiff Pro Master Edition 16.0.1.10</title><pubDate> Thu, 02 Oct 2025 19:45:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-examdiff-pro-master-312.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-examdiff-pro-master-312.html
</guid><description>
ExamDiff Pro Master is a tool to compare files and folders intuitive and easy to use, intuitive and easy to use for Windows. ExamDiff Pro Master has unique features distinguishes ExamDiff Pro with the program compare other. ExamDiff Pro Master to help perform reviews of code and share other reports with your colleagues and compare local website with FTP server by plug-ins more integrated.
ExamDiff Pro Master can create a snapshot folder for comparison and storage in the future, compare...
</description></item><item><title>Download Reg Organizer 9.85</title><pubDate> Thu, 02 Oct 2025 19:44:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reg-organizer-1595.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reg-organizer-1595.html
</guid><description>
Reg Organizer is a software to scan and clean your registry windows register errors and help optimize performance computer system. Reg Organizer is a software subscription, professional, and professional, and any way that the Windows registry are necessary and therefore, the overall performance of Windows improves, there is this software.
Reg Organizer - registry Cleaning and pc optimization
The main features of Reg Organizer
	Cleaning the registry of the lock is not valid and not...
</description></item><item><title>Download Acoustica Mixcraft Recording Studio 10.6 Build 636</title><pubDate> Thu, 02 Oct 2025 19:44:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-acoustica-mixcraft-recording-studio-3450.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-acoustica-mixcraft-recording-studio-3450.html
</guid><description>
Record and mix your tracks to perfection, in record time, the interface is extremely intuitive of Mixcraft, sound engine as fast as lightning, technology extends the actual time and prolonged duration, and close support as global for the plug-in, the sound of the Tuesday, interface, and controller hardware.
Record the number of sounds and virtual instruments, unlimited, edit, cut and mix sounds easy, add tons of effects and automation, mixing and mastering your project with WAV, MP3 and...
</description></item><item><title>Download IntraWEB Ultimate 16.1.6</title><pubDate> Thu, 02 Oct 2025 19:43:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intraweb-ultimate-2007.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intraweb-ultimate-2007.html
</guid><description>
IntraWEB Ultimate is a tool to build the website. With this tool, the developer can create the page using the same method used to build the Windows program. Because the HTML page directly from the concept design to the user's computer does not download a bit more complicated and in fact is required from web server. So, the template IntraWeb on the server and download server and displays them to the user. Things technology direction of the IntraWEB Ultimate provides part flexibility and...
</description></item><item><title>Download QuickSurface Pro 2026 v7.9.62</title><pubDate> Thu, 02 Oct 2025 19:42:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quick-surface-3724.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quick-surface-3724.html
</guid><description>
Quick Surface is the optimal solution for reverse Engineering compatible with any 3D scanner export mesh in STL or point cloud PTX. Model parameter future for both organic shapes and prismatic. Export data in IGES standard or file format STEP or build full parameter tree history directly into SOLIDWORKS.
Quick Surface - pattern design, 3D product
The features and characteristics of Quick Surface
	Interactive selection of the user instead of the dynamic segment on grid...
</description></item><item><title>Download Colorpicker 2.3.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 02 Oct 2025 19:41:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-toinane-colorpicker-7999.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-toinane-colorpicker-7999.html
</guid><description>
Created for designers and developers, Colorpicker allows you to select, edit, organize and store your colors easily. Colorpicker works efficiently through its interface. All features are accessible from the toolbar and keyboard shortcuts. You have the ability to choose any color thanks to the three RGB sliders (coming soon HSL, CMYK, ...).
It allows select that allows you to get any color on your screen. You can see the colors on the Colorpicker interface in real time. This way, you can...
</description></item><item><title>Download AndreaMosaic 3.54.3</title><pubDate> Thu, 02 Oct 2025 19:39:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-andreamosaic-1684.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-andreamosaic-1684.html
</guid><description>
AndreaMosaic is a other tool allows you to transform photos into mosaics created from collection of photos of you. The manner of operation of the program is very simple, but it does not always give you the results you are looking for. The user must choose the image collection you want to use to create the mosaic and the photo will be converted on AndreaMosaic.
&amp;nbsp;
AndreaMosaic allows you to configure a number of options, such as width the last of the mosaic, the number of images on...
</description></item><item><title>Download SpyZooka Pro 5.3.0.31</title><pubDate> Thu, 02 Oct 2025 19:38:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-spyzooka-pro-10529.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-spyzooka-pro-10529.html
</guid><description>
SpyZooka Pro is a professional anti-adware, anti-Trojan and anti-spyware program. The program can perform both quick scans and full system scans, and you will be able to see the number of infections found during the scan. SpyZooka is a trusted and helpful partner in the fight against computer threats. It gives one a lot of tools to work with, each protecting or maintaining a specific area of your machine. The only thing users will have to worry about is which tools to use and specific...
</description></item><item><title>Download 2BrightSparks SyncBackPro 11.3.113</title><pubDate> Thu, 02 Oct 2025 19:38:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-2brightsparks-syncbackpro-812.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-2brightsparks-syncbackpro-812.html
</guid><description>
SyncBackPro is a backup utility, restore and synchronize professional and enhanced with many advanced features. With SyncBackPro you can copy any file whether it is locked or is open, which usually isn't possible to copy in these conditions. But this feature works only on window XP or higher version of window. Backup with SyncBackPro is a process that is very fast and it can handle the number of files is not limited.
2BrightSparks SyncBackPro - backup, restore data
The main features of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ocenaudio 3.16.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 02 Oct 2025 19:37:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ocenaudio-837.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ocenaudio-837.html
</guid><description>
Ocenaudio: software for windows, this is the sound editing easy, fast and powerful. ocenaudio is a program for audio editing multi-platform, easy to use, fast and functional. This is the ideal software for those who need to edit and analyze audio files.
Ocenaudio - editor powerful audio for windows
This software is based on Ocen Framework , a powerful library developed to simplify and standardize the development of application analysis and sound processing on many platforms.
Features...
</description></item><item><title>Download MoneyWorks Gold 9.2.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 02 Oct 2025 19:37:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-moneyworks-gold-12652.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-moneyworks-gold-12652.html
</guid><description>
MoneyWorks Gold is comprehensive accounting software designed for small and medium businesses, providing many superior features compared to MoneyWorks Express. It has all the features of MoneyWorks Express plus cost center accounting, multi-currency, job costing, advanced inventory management and more.
Main features
	Cost center accounting: Allows businesses to manage and report on different departments or projects, facilitating better budgeting and financial analysis.
	Multi-currency...
</description></item><item><title>Download K-Lite Codec Pack Update 19.2.5</title><pubDate> Thu, 02 Oct 2025 19:37:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-update-5145.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-update-5145.html
</guid><description>
K-Lite Codec Pack Update is the update of the set of codecs and related tools. Codec stands for Compressor-decompressor. Codec is necessary to encode and decode (play) audio and video. K-Lite Codec Pack Update is designed as a user-friendly solution with users to play all movie files your. With Codec Pack K-Lite, you can play 99% of all the movies found on your computer. A number of packages codec is not friendly with computers, as they tend to slow down Windows, break down multimedia...
</description></item><item><title>Download Macs Fan Control 1.5.19</title><pubDate> Thu, 02 Oct 2025 19:35:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mac-boot-camp-fan-control-3054.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mac-boot-camp-fan-control-3054.html
</guid><description>
Mac &amp;amp; Boot Camp Fan Control is software that allows you to retrieve detailed information about the fan used to cool equipment Macintosh. As the name suggests, it can only be used on devices running Windows. You can use utility fan control when you need to optimize the sound level or heat level of the components the main system. It allows you to control fan speed directly from Windows and supports the fan from the device iMac or MacBook Pro.
Mac &amp;amp; Boot Camp Fan Control - computer...
</description></item></channel></rss>