<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 15:46:42 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 15:46:42 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Winaero Tweaker 1.64.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 17:19:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winaero-tweaker-1063.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winaero-tweaker-1063.html
</guid><description>
Winaero Tweaker is a customization tool is provided for windows for you to change the default settings, and personalization Windows liking. The program includes the tweaks for all version of operating system from Windows 7 to Windows 10. Winaero Tweaker automatically detect OS version of Windows you're running and show the custom and custom custom. Software can be installed as a mobile app so that you can carry with you when you move from this computer to another computer.
Winaero...
</description></item><item><title>Download Advanced System Repair Pro 2.0.1.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 17:15:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-system-repair-pro-80.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-system-repair-pro-80.html
</guid><description>
Advanced System Repair Pro gives you all the tools you need in a program to clean, repair, protect, optimize and increase your PC!
Advanced System Repair Pro speed 300% faster help your computer run faster by increasing the launch speed, optimizing registry, as well as get rid of unwanted apps and files, useless other causing your computer to run slower.
Advanced System Repair Pro - optimized system
Features, characteristics, Advanced System Repair Pro
Get a computer cleaner in a few...
</description></item><item><title>Download JRiver Media Center 35.0.29</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 17:14:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jriver-media-center-110.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jriver-media-center-110.html
</guid><description>
JRiver Media Center can help you strictly manage all your files media and enjoy them in a completely new way. Launching the application for the first time, users will be immediately impressed with the intuitive and eye-catching interface with many interesting features to explore. Most people who have used JRiver Media Center evaluate that the software interface design is youthful and modern.
The software for arranging cover art of music files is also extremely neat, especially Insert...
</description></item><item><title>Download StartIsBack ++ 2.9.21</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 17:13:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-startisback-402.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-startisback-402.html
</guid><description>
StartIsBack ++ is software customizable start menu and taskbar support, booting the computer and showing the feature started working on the start menu. StartIsBack is for the screen is not upside down when booting, help easy yùy variables and configuration rich; And much more.
The main features StartIsBack ++
Computer support:
	Launch programs you use frequently
	Open the document you are working
	Find content you are looking for
	To place the system just by a click of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Audacity 3.7.7</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 17:13:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-audacity-1648.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-audacity-1648.html
</guid><description>
Audacity software to record audio along with editing features such as noise filtering, distortion noise, insert unique effects. The latest version of Audacity include the improvement of effects, interface, updates Nyquist and libflac. A number of bugs have also been fixed to help the software operate more smoothly. Audacity accompanied by the link to various sources, assist you learn how to use all the features of the program. These sources include Quick Help Guide (quick help), a guide,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Remote Desktop Manager Enterprise 2025.3.27</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 17:12:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-remote-desktop-manager-enterprise-242.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-remote-desktop-manager-enterprise-242.html
</guid><description>
Remote Desktop Manager Enterprise software is the complete management of remote connections and virtual machines from a single location, at the same time access support data online and cloud storage. Remote Desktop Manager supports multiple types of connections, not only connections for the protocol connect remote computer Remote Desktop Protocol (RDP).
Remote Desktop Manager easily add, edit, delete, share, organize and find your remote connection of you quickly. Compatible with...
</description></item><item><title>Download Avast Premium Security 25.12.10659</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 17:12:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avast-premier-antivirus-security-1359.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avast-premier-antivirus-security-1359.html
</guid><description>
Avast! Premier Antivirus is antivirus software famous by combining all the technologies and methods virus advanced. The developer software this anti-virus have invested in all their knowledge about fighting viruses to create one of the software anti-virus best. Program anti-virus this combines all the technology and advanced methods to get the level of computer security highest. This product is ideal for all the Windows operating system.
Avast! Premier Antivirus - antivirus...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft Edge 143.0.3650.80</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 17:01:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-edge-3940.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-edge-3940.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft Edge is web browser developed specifically for Windows operating system 10 alternatives to Internet Explorer is the default browser on Windows. Browser Microsoft Edge built-in assistant Cortana brings content and website based on the user's preferences, there are also system utilities quite extensive help you to customize according to individual. Microsoft Edge has the similarity with Google Chrome quite large, except the target is marked more of the interface and the rounded...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Downloader 10.0.9</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 17:00:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html
</guid><description>
YTD Youtube Downloader is an application that reliable and intuitive, allowing you to quickly download YouTube videos and save them to your computer. You can also convert the media files to the format desired video or extract audio streams and save separately. YTD Youtube Downloader lets you save your favorite clips of yourself from Youtube, Facebook, Vimeo and Dailymotion to your desktop. The software supports URLS from many web site hosting, multimedia and allows you to download desired...
</description></item><item><title>Download PassFab 4EasyPartition 3.9.0.12</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 17:00:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-passfab-4easypartition-7983.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-passfab-4easypartition-7983.html
</guid><description>
After using your PC for many years, there are bound to be many files you want to transfer to your new PC. PassFab 4EasyPartition can perform a one-click migration saving you hours of reinstalling operating systems and applications. It has an intuitive interface and step-by-step wizard that makes migrating the system in just a few steps. PassFab 4EasyPartition will effectively solve the problem of low disk space, speed up your computer and make it run faster.
Features of PassFab...
</description></item><item><title>Download SoftPerfect Network Scanner 25.12</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 16:59:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-softperfect-network-scanner-465.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-softperfect-network-scanner-465.html
</guid><description>
SoftPerfect Network Scanner is software scan ip address fast with many features for the programmer. With SoftPerfect Network Scanner you can completely scan IPv4 / IPv6 universal fast with many options. Program this powerful can ping computers, scan ports, discover the folder is shared and comes with filtering options and flexible display. It can take practically any information about the network device through WMI, SNMP, HTTP, SSH , and PowerShell. In addition, it can scan the remote...
</description></item><item><title>Download Internet Download Accelerator Pro 7.3.1.1745</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 16:58:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-internet-download-accelerator-pro-234.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-internet-download-accelerator-pro-234.html
</guid><description>
Internet Download Accelerator Pro is software acceleration support download support users in the download file like IDM running on multiple network protocols, including FTP. Internet Download Accelerator will help your computer be file download speed is fast even when the transmission line do not have high speed. Internet Download Accelerator Pro is completely compatible with most web browsers such as Internet Explorer, Firefox, Mozilla, Opera,..
Internet Download Accelerator also...
</description></item><item><title>Download Kotato All Video Downloader Pro 10.0.6</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 16:58:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kotato-all-video-downloader-pro-5228.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kotato-all-video-downloader-pro-5228.html
</guid><description>
Kotato All Video Downloader Pro is a Windows application professional to download and convert your favorite videos from the video sharing website. It speeds up your downloads up to 5 times! Kotato All Video Downloader Pro can download videos from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion and hundreds of video sharing sites, other. After downloading, you will be able to play them smoother on your PC or your mobile device, even when you don't have Internet access.
The main features of Kotato All...
</description></item><item><title>Download Viber for PC 26.8.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 16:57:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-viber-2406.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-viber-2406.html
</guid><description>
Viber is a software of instant messaging, based on VoIP protocols, multi-platform due to the Viber Media development for smart phones used to send sms and make calls over the internet. Along with text messaging, users can exchange images, video and audio.
Viber - software news message, chat online
This is a program that is quite popular is mainly designed for mobile phones, but now we are talking about the version for Windows, so immediately. It will allow you to send messages to other...
</description></item><item><title>Download Youtube Downloader HD 5.9.9.6</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 16:57:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-downloader-hd-3122.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-downloader-hd-3122.html
</guid><description>
Youtube Downloader HD is the best application to download and save Youtube videos. And it's completely free :) You can also convert the downloaded video into various formats easily. Youtube Downloader HD is the download at video free. Download at your videos easily and convert to AVI video format or into MP4 video format (compatible with iPad, iPhone). You can download high quality videos, high definition videos and Full HD from YouTube.
Youtube Downloader HD - Download Youtube videos...
</description></item><item><title>Download Room Arranger 10.3.1.737</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 16:56:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-room-arranger-3779.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-room-arranger-3779.html
</guid><description>
Room Arranger is a 3D application lets you easily plan for the room, office or his apartment just a few mouse clicks. The application comes with a simple interface will significantly simplify your work. You can draw many kinds of objects and items to create furniture of your own. This app also includes a library of object rich.
Software Room Arranger enables you to view your project in 3D form. You can also upload the 3D scene interact on your blog or your website. The application uses...
</description></item><item><title>Download 4DDiG Partition Manager 3.9.0.12</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 16:56:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4ddig-partition-manager-2024-9781.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4ddig-partition-manager-2024-9781.html
</guid><description>
4DDiG Partition Manager is a powerful Windows disk partition software expert in system migration, disk cloning and disk partition management. It can effectively clone your entire disk or partition, providing a reliable solution for data backup.
This is Windows 10 fast system and data transfer solution &amp;amp; 11. 4DDiG Partition Manager can move the system and large files or folders from one disk partition to a larger one with just one click. Or you can use it to move the system and large...
</description></item><item><title>Download K-Lite Codec Pack Update 19.3.6</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 16:55:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-update-5145.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-update-5145.html
</guid><description>
K-Lite Codec Pack Update is the update of the set of codecs and related tools. Codec stands for Compressor-decompressor. Codec is necessary to encode and decode (play) audio and video. K-Lite Codec Pack Update is designed as a user-friendly solution with users to play all movie files your. With Codec Pack K-Lite, you can play 99% of all the movies found on your computer. A number of packages codec is not friendly with computers, as they tend to slow down Windows, break down multimedia...
</description></item><item><title>Download Stellar Photo Recovery Professional 12.3.0.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 16:54:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stellar-photo-recovery-professional-3934.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stellar-photo-recovery-professional-3934.html
</guid><description>
Stellar Photo Recovery Professional is photo recovery software for computer users running the Windows operating system restore the photos, songs, movies and other multimedia files, other deleted or lost. Stellar Photo Recovery Professional help you to restore all the pictures lost or deleted from any storage media based on Windows operating system, how. Also recovers photos / pictures from storage media damaged or formatted.
Stellar Photo Recovery Professional - Recover lost...
</description></item><item><title>Download LibreWolf 146.0-2</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 16:53:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-librewolf-11967.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-librewolf-11967.html
</guid><description>
LibreWolf is a customized and independent version of Firefox, with the main goals being user privacy, security and freedom. LibreWolf is designed to provide increased protection against tracking and fingerprinting techniques and includes a number of security enhancements. This is achieved through our security and privacy oriented settings and patches. LibreWolf also aims to remove all telemetry, data collection and annoyances, as well as disable anti-free features like DRM.
LibreWolf...
</description></item><item><title>Download Software Companions GerbView 11.32.0.636</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 16:52:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-software-companions-gerbview-1484.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-software-companions-gerbview-1484.html
</guid><description>
GerbView is a file, advanced, but easy to use, convert, print, and view files HPGL, HPGL / 2, Excellon and raster. It supports both RS274D and RS274X. You can use this software to convert the old format and RS274D standard to the new RS274X have default data. Gerbview is used to represent and illustrate the intricate design of you.
Software Companions GerbView - conversion, printing, and viewing HPGL, HPGL / 2, Excellon
You don't need to wait for rendered images to see the picture of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sante PACS Server 4.4.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 16:52:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sante-pacs-server-7541.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sante-pacs-server-7541.html
</guid><description>
Sante PACS Server is an HTTP (web) server for DICOM files and a CD/DVD Burn and Print server that offers high performance and reliability at an affordable price. It provides connectivity to all DICOM methods (CT, MR, US, CR, NM, XA, MG, DX, etc.). Reviewing of DICOM images can be done using the Sante PACS Viewer (the system's built-in, full-featured DICOM Viewer). The built-in web server can be used as a free cloud server for DICOM files!
Tools of Sante PACS Server
	The Migration Tool...
</description></item><item><title>Download Brave Browser 1.85.116</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 16:51:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-brave-browser-2874.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-brave-browser-2874.html
</guid><description>
Brave Browser is a browser based on Chromium, the basic principle is that operation fast and privacy of users. The program can block pop-up windows and other ads, plus it blocked the mechanism for monitoring the online activities of your. Therefore, you can purchase and safely browse the website you are interested in without having to worry about the fact that your activity will be monitored and then you will be shown the necessary advertising or service provider of parties...
</description></item><item><title>Download SoftPerfect WiFi Guard 25.12</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 16:51:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-softperfect-wifi-guard-503.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-softperfect-wifi-guard-503.html
</guid><description>
SoftPerfect WiFi Guard is a software to help users to scan periodically the wifi network at the same time allows you to view all the connected equipment.  If you work in a WiFi network small and want to stay safe, then you should try this program. Typically, the modern network of this type is well protected, but there are still some bugs to make your access password, you risk measuring so you should use SoftPerfect WiFi Guard.
SoftPerfect WiFi Guard allows the user to view information...
</description></item><item><title>Download Imaginando BAM 1.5.4</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 16:50:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-imaginando-bam-10547.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-imaginando-bam-10547.html
</guid><description>
Imaginando BAM gives you everything you need to turn your musical ideas into reality. Whether you want to make beats or create music, Imaginando BAM is perfect for both beginners and pros. If you're new to beat making, BAM is the ideal way to learn how to make beats and create music; Easy-to-use interface means you can be a beat maker in minutes!
BAM is equipped with many great built-in synthesis and effects tools: oscillator synthesizer, sampler, drum synthesizer, analog bass...
</description></item></channel></rss>