<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 21:30:10 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 21:30:10 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download R-Wipe &amp;amp; Clean 20.0 Build 2529</title><pubDate> Sun, 05 Oct 2025 21:13:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-wipe-clean-891.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-wipe-clean-891.html
</guid><description>
R-Wipe &amp;amp; Clean is software to delete junk files, unnecessary files from your computer to release the storage space and speed up your computer. In addition, R-Wipe &amp;amp; Clean also unleash the capacity of your drive and delete information invasion of privacy on different operations online and offline including your internet history and cookies, the list of downloaded files and documents were open, buffer different data, temporary files and many other items, created by the operating...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ahnenblatt 4.35.0.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 05 Oct 2025 21:12:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ahnenblatt-3844.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ahnenblatt-3844.html
</guid><description>
Ahnenblatt is a genealogy software full-featured, easy to use suitable for beginners and even pedigree has the experience to organize genealogy research by you. Use plausibility checks to find out the inaccuracies in your family and create the chart impressive with just a few mouse clicks.
Ahnenblatt - Create family tree,
Recently, there has been strong increase of the general interest of the public for genealogical tree. Users who desire to track their heritage have many tools at...
</description></item><item><title>Download StartAllBack 3.9.16.5317</title><pubDate> Sun, 05 Oct 2025 21:12:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-startallback-6857.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-startallback-6857.html
</guid><description>
With the official release of Windows 11, chances are that most of you want to try it out. As the name suggests, StartAllBack is a small, lightweight tool that can help you enjoy the power of the new operating system while keeping the look and feel, especially because main work area, desktop of Windows 7, Windows 10 as taskbars and start menu styles.
StartAllBack is specially designed for Windows 11 and will not work on any older operating systems. If you want to get the start menu back...
</description></item><item><title>Download Active Data Studio 25.2.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 05 Oct 2025 21:11:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-active-data-studio-306.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-active-data-studio-306.html
</guid><description>
Active Data Studio is software to backup and restore discs, restore documents and deleted photos, delete disks securely, monitor HDD status and can repair PC when Windows can't start normally. Active@ Data Studio is a set of both apps to the desktop with a CD / DVD boot or USB disk to boot any system into the Windows Recovery Environment.
Features Active Data Studio
Active Data Studio perform data recovery
	Active@ File Recovery - recover files and folders deleted, even when deleted,...
</description></item><item><title>Download UWPSpy 1.4.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 05 Oct 2025 21:11:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-uwpspy-10357.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-uwpspy-10357.html
</guid><description>
UWPSpy is a testing tool for UWP and WinUI 3 applications. Seamlessly view and manipulate UI elements and their properties in real time.
It allows users to observe how changes affect the structure and functionality of their UWP app. This is beneficial for helping with user interface design tasks during application development. When you select specific properties, the associated elements will be highlighted and any changes will update in real time.
How to use:
	Run UWPSpy.exe and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Soft Organizer Pro 10.31</title><pubDate> Sun, 05 Oct 2025 21:11:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-soft-organizer-498.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-soft-organizer-498.html
</guid><description>
Soft Organizer is versatile software just install the software to help uninstall software quickly and safely to release the hard drive or restore when necessary.  That side, Soft Organizer also keep track of the changes made to the system during installation of new utilities or help test the new version of the software on the computer to update timely, classification, and management of programs for users to follow easily.
Soft Organizer has a modern interface with simple manipulation to...
</description></item><item><title>Download ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro 15.25.1004</title><pubDate> Sun, 05 Oct 2025 21:10:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-videotube-downloader-pro-1276.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-videotube-downloader-pro-1276.html
</guid><description>
ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro is the professional version support download videos and playlists from YouTube, videos from Dailymotion, BBC iPlayer, ITV Player, ABC,  FOX,CBS.com Vimeo, Prosieben, Metacafe, Blip.tv CBC.ca many more video sites. After the video is downloaded, you can convert them to the formats compatible with iPad, iPhone, iPod, MPEG-4, H. 264, MP3, AC3.
ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro - Download videos on Youtube
This is one of the software download the most...
</description></item><item><title>Download SUPERAntiSpyware Pro X 10.0.1280</title><pubDate> Sun, 05 Oct 2025 21:10:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-superantispyware-pro-396.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-superantispyware-pro-396.html
</guid><description>
SUPER AntiSpyware Pro is a part mễm perfect provides the function of remove Spyware and Adware, Malware, Trojans, KeyLoggers, Dialers, Hi-Jackers from your computer. Besides the main task is prevent Spyware, SUPERAntiSpyware Pro also helps you to scan virus quickly, system restore and operate the computer fast, stable.
Main features SUPER AntiSpyware Pro
Detect and remove malicious threats:
	Prevent malware, spyware, adware, trojan, worm, ransomware, Hijackers, Parasites, Rootkits,...
</description></item><item><title>Download foobar2000 2.25.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 05 Oct 2025 21:09:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-foobar2000-1812.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-foobar2000-1812.html
</guid><description>
foobar2000 is the media player for media formats MP3, WAV, OGG and other formats multimedia other. It has no bells and whistles, however, under the hood, the program offers quite many features, including format, title and layout of the interface can be customized, convert WAV, Equalizer, Resampler, note cards, MP3, playlists, music album, CD, drag / drop and more. It also includes all the standard features like shuffle, random play, etc.
foobar2000 - The media player
foobar2000 running...
</description></item><item><title>Download Agisoft Metashape Professional 2.3.0 Build 21378</title><pubDate> Sun, 05 Oct 2025 21:09:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-agisoft-metashape-professional-1731.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-agisoft-metashape-professional-1731.html
</guid><description>
Agisoft Metashape (formerly PhotoScan) is a software product independently perform image processing and digital data creation, 3D space used in GIS applications, material cultural heritage and the production visual effects as well as the indirect measurement of the different subjects scale. Technical digital photography is deployed wisely is applied with the method of computer vision led to the system processor, smart auto, on the one hand, can be managed by a new person in the field of...
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 7.3.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 05 Oct 2025 21:08:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-11-7760.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-11-7760.html
</guid><description>
TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 is a program that allows users to discover hidden settings in Windows 11. This application is specially designed for Windows 11, groups many registry settings and distribute them from the easy and secure user interface. With TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 you can move the Windows taskbar to the top and resize the taskbar by editing the registry value. With any application that modifies the registry, we recommend that you have a backup copy...
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 7.3.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 05 Oct 2025 21:08:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-10-7759.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-10-7759.html
</guid><description>
TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 is a utility that allows users to discover hidden settings in Windows 10. This application is specially designed for Windows 10, groups many registry settings and provide them from an easy and secure user interface. With TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 you can move the Windows taskbar to the top and resize the taskbar by editing the registry value. With any application that modifies the registry, we recommend that you have a backup copy to...
</description></item><item><title>Download RadioLogger 4.1.0.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 05 Oct 2025 21:07:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-radiologger-11441.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-radiologger-11441.html
</guid><description>
RadioLogger is a program used to record (store) radio stations on a computer hard drive. Archiving can be useful, for example, in disputes with advertisers over the fact that an ad is being broadcast, or useful for various vetting activities. Recording can be done 24 hours a day or during certain periods of time. The program uses leading audio compression technologies so the files created are very small in size.
RadioLogger Features
	Scheduler: automatically start/stop recording...
</description></item><item><title>Download RadioCaster 3.6.0.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 05 Oct 2025 21:02:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-radiocaster-6516.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-radiocaster-6516.html
</guid><description>
RadioCaster is a program that takes any audio including the same signal that is connected to your computer or broadcast device and streaming the entire world. That means using seamless audio sources, existing radio programs and other materials while maintaining your own digital presence. The configuration is not difficult, while the detailed statistics help you track your subject.
Features of RadioCaster
	To any sound you have on your computer: support for audio recording from any...
</description></item><item><title>Download MailWasher Pro 7.15.44</title><pubDate> Sun, 05 Oct 2025 21:02:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-firetrust-mailwasher-pro-825.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-firetrust-mailwasher-pro-825.html
</guid><description>
MailWasher Pro software is ready to filter all of your email accounts and blocked, remove the spam from the list of email. MailWasher allows you to preview all your email before to your computer or your mobile device, you allows you to read all your email securely, and instantly delete any unwanted emails or suspicious. Email good rest of you is download at PC or mobile devices, to help you not get any virus, spam or any email.
Firetrust MailWasher Pro - Blocker remove spam
The...
</description></item><item><title>Download Minimal Firewall 2.4</title><pubDate> Sun, 05 Oct 2025 21:02:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minimal-firewall-13877.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minimal-firewall-13877.html
</guid><description>
Minimal Firewall works in conjunction with Windows Firewall to block all unknown connections by default, prompting you to create application-based rules to mitigate malware, telemetry, and data leaks. Completely eliminate applications that call home without your knowledge. Minimal Firewall provides a more secure and integrated approach by interacting directly with the native Windows Firewall, eliminating the need for risky system modifications.
Core Features
	Lockdown Mode: The core...
</description></item><item><title>Download IK Multimedia ARC X 1.0.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 05 Oct 2025 21:01:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ik-multimedia-arc-system-11503.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ik-multimedia-arc-system-11503.html
</guid><description>
ARC 4 combines ultra-precise measurement microphones, analysis software, and calibration plugins to improve the accuracy of your monitoring in any room. Work faster and more freely, confident that you're hearing your own music and that your music will sound great anywhere. With a faster, easier calibration process, new more natural algorithms, and configuration management on ARC Studio hardware, everything about ARC Studio is designed to help you focus on your music and creating tones....
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaMonkey Gold 2024.2.0.3168 Beta</title><pubDate> Sun, 05 Oct 2025 21:01:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediamonkey-gold-231.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediamonkey-gold-231.html
</guid><description>
MediaMonkey Gold is music manager and music player multimedia for the music collection and iPod users. MediaMonkey lists the audio file of you as CD, OGG, WMA, MPC, FLAC, APE, WAV and MP3 and includes the edit smart card and an automatic file and folder to arrange your music library.
MediaMonkey Gold also has CD ripper, CD / DVD Burner, and audio converter for saving music, and manual or editor list automatically to create mixed music.
Features MediaMonkey Gold
	Automatically find...
</description></item><item><title>Download Exportizer Enterprise 10.2.4.611</title><pubDate> Sun, 05 Oct 2025 21:00:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-exportizer-pro-470.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-exportizer-pro-470.html
</guid><description>
Exportizer Pro is software export base, robust data that allows view, edit and export the database to a data file, text, clipboard. Exportizer Pro is a software tool effective and simple, can be used to help individuals view, filter and copy an entire database to clipboard or convert it to another format.
Simple interface and no complex also indicates that Exportizer Pro meet the system requirements, the application can run on most operating systems.
The main window of Exportizer Pro...
</description></item><item><title>Download FmjSoft Awave Studio 12.11.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 05 Oct 2025 21:00:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fmjsoft-awave-studio-5476.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fmjsoft-awave-studio-5476.html
</guid><description>
FmjSoft Awave Studio is a versatile audio tool that can read a wide range of file formats that carry real audio from different platforms, synthesizers, trackers, mobile phones ... It can be used in many ways - as a file format converter, as an audio editor, or as a synth tool editor.
FmjSoft Awave Studio will easily convert MIDI (and similar) song data between several formats (e.g. you can convert MOD-tracker module to MIDI format accompanying the music custom tools!). Convert your MIDI...
</description></item><item><title>Download ToneBoosters Plugin Bundle 2.1.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 05 Oct 2025 20:59:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-toneboosters-plugin-bundle-3675.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-toneboosters-plugin-bundle-3675.html
</guid><description>
ToneBoosters Plugin Bundle is a package tool sound is to combine the digital signal processing advanced and deployed multi-platform is optimized with the easy to use interface to optimize workflow of you. We combine the digital signal processing advanced and highly optimized deployment platform interface with simple-to-use to optimize your work.
ToneBoosters Plugin Bundle - audio tools
ToneBoosters Plugin Bundle includes:
	Barricade: True-peak mastering limiter.
	BitJuggler: The...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wintoys 2.4.12.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 05 Oct 2025 20:57:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wintoys-11863.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wintoys-11863.html
</guid><description>
Are you looking for a utility that makes Windows your own and keeps it up to date, clean, functional and efficient while having all the essentials in one convenient location. Use Wintoys, it helps you organize and easily navigate through available edits etc.
Experience Windows your way and keep it fresh every day. Set up, debug, optimize, repair and tweak your operating system in a simple, time-saving yet secure approach. Keep it clean, healthy and efficient while having everything you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Slimjet 47.0.2.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 05 Oct 2025 20:54:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-slimjet-3298.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-slimjet-3298.html
</guid><description>
Slimjet is a web browser that the page loading speed quite fast. Launch the browser, faster page loading, faster user interface response is provided by the tool Blink in the industry. Slimjet is loaded with powerful features and flexible options, Slimjet do more for every user without relying on external plugins. Automatic protection against phishing and malicious software, the control options privacy advanced architecture multi-process strong.
Slimjet - web-browser automatically...
</description></item><item><title>Download AnExplorer Pro File Transfer 5.8.8</title><pubDate> Sun, 05 Oct 2025 19:27:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-file-manager-pro-tv-usb-otg-8358.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-file-manager-pro-tv-usb-otg-8358.html
</guid><description>
AnExplorer File Explorer is a unique file manager for TV and Watch file management tool. It is simple, small, fast and efficient File Explorer. Only file managers support RTL and display the size of folders on storage. It is designed for all devices including Phones, Phablets, Tablets, Watches and TVs. It is completely designed using Material Design.
Pro TV USBOTG File Manager Features
	Full-featured It provides all file management features including cut, copy, delete, rename,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Duolingo: language lessons 6.50.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 05 Oct 2025 19:25:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-duolingo-language-lessons-8265.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-duolingo-language-lessons-8265.html
</guid><description>
Duolingo is a popular language learning app that offers interactive lessons to help users learn new languages. This application offers many languages for you to choose from, including Spanish, French, German, Italian, Portuguese, Chinese, Japanese and many more.
This app offers an gamified learning experience with interactive lessons, exercises, and quizzes designed to help users learn new words, phrases, and grammar rules. This app is designed to be easy to use and suitable for people...
</description></item></channel></rss>