<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 11:34:21 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 11:34:21 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download EaseUS Fixo Technician 3.8.5 Build 20250904</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Sep 2025 00:06:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-fixo-9814.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-fixo-9814.html
</guid><description>
Video is corrupted or inaccessible after power failure and sudden blackout, whole system crash, update failure, wrong file handling or some other reason? EaseUS Fixo allows you to repair many different video file formats including MOV, MP4, M2TS, MKV, MTS, 3GP, etc. easier no matter how broken it is.
It can intelligently and intelligently repair damaged and damaged photos from computers or other external storage devices such as USB flash drives, memory cards, SD cards, digital cameras...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare PDFelement Pro 12.0.0.3706</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Sep 2025 00:05:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-pdfelement-pro-105.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-pdfelement-pro-105.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare PDFelement Pro support users to convert PDF to office documents for easier use, modify in every situation. Is one of the software conversion material is rated best today, integrated with many features. We recommend that you should use experience software many useful features this.
Wondershare PDFelement Pro - conversion Fie PDF more features, multi-language
Wondershare PDFelement Pro what?
Convert PDF into Word, Excel, PowerPoint...
• Convert PDF and protected PDF into...
</description></item><item><title>Download Minimal Firewall 2.1.3</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Sep 2025 00:05:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minimal-firewall-13877.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minimal-firewall-13877.html
</guid><description>
Minimal Firewall works in conjunction with Windows Firewall to block all unknown connections by default, prompting you to create application-based rules to mitigate malware, telemetry, and data leaks. Completely eliminate applications that call home without your knowledge. Minimal Firewall provides a more secure and integrated approach by interacting directly with the native Windows Firewall, eliminating the need for risky system modifications.
Core Features
	Lockdown Mode: The core...
</description></item><item><title>Download ClassicMenu by Reuschtools 4.65</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Sep 2025 00:04:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-classicmenu-by-reuschtools-13987.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-classicmenu-by-reuschtools-13987.html
</guid><description>
ClassicMenu by Reuschtools is a software tool designed for Windows that allows users to switch between the classic and the new context menu introduced in Windows 11. The tool allows the classic context menu to be enabled or disabled, which is useful for users who prefer the traditional full context menu over the newer compact version with fewer items. ClassicMenu is free, requires no installation (click to run), and is accessible from the Start Menu after installing Reuschtools.
When...
</description></item><item><title>Download Auslogics SSD Optimizer Pro 2.1.0.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Sep 2025 00:03:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-auslogics-ssd-optimizer-pro-12530.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-auslogics-ssd-optimizer-pro-12530.html
</guid><description>
Auslogics SSD Optimizer Pro is a specialized software tool designed to enhance the performance and longevity of solid state drives (SSDs). The software uses complex algorithms to optimize SSD performance, significantly improving read and write speeds, providing faster file access and overall system responsiveness. Users can check the health of their SSD, including real-time statistics on read and written data, helping to assess drive health and expected lifespan.
Features of Auslogics...
</description></item><item><title>Download 4K Video Downloader Plus 25.3.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Sep 2025 00:03:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-video-downloader-617.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-video-downloader-617.html
</guid><description>
4K Video Downloader Plus is software support downloads video, audio and subtitles from YouTube with high quality up to 4K. Download process video is very simple: just copy the video link from your browser and click Paste Url. Done! If you want that video on your iPad, iPhone or other device, we have protected you.
The feature on 4K Video Downloader Plus
	Download entire playlists and channels from YouTube and save them in MP4, MKV, M4A, MP3, FLV, 3G, create a file .m3u for...
</description></item><item><title>Download HE - Hardware Read and Write Utility 1.25.09.04</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Sep 2025 00:02:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-he-hardware-read-and-write-utility-4287.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-he-hardware-read-and-write-utility-4287.html
</guid><description>
HE - Hardware Read and Write Utility is a powerful utility intended for hardware engineer, engineer, BIOS developer, driver, engineer, QA engineers, performance test engineers, diagnostic, etc., this utility access almost all the computer hardware, including PCI (PCI Express), index / Data, PCI, memory, index memory / Data space I / O, Index I / O / Data, Super I / O, DIMM SPD, CPU The registers MSR, screen, SMART, physical area of the hard drive identification data, ATA, dump tables ACPI...
</description></item><item><title>Download Clean Space Pro 2025 v714</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Sep 2025 00:02:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-clean-space-pro-545.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-clean-space-pro-545.html
</guid><description>
Clean Space Pro is the professional software remove junk files from the system to release the hard drive and improve computer performance. From time to time when using computer files as buffers, temporary files of various programs, files, internet cookies, internet browsing history, diary, file index.dat, registry entries and even the Windows will gradually increase, occupy wise space your hard drive and make the computer suffer from stagnation. The best solution is to use the Clean Space...
</description></item><item><title>Download Calcpad 7.3.6</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Sep 2025 00:01:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-calcpad-12576.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-calcpad-12576.html
</guid><description>
Calcpad is free software for mathematical and engineering calculations. It is a flexible and modern programmable calculator with Html report generator. Calcpad uses a simple programming language that is fast and easy to learn. It does not require any special programming skills, which makes it suitable for engineers without any computer programming background. You can create calculation notes simply by writing your formula and text, enclosed in 'quotation marks'.
The program includes...
</description></item><item><title>Download FakeDriveCheck 4.64</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Sep 2025 00:01:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fakedrivecheck-11322.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fakedrivecheck-11322.html
</guid><description>
FakeDriveCheck is a simple utility you can run to verify if your USB stick or MicroSD card is fake. It's easy to get and use, making it a good choice for anyone skeptical about the authenticity of their external storage.
FakeDriveCheck Features
	Existing files will not be destroyed while the USB drive is verified.
	Super fast verification.
	No need to unplug and plug in.
	Hot Plug: FakeDriveCheck detects USB drives
	inserted after FakeDriveCheck is started.
</description></item><item><title>Download Auslogics BoostSpeed 14.1.0.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Sep 2025 00:01:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-auslogics-boostspeed-140.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-auslogics-boostspeed-140.html
</guid><description>
Auslogics BoostSpeed is software support speed up an Internet connection for the computer with Auslogics BoostSpeed restrictions on your Internet speed will be corrective and limited to the lowest level to bring high efficiency in work as well as in their learning. Auslogics BoostSpeed improves the speed surfing the web for the computer through the way in data compression and image to gảm capacity when participating online, with the mechanism and how it works so users also software feel...
</description></item><item><title>Download Auslogics Disk Defrag Pro 12.1.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Sep 2025 00:00:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-auslogics-disk-defrag-pro-648.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-auslogics-disk-defrag-pro-648.html
</guid><description>
Auslogics Disk Defrag Pro is a software for your drive is optimized for maximum speed and maximum efficiency with its smart algorithms and technology, defragmentation boot time of the program this powerful. Auslogics Disk Defrag Pro is a full program features using the algorithm various optimizations to the best available space on your hard drive.
Auslogics Disk Defrag Pro - Watched the piece, system optimization
Auslogics Disk Defrag Pro based on an algorithm, a powerful optimization...
</description></item><item><title>Download 4K YouTube to MP3 25.3.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Sep 2025 23:59:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-youtube-to-mp3-622.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-youtube-to-mp3-622.html
</guid><description>
4K YouTube to MP3 is a software to convert video youtube to mp3 quickly and easily by the manipulation drag-and-drop simple. With 4K YouTube to MP3 you just drag and drop the link to the favorite songs of you and get the MP3 files to your computer, as easy as that. Transfer songs directly to iPod, iPhone and iPad everywhere you go. No install annoying and complex to solve, just a clean interface, user friendly and functional.
When using 4K YouTube to MP3, users will get the playlists,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Opera GX (Gaming Browser) 121.0.5600.55</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Sep 2025 23:58:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-gx-3170.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-gx-3170.html
</guid><description>
Opera GX is a special version of the Opera browser is built to complement gamers avid. Browser this game comes with the unique features to help users make maximum use of both the game and their browser. Opera GX is built specifically to support the game. This browser includes the unique features to help users have the best experience when gaming and surfing the web.
Opera GX - special browser for gamers
GX Control allows you to set a limit on the level of use RAM, CPU and network where...
</description></item><item><title>Download AB Download Manager 1.6.11</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Sep 2025 23:57:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ab-download-manager-12399.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ab-download-manager-12399.html
</guid><description>
With this application, you can easily download files from anywhere. Enjoy fast, free downloads with seamless browser extension support. It is built to be a desktop application that allows you to manage and organize your downloads better than before.
AB Download Manager features
	Simple and modern UI: Simple UI and dark mode by default
	Faster download speeds: Download files using multiple connections to increase your download speed by up to 500%
	Download Queue: Create and manage your...
</description></item><item><title>Download DroidKit 2.3.7.20250904</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Sep 2025 23:57:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-droidkit-6578.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-droidkit-6578.html
</guid><description>
DroidKit is data recovery software for your mobile device, it will quickly scan your phone memory and save photos, WhatsApp chats and files, messages Messages, contacts and more essential data up to 13 categories, covering almost everything you need every day. All Android phones and tablets are supported. Without rooting your device. No tech skills required. No need to wait many days. You can get back what you've lost with just a few simple clicks, instantly.
Besides, DroidKit also has...
</description></item><item><title>Download Auslogics Registry Cleaner Pro 11.1.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Sep 2025 23:56:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-auslogics-registry-cleaner-pro-1892.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-auslogics-registry-cleaner-pro-1892.html
</guid><description>
Auslogics Registry Cleaner Pro is the most advanced Version of the software cleans the registry stable help users delete the outdated Registry to speed up your pc. Auslogics Registry Cleaner Pro contains all the features of Auslogics Registry Cleaner Free. User easy download Auslogics Registry Cleaner on the website taiwebs.com with many new features. The software will fix all the errors in the registry of your Windows and clean it from obsolete entries. With Auslogics Registry Cleaner you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Auslogics Registry Cleaner 11.1.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Sep 2025 23:56:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-auslogics-registry-cleaner-1249.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-auslogics-registry-cleaner-1249.html
</guid><description>
Auslogics Registry Cleaner , so we introduce is proud to be cleaning software registry stable help users delete the outdated Registry to speed up your computer. User easy download Auslogics Registry Cleaner on our website taiwebs.com with many new features. The software will fix all the errors in the registry of your Windows and clean it from obsolete entries. With the Auslogics Registry Cleaner, you can avoid system malfunction and help your Windows running more stable.
Auslogics...
</description></item><item><title>Download ToonTrack EZdrummer 3.1.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Sep 2025 23:52:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-toontrack-ezdrummer-13426.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-toontrack-ezdrummer-13426.html
</guid><description>
EZdrummer 3 reinvents the role that drum production software can play in the music composition scene. It gives you creative freedom with a comprehensive set of easy-to-use features that allow you to create complete drum tracks without ever leaving the software. A solid beat is the heartbeat of any great song. EZdrummer 3 is packed with features designed to help you easily create the right rhythm for your music.
Key features of EZdrummer 3 include:
	Seven high-quality drum kits and six...
</description></item><item><title>Download Auslogics Windows Slimmer Pro 5.1.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Sep 2025 23:51:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-auslogics-windows-slimmer-1252.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-auslogics-windows-slimmer-1252.html
</guid><description>
Auslogics Windows Slimmer is software recover hard disk space by removing the rest from older versions of Windows, files, Windows Update, system restore points old, and other items not required and engross your disk space. Use Auslogics Windows Slimmer is necessary because simple as running system maintenance periodically is mandatory, because the data are temporary and not necessary to continue piling up and may eventually occupy an amount of storage space substantially.
Auslogics...
</description></item><item><title>Download Digital Anarchy Beauty Box Video 6.0.1 for DaVinci Resolve and Nuke (OFX)</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Sep 2025 23:50:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-digital-anarchy-beauty-box-video-6557.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-digital-anarchy-beauty-box-video-6557.html
</guid><description>
Digital Anarchy Beauty Box Video is a plugins that allows you to automatically determine the skin tone and create a mask that limits the effect of smoothing only to the skin regions. Just apply the filter, to filter the video analysis, set a few smoothing options and to add a display plugin to make the skin editing very easy.
Digital Anarchy Beauty Box Video acts as the digital makeup in the post-production process by combining the detection algorithms and the modern skin smoothing and...
</description></item><item><title>Download System Info 18.25</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Sep 2025 23:45:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-system-info-11391.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-system-info-11391.html
</guid><description>
System Info is a simple piece of software that displays various information about your system, including its hardware, operating system, and more. Having everything presented in a single interface, where you can copy and share that data elsewhere, can finally become convenient for regular users. That's what System Information does: it gives you various data about your system, including hardware specifications, operating system, network, and more. without installation.
This application...
</description></item><item><title>Download Certificate Manager 18.25</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Sep 2025 23:45:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-certificate-manager-13958.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-certificate-manager-13958.html
</guid><description>
Certificate Manager provides an in-depth overview of your current certificates, allowing you to easily access detailed information. It also provides functions for both exporting existing certificates and importing new certificates, enhancing your certificate management capabilities.
Application certificates are often overlooked by most users until problems arise during application installation. For the average end user, there is little reason to focus on application certificates....
</description></item><item><title>Download Digital Anarchy Flicker Free OFX 3.0.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Sep 2025 23:44:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-digital-anarchy-flicker-free-ofx-11150.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-digital-anarchy-flicker-free-ofx-11150.html
</guid><description>
Digital Anarchy Flicker Free OFX is a plugin designed for video editing and compositing software that supports the OFX (OpenFX) standard. It was developed by Digital Anarchy, a software company known for creating various plugins and tools for video editors and visual effects artists.
Flicker Free OFX is specifically designed to solve the problem of flickering or inconsistent lighting in video footage. Flicker can occur in video for a variety of reasons, including changes in lighting...
</description></item><item><title>Download Beauty Box Video for After Effects &amp;amp; Premiere Pro 6.0.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Sep 2025 23:44:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-beauty-box-video-for-after-effects-premiere-pro-12591.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-beauty-box-video-for-after-effects-premiere-pro-12591.html
</guid><description>
Digital Anarchy's Beauty Box Video is a powerful skin retouching plugin designed for use in Adobe After Effects and Premiere Pro. This plugin streamlines the process of enhancing skin tones and removing imperfections, allowing editors to achieve professional results with minimal effort.
Beauty Box Video will assist in this digital skin and makeup editing by automatically identifying skin tones and creating masks that limit the smoothing effect on skin areas. Simply apply a video filter,...
</description></item></channel></rss>