<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 11:49:44 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 11:49:44 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Telegram for Desktop 6.3.7</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Dec 2025 23:01:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-telegram-3376.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-telegram-3376.html
</guid><description>
Telegram is an instant messaging service and voice over IP services on the cloud platform. Client application Telegram is available for Android, iOS, Windows Phone, Windows NT, macOS, and Linux. Users can send messages and exchange photos, videos, stickers, audio and files of any kind.
Telegram - Messaging and free phone calls
Telegram seamless sync across all your devices and can be used on desktop, tablet and phone. You can send unlimited amount of messages, photos, videos and files...
</description></item><item><title>Download KMPlayer (KMP) 2025.11.14.11 x64 / 4.2.3.30 x86</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Dec 2025 23:00:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kmplayer-kmp-902.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kmplayer-kmp-902.html
</guid><description>
KMPlayer (KMP) is software watch movies listen to music multi-function for video enthusiasts. KMPlayer development is many types of the format different. KMPlayer has improved on sound quality, images when listening to music and watching movies, the playback speed of video is faster, more codec player is added to the software video decoder is optimized.
KMPlayer also supports a variety of audio formats and video and offers a the interface can be customized with the preview coverflow and...
</description></item><item><title>Download FoneLab Data Retriever 3.0.32</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Dec 2025 22:59:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fonelab-data-retriever-593.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fonelab-data-retriever-593.html
</guid><description>
FoneLab Data Retriever is a tool safe and convenient to restore data deleted or lost (such as photos, documents, email, video, etc.) on windows / mac, hard drive, flash drive, memory card, digital camera and more. There are many different methods that you can try to restore lost data on computer hard drive and other devices due to deleting, partition formatted, hard drive RAW or other incidents, the collected data FoneLab will be the best choice for you because of the convenience and...
</description></item><item><title>Download reaConverter Pro 8.0.170</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Dec 2025 22:58:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html
</guid><description>
reaConverter Pro is software image processing feature with batch conversion and image editing periodically becomes simple. eaConverter also provide command line utilities allow you to process images automatically, thus helping you shorten the time for other work.
reaConverter Pro integrated powerful tool of Uber with many great features. It provides advanced solutions to process and adjust images. Management of the conversion process the base image with the latest version of...
</description></item><item><title>Download AnyMP4 Data Recovery 3.0.32</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Dec 2025 22:58:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anymp4-data-recovery-2499.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anymp4-data-recovery-2499.html
</guid><description>
AnyMP4 Data Recovery software is data recovery professional and safe. AnyMP4 Data Recovery can help you recover almost all files lost, such as photos, documents, email, audio, video and many other things from the computer disk, flash drive, memory card / memory card on mobile phone or camera. Whether you lost files to delete, format, etc., or your data are gone for the collapse of the system, virus attack, etc., you can also use the program data recovery this powerful to help...
</description></item><item><title>Download Red Gate SmartAssembly Professional 8.4.1.6697</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Dec 2025 22:57:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-red-gate-smartassembly-1593.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-red-gate-smartassembly-1593.html
</guid><description>
Red Gate SmartAssembly is a tool that helps protect your application against reverse engineering or modifications prevent side Tuesday access to source code. This comprehensive solution protects the data card of you and more likely to report errors. This program makes files difficult can disassemble and injection code does not use, to help engineer can reverse and understand the core structure of the code. With your smartphone, you will have many features to tamper with the code as the...
</description></item><item><title>Download AOMEI Backupper Pro / Technician / Server 8.1.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Dec 2025 22:57:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aomei-backupper-pro-98.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aomei-backupper-pro-98.html
</guid><description>
AOMEI Backupper pro is a software backup and recovery professional, easy to use. Fully protect your computer from data loss. It allows you to backup an entire PC and Server, provides one-click backup your system partition or your disk and execute it in a few minutes. This software also can explore the created image and restore it on hard drive if your data gets lost or corrupted. In addition, you can create the recovery disk the ability to boot to recover his data after a system crash and...
</description></item><item><title>Download CoolUtils Total Image Converter 8.2.0.286</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Dec 2025 22:56:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-total-image-converter-848.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-total-image-converter-848.html
</guid><description>
CoolUtils Total Image Converter is software to convert images to other formats, and can edit, cut, resize and rotate them. With Total Image Converter you easy convert TIFFs into JPEGS, make photos suitable for the web or recover old photos in the supported format.
&amp;nbsp;CoolUtils Total Image Converter - convert images to other formats
Features CoolUtils Total Image Converter
	Total Image Converter supports almost all image formats
	Support convert eagle picture series.
	Total Image...
</description></item><item><title>Download ProgeCAD Professional 26.0.10.10</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Dec 2025 22:56:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-progecad-professional-847.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-progecad-professional-847.html
</guid><description>
ProgeCAD Professional is a CAD application 2D / 3D compatibility AutoCAD works with the file DWG of AutoCAD. This is a best solution for AEC, MCAD and all usages CAD generic. ProgeCAD Professional works natively with DWG! Fully compatible with AutoCAD® without conversion.
ProgeCAD Professional - Cad application in 2D and 3D
The main features of ProgeCAD Professional from the developer
	ProgeCAD convert PDF to DWG
	22.000 blocks are ready to use
	Export STEP, IGES, PDF, DWF, 3DS, DAE...
</description></item><item><title>Download AOMEI Backupper WinPE 8.1 Technician</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Dec 2025 22:55:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aomei-backupper-sever-99.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aomei-backupper-sever-99.html
</guid><description>
AOMEI Backupper server is a software backup and recovery professional, easy to use. It allows you to backup, secure Server, providing one-click backup your system partition or your disk and execute it in a few minutes. This software also can explore the created image and restore it on hard drive if your data gets lost or corrupted.
AOMEI Backupper sever what ?
AOMEI Backupper sever - backup data recovery sever
√ AOMEI Backupper sever also allows you to copy partitions or disk. The...
</description></item><item><title>Download Syncovery Premium 11.11.8.138</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Dec 2025 22:54:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncovery-pro-enterprise-232.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncovery-pro-enterprise-232.html
</guid><description>
Syncovery Pro Enterprise is a great application used to back up data and to synchronize personal computers, servers, laptops, notepads and storage online. The software comes with support for FTP and secure FTP servers, SSH, WebDAV, Amazon S3, http, update the part file, ZIP compression, data encryption, and schedule automatic backups.
Syncovery Pro Enterprise have the ability to freely select files and folders across the whole folder hierarchy in tree view and supports email...
</description></item><item><title>Download Apeaksoft Data Recovery 3.0.32</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Dec 2025 22:54:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-apeaksoft-data-recovery-2546.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-apeaksoft-data-recovery-2546.html
</guid><description>
Apeaksoft Data Recovery offers professional solutions to handle the data loss problems different. It can help you to recover all kinds of data from your computer, recycle bin, hard drive / flash memory card, etc. whether you mistakenly deleted some key files or lost data due to hard drive formatted or system malfunction, loss of data will no longer be the biggest nightmare of you.
Apeaksoft Data Recovery - Restore lost data
The features of Apeaksoft Data Recovery
	Recover data from...
</description></item><item><title>Download VovSoft Tree Notes 2.6</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Dec 2025 22:53:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-tree-notes-11294.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-tree-notes-11294.html
</guid><description>
Vovsoft Tree Notes is a decentralized note-taking application designed to improve your organizational efficiency and streamline your information management process. This powerful software provides users with a user-friendly platform to create, organize and access their notes with ease.
Tree Notes for Windows is a flexible and powerful note-taking solution that meets the needs of individuals, students, professionals, and creative minds alike. Boost your productivity, stay organized, and...
</description></item><item><title>Download JWIZARD Cleaner 1.10.6</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Dec 2025 22:53:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jwizard-cleaner-12853.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jwizard-cleaner-12853.html
</guid><description>
Effective Windows cleaning software to remove unnecessary files from your PC. JWIZARD Cleaner for Windows quickly frees up disk space and keeps your system in an optimal state, ensuring your PC runs stably and efficiently. This application is designed to provide you with a comprehensive tool to analyze and optimize your PC by performing a comprehensive cleanup or a more detailed cleanup, targeting specific areas such as system, browser, mail, etc.
Features of JWIZARD Cleaner
	Clean...
</description></item><item><title>Download Muni Animation MotionMuse 1.1.8</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Dec 2025 22:52:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-muni-animation-motionmuse-12700.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-muni-animation-motionmuse-12700.html
</guid><description>
MotionMuse is a user-friendly toolkit designed for 3D character animation, intended to simplify the animation process and make it accessible to new artists without the need for deep knowledge. wide. Its intuitive interface allows users to create, edit and animate animations with ease.
Main features
	Easy-to-use toolset: MotionMuse is built to accommodate users who may not have a background in 3D animation, featuring a streamlined interface that reduces complexity.
	Character Rigging:...
</description></item><item><title>Download Allround Automations PL-SQL Developer 16.0.8.2176</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Dec 2025 22:52:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allround-automations-plsql-developer-4730.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allround-automations-plsql-developer-4730.html
</guid><description>
Allround Automations PL/SQL Developer is a development environment integration is specifically targeted at the development application units are stored for the Oracle database. Over time, we have seen the business logic more and move towards the Oracle server, make PL / SQL programming become an important part of the development process overall. This software focuses on ease of use, coding quality and the main advantage in the process of software development, Oracle.
The features of...
</description></item><item><title>Download FeatherType 1.0.0.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Dec 2025 19:50:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-feathertype-14340.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-feathertype-14340.html
</guid><description>
Welcome to FeatherType, the minimalist writing app designed to help you focus and write fluently. Whether you're writing your next novel draft, a blog post, or jotting down your daily thoughts, FeatherType helps you stay focused – without distractions, without hassle.
Why choose FeatherType?
FeatherType is designed to eliminate everything except your words. No icon strips, no complicated menus—just your thoughts flowing onto the page. With auto-save, session management, and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ratiborus KMS Tools 15.12.2025</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Dec 2025 16:33:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ratiborus-kms-tools-78.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ratiborus-kms-tools-78.html
</guid><description>
Ratiborus KMS Tools: All-in-one activator from Ratiborus for Windows XP, Vista, 7, 8, 8.1, 10.11, Server 2008, 2008 R2, 2012, 2012 R2, Office 2010/2013/2016/2019/2021. Ratiborus KMS Tools is a small tool Compact used to activate Windows copyright with full features, with all versions like Windows 7, 8, 10, 11 easily.
Programs include:
AAct Network Portable
AAct Portable
ConsoleAct Portable
Defender Tools
Garbage Collector x86_x64
KMSAuto Lite Portable
KMSAuto Net 2016 Portable
KMSCleaner...
</description></item><item><title>Download Internet Download Manager (IDM) 6.42 Build 58</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Dec 2025 16:27:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-inetnet-download-manager-161.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-inetnet-download-manager-161.html
</guid><description>
Internet Download Manager is the download acceleration software, the best download support now, it can help you speed up the download up to five times, continue and schedule downloads. The latest version of IDM adds the compatibility of Windows 10 and Windows 11, it has supported all current popular browsers such as Internet Explorer, Mozilla Firefox, Opera, Google Chrome, ..
Download IDM with the latest version on taiwebs.com making it easy to download and manage your downloaded files...
</description></item><item><title>Download MathType Portable 7.10.1.458</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Dec 2025 16:26:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mathtype-portable-7171.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mathtype-portable-7171.html
</guid><description>
MathType Portable is a powerful interactive equation editor for Windows and helps you create mathematical notation for word processing, web pages, desktop publishing, and so on. desks, presentations, elearning and for TeX, LaTeX and MathML documents. Features are constantly being updated into the latest MathType to help users get more done, saving time when creating documents. What do you think, when you can enter equations as easy as writing math on paper and pencil using the...
</description></item><item><title>Download IDM Retail 6.42 Build 58</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Dec 2025 16:25:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-internet-download-manager-retail-3609.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-internet-download-manager-retail-3609.html
</guid><description>
IDM - Internet Download Manager Retail is a reliable utility and high efficiency will help you to increase your download speed and manage download at better. The program allows you to easily schedule, pause and resume downloads with a single click. Moreover, the application provides error resilience robust and can restart the download at the interrupted or broken. You can restore the download is interrupted due to network problems, lost connections, unexpected power outages, computer...
</description></item><item><title>Download Foxit PDF Editor Pro Portable 14.0.2.33402 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Dec 2025 16:24:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-foxit-pdf-editor-pro-portable-3495.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-foxit-pdf-editor-pro-portable-3495.html
</guid><description>
Foxit is almost the first company to develop software to edit the PDF directly and professionally in a new way. The development of this product, known as Foxit PhantomPDF, is currently growing company and are adding more features every day. And today we give you version Foxit PhantomPDF Business Portable activated full-featured and completely free.
Foxit PhantomPDF Business Portable - mobile Version support create and edit PDF documents
The professional features that this software...
</description></item><item><title>Download Glary Utilities Pro Portable 6.35.0.39</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Dec 2025 16:23:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-utilities-pro-portable-3500.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-utilities-pro-portable-3500.html
</guid><description>
Glary Utilities Pro Portable is a program that provides you with the necessary options to clean and maintain your PC system. The software's interface consists of a small window, simple to use. Newbies shouldn't have any problems getting around the program. So you can scan for problems revolving around incorrect registry entries, dangerous startup entries, invalid shortcuts, Internet history and traces, temporary files, spyware and adware.
Glary Utilities Pro Portable - Optimize and...
</description></item><item><title>Download XYplorer 28.10.0100</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Dec 2025 16:23:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-533.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-533.html
</guid><description>
XYplorer - File Manager for Windows is software that supports users to manage files on the Window quickly and to arrange the folder tidy. XYplorer features tabbed browsing, search, files, powerful, preview, flexible, highly customizable interface, dual frame options and a variety of unique ways to automate effective tasks often repeat. It's fast, lightweight, and portable.
Features XYplorer
	XYplorer is a file manager mobile. It does not require any settings, store all configuration...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinToHDD Enterprise Portable 6.8</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Dec 2025 16:22:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wintohdd-portable-11911.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wintohdd-portable-11911.html
</guid><description>
WinToHDD Portable is convenient and easy-to-use portable software that allows users to easily reinstall or clone their Windows operating system without the need for a CD/DVD or USB drive. This program will help you easily reinstall Windows, install Windows to disks other than the drive where your Windows operating system is installed, or clone your current Windows operating system installation (Windows vista or more) to another disk.
In addition to creating a bootable USB drive...
</description></item></channel></rss>