<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 15:36:22 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 15:36:22 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download reaConverter Pro 8.0.163</title><pubDate> Sun, 30 Nov 2025 17:25:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html
</guid><description>
reaConverter Pro is software image processing feature with batch conversion and image editing periodically becomes simple. eaConverter also provide command line utilities allow you to process images automatically, thus helping you shorten the time for other work.
reaConverter Pro integrated powerful tool of Uber with many great features. It provides advanced solutions to process and adjust images. Management of the conversion process the base image with the latest version of...
</description></item><item><title>Download lessmsi 2.10.8</title><pubDate> Sun, 30 Nov 2025 17:25:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lessmsi-12392.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lessmsi-12392.html
</guid><description>
Lessmsi (Less MSIerables) is a free and portable application that allows users to view and extract the contents of MSI files.
How does it work? Files with the .msi extension are not as widely used as their .exe cousins, but both contain programs for Windows. The main difference between them is that the latter does not always come with an installer, while it comes standard with the former. However, there will be cases where you just need to view or want to extract specific content from...
</description></item><item><title>Download MedCalc 23.4.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 30 Nov 2025 17:24:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-medcalc-1536.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-medcalc-1536.html
</guid><description>
MedCalc is a statistical software for biomedical research can analyze many performance curve system with a set of rich functionality, chart types and advanced module. MedCalc was designed to meet the needs and requirements of the study nature and aims to analyze the statistical calculations of the project. This software provides the tools and means essential to analyze the characteristic curve of the system (ROC), drawing data and perform the statistical calculations.
MedCalc -...
</description></item><item><title>Download Desktop.Calendar.Tray.OK 4.45</title><pubDate> Sun, 30 Nov 2025 17:24:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopcalendartrayok-2837.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopcalendartrayok-2837.html
</guid><description>
Desktop.Calendar.Tray.OK is one of the alternatives they can choose to use instead of the calendar app Windows. A plus point of the Desktop.CalWiki.Tray.OK is it possible to calculate the difference in the number of days between selected date and current date. In other words, only by clicking on a specific date, users can find out the number of weeks and days until that date. This feature is useful when you schedule appointments and meetings.
Desktop.Calendar.Tray.OK - the calendar App...
</description></item><item><title>Download OneCommander Pro 3.104.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 30 Nov 2025 17:23:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-one-commander-4232.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-one-commander-4232.html
</guid><description>
One Commander is a file manager for Microsoft Windows with function improved user interface and navigation experience, system file and manipulating the files. Utilities use the tree view to sort the folder, subfolders, and files your, make sure that the current location of you always clear. It supports multiple tabs, allowing you to easily switch between them and access the folder you need.
One Commander - a filemanager for Windows
Depending on the format of the files, some files can...
</description></item><item><title>Download n-Track Studio Suite 10.2.3.10362</title><pubDate> Sun, 30 Nov 2025 17:23:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-n-track-studio-2991.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-n-track-studio-2991.html
</guid><description>
n-Track Studio is a recording software allows you record and create MIDI music and sounds top quality. The software allows you to add effects, VST3, DirectX, AU (Mac), VST and ReWire different on each track or channel. This program also allows you to automatically fade out, fade in and fade out or increase the volume of the music to indicate the voice of the singer.
n-Track Studio can record and playback the number of audio, MIDI and sound unlimited. In addition, you can handle the...
</description></item><item><title>Download ChrisPC Free VPN Connection 4.25.1129</title><pubDate> Sun, 30 Nov 2025 17:23:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-free-vpn-connection-2887.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-free-vpn-connection-2887.html
</guid><description>
ChrisPC Free VPN Connection software allows you to create VPN connection (virtual private network) to the server for free from the United States, Germany, Canada, France, Germany, Russia, Singapore, the Netherlands. This will help you to unblock your favorite sites to watch free TV and on-demand television when living abroad, travelling, on business or vacation. In addition, here is the solution to overcome the limited area for the popular websites: Google, YouTube, Facebook, Instagram,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Syncovery Premium 11.11.2.132</title><pubDate> Sun, 30 Nov 2025 17:22:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncovery-pro-enterprise-232.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncovery-pro-enterprise-232.html
</guid><description>
Syncovery Pro Enterprise is a great application used to back up data and to synchronize personal computers, servers, laptops, notepads and storage online. The software comes with support for FTP and secure FTP servers, SSH, WebDAV, Amazon S3, http, update the part file, ZIP compression, data encryption, and schedule automatic backups.
Syncovery Pro Enterprise have the ability to freely select files and folders across the whole folder hierarchy in tree view and supports email...
</description></item><item><title>Download Power-user Premium 1.7.67.230</title><pubDate> Sun, 30 Nov 2025 17:22:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-power-user-premium-3149.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-power-user-premium-3149.html
</guid><description>
Power-user is a plugin for software, Microsoft Excel, PowerPoint and Word help you to provide more visual content so you can create the spreadsheet attractive. It contains templates, icons, tables, drawings and charts, modern, professional, allows you to build professional looking documents. You can add custom content to your project just by a click of the mouse and surprise clients and colleagues with your skills on Excel, PowerPoint and Word.
Power-user Premium - Plugin Excel,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Unicodia 3.0.4</title><pubDate> Sun, 30 Nov 2025 17:22:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-unicodia-8521.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-unicodia-8521.html
</guid><description>
Unicodia is free, open source software that can be used as an alternative character map for your Windows machine. The interface contains everything you need, allowing you to easily cycle through all the available ASCII symbols and copy them to the clipboard. Uncicodia is a great alternative to your standard Unicode characters and is filled with symbols/characters that make it useful for a number of different uses.
Features of Unicodia
	In Windows 10/11 — all characters of Unicode 15...
</description></item><item><title>Download Power-user for PowerPoint and Excel 1.7.67.230</title><pubDate> Sun, 30 Nov 2025 17:21:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-power-user-for-powerpoint-and-excel-522.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-power-user-for-powerpoint-and-excel-522.html
</guid><description>
Power-user for PowerPoint and Excel is a utility providing you with a library of templates, icons, charts, maps and diagrams for spreadsheet and presentation. With Power-user for PowerPoint and Excel, you will attract the attention of your audience with stunning graphics will certainly impress.
Power-user comes with a collection of 2,000 icons to illustrate your slides. The icons are vector shapes so you can resize them without distortion and color back as you with. With Power-user, you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Family Tree Maker 2024 v25.0.2.1181</title><pubDate> Sun, 30 Nov 2025 17:21:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-family-tree-maker-3381.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-family-tree-maker-3381.html
</guid><description>
Family Tree Maker is a simple application that will help you create a family tree. All you have to do to fill in your name, marriage, birth, and any other important information. The program will link the individual with parents, children, aunts, uncles, cousins and their spouses.
Family Tree Maker - Creating family tree family tree
Family Tree Maker allows you to add documents and various data, such as maps, birth certificates, form, census, photos and many other things. Each document...
</description></item><item><title>Download JangaFX EmberGen Enterprise 1.2.6</title><pubDate> Sun, 30 Nov 2025 17:20:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jangafx-embergen-enterprise-9820.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jangafx-embergen-enterprise-9820.html
</guid><description>
JangaFX EmberGen Enterprise is professional grade real-time fluid simulation and particle rendering software developed by JangaFX. It is specially designed to create realistic and high quality fire, smoke and liquid effects for use in various industries, including movies, games, virtual reality, and more.
EmberGen Enterprise provides advanced features and capabilities to meet the needs of large-scale production environments. It allows users to create and simulate dynamic fluid effects...
</description></item><item><title>Download InstaBot Pro 7.2.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 30 Nov 2025 17:20:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-instabot-pro-8820.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-instabot-pro-8820.html
</guid><description>
InstaBot Pro is a piece of software designed to automate your “likes”, finding new followers profiled by similar accounts and Get your followers really interested in your content. Everyone knows now that the success of an instagram account also depends on the interactions and activity level of that particular account in the community.
Features of InstaBot Pro
	GET FOLLOWERS: Export followers of other profiles and/or users based on specific Hashtags.
	AUTO FOLLOW: Automatically...
</description></item><item><title>Download JOPDF 1.2.4.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 30 Nov 2025 17:00:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jopdf-14313.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jopdf-14313.html
</guid><description>
If you want the best free PDF editor, you'll definitely like JOPDF, a reliable, user-friendly, and lightweight editor. The software puts a lot of emphasis on speed and ease of use, even when handling large files. It includes all the essential editing features that are even found in paid programs. This best free PDF editor saves time, money, and effort for small businesses and students who need both basic and powerful features.
JOPDF helps you handle any PDF task with ease. Edit, create,...
</description></item><item><title>Download LibreWolf 145.0.2-1</title><pubDate> Sun, 30 Nov 2025 16:59:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-librewolf-11967.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-librewolf-11967.html
</guid><description>
LibreWolf is a customized and independent version of Firefox, with the main goals being user privacy, security and freedom. LibreWolf is designed to provide increased protection against tracking and fingerprinting techniques and includes a number of security enhancements. This is achieved through our security and privacy oriented settings and patches. LibreWolf also aims to remove all telemetry, data collection and annoyances, as well as disable anti-free features like DRM.
LibreWolf...
</description></item><item><title>Download tinyMediaManager 5.2.4</title><pubDate> Sun, 30 Nov 2025 16:58:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tinymediamanager-1819.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tinymediamanager-1819.html
</guid><description>
tinyMediaManager is a media manager full-featured to arrange and cleanup your media library your. Just choose (s) the folder containing your movies and the program can automatically get all meta data required for movies and program your TV from TheMovieDB.org, Imdb.com, OFDb.de and other online sources. tinyMediaManager download at artwork, film, cast, plot and details of other communication. Each film or program is presented with a unique art background, category, and appropriate...
</description></item><item><title>Download Twilight: Blue light filter 14.15 build 579</title><pubDate> Sun, 30 Nov 2025 16:52:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-twilight-blue-light-filter-12193.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-twilight-blue-light-filter-12193.html
</guid><description>
Are you having trouble falling asleep? Is your child hyperactive when playing with the tablet before going to bed? The Twilight app helps your device's screen adapt to the time of day. It filters the blue light emitted from your phone or tablet after sunset and protects your eyes with a soft and pleasant red filter. Filter intensity is smoothly adjusted to the solar cycle based on your local sunset and sunrise times.
Get more from Twilight
	- Reading in bed: Twilight is more...
</description></item><item><title>Download MDScan + OCR 3.9.95</title><pubDate> Sun, 30 Nov 2025 16:52:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-mobile-doc-scanner-mdscan-ocr-8307.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-mobile-doc-scanner-mdscan-ocr-8307.html
</guid><description>
Mobile Doc Scanner (MDS) is an application that allows users to scan, edit and save documents using the Android device's camera. It's designed to work as a portable scanner so you can easily digitize documents, receipts, business cards, and more.
All image processing is done on your device only! No material will be posted online without your wishes! Take photos with your camera, edit them with many advanced features, save to your favorite format and share on social networks, email,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Solid Explorer File Manager 3.2.4</title><pubDate> Sun, 30 Nov 2025 16:51:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-solid-explorer-file-manager-8924.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-solid-explorer-file-manager-8924.html
</guid><description>
Solid Explorer is a file management application inspired by old file management applications. Solid Explorer is a popular file management app for Android devices that allows users to manage and organize their files and folders in an intuitive and user-friendly interface. It offers many features that make it stand out from other file management apps.
Solid Explorer allows you to navigate to files stored on your device and automatically organize them into collections. You can view,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sygic GPS Navigation &amp;amp; Maps 25.6.2-2488</title><pubDate> Sun, 30 Nov 2025 16:51:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sygic-gps-navigation-maps-8606.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sygic-gps-navigation-maps-8606.html
</guid><description>
Sygic GPS Navigation &amp;amp; Maps is the most downloaded GPS navigation app in the world, trusted by more than 200 million drivers. Offline 3D maps stored on your phone for GPS navigation without an internet connection. We update our maps for free multiple times each year so you can always rely on Sygic GPS Navigation.
Navigate anywhere, even without an Internet connection
	Offline maps of all the countries in the world, from TomTom and other providers
	Free map updates several times...
</description></item><item><title>Download Avast Cleanup – Phone Cleaner 25.24.0 build 800011308</title><pubDate> Sun, 30 Nov 2025 16:51:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-avast-cleanup-phone-cleaner-8885.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-avast-cleanup-phone-cleaner-8885.html
</guid><description>
Avast Cleanup - Phone Cleaner is a mobile app for Android devices designed to help users optimize their phone's performance and free up storage space. This application provides many tools and features to clean and speed up your phone.
One of the main features of Avast Cleanup is the Junk Cleaner, which scans your phone for unnecessary files such as temporary files, app cache, and other junk data. The app will then provide a list of files that can be safely deleted to free up space on...
</description></item><item><title>Download Bluelight Filter for Eye Care 6.5.8</title><pubDate> Sun, 30 Nov 2025 16:50:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-bluelight-filter-for-eye-care-8192.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-bluelight-filter-for-eye-care-8192.html
</guid><description>
Blue light from smartphones or tablets causes eye strain and makes it difficult to sleep at night. This app adjusts your screen color to reduce blue light and relax your eyes, helping you sleep better.
Features of Blue Light Filter for Eye Care
	Free screen filter app to protect your eyes
	Screen filter with natural colors
	Easy operation
	Turn on or off quickly and easily
	Automatic start
	Eye care on your smartphone or tablet
	This app works on most smartphones like Samsung Galaxy,...
</description></item><item><title>Download EOBD Facile: OBD2 Car Scanner 3.81.1131</title><pubDate> Sun, 30 Nov 2025 16:50:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-eobd-facile-obd2-car-scanner-8698.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-eobd-facile-obd2-car-scanner-8698.html
</guid><description>
Run diagnostics on your car with your Android Smartphone or tablet and discover why the engine light is on... no need to check the manufacturer's manual! Connect the ELM 327 interface to your car's OBD2 port and run the app: you will be able to read engine and transmission error codes and view data from your vehicle in real time.
EOBD Facile features for Android
	View engine and transmission fault codes (also known as DTCs) and see what they mean (over 11,000 definitions...
</description></item><item><title>Download Enpass Password Manager 6.11.17.1210</title><pubDate> Sun, 30 Nov 2025 16:50:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-enpass-password-manager-8212.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-enpass-password-manager-8212.html
</guid><description>
Enpass helps you avoid having to remember too many passwords and other important authentication information. It protects them in one place with your master password and makes them accessible anywhere and everywhere - on your smartphone, tablet or desktop. This application also helps you create strong and unique passwords for each login without having to remember any passwords.
Features of Enpass Password Manager APK
	Free full-featured desktop version for Mac, Windows and Linux
	No...
</description></item></channel></rss>