<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 23:37:28 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 23:37:28 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download IObit Driver Booster Pro Portable 12.6.0.620</title><pubDate> Sat, 16 Aug 2025 23:38:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iobit-driver-booster-pro-portable-4169.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iobit-driver-booster-pro-portable-4169.html
</guid><description>
IObit Driver Booster Pro Portable is a portable version developed with IObit's most advanced driver update technology, which automatically identifies and scans for outdated, downloaded drivers and install the correct update for you with just one click, saving you a lot of time. In addition, IObit Driver Booster Pro Portable is specially developed to enhance drivers for better gaming performance and ensure better computer performance by improving update security with Restore, Uninstall...
</description></item><item><title>Download Topaz Video AI Pro 7.1.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 16 Aug 2025 23:38:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-video-enhance-ai-3733.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-video-enhance-ai-3733.html
</guid><description>
Topaz Video Enhance AI is a tool to increase video quality with this great technology ONE. Topaz Video Enhance WHO wide open your video to resolutions up to 8K with the details and consistency of motion. Until the present, there is no way to re-create a perfect high resolution video from the footage is low resolution. From the family film to SD low quality to DVD quality and more than that, Video Enhance WHO will convert your video into the footage is upgrade clear with resolutions up to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Remote Desktop Manager Enterprise 2025.2.26</title><pubDate> Sat, 16 Aug 2025 23:37:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-remote-desktop-manager-enterprise-242.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-remote-desktop-manager-enterprise-242.html
</guid><description>
Remote Desktop Manager Enterprise software is the complete management of remote connections and virtual machines from a single location, at the same time access support data online and cloud storage. Remote Desktop Manager supports multiple types of connections, not only connections for the protocol connect remote computer Remote Desktop Protocol (RDP).
Remote Desktop Manager easily add, edit, delete, share, organize and find your remote connection of you quickly. Compatible with...
</description></item><item><title>Download Glary Utilities Pro Portable 6.29.0.33</title><pubDate> Sat, 16 Aug 2025 23:36:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-utilities-pro-portable-3500.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-utilities-pro-portable-3500.html
</guid><description>
Glary Utilities Pro Portable is a program that provides you with the necessary options to clean and maintain your PC system. The software's interface consists of a small window, simple to use. Newbies shouldn't have any problems getting around the program. So you can scan for problems revolving around incorrect registry entries, dangerous startup entries, invalid shortcuts, Internet history and traces, temporary files, spyware and adware.
Glary Utilities Pro Portable - Optimize and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Duplicate File Finder Professional 2025 v405</title><pubDate> Sat, 16 Aug 2025 23:35:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-duplicate-file-finder-professional-4425.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-duplicate-file-finder-professional-4425.html
</guid><description>
Duplicate File Finder Professional is a compact application helps you quickly find and remove files duplicate on the computer. With Duplicate File Finder Professional you can choose any folder on the hard drive or use the folder standard user and our app will analyze the deep content of the selected folder to copy. It will take only a few seconds. The files will be compared by the hash algorithm MD5, which means they will be compared by content, not by name. Then, use our convenient...
</description></item><item><title>Download O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro 21.1.183 / Server</title><pubDate> Sat, 16 Aug 2025 23:28:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-diskimage-pro-218.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-diskimage-pro-218.html
</guid><description>
O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro is software backup data comprehensive and effective is provided to protect the data of the computer system, it creates images for individual drives or the entire system that still does not affect your system.
O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro allows the user to backup the entire computer or drive, the and files whenever you want even while the computer is being used. Or can use O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro to create a copy chinh sac of computer disk drives, can be used instead of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download VCap Downloader Pro 0.1.35.6662</title><pubDate> Sat, 16 Aug 2025 23:27:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vcap-downloader-pro-8474.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vcap-downloader-pro-8474.html
</guid><description>
VCap Downloader Pro (VCapDL) is a popular piece of software that allows you to record video and audio from websites on the internet. The interface of the software is similar to a normal browser, making it easy for users to get used to and work with this software. User just need to copy video url from favorite browser and convert it to VCap Downloader Pro. It will capture the video and make the quality available for download. You can also extract the audio track from any video and convert...
</description></item><item><title>Download MOTU Digital Performer 11.35.100361</title><pubDate> Sat, 16 Aug 2025 23:27:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-motu-digital-performer-1514.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-motu-digital-performer-1514.html
</guid><description>
MOTU Digital Performer is processor plug-ins, exciting new, a synth, strong and much improved workflow title new upgrade this big. Let's arouse your creativity, then tweak the distribution of you - all in a workflow alone. DP version 10 offers new exciting features such as short window, and Stretch Audio, plus hundreds of virtual instruments included and dozens of process improvement work according to the requirements of users DP.
MOTU Digital Performer - tools audio editing
MOTU...
</description></item><item><title>Download Robin YouTube Video Downloader Pro 6.15.7</title><pubDate> Sat, 16 Aug 2025 23:26:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-video-downloader-pro-2828.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-video-downloader-pro-2828.html
</guid><description>
YouTube Video Downloader Pro is a Windows application professional to download and convert videos from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion and thousands of video sharing sites, other. It accelerates your download up to 5 times. YouTube Video Downloader Pro allows you to download multiple videos at the same time. It also allows you to pause, resume and cancel a download at any time.
YouTube Video Downloader Pro - Download online videos on social networks
Features of YouTube Video Downloader...
</description></item><item><title>Download IntraWEB Ultimate 16.1.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 16 Aug 2025 23:21:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intraweb-ultimate-2007.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intraweb-ultimate-2007.html
</guid><description>
IntraWEB Ultimate is a tool to build the website. With this tool, the developer can create the page using the same method used to build the Windows program. Because the HTML page directly from the concept design to the user's computer does not download a bit more complicated and in fact is required from web server. So, the template IntraWeb on the server and download server and displays them to the user. Things technology direction of the IntraWEB Ultimate provides part flexibility and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Muziza YouTube Downloader Converter 8.11.6</title><pubDate> Sat, 16 Aug 2025 23:21:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-muziza-youtube-downloader-converter-3972.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-muziza-youtube-downloader-converter-3972.html
</guid><description>
Muziza YouTube Downloader Converter is a tool to create conditions for an attractive interface and many features to help you to download video clips from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion, Instagram and other sites. Muziza YouTube Downloader Converter can also download the video UHD 8K, 5K, 4K, QHD 2K, HD 1080p and 720p from YouTube. The app allows you download only audio stream from YouTube and save as MP3. You don't need to download the entire video file.
Muziza YouTube Downloader...
</description></item><item><title>Download PACETEQ OneTiming 1.10.144</title><pubDate> Sat, 16 Aug 2025 23:20:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-paceteq-onetiming-12731.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-paceteq-onetiming-12731.html
</guid><description>
OneTiming integrates all important data sources, including all major timing protocols, GPS feeds, Race Control Messages, weather data and video feeds. The optimal balance of performance and durability is designed to be the benchmark for dynamic and complex racing environments.
Key Features of OneTiming
	Data Integration: OneTiming seamlessly combines information from multiple channels, including timekeeping, telemetry, weather data, and audio/video feeds. This integration supports all...
</description></item><item><title>Download Rocrail Build 5999</title><pubDate> Sat, 16 Aug 2025 23:20:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rocrail-3193.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rocrail-3193.html
</guid><description>
Rocrail is a free software to control the training model for the operating system Linux , Apple macOS , Windows and Raspbian / Armbian . Rocrail bear all responsibility in the control of a railway model, and accessories of them. Trains can be controlled manually or fully controlled by software in automatic mode. A mixed operation, i.e. control a number of ships and other vessels at high speed fully automatic is possible.
Rocrail - control layout for the operating system
With Rocrail,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Total Uninstaller 2025 v3.0.0.799</title><pubDate> Sat, 16 Aug 2025 20:37:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-total-uninstaller-5527.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-total-uninstaller-5527.html
</guid><description>
Total Uninstaller is a software that completely removes unwanted applications from your PC with just a few clicks. 3 simple steps allow you to effectively complete the deletion: select the program, Run the Analysis and Delete. Completely uninstall all files, registry entries and configuration related to the removal program and you will get an automatic and fast removal process. Completely remove stubborn files and data, especially those that always lurk in your hard drive.
Total...
</description></item><item><title>Download Macro Express Pro 6.6.5.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 16 Aug 2025 20:34:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-macro-express-pro-14053.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-macro-express-pro-14053.html
</guid><description>
Macro Express Pro is a Windows automation utility developed by Insight Software Solutions. It allows users to automate common computer tasks such as filling out web forms, opening programs, performing mouse clicks, and other repetitive actions.
Why use macros?
A macro is a way to automate a task that you perform repeatedly or frequently. It is a series of commands and actions that can be stored and run whenever you need to perform the task. You can record or create a macro, then run...
</description></item><item><title>Download Abelssoft KeyDepot 2025 v11.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 16 Aug 2025 20:25:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-abelssoft-keydepot-14052.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-abelssoft-keydepot-14052.html
</guid><description>
Abelssoft KeyDepot is a password manager software designed to securely store and manage passwords, logins, and other sensitive data. The software uses advanced encryption technology, specifically AES-256 encryption, to protect user data from unauthorized access. KeyDepot allows users to create a master password to secure access to their password vault, and this master password will never be stored on Abelssoft servers for added security.
Features of Abelssoft KeyDepot
	Secure password...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Premiere Pro 2025 v25.4.0.099 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Sat, 16 Aug 2025 16:23:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-premiere-pro-0021-1361.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-premiere-pro-0021-1361.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Premiere Pro is the leading video editing software for film, TV, and the web. Creative tools, integration with other Adobe apps and services, and the power of Adobe Sensei help you turn footage into finished movies and videos in a seamless workflow. It offers high-quality video editing at 4K x 4K resolution and beyond, with 32-bit color, in both RGB and YUV color spaces. Edit audio samples, support for VST audio plug-ins (plug-ins), and 5.1 surround sound tracks. The Premiere Pro...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe After Effects 2025 v25.4.0.086 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Sat, 16 Aug 2025 16:22:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-after-effects-0001-2793.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-after-effects-0001-2793.html
</guid><description>
Adobe After Effects is a powerful digital visual effects, motion graphics, and compositing application developed by Adobe Inc. The software is widely used in the film, television, and video game industries to animate and enhance video content.
After Effects allows users to create stunning motion graphics and visual effects by animating text, images, and video clips. Its capabilities include keying, tracking, compositing, and basic audio editing, making it a versatile tool for...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Media Encoder 2025 v25.4.0.090 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Sat, 16 Aug 2025 16:21:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-0010-adobe-media-encoder-1360.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-0010-adobe-media-encoder-1360.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Media Encoder 2024 is a professional audio and video converter that allows you to encode audio and video files into various distribution formats for applications different uses and audiences. Such video and audio formats are characterized by a high degree of compression. By downloading this program on taiwebs.com, you can export videos in formats supported by various devices, from DVD players and websites to mobile phones, portable media players and High Definition and High...
</description></item><item><title>Download Free YouTube Download 4.4.36.815 Premium</title><pubDate> Sat, 16 Aug 2025 16:20:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-download-1177.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-download-1177.html
</guid><description>
Free YouTube Download Premium is the most popular application to download videos from YouTube. The program was released in 2006 and regularly updated since then. Use the program to download and convert YouTube videos to view offline anytime.
Free YouTube Download - added Support to download youtube
Download more videos! Save whole playlists and YouTube channels, videos from a playlist individually (history, video be favorite, favourites, Watch later), videos from many different...
</description></item><item><title>Download Scooter Beyond Compare 5.1.3.31238</title><pubDate> Sat, 16 Aug 2025 16:20:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-scooter-beyond-compare-2649.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-scooter-beyond-compare-2649.html
</guid><description>
Scooter Beyond Compare is a powerful tool to compare quickly and easily the files and folders. This program provides you with a full report on work done so you can compare the complete data on the file, folder, folder with speed and file size, very fast and incredible, time changes on the file as well as the compared bytes Do byte this information. With the strong command of this program, you can merge the changes, synchronize files, create a report to record.
Scooter Beyond Compare -...
</description></item><item><title>Download GoodSync Enterprise 12.9.6.6</title><pubDate> Sat, 16 Aug 2025 16:19:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-goodsync-enterprise-163.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-goodsync-enterprise-163.html
</guid><description>
GoodSync Enterprise is a software that saves files and files easily and is reliable. It automatically analyts, synchronize and backup your email, family photos, contacts, MP3, financial documentation and other important files-between desktop computers, laptops, servers, external drives and Windows Mobile devices as well as remotely via FTP , SFTP, WebDAV and more. The GoodSync synchronized software combines bulletproof reliability with an extremely easy interface to compare, synchronize...
</description></item><item><title>Download Photo Supreme 2025.3.1.8015</title><pubDate> Sat, 16 Aug 2025 16:18:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photo-supreme-430.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photo-supreme-430.html
</guid><description>
Photo Supreme is a software product management professional pictures of idimager. With Photo Supreme you can arrange, manage back stock photo archive of yourself and share them with you here and relatives easily via Email or Facebook. Photo Supreme provides users method to sort images effective, logical, as well as edit and share your photos with friends and relatives in the family. Especially the Photo Supreme allows to work with multiple image formats and support mounting support,...
</description></item><item><title>Download DeskSoft EarthView 7.13.7</title><pubDate> Sat, 16 Aug 2025 16:18:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desksoft-earthview-184.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desksoft-earthview-184.html
</guid><description>
With software DeskSoft EarthView you can easily create wallpapers to your computer or select screen saver of your favorite. the program can change day and night, the clouds will also change according to weather conditions current on one or another part of the earth, you can see the lights of the city.
Features of DeskSoft EarthView can be interesting, because of DeskSoft EarthView support for day and night, you can view atmospheric phenomena, light city can see, the cloud is displayed,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium 4.4.36.815</title><pubDate> Sat, 16 Aug 2025 16:17:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-to-mp3-converter-premium-844.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-to-mp3-converter-premium-844.html
</guid><description>
Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium version is a software used to convert YouTube to MP3, extract audio from playlists YouTube, show listings, charts, video responses, channels, favorites of the user. With Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium, you can download and convert playlists, channels, stream original tv series and get them into iTunes at the same time.
Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium - convert YouTube to MP3
Features Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium from the...
</description></item></channel></rss>