<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 05:35:07 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 05:35:07 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download OpenShot Video Editor 3.4.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 03:14:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-openshot-video-editor-3485.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-openshot-video-editor-3485.html
</guid><description>
OpenShot Video Editor is video editor free and open source for FreeBSD, Linux, Haiku, macOS and Windows. The project was started on January 8, 2008 by Jonathan Thomas, with the goal of providing editing video stable, free and friendly to use. OpenShot Video Editor to be easy to use, quick to learn and the video editor surprisingly powerful. Take a quick look at some of the features and capabilities of our most popular I.
OpenShot Video Editor - video editor free
The features of...
</description></item><item><title>Download TeamViewer 15.73.3 + Portable</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 03:12:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-teamviewer-528.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-teamviewer-528.html
</guid><description>
TeamViewer is software that functions to connect and control the remote computer, the ability to connect with any system anywhere from all over the place. This is a support tool users is very convenient. TeamViewer to help users control remote computer becomes much more simple, help you interact and collaborate with others in the exchange and share of information, instruction manual, application software or fix the computer.
TeamViewer as a revolution of computer science. when you have...
</description></item><item><title>Download iTop Easy Desktop 4.0.0.230</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 03:12:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-itop-easy-desktop-7879.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-itop-easy-desktop-7879.html
</guid><description>
iTop Easy Desktop is a lightweight and easy-to-use desktop manager that organizes desktop icons, files and folders according to your rules, helping you Freed from the tedious arrangement of icons on the screen. It provides various practical features including but not limited to grouping desktop items, awakening live search, and quickly accessing icons and files even across multiple desktop sites. desktop.
Untidy desktop If you're not one to diligently organize your Windows desktop icons...
</description></item><item><title>Download Easy Code 2.02.0.0049</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 03:11:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easy-code-3690.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easy-code-3690.html
</guid><description>
Easy Code is a perfect environment for programmers. Easy Code create programming environment for assembly intuitive are made to build Windows applications 32 bit / 64 bit. First use the software you will find the interface Easy Code looks like Visual Basic, allows you to program the app translation Windows (executables, dynamic libraries and static file object-COFF apps, dashboard, drivers NT, and service) be done in an easy way never before possible.
Easy Code - Write Code, build the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Blender 5.0.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 00:13:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blender-3017.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blender-3017.html
</guid><description>
Blender has a tool that new and very powerful, whose name is Ciking provides the ability to display extremely impressive and extremely realistic.
Features of Blender
	- Feature button support complete
	- The ball exactly on the physical side, SSS and translucency
	- Support languages open for coding the ball unique
Blender - The software-rendered optical
Tool output integration provides:
	- The GPU and CPU
	- Preview options view real-time
	- Support light HDR
	- The license...
</description></item><item><title>Download Telegram for Desktop 6.3.9</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 20:32:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-telegram-3376.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-telegram-3376.html
</guid><description>
Telegram is an instant messaging service and voice over IP services on the cloud platform. Client application Telegram is available for Android, iOS, Windows Phone, Windows NT, macOS, and Linux. Users can send messages and exchange photos, videos, stickers, audio and files of any kind.
Telegram - Messaging and free phone calls
Telegram seamless sync across all your devices and can be used on desktop, tablet and phone. You can send unlimited amount of messages, photos, videos and files...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ashampoo Zip Pro 4.70.01</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 20:31:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-zip-pro-2650.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-zip-pro-2650.html
</guid><description>
Ashampoo Zip Pro is a program strong enough to compress your files, it is also a management tool, storage and encryption, well, there are also browser integration and cloud backup. The entire features and beautiful user interface make the program become heavy (if compared with the other similar), although there is a another program in memory of I weighed under a hundred megabytes, which is a winzip.
Ashampoo ZIP Pro 3 not only is the app ZIP that is a complete, full-featured to zip,...
</description></item><item><title>Download ExifTool 13.44</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 20:30:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-exiftool-1685.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-exiftool-1685.html
</guid><description>
ExifTool is a library of Perl platform-independent plus a command line application for reading, writing, and editing meta information in various file types. ExifTool supports many metadata formats including EXIF , GPS , IPTC , XMP , JFIF , GeoTIFF , ICC Profile , Photoshop IRB , FlashPix , AFCP and ID3 , as well as notes of the manufacturer of many digital cameras by Canon , Casio , DJI , FLIR , FujiFilm , GE , GoPro , HP , JVC / Victor , Kodak , Leaf , Minolta / Konica-Minolta , Motorola...
</description></item><item><title>Download Alternate TextBrowser 4.430</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 20:30:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-alternate-textbrowser-2743.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-alternate-textbrowser-2743.html
</guid><description>
Alternate TextBrowser is a text editor, markup syntax, reliable and useful, useful for users that need to browse through a number of documents TXT and HTML in few minutes. Alternate TextBrowser will syntax highlighting for some programming languages / file types are available and can be configured for the file extensions different. The program includes the memorandum replaced and the Computer replaced as the additional tool. It is free software and requires Net-Framework 2.0 or higher...
</description></item><item><title>Download Topaz Gigapixel Pro 1.0.6</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 20:29:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-ai-gigapixel-1318.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-ai-gigapixel-1318.html
</guid><description>
Topaz ONE Gigapixel is the first app and only use the power of artificial intelligence to enhance your photos, add natural details, for great results. Use technology to learn deep, AIGigapixel ™ can zoom in and fill in the details that the products change in size other are not included. The traditional method this created blurred image, a non-realistic and do not have the detail present in the image have high resolution.
Topaz A.I. Gigapixel - enhance image quality
The content of...
</description></item><item><title>Download MixPad Masters Edition 13.50</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 20:29:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mixpad-masters-edition-505.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mixpad-masters-edition-505.html
</guid><description>
MixPad Masters Edition is software mixing many different songs, mix music files available, or the recording is completed and combine them. MixPad Masters Edition is software recording and mixing music is designed to produce sounds easily. Mix music, vocal and audio, adjust the volume, pan, fade and more with MixPad as your digital mixing your.
MixPad Masters Edition will save the sound under the popular formats such as MP3,WAV, AIF, WMA, VOX, M4A, GSM,... user can create, add and remove...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ahnenblatt 4.40.0.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 20:22:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ahnenblatt-3844.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ahnenblatt-3844.html
</guid><description>
Ahnenblatt is a genealogy software full-featured, easy to use suitable for beginners and even pedigree has the experience to organize genealogy research by you. Use plausibility checks to find out the inaccuracies in your family and create the chart impressive with just a few mouse clicks.
Ahnenblatt - Create family tree,
Recently, there has been strong increase of the general interest of the public for genealogical tree. Users who desire to track their heritage have many tools at...
</description></item><item><title>Download VideoPad Video Editor Pro 17.54</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 20:19:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-videopad-video-editor-pro-268.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-videopad-video-editor-pro-268.html
</guid><description>
VideoPad Video Editor Pro is software edit video from any camcorder, DV camcorder, VHS player or webcam for best quality. The interface of this utility is divided into several parts (for example: list of multi-media, Effects, transitions, Files, Clips, video track, audio track, overlay), which makes everything seem difficult to operate. You can capture videos from camcorder or other devices like webcam or capture card TV and after you have added files and sequence clips to the queue, you...
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 7.6.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 20:19:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-11-7760.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-11-7760.html
</guid><description>
TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 is a program that allows users to discover hidden settings in Windows 11. This application is specially designed for Windows 11, groups many registry settings and distribute them from the easy and secure user interface. With TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 you can move the Windows taskbar to the top and resize the taskbar by editing the registry value. With any application that modifies the registry, we recommend that you have a backup copy...
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 7.6.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 20:19:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-10-7759.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-10-7759.html
</guid><description>
TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 is a utility that allows users to discover hidden settings in Windows 10. This application is specially designed for Windows 10, groups many registry settings and provide them from an easy and secure user interface. With TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 you can move the Windows taskbar to the top and resize the taskbar by editing the registry value. With any application that modifies the registry, we recommend that you have a backup copy to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Lightroom 9.1 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 20:18:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-photoshop-lightroom-0006-5334.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-photoshop-lightroom-0006-5334.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Photoshop Lightroom is the most professional version completely redesigned and based on a performance architecture that is better responsive to ever expanding galleries, while also featuring unrivaled processing tools with noise reduction and sharpening tools to get the best picture quality. Adobe Photoshop Lightroom gives the basic ideas of software produced by Adobe in 2002, as one of the developers and gradually improving and the features of the ImageReady software are included.
...
</description></item><item><title>Download Debut Video Capture Software Pro 12.04</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 20:18:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-debut-video-capture-software-pro-951.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-debut-video-capture-software-pro-951.html
</guid><description>
Debut Video Capture Software Pro is software record and capture video from any source and features editing video color, resolution, and output settings. Debut Video Capture Software Pro is designed to use very easy and intuitive, giving you the ability to record everything from the video recording from your webcam, screen or video input device such as recorder, VHS in few minutes after download.
Debut Video Capture Software Pro - Recording and video recording
The main features of Debut...
</description></item><item><title>Download VectorStyler 1.3.003</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 20:17:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vectorstyler-7917.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vectorstyler-7917.html
</guid><description>
VectorStyler provides a complete set of drawing, design and illustration tools needed for modern design. Create illustrations, logos, icons, drawings, typography, vector art for screen, print and web. With many new features, VectorStyler redefines and extends the tools available to illustrators and designers, improving the creation of complex illustrations and designs.
Shape effects can be used to adjust the shape of objects, create different distortions, or add detail to shapes. Shape...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sublime Merge 2 Build 2119 Dev</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 20:17:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sublime-merge-3957.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sublime-merge-3957.html
</guid><description>
Sublime Merge is the name of the application software and of course very useful for the programmer. In fact, the software in front of you is a text editor and the code light on the mass, and of course is strong. When using this software, you can view and edit multiple page text and his code at the same time and edit and complete them. User interface with great editing tools will give you experience coding very interesting.
Sublime Merge - source Editor and write the Code
Software...
</description></item><item><title>Download Blumentals Surfblocker 5.16.0.66</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 20:13:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blumentals-surfblocker-6182.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blumentals-surfblocker-6182.html
</guid><description>
Blumentals Surfblocker is software that helps you to easily restrict internet access at specific times or on demand. You can allow and block websites as well as limit programs and features that have access to the internet. For example, you can only allow e-mails and websites related to work or learning. You can also just need the password to protect the internet connection or place it automatically off after a certain period of time. Of course, you can also automatically block malicious...
</description></item><item><title>Download BoostPing 1.6.4</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 20:12:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-boostping-12519.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-boostping-12519.html
</guid><description>
BoostPing helps optimize your online gaming experience by modifying the network throttling index and disabling the Nagle algorithm. By turning this feature off, you can achieve more instantaneous data transfer speeds, potentially reducing latency.
What is Nagle's algorithm?
The Nagle algorithm is designed to improve network efficiency by combining small data packets into larger packets, which can cause lag in online games. Disabling it can result in more responsive gameplay. On the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cloanto Amiga Forever Plus Edition 11.2.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 20:12:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cloanto-amiga-forever-plus-edition-4743.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cloanto-amiga-forever-plus-edition-4743.html
</guid><description>
Cloanto Amiga Forever Plus Edition is the emulator, preservation and support of official Amiga of Cloanto, a software developer Commodore / Amiga brought to you from the 1980s. The different editions of Amiga Forever blend high-quality software and original content with the video great top to record the time and let you experience firsthand the history, culture, challenges and passion behind the Amiga.
The features of Cloanto Amiga Forever Plus Edition
	Interface player revolutionary...
</description></item><item><title>Download Crescendo Masters 11.29</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 20:09:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-crescendo-masters-6038.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-crescendo-masters-6038.html
</guid><description>
Crescendo Masters is a simple and intuitive way to write music notation, Crescendo Masters allows composers to write, save and print their music works on their computers. A wide variety of music, time and sign symbols, along with the free-form layout, allows the composer to optimize the creation of the music for their arrangements.
The features of Crescendo Masters
	The visual interface to work with the music notation
	Set up your own professional quality music
	Composer for the film,...
</description></item><item><title>Download WavePad Sound Editor Master 20.50</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 20:08:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wavepad-sound-editor-1149.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wavepad-sound-editor-1149.html
</guid><description>
WavePad Sound Editor is editor software and improve the quality of sound create recordings music best quality. WavePad is mootij in the editor software sound good for the computer are configured midrange and low. Because WavePad very compact only about 4MB of space is you already own the software editor sounds good.
WavePad Sound Editor - Side audio quality
WavePad help you edit audio created the Nightcore quality. WavePad Sound Editor there are many options is very impressive as add...
</description></item><item><title>Download Secret Disk Pro 2025 v316</title><pubDate> Tue, 16 Dec 2025 20:08:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secret-disk-pro-933.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secret-disk-pro-933.html
</guid><description>
Secret Disk Pro 4 is a software to create a virtual disk can be hidden and password protected to keep your data private and safe. You can store any file and folder on the disk. Disc secret works like a hard disk typically, and is compatible with any any other program that you have installed. You can have more than one disk secret, and you can also choose disk letter.
Secret Disk Pro 4 - Create and secure drive
Secret Disk does not encrypt any files, it just limits access to your files...
</description></item></channel></rss>