<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 01:46:14 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 01:46:14 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download TidyWindow 3.9.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 18 Jan 2026 01:10:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tidywindow-14454.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tidywindow-14454.html
</guid><description>
TidyWindow is a Windows desktop assistant that automates developer PC setup, cleanup, diagnostics, software package installation, registry tweaking, and driver updates—powered by a WPF interface and robust PowerShell 7 automation capabilities in the background.
Key Features
	Essentials Repair Center (docs/essentials.md): Queues selected automation tasks Filter for network, Defender, printing, and Windows Update issues. Each task supports preview run, sequential execution, restore...
</description></item><item><title>Download Realtek High Definition Audio Drivers 6.0.9927.1 WHQL</title><pubDate> Sun, 18 Jan 2026 00:59:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-realtek-high-definition-audio-drivers-r282-32bit-64bit-442.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-realtek-high-definition-audio-drivers-r282-32bit-64bit-442.html
</guid><description>
Realtek High Definition Audio Drivers is audio drivers Realtek high-quality latest for windows operating systems, virgin audio controller is based on Realtek for Windows 7/8/8.1/10. When the window is integrated this Driver will make the sound of computer, laptop, your back up crisp, and the sound output for the highest quality possible.
Realtek High Definition Audio Drivers and devices are supported :
ALC880, ALC882, ALC883, ALC885, ALC888, ALC889, ALC861VC, ALC861VD, ALC892, ALC663,...
</description></item><item><title>Download IObit Driver Booster Pro Portable 13.2.0.184</title><pubDate> Sun, 18 Jan 2026 00:59:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iobit-driver-booster-pro-portable-4169.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iobit-driver-booster-pro-portable-4169.html
</guid><description>
IObit Driver Booster Pro Portable is a portable version developed with IObit's most advanced driver update technology, which automatically identifies and scans for outdated, downloaded drivers and install the correct update for you with just one click, saving you a lot of time. In addition, IObit Driver Booster Pro Portable is specially developed to enhance drivers for better gaming performance and ensure better computer performance by improving update security with Restore, Uninstall...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft Office 2021-2024 Professional Plus VL (64-bit) 2512 Build 19530.20144 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Sun, 18 Jan 2026 00:58:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-office-2021-6670.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-office-2021-6670.html
</guid><description>
Since the end of February 2021, Microsoft has announced two new versions of Office 2021 including: Office 2021 and Office LTSC. Reportedly, Office 2021 is the next version of Office 2019, promising to bring users a better experience in the new Word, Excel or PowerPoint tools.
With each office user, the Microsoft Office toolkit is essential and indispensable software in the job. Microsoft Office has undergone numerous editions from Office 2010, 2013, 2016, 2019 to Microsoft 365 developed...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare PDFelement Professional Portable 12.1.6.3963</title><pubDate> Sun, 18 Jan 2026 00:57:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-pdfelement-professional-portable-12154.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-pdfelement-professional-portable-12154.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare PDFelement Professional Portable is a portable version of PDF editing software called PDFelement Professional developed by Wondershare. The portable version of the software is designed to be used directly from a portable storage device, such as a USB drive, without the need for installation on a computer.
PDFelement Pro is the simplest and most powerful PDF solution that will forever change the way you work with your important documents. The easiest way to create, edit,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Fender Studio Pro (PreSonus Studio One Pro) 8.0.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 18 Jan 2026 00:56:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-presonus-studio-one-pro-780.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-presonus-studio-one-pro-780.html
</guid><description>
PreSonus Studio One Pro is software production music professional perfect combination between the studio model with the production process according to the beat and loop today so you can bring music ideas to actual sounds. Screen interface, simple, effective contains the number of tracks is not limited to , the editing tools are intuitive and the tools advanced virtual. Spend precious time to create music instead of wondering what to click next. Studio One does not dictate how you work or...
</description></item><item><title>Download Prevent Restore Pro 2026 v117</title><pubDate> Sun, 18 Jan 2026 00:56:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-prevent-restore-pro-1473.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-prevent-restore-pro-1473.html
</guid><description>
Prevent Restore Pro is software prevent restore files deleted in any drive: external hard drives and hard drives mounted in hard drive, SSD, Flash drives, except CD-ROM and CD-RW. The software uses many security algorithms can be used to get data.Our program includes some of the most reliable and accepted as standard.
Prevent Restore Pro - Prevent restore files deleted
The features of Prevent Restore Pro
Mode to clean up quickly
	In this mode, the program will not overwrite the free...
</description></item><item><title>Download PhotoCHAT AI 0.3.1.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 18 Jan 2026 00:54:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photochat-ai-14302.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photochat-ai-14302.html
</guid><description>
PhotoCHAT AI is a Windows app that instantly searches your entire photo library using AI, allowing you to quickly recall and rediscover memories from your photo collection with natural language search features. The app runs entirely on your computer, no uploading, no account and no registration required, prioritizing privacy and ease of use.
Features of PhotoCHAT AI
	Natural Language Search: Describe the moment in plain English and get instant results.
	Voice Search: Just say your...
</description></item><item><title>Download HTTP Logs Viewer 7.10</title><pubDate> Sun, 18 Jan 2026 00:54:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-apache-logs-viewer-5363.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-apache-logs-viewer-5363.html
</guid><description>
HTTP Logs Viewer (Formerly named: Apache Logs Viewer) is an apache log viewer you can easily filter and analyze log files Apache/IIS/nginx. Built-in search and filter functions. Custom log formats are also supported. Apache Logs Viewer (ALV) is a free and powerful tool that allows you to monitor, view and analyze Apache/IIS/nginx logs more easily. It provides search and filter functionality for log files, highlighting different http requests based on their status codes.
There is also a...
</description></item><item><title>Download Playnite 10.48</title><pubDate> Sun, 18 Jan 2026 00:53:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-playnite-6972.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-playnite-6972.html
</guid><description>
Playnite is an open-source video game library manager and manager with support for third-party libraries such as Steam, GOG, Origin, Battle.net and Uplay. Includes supporting the game, providing a unified interface for your game. With Playnite, you can comfortably enter the game from Steam, Battle.net, Origin, GOG and Uplay services, including uninstalled games.
You have three options to view when using Playnite. You also have the custom game option or add any game or program with...
</description></item><item><title>Download Rocrail Build 6521</title><pubDate> Sun, 18 Jan 2026 00:53:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rocrail-3193.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rocrail-3193.html
</guid><description>
Rocrail is a free software to control the training model for the operating system Linux , Apple macOS , Windows and Raspbian / Armbian . Rocrail bear all responsibility in the control of a railway model, and accessories of them. Trains can be controlled manually or fully controlled by software in automatic mode. A mixed operation, i.e. control a number of ships and other vessels at high speed fully automatic is possible.
Rocrail - control layout for the operating system
With Rocrail,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Allavsoft Video Downloader Converter Portable 3.28.8.9497</title><pubDate> Sun, 18 Jan 2026 00:52:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allavsoft-video-downloader-converter-portable-12064.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allavsoft-video-downloader-converter-portable-12064.html
</guid><description>
Allavsoft Video Downloader Converter Portable is a portable version of the software application that allows users to download videos from various websites and convert them to different formats. It supports popular video sharing platforms such as YouTube Vimeo, Dailymotion and many others.
Besides downloading videos in their original format, Allavsoft also has a one-click feature to download as well as convert downloaded videos to popular video formats like MP4, AVI, WMV, MOV, MPEG-1,...
</description></item><item><title>Download VovSoft URL Extractor 2.6</title><pubDate> Sun, 18 Jan 2026 00:52:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-url-extractor-7380.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-url-extractor-7380.html
</guid><description>
VovSoft URL Extractor is one of the best programs that can tap site addresses and https. You can extract and restore all URLs from the file in a few seconds. After installation, you can start the app and start looking for the links almost immediately. You only need to provide a folder, because the program can take care of the rest.
The software scans the entire directory to find the files that contain the URL and display them all in its main window, allowing you to export the list to...
</description></item><item><title>Download EIVA NaviScan 9.10.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 18 Jan 2026 00:51:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-eiva-naviscan-12225.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-eiva-naviscan-12225.html
</guid><description>
Collect data using sonar, sensors and lasers. NaviScan collects data from all major pipe/cable monitors and sonar on the market, including multibeam acoustic detectors, scanning and profiling sonar, and conventional side-scan sonar.
Features include:
	Laser/LiDAR, side scanning and multi-beam acquisition
	Real-time sensor monitoring
	Sensor-compensated real-time digital terrain model
	Show sonar coverage
	Sonar waterfall display
	Real-time 2D and 3D display
</description></item><item><title>Download tinyMediaManager 5.2.5</title><pubDate> Sun, 18 Jan 2026 00:51:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tinymediamanager-1819.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tinymediamanager-1819.html
</guid><description>
tinyMediaManager is a media manager full-featured to arrange and cleanup your media library your. Just choose (s) the folder containing your movies and the program can automatically get all meta data required for movies and program your TV from TheMovieDB.org, Imdb.com, OFDb.de and other online sources. tinyMediaManager download at artwork, film, cast, plot and details of other communication. Each film or program is presented with a unique art background, category, and appropriate...
</description></item><item><title>Download Database Tour Pro 11.6.1.819</title><pubDate> Sun, 18 Jan 2026 00:51:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-database-tour-pro-5321.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-database-tour-pro-5321.html
</guid><description>
Database Tour Pro application is a comprehensive software that allows you to organize all the database is connected his. It provides support for Borland Database Engine (BDE) and Microsoft ActiveX Data Objects (ADO), SQL scripts, reports, along with conversion and data export, among others.
It contains a browser object for the function, package, triggers, folders, users, roles, profiles, sequences, work, style, Java, exception, link, database, general properties, table, schema, and...
</description></item><item><title>Download EIVA NaviEdit 9.2.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 18 Jan 2026 00:50:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-eiva-naviedit-8678.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-eiva-naviedit-8678.html
</guid><description>
EIVA NaviEdit is a software product developed by EIVA A/S, a company specializing in software solutions for the offshore construction and surveying industry. EIVA NaviEdit is a geospatial software application used to manage and edit survey data, as well as create reports, charts, and presentations.
This software is designed for use by surveyors, geologists, engineers and other professionals in the construction and offshore surveying industries, and it is capable of handling a wide range...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinToHDD Professional Portable 6.9</title><pubDate> Sat, 17 Jan 2026 21:55:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wintohdd-portable-11911.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wintohdd-portable-11911.html
</guid><description>
WinToHDD Portable is convenient and easy-to-use portable software that allows users to easily reinstall or clone their Windows operating system without the need for a CD/DVD or USB drive. This program will help you easily reinstall Windows, install Windows to disks other than the drive where your Windows operating system is installed, or clone your current Windows operating system installation (Windows vista or more) to another disk.
In addition to creating a bootable USB drive...
</description></item><item><title>Download ON1 Effects 2026.2 v20.2.1.17958</title><pubDate> Sat, 17 Jan 2026 17:53:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-on1-effects-1430.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-on1-effects-1430.html
</guid><description>
ON1 Effects is a collection of photo effects includes hundreds of effects, photo filters, LUT, borders, textures and presets and all can be fully customized according to your style. The ability to create endless Effects with ON1. Most popular our included HDR Look, B &amp;amp; W, Lens Blur (tilt-shift), Glows, Color Enhancer, Tone Enhancer, Textures, B Border, Film Look, Split Tone,...
ON1 Effects 2019 - The visual effects
ON1 Effects 2019 includes everything you need to create any style...
</description></item><item><title>Download Aeon Timeline 3.5.36</title><pubDate> Sat, 17 Jan 2026 17:52:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aeon-timeline-4952.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aeon-timeline-4952.html
</guid><description>
Aeon Timeline is a tool line-time for creative thinking. Most of the application time line traditional designed to suit a single need: to create attractive screen on time one way. They are present, static, and perfectly aligned with the slide and overhead projector.
With Aeon Timeline, you can split your timeline into logical groups, projects or arcs at the same time. You can model the relationships between events and people, places, and ideas. Aeon calculate ages of people for you. And...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mozilla Firefox 147.0.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 17 Jan 2026 17:52:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-firefox-quantum-501.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-firefox-quantum-501.html
</guid><description>
Firefox Quantum is a web browser independently provide the tabbed browsing combined with numerous handy features like pop-up blocker, Bookmarks, direct (integrated RSS), password manager, and more. Functionality can be extended with dozens of plugins available for free (extensions).
Firefox Quantum are interface completely new, beautiful, neat, minimalistic and delicate, eats less RAM to 30% compared with the old version and solve the condition consuming capacity
Firefox can import all...
</description></item><item><title>Download StartAllBack 3.9.21.5350</title><pubDate> Sat, 17 Jan 2026 17:51:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-startallback-6857.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-startallback-6857.html
</guid><description>
With the official release of Windows 11, chances are that most of you want to try it out. As the name suggests, StartAllBack is a small, lightweight tool that can help you enjoy the power of the new operating system while keeping the look and feel, especially because main work area, desktop of Windows 7, Windows 10 as taskbars and start menu styles.
StartAllBack is specially designed for Windows 11 and will not work on any older operating systems. If you want to get the start menu back...
</description></item><item><title>Download 4K Video Downloader Plus 26.0.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 17 Jan 2026 17:51:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-video-downloader-617.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-video-downloader-617.html
</guid><description>
4K Video Downloader Plus is software support downloads video, audio and subtitles from YouTube with high quality up to 4K. Download process video is very simple: just copy the video link from your browser and click Paste Url. Done! If you want that video on your iPad, iPhone or other device, we have protected you.
The feature on 4K Video Downloader Plus
	Download entire playlists and channels from YouTube and save them in MP4, MKV, M4A, MP3, FLV, 3G, create a file .m3u for...
</description></item><item><title>Download Perfectly Clear WorkBench 5.0.1.3049</title><pubDate> Sat, 17 Jan 2026 17:50:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfectly-clear-workbench-6892.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfectly-clear-workbench-6892.html
</guid><description>
Perfectly Clear Workbench is an application that uses image editing libraries Perfectly Clear by Athentech and is provided to demonstrate the capabilities of the Perfectly Clear processing libraries, which recognize faces and allow quick export of processing settings for use.
One of the key features in Workbench is the ability to "export to API" when saving a Preset. This allows you to make image edits in Workbench and adjust the settings to suit your editing style and needs. You can...
</description></item><item><title>Download 4K YouTube to MP3 26.0.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 17 Jan 2026 17:50:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-youtube-to-mp3-622.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-youtube-to-mp3-622.html
</guid><description>
4K YouTube to MP3 is a software to convert video youtube to mp3 quickly and easily by the manipulation drag-and-drop simple. With 4K YouTube to MP3 you just drag and drop the link to the favorite songs of you and get the MP3 files to your computer, as easy as that. Transfer songs directly to iPod, iPhone and iPad everywhere you go. No install annoying and complex to solve, just a clean interface, user friendly and functional.
When using 4K YouTube to MP3, users will get the playlists,...
</description></item></channel></rss>