<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 17:43:03 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 17:43:03 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Google Chrome 143.0.7499.147</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 19:57:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-chrome-1012.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-chrome-1012.html
</guid><description>
Google Chrome web browser is the most used today. Support surf the web, listen to music, watch movies, play web game effective no jerky lag with the internet connection stable. When you are surfing the web or performing an important task, whether it is operation big or small, work or entertainment, then Chrome has the smart features and the speed you need to make, create and explore on the net.
The latest version of Google Chrome is the third 114. But we are providing for users Google...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ratiborus KMS Tools Lite 17.12.2025</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 19:52:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ratiborus-kms-tools-lite-11160.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ratiborus-kms-tools-lite-11160.html
</guid><description>
Ratiborus KMS Tools Lite is a collection of activators from Ratiborus for Windows XP, Vista, 7, 8, 8.1, 10, 11, Windows Server, Office 2010/2013/2016/2019 /2021/2024. It includes several utilities, each with its own set of features, mainly aimed at activating Microsoft Windows and Office products. The program is used to activate Microsoft products such as Windows and Office using Key Management Service (KMS). With a simple, easy-to-use interface that allows users to activate the product...
</description></item><item><title>Download Topaz Gigapixel Pro 1.0.7</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 19:51:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-ai-gigapixel-1318.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-ai-gigapixel-1318.html
</guid><description>
Topaz ONE Gigapixel is the first app and only use the power of artificial intelligence to enhance your photos, add natural details, for great results. Use technology to learn deep, AIGigapixel ™ can zoom in and fill in the details that the products change in size other are not included. The traditional method this created blurred image, a non-realistic and do not have the detail present in the image have high resolution.
Topaz A.I. Gigapixel - enhance image quality
The content of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Rhinoceros 8.26.25349.19001</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 19:50:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rhinoceros-179.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rhinoceros-179.html
</guid><description>
Rhinoceros is design software 3D easy to learn, easy to use and has range of application in various industries. Rhinoceros (or Rhino, Rhino3D) is a graphics software CAD and 3D developed by Robert McNeel &amp;amp; Associates, a private company established in the year 1980. Rhinoceros is developed according to the algorithm NURBS mathematical model, algorithm, focus on the correct presentation of curves and surfaces mathematics in computer graphics (in contrast to the application polygon...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare Recoverit 14.0.10.4</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 19:50:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-recoverits-374.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-recoverits-374.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare Recoverit is a data recovery software that is easily lost at a rapid rate and is used by many people. You will do what happens if one day your data is suddenly lost due to the virus or deleted it, .. Wondershare Recoverit will provide you with an environment to protect important data.
Wondershare Recoverit has all the scanning processes that are divided into multiple types, from the typical recovery of the deleted files that are deleted to the recovery of missing files due...
</description></item><item><title>Download AAct Portable 4.3.3</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 19:49:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aact-portable-537.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aact-portable-537.html
</guid><description>
AAct Portable is a compact software used to activate licensed Windows similar to Kmspico. This is the latest version of AAct and is highly appreciated in activating licensed Windows today. The software is comparable to Ratiborus KMS Tools or KMSpico . AAct Portable version is mainly used to activate: Active Win 10 and Active Office 2016.
The special thing about AAct Portable is that you do not need to install .NET Framework like KMSpico above and activate 7/8/8.1/10 as well as Office...
</description></item><item><title>Download ON1 Resize AI 2026.2 v20.2.0.17850</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 19:49:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-on1-resize-2055.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-on1-resize-2055.html
</guid><description>
ON1 Resize 2019 is the edited final image when you need to zoom in the highest quality - with technology genuine Fractals® - to resize your photo to print. You can quickly change the image size without losing sharpness or detail. ON1 Resize also includes one of the fastest ways to view, remove and edit photos.
ON1 Resize - Zoom, change photo size
The features of ON1 Resize
	ON1 Resize using interpolation algorithm based on fractal - helps quickly change the image size without losing...
</description></item><item><title>Download MAGIX VEGAS Pro 23.0.0.356</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 19:48:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-magix-vegas-pro-81.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-magix-vegas-pro-81.html
</guid><description>
MAGIX VEGAS Pro provides an interface fully customizable brings maximum flexibility. Full of new features, both inside and outside, MAGIX VEGAS Pro create the power for your creativity. Whether you work in HD or 4K, VEGAS Pro willing to become a partner of your creativity. Video / Audio production, and DVD / Blu-ray authoring all in one powerful software package.
FEATURES, CHARACTERISTICS MAGIX VEGAS Pro
VEGAS Pro provides all the tools you need to edit your video quickly. Coding...
</description></item><item><title>Download Psiphon 186.20251216</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 19:47:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-psiphon-7347.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-psiphon-7347.html
</guid><description>
Psiphon is a firewall bypass tool by Psiphon Inc. Uses VPN, SSH and HTTP Proxy technology to give you uncensored access to Internet content. Your Psiphon app automatically learns about new hotspots to maximize your chances of bypassing censorship.
The way the software works is that Psiphon constantly changes the proxy, so the user's IP address is also constantly changing, the server will not detect the user's real address, so you can feel free. roof. access to websites and software...
</description></item><item><title>Download Macs Fan Control 1.5.20</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 19:47:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mac-boot-camp-fan-control-3054.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mac-boot-camp-fan-control-3054.html
</guid><description>
Mac &amp;amp; Boot Camp Fan Control is software that allows you to retrieve detailed information about the fan used to cool equipment Macintosh. As the name suggests, it can only be used on devices running Windows. You can use utility fan control when you need to optimize the sound level or heat level of the components the main system. It allows you to control fan speed directly from Windows and supports the fan from the device iMac or MacBook Pro.
Mac &amp;amp; Boot Camp Fan Control - computer...
</description></item><item><title>Download ON1 Photo RAW 2026.2 v20.2.0.17850</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 19:47:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-on1-photo-raw-1791.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-on1-photo-raw-1791.html
</guid><description>
ON1 Photo RAW 2023  includes the essential tools and features every photographer needs in their workflow. Our state-of-the-art, super-fast, non-destructive processing engine gives you an extremely smooth and efficient editing experience.
ON1 Photo RAW focuses on letting you get the most out of every photo. Photographers now have a quick photo management engine, hundreds of customizable photo effects, fast and beautiful HDR, masking and selection tools, layers and more in one app. Quickly...
</description></item><item><title>Download CoolUtils Total Image Converter 8.2.0.288</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 19:46:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-total-image-converter-848.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-total-image-converter-848.html
</guid><description>
CoolUtils Total Image Converter is software to convert images to other formats, and can edit, cut, resize and rotate them. With Total Image Converter you easy convert TIFFs into JPEGS, make photos suitable for the web or recover old photos in the supported format.
&amp;nbsp;CoolUtils Total Image Converter - convert images to other formats
Features CoolUtils Total Image Converter
	Total Image Converter supports almost all image formats
	Support convert eagle picture series.
	Total Image...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cisdem Video Converter 4.3.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 19:46:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cisdem-video-converter-9557.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cisdem-video-converter-9557.html
</guid><description>
Cisdem Video Converter is an all-in-one solution for converting video and audio files of any format, ripping DVD movies and converting online videos. The converter provides support for more than 150 audio and video file formats, and helps you download or share content with others. Cisdem Video Converter gives you the ability to make audio or video content compatible with almost any device.
Save videos and music from 1000+ hosting sites for offline viewing, including YouTube, Facebook,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Fast Screen Recorder 2.1.0.17</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 19:45:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fast-screen-recorder-7132.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fast-screen-recorder-7132.html
</guid><description>
With the Fast Screen Recorder app, you can capture any moment on your screen. Fast Screen Recorder helps capture your online conferences, meetings, tutorials, gaming moments and more. You can only record audio, video and both with or without a voice mic.
Fast Screen Recorder provides an option to enable/disable your microphone before recording begins. So you can make videos with your voice. This is useful for recording tutorials and presentations. After recording video or audio from...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sysinternals Suite 2025.12.16</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 19:40:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sysinternals-suite-1447.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sysinternals-suite-1447.html
</guid><description>
Sysinternals Suite is a software monitoring and control system helps to find and fix errors most impressive. The software includes more than seventy utilities aimed at overcoming the problem related to managing files and disks, network problems and security, as well as information about processes and systems. Because of this very rich, the analysis of each ministry will take a significant period of time and therefore, we decided to focus on the most popular.
Sysinternals Suite - Set of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Boris FX Music Studio 2025.0.3.25267</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 19:39:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-magix-samplitude-music-studio-5122.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-magix-samplitude-music-studio-5122.html
</guid><description>
MAGIX Samplitude Music Studio - Brings the vision of your music come to life. Compose, record, mix and master. Use the creative tools and workflows, object-oriented, to create the complex arrangement. Choose from a variety of audio tools needed to prepare your songs for the stage. Discover music studio Samplitude. Everything a musician needs.
This program allows you to record your own music in a professional way, from creating it to burn CDS. In a very simple interface, you can easily...
</description></item><item><title>Download Remote Desktop Manager Enterprise 2025.3.28</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 19:38:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-remote-desktop-manager-enterprise-242.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-remote-desktop-manager-enterprise-242.html
</guid><description>
Remote Desktop Manager Enterprise software is the complete management of remote connections and virtual machines from a single location, at the same time access support data online and cloud storage. Remote Desktop Manager supports multiple types of connections, not only connections for the protocol connect remote computer Remote Desktop Protocol (RDP).
Remote Desktop Manager easily add, edit, delete, share, organize and find your remote connection of you quickly. Compatible with...
</description></item><item><title>Download HTTP Toolkit 1.24.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 19:34:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-http-toolkit-6246.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-http-toolkit-6246.html
</guid><description>
HTTP Toolkit is software that provides the ability to automatically block HTTP and HTTPS traffic from most client applications, including web browsers such as Chrome and Firefox, most CLI tools and auxiliary languages such as Node.js, Python, Ruby etc. You can browse through traffic by marking the content type, status, and source or search by URL, status, and title to find important notifications.
You can check the URL, status, title, and content of each request or feedback, along with...
</description></item><item><title>Download Lyric Video Creator Professional 6.5.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 19:33:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lyric-video-creator-professional-2192.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lyric-video-creator-professional-2192.html
</guid><description>
Lyric Video Creator Professional is the professional version the most help support more lyrics on music video very suitable for those who want to evolve to create video karaoke. All what you need, please visit the news below, there is a link to download the Lyric Video Creator with key free. Interface like a the media player classic, but with optional integration responsible for creating. At first glance, you can see the preview screen where all the videos or photos that you upload will be...
</description></item><item><title>Download TubeMate Downloader 6.0.12</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 19:32:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubemate-downloader-4250.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubemate-downloader-4250.html
</guid><description>
TubeMate Downloader is a smart application that lets you download any clip you want from the website hosting the main video and convert them in when download at or then. If you need a simple and effective tool to download videos, you can give it a try. With TubeMate Downloader, you can directly drag and drop video link from your browser into the drop-down box or application window to start downloading. You don't even need to copy and paste the video URL.
TubeMate Downloader - Support...
</description></item><item><title>Download Avast Ransomware Decryption Tools 1.0.0.814</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 19:31:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avast-ransomware-decryption-tools-5371.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avast-ransomware-decryption-tools-5371.html
</guid><description>
Avast Ransomware Decryption Tools is a package of ransomware decryption tools to help you get back files from 20 different ransomware encrypted. Avast Ransomware Decryption Tools supports decryption AES_NI, Alcatraz Locker, Apocalypse, BadBlock, Bart, BTCWare, Crypt888, CryptoMix (Offline), CrySiS, EncrypTile, FindZip, Globe HiddenTear, Jigsaw, Legion NoobCrypt, Stampado, SZFLocker, TeslaCrypt, XData.
Features of Avast Ransomware Decryption Tools
	Easily remove ransomware
	Decrypt and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Pulsar Modular P42 Climax 6.2.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 19:31:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pulsar-modular-p42-climax-mod-8897.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pulsar-modular-p42-climax-mod-8897.html
</guid><description>
Pulsar Modular P42 Climax Mod is a powerful and versatile modulation module that can be used to create a wide variety of complex and evolving sounds. It is especially useful for adding movement and interest to more static patches and can be used in a variety of musical genres and styles.
It can sync many different coloring hardware devices, but never intended to clone any! With Mid/Side processing and detailed metering (peak, RMS and LUFS) and Auto. Gain compensation, the P42 fits...
</description></item><item><title>Download Windows and Office Genuine ISO Verifier 12.29.50.25</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 17:47:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-and-office-genuine-iso-verifier-542.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-and-office-genuine-iso-verifier-542.html
</guid><description>
Windows and Office Genuine ISO Verifier is a small utility used to check for Microsoft Office and Windows ISO genuine or not by carrying out verification fast SHA-1 and MD5. The software has a friendly interface with the user and not cause you any real trouble whatsoever while navigating.
Users use tool requires to specify the file input and the application will automatically perform the rest of the work. Windows and Office Genuine ISO Verifier can compare the file SHA-1 with the...
</description></item><item><title>Download AllDup 4.5.72</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 17:42:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-alldup-2023.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-alldup-2023.html
</guid><description>
AllDup is a file manager app intuitive comes with a powerful search engine to help you find and delete the duplicate files. You can copy the AllDup on any USB flash drive or any other device and carry it with you whenever you want to scan the computer to copy files. Added to that, it does not leave any traces in the Windows Registry.
AllDup - Manager and search file
The search process can be done on name, extension, size, contents, date last modified, attributes, and creation date....
</description></item><item><title>Download CyberLink PhotoDirector Ultra 2026 v17.0.1205.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 17:41:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-photodirector-ultra-129.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-photodirector-ultra-129.html
</guid><description>
Cyberlink PhotoDirector Ultra is known to be photo editing tools and videos with the effect is extremely rich, help you to change the style for the individual images or the videos of his favorite. This software integrated the 3D engine helps to speed up Video processing, which allows accessing the repository effect online and extract the Videos into the movies 3D Bru-ray, 3D AVCHD.
Cyberlink PhotoDirector Ultra to offer users a more professional tool to handle their images, remove...
</description></item></channel></rss>