<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 20:02:36 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 20:02:36 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Lansweeper 12.6.0.12</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 23:00:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lansweeper-2011.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lansweeper-2011.html
</guid><description>
Lansweeper is an application to manage IT assets and the scanning device is connected to the network. This software can scan and identify all network devices have workstation IP and Windows, Linux and Mac and indexing for them. Deep Scan Engine this software uses a set of protocols to detect and receive data from any device connected to the network. All data received can be stored in database SQL Compact or SQL Server.
Lansweeper - Scan system Internet
Software Lansweeper design open...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinMerge 2.16.52.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 22:37:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winmerge-2028.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winmerge-2028.html
</guid><description>
WinMerge is a tool to merge and distinguish open source for Windows. WinMerge can compare and folders and files, presenting differences in a visual text easy to understand or manipulate. WinMerge is very useful for determining what has changed between the version of the project and merge the changes between the versions. WinMerge can be used as a tool to compare / merge, external or as a standalone application.
In addition, Winmerge has many helpful features helps to compare, synchronize...
</description></item><item><title>Download AcaStat 11.1.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 19:59:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-acastat-14308.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-acastat-14308.html
</guid><description>
Enter data in the data tab, import and export delimited files, copy and paste or drag and drop data directly from spreadsheets. AcaStat creates frequency tables, cross-tabs, descriptive statistics, correlations, OLS and logistic regressions, t-tests, non-parametric tests, etc. Format variable labels and values, set missing values, use controls and recode variables. Includes 31 summary statistics procedures and five helper modules.
Core Statistics Procedures
	Frequency tables and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Razer Cortex 11.4.10.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 17:03:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-razer-cortex-5468.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-razer-cortex-5468.html
</guid><description>
Razer Cortex is one of the first game enhancement apps released on the market and as the name suggests, it can help you tweak the performance of your PC and game at the same time. If you're playing video games on a regular basis, then we don't need to tell you more about how FPS or a split-second delay can cost you with a round, ranked arena or a single hit. impressive headshot. The advanced graphics not only make the game more interesting, but they can sometimes determine if you can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Find.Same.Images.OK 5.84</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 17:02:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-find-same-images-ok-113.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-find-same-images-ok-113.html
</guid><description>
Find.Same.Images.OK lets find the images identical or similar in the folder of you, even if they were to rotate, change size or change.
Just select one or more folders that you want the program to scan and it will return a list of all the duplicate images or very similar, as indicated by the percent the same and the preview is built.Then, you can select images from the list and then copy, move or delete them.
Find.Same.Images.OK
In addition, there are other options smart option allows...
</description></item><item><title>Download WSCC Windows System Control Center 10.0.1.4 Commercial</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 17:01:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wscc-windows-system-control-center-1599.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wscc-windows-system-control-center-1599.html
</guid><description>
WSCC Windows System Control Center can automatically install and update the add-ons are supported. Alternatively, WSCC can use the http protocol to download and run the program. WSCC is portable device, no installation required. Extract content of zip archive downloaded into any folder on your computer.
The interface is very simple and intuitive, thus allowing any type of user how to find his way, regardless of the experience of their previous with the IT world. Besides, it includes a...
</description></item><item><title>Download Gilisoft Total Repair 11.2.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 17:00:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-total-repair-12836.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-total-repair-12836.html
</guid><description>
Total Repair Toolkit is an all-in-one system maintenance tool that integrates smart diagnosis, in-depth repair, and performance optimization. It has a one-click smart repair engine that can automatically resolve over 500 common problems such as system lag, game crashes, and file corruption. Meanwhile, it provides a professional manual repair module to meet advanced requirements.
Gilisoft Total Repair Features
	Application error repair based on a large DLL library
	In-depth diagnosis...
</description></item><item><title>Download Zoom Player Max 22.0 RC2</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 17:00:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zoom-player-max-104.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zoom-player-max-104.html
</guid><description>
Zoom Player MAX help you to see the film on DVD, Blu-ray, Flash movies and HD format with high quality and the ability to display subtitles in English very well. The advantage of software is that takes up very little system resources to play the movie with quick speed, change the wallpaper options while viewing movies.
Zoom Player MAX is the movies, browse high-quality photos on the computer with the advantages such as compact size, quick start, built-in codec. The application supports...
</description></item><item><title>Download MusConv 4.10.434 Lifetime</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 17:00:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html
</guid><description>
MusConv transfers playlists, albums, followed artists and liked songs across a variety of services – Spotify, Apple Music, Amazon Music, YouTube, YouTube Music, iTunes, Deezer, Tidal, SoundCloud, Pandora and more 125 music services!
Features of MusConv Ultimate
	Transfer playlists, albums, followed artists and liked tracks between over 125 music servicesManage playlists (Delete, Merge, Split, Copy...)
	More than 125 music services supported
	Access DAILY updated music charts on...
</description></item><item><title>Download Minimal Firewall 2.6.4</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 16:59:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minimal-firewall-13877.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minimal-firewall-13877.html
</guid><description>
Minimal Firewall works in conjunction with Windows Firewall to block all unknown connections by default, prompting you to create application-based rules to mitigate malware, telemetry, and data leaks. Completely eliminate applications that call home without your knowledge. Minimal Firewall provides a more secure and integrated approach by interacting directly with the native Windows Firewall, eliminating the need for risky system modifications.
Core Features
	Lockdown Mode: The core...
</description></item><item><title>Download Native Instruments Traktor Pro 4.4.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 16:59:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-traktor-pro-220.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-traktor-pro-220.html
</guid><description>
Traktor PRO is the professional DJ software is the world's top DJS trust, and is designed to handle even the biggest clubs. Traktor PRO is integrated with filter, EQ and studio quality effects, with flexible operation , functions intuitive controls and mark automatically matching with the DJ of all styles and levels of experience.
Now, with TRAKTOR PRO 3 new tools for sculpting sound, quality sound our best, and clear interface of our best to date - so you can play whatever you want,...
</description></item><item><title>Download IK Multimedia Tonex Max 1.10.5</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 16:58:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ik-multimedia-tonex-max-7877.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ik-multimedia-tonex-max-7877.html
</guid><description>
TONEX software uses groundbreaking AI Machine Modeling technology to let you model the sound of any amp, cabinet, or combo and turn it into a plug-in, all with precision sounds are almost indistinguishable from reality. You can instantly play up to the more than 1,000 already available Melody Models along with browsing, performing, and downloading more and more Melody Models available on TONEX in ToneNET.
Features of IK Multimedia Tonex Max
	Modeled tone generator, player,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sure Cuts A Lot Pro 6.079</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 16:58:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sure-cuts-a-lot-pro-2614.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sure-cuts-a-lot-pro-2614.html
</guid><description>
Sure Cuts A Lot Pro is this program offers you a set of drawing tools and you get a work environment, comprehensive, where you can create interesting shapes and cut them by a special electronic. The intelligent combination of fonts OpenType and TrueType in your system, in conjunction with the library program rich text, photos, and other input, will help you create everything you can imagine.
This app is compatible with hundreds of font style and provide support for various cutting...
</description></item><item><title>Download HTML5Point 4.1.72</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 16:57:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-html5point-5610.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-html5point-5610.html
</guid><description>
HTML5Point is the world's first PowerPoint to HTML5 converter that allows you to convert your PowerPoint presentation into interactive HTML5 content that can be viewed on iPad, iPhone, other mobile devices and on all modern browsers all in one click.
HTML5Point converts your PowerPoint content correctly into HTML5 preserving all animations, transitions, and other special effects associated with the original PowerPoint presentation. Developing an e-Learning package with support on all...
</description></item><item><title>Download ColorCatcher 4.7</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 16:57:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-colorcatcher-14269.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-colorcatcher-14269.html
</guid><description>
ColorCatcher is a small but powerful free Windows program that allows you to extract colors from your screen using the built-in magnifier and save them to your own color lists, which are easy to edit. Moreover, you can use ColorCatcher as a portable program, for example on a USB drive. This way you can take your color list with you.
ColorCatcher's Highlight Features
	ColorCatcher can copy colors as Hex, Decimal, RGB, HSV or Integer values ​​and save them to a stack for later...
</description></item><item><title>Download Telegram for Desktop 6.3.4</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 16:56:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-telegram-3376.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-telegram-3376.html
</guid><description>
Telegram is an instant messaging service and voice over IP services on the cloud platform. Client application Telegram is available for Android, iOS, Windows Phone, Windows NT, macOS, and Linux. Users can send messages and exchange photos, videos, stickers, audio and files of any kind.
Telegram - Messaging and free phone calls
Telegram seamless sync across all your devices and can be used on desktop, tablet and phone. You can send unlimited amount of messages, photos, videos and files...
</description></item><item><title>Download Steinberg SpectraLayers Pro 12.0.40</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 16:56:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-steinberg-spectralayers-pro-2045.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-steinberg-spectralayers-pro-2045.html
</guid><description>
Steinberg SpectraLayers Pro is a new approach to audio editing, with the new concept to change the way you work. The first time you can directly edit the data spectrum, open to the world advanced audio and the use of innovative enhancements to the traditional techniques. With SpectraLayers Pro you will visualise sound in new ways incredible, including 3D. Work with the distribution like them is the music. Integration of this capability into your DAW and other tools. And all in a familiar...
</description></item><item><title>Download PTE AV Studio Pro 11.0.19 Build 3</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 16:55:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pte-av-studio-pro-2899.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pte-av-studio-pro-2899.html
</guid><description>
PTE AV Studio Pro is software for processing video professional, allowing for enthusiasts and creative professionals the max with advanced features. Create slideshows professional photo in PTE AV Studio. Add photos, video clips and music. Use Keyframe animations and Slide Slide. Editing audio clips in view mode the time Line. Output for PC, HD video and 4K, mobile devices.
Sound editor
Edit sound clip: fade in / out, start time, duration, fading cross.
Adjust the color
Adjust...
</description></item><item><title>Download AnyTrans for iOS 8.9.13.20251126</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 16:54:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anytrans-for-ios-755.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anytrans-for-ios-755.html
</guid><description>
AnyTrans for iOS is content manager essential fully managed iPhone, Android and content of your cloud. Including all mobile devices, all cloud drives from your iPhone, iPad, iPod touch to phones and tablets. From local disk to cloud storage. AnyTrans has protected them all, providing you convenient management for all data and your files, regardless of whether they are stored where.
AnyTrans is the one stop solution to meet all the management needs of your data. For the first time, you can...
</description></item><item><title>Download CapCut PC 7.5.0.3053 / 7.6.0.3105 Beta 5</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 16:54:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capcut-pc-9995.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capcut-pc-9995.html
</guid><description>
CapCut PC is a simple video editing tool that you can freely use anywhere. You can create videos on your browser, desktop and laptop, or on your phone. Versatile editing, magical AI tools, team collaboration, and built-in assets. Create videos in a whole new way.
You can edit videos based on editing the timeline, in the process you can add different elements and effects to the video to give the best effect to your work. It is a simple and intuitive set of editing tools and effects that...
</description></item><item><title>Download Visual Studio Code 1.106.3</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 16:53:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-visual-studio-code-3182.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-visual-studio-code-3182.html
</guid><description>
Visual Studio Code is the encryption tool of Microsoft has met most of the needs of the developer. Environment this encoding was introduced to compete with other products such as Sublime and Nodepad ++ . Microsoft, in its new product, has not been released in many years, has provided many features in a simple environment. In addition to the familiar with a dozen programming languages, the syntax and get to know coding language as soon as be encrypted and allows for syntax highlighting, it...
</description></item><item><title>Download VovSoft Sound Recorder 3.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 16:53:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-sound-recorder-10245.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-sound-recorder-10245.html
</guid><description>
VovSoft Sound Recorder helps you record sound from an input device (microphone) and from an output device (loop recording) by leveraging WASAPI. It is made to quickly capture the microphone or sound emitted by your desktop or laptop even if you don't connect any speakers.
Features of VovSoft Sound Recorder
	Save full record
	Save the silent trimmed recording
	Save split record
</description></item><item><title>Download VoiceAgent 1.0.20</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 16:52:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-voiceagent-13701.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-voiceagent-13701.html
</guid><description>
Turn your voice into text instantly anywhere on your PC. Voiceagent runs 100% locally, transcribes your voice in real-time and pastes directly at your cursor position. Seamless voice-to-text conversion in just 3 steps. Just tap, speak, and your words appear—no setup, no hassle.
Key Features
	Activate Voiceagent: Press Ctrl+Space + left click to activate.
	Speak freely and our AI will understand context, punctuation, and technical terms accurately.
	Text appears instantly: Your words...
</description></item><item><title>Download Eltima CloudMounter 3.4.2096</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 16:52:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-eltima-cloudmounter-6553.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-eltima-cloudmounter-6553.html
</guid><description>
Eltima CloudMounter is a reliable system utility that allows mounting various cloud storages and web servers to your personal computer as a local disk . Connect to Microsoft OneDrive, Google Drive, Amazon S3, Dropbox, FTP, and WebDAV servers in Finder, just as if they were on your machine.
Eltima CloudMounter Features
	Mapping cloud storage as a network drive to manage files online the same way you manage files locally.
	Access the clouds easily with CloudMounter
	You can mount...
</description></item><item><title>Download PC Timer 18.40</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 16:52:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pc-timer-7519.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pc-timer-7519.html
</guid><description>
PC Timer is a simple tool to automatically shut down, log out, restart or lock your PC based on your scheduled time. A handy feature of the app is its ability to prevent unauthorized cancellation of a scheduled task. To do so, PC Timer .NET allows you to set a password that the user must provide to cancel the operation.
The advantage of the application is its simplicity, small footprint on the system and the fact that it does not require installation. Thanks to the ability to set tasks...
</description></item></channel></rss>