<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 05:33:45 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 05:33:45 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Calibre 8.16.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 00:24:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-calibre-1669.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-calibre-1669.html
</guid><description>
Calibre  is an eBook library management application that allows you to manage your eBook collection, convert eBooks between different formats, Sync with popular e-reading devices and read your e-books with included viewer. You can sort books by author, title, date and other details, download meta information and book covers, add personalized tags and comments, and view your images in the cover display.
Collection of essential tools for adding metadata editing books or managing your...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinSetView 3.1.6</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 00:22:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winsetview-8971.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winsetview-8971.html
</guid><description>
WinSetView is a tool that allows you to easily set File Explorer's default folder view (including disabling grouping everywhere if desired). It works by setting registry values that File Explorer already supports. It does not modify Explorer or add any tasks or services.
Features of WinSetView
	Is a portabe application. That is, it requires no installation (just unzip and run) and it saves its settings in an INI file with the application. So you can easily run it from a flash drive or...
</description></item><item><title>Download PeaZip 10.8.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 00:21:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-peazip-1800.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-peazip-1800.html
</guid><description>
PeaZip is an Archive Utility And Compressed open-source, support multiple compression formats. It lets you create 7Z, ARC, BZ2, GZ, PAQ / ZPAQ, PEA, QUAD / BALZ, TAR, UPX, and ZIP, and enables you to open and extract 133 format additional storage, including RAR. PeaZip has the ability to open and extract over 150 file formats compressed downloads, have the ability to create and switch between multiple file formats, different background on an interface intuitive and easy to use. In...
</description></item><item><title>Download PrivaZer 4.0.115</title><pubDate> Sun, 07 Dec 2025 00:20:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-privazer-66.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-privazer-66.html
</guid><description>
PrivaZer : the program performs the scan is very thorough not only includes the trace downloads like registration, Internet history, cookies, etc but also find the traces of potential in the field of free disk space of you. PrivaZer can permanently delete all traces by using the method of secure erase and also re-establish the sector disk free to 0 to remove all traces from the delete operation earlier. The process of scanning and cleaning the original can spend less time (20-30 minutes),...
</description></item><item><title>Download OBS Studio 32.0.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Dec 2025 17:15:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-open-broadcaster-software-2451.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-open-broadcaster-software-2451.html
</guid><description>
Open Broadcaster Software is abbreviated as OBS is a program to detect the type of multimedia content to the internet. It is worth noting that a simple interface and the presence of a good tool. You can adjust the quality of the audio and video before starting the broadcast, you can specify the URL, choose the resolution of the screen, etc. With strong desire, videos which you found can be saved to your hard drive.
Open Broadcaster Software - LiveStream on PC
The basic features of Open...
</description></item><item><title>Download CapCut PC 7.6.0.3123</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Dec 2025 17:14:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capcut-pc-9995.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capcut-pc-9995.html
</guid><description>
CapCut PC is a simple video editing tool that you can freely use anywhere. You can create videos on your browser, desktop and laptop, or on your phone. Versatile editing, magical AI tools, team collaboration, and built-in assets. Create videos in a whole new way.
You can edit videos based on editing the timeline, in the process you can add different elements and effects to the video to give the best effect to your work. It is a simple and intuitive set of editing tools and effects that...
</description></item><item><title>Download JRiver Media Center 35.0.27</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Dec 2025 17:13:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jriver-media-center-110.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jriver-media-center-110.html
</guid><description>
JRiver Media Center can help you strictly manage all your files media and enjoy them in a completely new way. Launching the application for the first time, users will be immediately impressed with the intuitive and eye-catching interface with many interesting features to explore. Most people who have used JRiver Media Center evaluate that the software interface design is youthful and modern.
The software for arranging cover art of music files is also extremely neat, especially Insert...
</description></item><item><title>Download Dont Sleep 9.93</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Dec 2025 17:13:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dont-sleep-89.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dont-sleep-89.html
</guid><description>
Don't Sleep allows you can set the date and custom time that you want to reactivate the feature manager usual sources or you can set a countdown fast to pause the power management in X hours.
Can temporarily disable the protection of your screen or off your computer at a certain time.
The main features of the Dont Sleep:
- Optimal power supply for computer
- Installation time power source according to
- Prevent computer reboot
Content update Dont Sleep 5.66:
The official website...
</description></item><item><title>Download Blank And Secure 8.23</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Dec 2025 17:12:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blank-and-secure-2934.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blank-and-secure-2934.html
</guid><description>
Blank And Secure is a application lightweight and portable allows you to completely erase your sensitive data without possibility to restore. This add-on accomplish this by overwriting your files with zeros (0) before you delete them. This method is also called "zeroing data / drives". You should know that once completed, the complete data can't be recovered, so you should only use this tool if you want to permanently delete your files.
Blank And Secure - Delete data permanently
Blank...
</description></item><item><title>Download Telegram for Desktop 6.3.6</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Dec 2025 17:12:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-telegram-3376.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-telegram-3376.html
</guid><description>
Telegram is an instant messaging service and voice over IP services on the cloud platform. Client application Telegram is available for Android, iOS, Windows Phone, Windows NT, macOS, and Linux. Users can send messages and exchange photos, videos, stickers, audio and files of any kind.
Telegram - Messaging and free phone calls
Telegram seamless sync across all your devices and can be used on desktop, tablet and phone. You can send unlimited amount of messages, photos, videos and files...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ocenaudio 3.16.5</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Dec 2025 17:11:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ocenaudio-837.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ocenaudio-837.html
</guid><description>
Ocenaudio: software for windows, this is the sound editing easy, fast and powerful. ocenaudio is a program for audio editing multi-platform, easy to use, fast and functional. This is the ideal software for those who need to edit and analyze audio files.
Ocenaudio - editor powerful audio for windows
This software is based on Ocen Framework , a powerful library developed to simplify and standardize the development of application analysis and sound processing on many platforms.
Features...
</description></item><item><title>Download GoodSync Enterprise 12.9.18.8</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Dec 2025 17:11:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-goodsync-enterprise-163.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-goodsync-enterprise-163.html
</guid><description>
GoodSync Enterprise is a software that saves files and files easily and is reliable. It automatically analyts, synchronize and backup your email, family photos, contacts, MP3, financial documentation and other important files-between desktop computers, laptops, servers, external drives and Windows Mobile devices as well as remotely via FTP , SFTP, WebDAV and more. The GoodSync synchronized software combines bulletproof reliability with an extremely easy interface to compare, synchronize...
</description></item><item><title>Download reaConverter Pro 8.0.165</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Dec 2025 17:11:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html
</guid><description>
reaConverter Pro is software image processing feature with batch conversion and image editing periodically becomes simple. eaConverter also provide command line utilities allow you to process images automatically, thus helping you shorten the time for other work.
reaConverter Pro integrated powerful tool of Uber with many great features. It provides advanced solutions to process and adjust images. Management of the conversion process the base image with the latest version of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Any Video Downloader Pro 10.0.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Dec 2025 17:10:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-video-downloader-pro-3731.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-video-downloader-pro-3731.html
</guid><description>
Any Video Downloader Pro is software support you can download video HD 720p, 1080p, 2K, 4K and 8K from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion, Vimeo, Metacafe and thousands of video sharing sites, other. It is a tool to speed up multi-threading can speed up your download faster up to 5 times. This helpful program support download at the same time. Any Video Downloader Pro lets you download multiple videos at the same time. Moreover, it allows you to pause and resume downloads if you need more...
</description></item><item><title>Download 4KSoftware 4K Downloader 6.0.10</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Dec 2025 17:10:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-downloader-3858.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-downloader-3858.html
</guid><description>
4K Downloader is a Windows application small but powerful to download and convert video in 4K and 8K Ultra HD from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion and thousands of other video-based websites. It speeds up your download by up to 5 times. Consider that most smart phones, TVS, computers, and tablets all support the high definition format, don't be surprised when many users want to enjoy quality content on their device. 4K Downloader is a lightweight software designed to help you grab videos...
</description></item><item><title>Download Syncovery Premium 11.11.4.134</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Dec 2025 17:09:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncovery-pro-enterprise-232.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncovery-pro-enterprise-232.html
</guid><description>
Syncovery Pro Enterprise is a great application used to back up data and to synchronize personal computers, servers, laptops, notepads and storage online. The software comes with support for FTP and secure FTP servers, SSH, WebDAV, Amazon S3, http, update the part file, ZIP compression, data encryption, and schedule automatic backups.
Syncovery Pro Enterprise have the ability to freely select files and folders across the whole folder hierarchy in tree view and supports email...
</description></item><item><title>Download Windhawk 1.7</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Dec 2025 17:09:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windhawk-10622.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windhawk-10622.html
</guid><description>
Windhawk aims to make customizing Windows programs easier. It allows installing and configuring mods (custom modules) in just a few clicks. For developers, it provides a convenient platform to develop and share such mods.
Another benefit for users is that each mod is just a text code file. This makes it easy to review what the mod actually does, unlike an executable which is difficult to verify. And that doesn't affect the user experience – installing a mod takes just a few clicks,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Patch My PC 5.4.1.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Dec 2025 17:09:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-patch-my-pc-3748.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-patch-my-pc-3748.html
</guid><description>
Patch My PC is a comprehensive application and reliable will provide the simple solution for managing patch party Tuesday. The category Enterprise SCUP will provide an incentive simple and unique about the updates and the application updates of the Tuesday easy and updated. The update application can be easily installed on your computer in a few minutes, through the function software updates are integrated into The configuration manager center system MS. No additional agent or server...
</description></item><item><title>Download XL-Connector 3.6.34.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Dec 2025 17:08:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xl-connector-12415.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xl-connector-12415.html
</guid><description>
XL-Connector is a popular plugin that securely integrates Excel and Salesforce to export, import, refresh and transform data seamlessly with ultra-fast api connection. It provides Salesforce administrators with a comprehensive toolbox that easily performs data and metadata management activities in a familiar Excel environment.
Features
Export from Salesforce to Excel
	Get data from existing Salesforce reports or build your own SOQL queries directly into Excel.
Import data into...
</description></item><item><title>Download UltFone Windows Data Recovery 10.6.7.16</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Dec 2025 17:08:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ultfone-windows-data-recovery-14195.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ultfone-windows-data-recovery-14195.html
</guid><description>
UltFone Windows Data Recovery is a comprehensive data recovery software designed for Windows system to recover lost or deleted files from various storage devices such as hard drive, USB drive, SD card, etc. The software supports recovering many file types, including photos, videos, documents, music and archive files. The software offers two scanning modes—quick scan for recently deleted files and deep scan for comprehensive recovery, and also allows users to preview recoverable files...
</description></item><item><title>Download Serato Sample 2.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Dec 2025 17:07:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-serato-sample-5811.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-serato-sample-5811.html
</guid><description>
Serato Sample is the fastest way to sample audio. A powerful and intuitive new sampling plugin for maker that lets you quickly find, crop, change keys, and time-stretching patterns. Serato Sample gives you the best time stretching quality on the market. Serato Sample will work in most DAWs that support additional AU / VST * including Ableton Live, FL Studio, Logic Pro and Maschine.
New feature of Serato Sample
software
	Adjust the beatgrids so they are perfectly timed
	Flick through...
</description></item><item><title>Download gSyncing 1.1.72</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Dec 2025 17:07:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gsyncing-10173.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gsyncing-10173.html
</guid><description>
gSyncing allows you to synchronize your contacts, calendar, and Outlook tasks with your Google account and other supported services such as smartphones and tablets runs on iOS, Android, Windows Phone, etc. For example, sync Outlook calendar with Google calendar. You can easily use your Gmail account while traveling and then continue using Outlook on your desktop. Syncing your Google contacts with Outlook helps you access and manage your contacts on any device.
The program runs on...
</description></item><item><title>Download Social Media Downloader 8.0.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Dec 2025 17:06:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-socialmediaapps-facebook-video-downloader-3742.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-socialmediaapps-facebook-video-downloader-3742.html
</guid><description>
SocialVideo Downloader (formerly SocialMediaApps Facebook Video Downloader) is a Windows application to download and convert your favorite videos from Facebook and hundreds of other video sharing sites. It increases your loading speed by up to 500%, or even more! The application has a simple and intuitive user interface, its main functions and features are quite obvious to anyone. , regardless of prior experience with similar purpose tools.
&amp;nbsp;
SocialVideo Downloader
The main...
</description></item><item><title>Download JPEG Saver 5.44</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Dec 2025 17:06:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jpeg-saver-4333.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jpeg-saver-4333.html
</guid><description>
JPEG Saver is a display image screen saver allows you to display photos of his favorite form saver Windows screen with the transition effect different. Program JPEG Saver provides many configuration options allow you to customize how to display his image and in what order they are displayed. You can select multiple folder location as the source for pictures, screensavers, and more control images are displayed by setting custom filters based on file name, date and other criteria.
JPEG...
</description></item><item><title>Download PentaLogix CAMMaster 11.24.71</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Dec 2025 17:05:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pentalogix-cammaster-5559.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pentalogix-cammaster-5559.html
</guid><description>
CAMMaster Designer is CAM software of choice by the Designer for the most demanding jobs. Experience the industry's best CAD companion to get your work done. The disinfection process is fast with all the features available in this package. Exploiting Netlist and DRC sets industry standards. Basically, CamMaster provides many functions depending on the relevant needs of the user. It also provides nearly five free technical support. Furthermore, net list comparison and class comparison make...
</description></item></channel></rss>