<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 19:59:44 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 19:59:44 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Wise Folder Hider Pro 5.0.9.239</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 19:57:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wise-folder-hider-432.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wise-folder-hider-432.html
</guid><description>
Wise Folder Hider is software file protection allows users to encrypt, put a password, hide file on the hard drive.  Wise Folder Hider will is perfect software to protect data files on your system. When using this software you complete peace of mind with important files by themselves do not leak out, and anyone who uses your computer also can't know these hidden files that of you.
Wise Folder Hider offers users the ability to hide files, folders on the hard drive so that other people...
</description></item><item><title>Download EaseUS BitWiper Pro 2.2.1 Build 2508141316</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 19:56:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-bitwiper-pro-11594.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-bitwiper-pro-11594.html
</guid><description>
EaseUS BitWiper Pro is an application that helps users delete data securely and completely unrecoverable. Designed with a simple and easy-to-use interface, this is a useful tool for erasing especially important data before selling, reusing or exchanging electronic devices.
	A secure tool to erase sensitive data from your Windows hard drive.
	Permanently delete files, entire disk or an individual partition.
	Save time with this high-speed data destruction software.
	Providing erasing...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare UniConverter Portable 16.5.9.323</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 19:56:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-uniconverter-portable-12162.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-uniconverter-portable-12162.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare UniConverter Portable - a portable version (unofficial), formerly known as Wondershare Video Converter Ultimate, is a comprehensive media conversion software developed by Wondershare. It offers a wide range of features to convert, edit and enhance multimedia files. Convert, download, compress, edit, record videos in 1000 formats and do more.
With this comprehensive program, you can customize your home movies through advanced editing features and get professional work in...
</description></item><item><title>Download Apowersoft Video Download Capture 6.6.0.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 19:55:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-apowersoft-video-download-capture-1556.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-apowersoft-video-download-capture-1556.html
</guid><description>
Apowersoft Video Download Capture is a comprehensive tool with advanced technologies for media streaming to choice cost-effective to download videos from YouTube, Dailymotion, Vimeo, Yahoo Screen and Hulu, as well as millions of other websites. Apowersoft Video Download Capture is your download video powerful and effective this can download and save videos, movies, tv episodes and music videos online. It also has the switch function, supports convert any video to MP4, AVI, MKV, WMV and the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Lazesoft Windows Recovery 5.0.1.1 Unlimited / Professional / Server Edition</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 19:54:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lazesoft-windows-recovery-6247.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lazesoft-windows-recovery-6247.html
</guid><description>
Lazesoft Windows Recovery  is a software that Fixes all Windows startup problems and problems including boot error, virus infection, blue / black screen etc. Lazesoft Windows Recovery provides home and business users complete solutions to troubleshoot boot-up problems, retrieve valuable files, Partition Recovery, and more. With its easy-to-use interface, you can use Lazesoft Windows Recovery to fix boot problems yourself without reinstalling your Windows. No technical background is...
</description></item><item><title>Download Reg Organizer Portable 9.80</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 19:54:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reg-organizer-portable-3534.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reg-organizer-portable-3534.html
</guid><description>
Reg Organizer Portable is a software solution that allows you to enhance the operational capabilities of the computer by cleaning and defragmenting the key registry of Windows, uninstall the program little or no need to use fix a bug in the system. Review ability to optimize the registry, Reg Organizer Portable feature support automatically shutdown computer after complete the task. In process handling and cleaning systems, you will not be able to open, disposal the manipulate on other...
</description></item><item><title>Download MedCalc 23.3.5</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 19:53:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-medcalc-1536.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-medcalc-1536.html
</guid><description>
MedCalc is a statistical software for biomedical research can analyze many performance curve system with a set of rich functionality, chart types and advanced module. MedCalc was designed to meet the needs and requirements of the study nature and aims to analyze the statistical calculations of the project. This software provides the tools and means essential to analyze the characteristic curve of the system (ROC), drawing data and perform the statistical calculations.
MedCalc -...
</description></item><item><title>Download Lazesoft Disk Image and Clone Professional 5.0.1.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 19:53:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lazesoft-disk-image-and-clone-professional-6487.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lazesoft-disk-image-and-clone-professional-6487.html
</guid><description>
Lazesoft Disk Image and Clone is the software that replices your hard disk, backup or restoring your hard disk when offline is easy and safe. Lazesoft Disk Image and Clone can be used for backup, hard disk upgrades or disk replication purposes. With Lazesoft Disk Image and Clone, copy/copy the entire disc including Windows, program, file, and personal settings to the new disk/partition in just a few clicks. Never need to reinstall Windows and programs.
Features of Lazesoft Disk Image...
</description></item><item><title>Download Lazesoft Disk Image and Clone Server 5.0.1.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 19:53:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lazesoft-disk-image-and-clone-server-6488.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lazesoft-disk-image-and-clone-server-6488.html
</guid><description>
Lazesoft Disk Image and Clone  is a software that copies your entire hard disk, backs up or restores your hard disk offline easily and safely. Lazesoft Disk Image and Clone can be used for backup, hard disk upgrade or disk cloning purposes. With Lazesoft Disk Image and Clone, Copy / copy entire disk including Windows, programs, files and personal settings to new disk / partition in just a few clicks. Never need to reinstall Windows and programs.
Features of Lazesoft Disk Image and...
</description></item><item><title>Download BluffTitler Portable 16.7.7</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 19:52:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blufftitler-ultimate-portable-3494.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blufftitler-ultimate-portable-3494.html
</guid><description>
BluffTitler Ultimate Portable is a simple application and efficient to create, export and playback of video effects 3D. With this program you can easily create titles and 3D text beautifully and add them to your video. It does not require developing specialized software to do the hard work . In a graphical environment, simple, choose from many different patterns and provide the final output by adjusting and editing it. In this program, you can use various effects such as gold text, small...
</description></item><item><title>Download XYplorer Portable 27.10.0500</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 19:51:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-portable-12066.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-portable-12066.html
</guid><description>
XYplorer Portable is a file management software application that provides a comprehensive set of features for organizing and managing files and folders on your computer. This is a portable version of XYplorer that you can run directly from a portable storage device, such as a USB drive, without installation.
XYplorer Portable Features
	File Management: XYplorer Portable provides a two-window interface, allowing you to view and work with two folders at the same time. It provides easy...
</description></item><item><title>Download XMind Portable 2025 v25.07.03033</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 19:50:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xmind-zen-1529.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xmind-zen-1529.html
</guid><description>
XMind ZEN is a great app to create mind maps. When you think about the idea or your team in a specific topic you caught the idea, information, data and clues in your mind. Software XMind is designed to collect scattered information in a central location and then processed and summarized them later. This software allows you to automatically save and coordinate the mental map under file format / online and it's easy to imagine the security of your data.
XMind ZEN - Set-mapping
The...
</description></item><item><title>Download Lazesoft Recovery Suite Professional 5.0.0.1 / Server / Unlimited</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 19:49:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lazesoft-recovery-suite-6251.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lazesoft-recovery-suite-6251.html
</guid><description>
Lazesoft Recovery Suite is the toolkit that helps to restore data, systems, Windows passwords quickly and easily. Do you want to restore your data or system when Windows does not start normal? Use Lazesoft Recovery Suite, with only three simple steps to restore your data, fix the Windows system or reset the Windows password.
Features of Lazesoft Recovery Suite
	Support all server and computer brands such as Dell, HP, IBM, etc.
	Comprehensive recovery environments based on WinPE and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Lazesoft Recover My Password Professional 5.0.1.1 / Server / Unlimited</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 19:47:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lazesoft-recover-my-password-6250.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lazesoft-recover-my-password-6250.html
</guid><description>
Lazesoft Recover My Password  is software that helps you to reset your admin password to blank, then you can login your administrator account with blank password. . If you forget the Administrator's password, or the Administrator's user account has been locked or disabled, you cannot gain access to the account. However, you can burn a Lazesoft Recover My Password CD or a USB flash drive and boot from there to remove the Administrator's password and unlock the user account.
Features of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Minimal Firewall 2.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 19:15:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minimal-firewall-13877.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minimal-firewall-13877.html
</guid><description>
Minimal Firewall works in conjunction with Windows Firewall to block all unknown connections by default, prompting you to create application-based rules to mitigate malware, telemetry, and data leaks. Completely eliminate applications that call home without your knowledge. Minimal Firewall provides a more secure and integrated approach by interacting directly with the native Windows Firewall, eliminating the need for risky system modifications.
Core Features
	Lockdown Mode: The core...
</description></item><item><title>Download Carly - OBD2 car scanner 49.58</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 19:09:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-carly-obd2-car-scanner-8278.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-carly-obd2-car-scanner-8278.html
</guid><description>
Carly is a mobile OBD2 (On-Board Diagnostics) car scanner application that allows users to diagnose, monitor and repair their vehicles. The application works by connecting to the vehicle's OBD2 port, usually located under the dashboard, and collecting data from the vehicle's computer system. The adapter and app work with Audi, BMW, Lexus, Mercedes, Mini, Porsche, Renault, Seat, Skoda, Toyota, VW and most car brands in the world with OBD2 port.
Carly - OBD2 car scanner Features
Check...
</description></item><item><title>Download JPEG Image Compressor &amp;amp; Resize 2.4</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 19:09:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-jpeg-image-compressor-resize-13175.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-jpeg-image-compressor-resize-13175.html
</guid><description>
Want to quickly and batch resize your photos, but also want to change the aspect ratio with a photo resizer? Download now to reduce photo size in seconds without losing quality. Do you have hundreds of photos? Don't worry, our batch photo resizer supports batch photo resizing. Moreover, our free photo resizer app also has an advanced jpg, png, heic converter that will save you a lot of time needed to convert photo formats online. Whether you are a photographer, social media content...
</description></item><item><title>Download PowerDirector - Video Editor 15.6.0 build 2508131</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 19:09:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-powerdirector-video-editor-8123.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-powerdirector-video-editor-8123.html
</guid><description>
PowerDirector APK - Video Editor (Unlocked Version) is video editing software developed by CyberLink. It is available for Windows and Android devices. If you are looking for the Android version of PowerDirector, you can download the APK (Android Package Kit) file from the Google Play Store or from taiwebs.com.
Features of PowerDirector APK - Unlocked Version:
	Easy-to-use interface: PowerDirector has a user-friendly interface that makes it easy to edit and create videos, even if...
</description></item><item><title>Download ChatBox: AI Chat Bot Assistant 1.68.6</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 19:08:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-chatbox-ai-chat-bot-assistant-12995.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-chatbox-ai-chat-bot-assistant-12995.html
</guid><description>
ChatBox is an advanced AI chat application and your virtual assistant built on the most advanced AI chat models. Designed to seamlessly integrate into your daily life, this AI chatbot uses advanced machine learning to improve productivity and provide instant solutions. Whether you're looking for help with a task or need answers to complex questions, your AI chatbot will leverage the latest advances in AI chat to help.
Some Highlights
	ChatBox leverages the latest AI technology to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Duolingo: language lessons 6.43.3</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 19:08:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-duolingo-language-lessons-8265.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-duolingo-language-lessons-8265.html
</guid><description>
Duolingo is a popular language learning app that offers interactive lessons to help users learn new languages. This application offers many languages for you to choose from, including Spanish, French, German, Italian, Portuguese, Chinese, Japanese and many more.
This app offers an gamified learning experience with interactive lessons, exercises, and quizzes designed to help users learn new words, phrases, and grammar rules. This app is designed to be easy to use and suitable for people...
</description></item><item><title>Download Background Video Recorder (BVR) 1.7.6</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 19:08:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-background-video-recorder-bvr-12923.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-background-video-recorder-bvr-12923.html
</guid><description>
HD Background Video Recorder (BVR) is a special camera app that helps you record videos in background camera mode with or without preview and unlimited recording time. With many useful functions such as continue recording when the screen is off or schedule recording.
Key features
	Unlimited number of video recordings.
	Record videos with or without preview.
	Support video recording with front or rear camera
	One touch to start/stop recording.
	Turn off the screen and continue...
</description></item><item><title>Download CamSam PLUS 3.9.5</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 19:07:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-camsam-plus-11110.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-camsam-plus-11110.html
</guid><description>
Camsam Plus the Speed ​​and Red Light Camera Warning System! With Camsam Plus You Receive Editorially Verified Speedcam Alerts in Real Time. More than 5 million participants worldwide report Daily on Newly Discovered Speedcams.
Overview of Functions
	Real Time Alerts of Mobile Radar Traps
	More than 60,000 Fixed Speedcams Worldwide from SCDB.Info
	Directional alerts for all fixed speedcams
	speed camera map
	Automatic Updates Every 5 Minutes
	Visual and Acoustic...
</description></item><item><title>Download GPS Camera Photo and Video Map 2.1.4</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 19:07:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-gps-camera-photo-and-video-map-13645.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-gps-camera-photo-and-video-map-13645.html
</guid><description>
In case you are looking for a mobile app for Time Stamp Camera Free that is flexible and suitable for professionals as well as explorers and field workers then this is the best tool for you.
With amazing features like timestamp gps camera and weather overlay images become powerful geo-documented records. With camera stamp free app everything is possible. For all the photos on your website, capture them easily with advanced GPS camera and photo timestamp functions. Now all your data is...
</description></item><item><title>Download Battery Guru: Battery Info 2.3.24 build 619</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 19:07:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-battery-guru-battery-health-8651.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-battery-guru-battery-health-8651.html
</guid><description>
Battery Guru displays battery usage information, measures battery capacity (mAh), shows estimates, and helps you change your charging habits with helpful tips to extend battery life and increase battery life up 200%.
Features of Battery Guru for Android
	Batteries have a limited lifespan, each time you charge your device, the battery wears out, reducing its total (design) capacity.
	Now you can reduce wear and tear, spend less time tethering your device to the charger, and get the...
</description></item><item><title>Download AccuWeather: Weather Radar 21.1.1-3-rc</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 19:07:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-accuweather-weather-radar-8893.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-accuweather-weather-radar-8893.html
</guid><description>
Weather warnings from AccuWeather are exceptionally accurate. Whether it's windy, sunny or rainy, you can stay one step ahead with AccuWeather weather radar. Be prepared for daily forecasts or sudden changes in weather with live alerts and accurate weather forecasts. Daily weather snapshots provide storm warnings, weather updates and RealFeel Temperature®, helping to predict today's weather.
With AccuWeather's superior accuracy™ for local forecasts, you'll never miss a memorable...
</description></item></channel></rss>