<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 01:37:33 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 01:37:33 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download EaseUS ClipAce (ScreenShot) 1.7.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 10 Sep 2025 01:08:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-screenshot-7937.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-screenshot-7937.html
</guid><description>
Capture everything on your screen easily through this tool, EaseUS ScreenShot provides users with a powerful set of screen capture tools to meet all their needs. The app is easy to start and use, and it does exactly what you'd expect: it helps you take screenshots without much effort.
You can capture the entire screen or just an area of ​​it. To help improve usability, double-pressing the Alt key automatically captures the full screen, while pressing Ctrl twice will let you select...
</description></item><item><title>Download Executor 2.0.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 10 Sep 2025 01:08:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-executor-271.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-executor-271.html
</guid><description>
Executor for windows is a software alternative premium customization features for the Windows "Run" and "Search Programs". When you press WIN + Z and provides the search results instant, as-you-type for any keywords you enter. By default, Executor will index all the Desktop and Start Menu and you can easily expand the search range by adding the folder location additional.
Executor for windows
The program comes with a list of commands built in which you can use to quickly access many...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare PDFelement Pro 12.0.1.3716</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 22:47:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-pdfelement-pro-105.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-pdfelement-pro-105.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare PDFelement Pro support users to convert PDF to office documents for easier use, modify in every situation. Is one of the software conversion material is rated best today, integrated with many features. We recommend that you should use experience software many useful features this.
Wondershare PDFelement Pro - conversion Fie PDF more features, multi-language
Wondershare PDFelement Pro what?
Convert PDF into Word, Excel, PowerPoint...
• Convert PDF and protected PDF into...
</description></item><item><title>Download IObit Uninstaller Pro 15.0.0.13</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 22:47:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iobit-uninstaller-pro-339.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iobit-uninstaller-pro-339.html
</guid><description>
IObit Uninstaller Pro is software to delete programs not needed easily even when Windows "Remove Programs" operation not successful. IObit Uninstaller Pro will uninstall the app Windows, browser toolbars, software packages and plug-ins added. It comes with a scan function is powerful and a tool, Force Uninstall, both of which help to easily and completely remove the app stubborn, and the excess useless, to release more disk space.
With IObit Uninstaller Pro you will have peace of mind...
</description></item><item><title>Download EASEUS Partition Master Professional Edition 19.15.0 Build 202509051142</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 22:46:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-partition-master-professional-edition-3459.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-partition-master-professional-edition-3459.html
</guid><description>
EASEUS Partition Master Professional Edition is a utility software powerful and full will help you to better manage hard drives and partitions by yourself. This application includes three main functions, such as Program instructions for copying disk and partition, manager partition and wizard restore partition. Moreover, the program allows you to create CD or DVD that can boot, to help you recover the system in case of no boot.
EASEUS Partition Master Professional Edition is the most...
</description></item><item><title>Download Serato DJ Pro 3.3.4</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 22:46:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-serato-dj-pro-169.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-serato-dj-pro-169.html
</guid><description>
Serato DJ Pro is software mix DJ music, professional support, sound effects, and combined to create music, Great DJ. Serato DJ Pro supports the sound effects such as Delay, Reverb, Flanger, Echo, PingPong Delay, Phaser, Distortion, High and Low Pass Filter, as well as combinations of them. Supports MIDI in full, be made in the program, providing the ability to adapt to the controller and program for every need. It allows you to use at the same time from two to four floors. Program Serato...
</description></item><item><title>Download DriverMax Pro 16.21.0.24</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 22:45:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-drivermax-pro-156.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-drivermax-pro-156.html
</guid><description>
DriverMax Pro : utility that allows to download the update the latest driver for your computer. In addition, DriverMax collects information about the drivers installed in system and prints a list of devices that use them. It scans and collects information about drivers installed in the system and create a list of the driver version, date, digital signature and many more.
DriverMax Pro offers information about the driver version, date, developer, number of files and you have digital...
</description></item><item><title>Download R-Wipe &amp;amp; Clean 20.0 Build 2525</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 22:44:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-wipe-clean-891.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-wipe-clean-891.html
</guid><description>
R-Wipe &amp;amp; Clean is software to delete junk files, unnecessary files from your computer to release the storage space and speed up your computer. In addition, R-Wipe &amp;amp; Clean also unleash the capacity of your drive and delete information invasion of privacy on different operations online and offline including your internet history and cookies, the list of downloaded files and documents were open, buffer different data, temporary files and many other items, created by the operating...
</description></item><item><title>Download ProfiCAD 13.2.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 22:44:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-proficad-1546.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-proficad-1546.html
</guid><description>
ProfiCAD is a software Program to draw diagram and circuit diagram of the electrical circuit and electronics with many features to support users. ProfiCAD will search the control circuit is different then help, you can design a variety of diagram techniques, such as diagrams, pneumatic and hydraulic. One of the obvious features of this product is the simplicity of it. Simple in the tool bar and the icons represent the parts. Simply arrange the menu, just put the items on the screen and...
</description></item><item><title>Download EASEUS Partition Master WinPE Edition 19.15.0 Build 202509051142</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 22:43:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-partition-master-winpe-edition-3460.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-partition-master-winpe-edition-3460.html
</guid><description>
EASEUS Partition Master WinPE Edition is a version plugins help you to create a disk partition on WinPE for you to easily recover hard drive partition computer if not may broken or error. Boot disk EasUS Partition Master WinPE, format software mobile, you can:
	Works well in Windows, such as extend system partition or settling low disk space and managing disk space, recovery partition deleted , rebuild MBR, restore partition GPT, etc.
	You are allowed to resize the primary drive to...
</description></item><item><title>Download EarthTime 6.30.9</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 22:42:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-earthtime-185.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-earthtime-185.html
</guid><description>
EarthTime is software that displays the time and date local time of any place in the world. This application has database integration good for 3000 city, users can manually add, download at EarthTime if you want to. EarthTime allows you to install for the time zone and current local time.EarthTime displays the Earth according to the view night and day, you can view the map in full screen mode.
EarthTime
The feature on EarthTime
	EarthTime allows users to interact with visualization...
</description></item><item><title>Download EaseUS Partition Master Technican Edition 19.15.0 Build 202509051142</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 22:41:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-partition-master-350.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-partition-master-350.html
</guid><description>
EaseUS Partition Master is software partition management all-in-one be used to redistribute capacity hard drive with high performance and keep all PC, laptop and server running perfect performance. Engineering software master partition deals with all the task partition in an effective way without loss of data. Just a few clicks to re-partition your hard drive, SSD, USB, flash drive, memory card, SD card, memory card and many other storage devices in Windows 10, 8.1, 8, 7, Vista, XP and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Blender 4.5.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 22:41:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blender-3017.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blender-3017.html
</guid><description>
Blender has a tool that new and very powerful, whose name is Ciking provides the ability to display extremely impressive and extremely realistic.
Features of Blender
	- Feature button support complete
	- The ball exactly on the physical side, SSS and translucency
	- Support languages open for coding the ball unique
Blender - The software-rendered optical
Tool output integration provides:
	- The GPU and CPU
	- Preview options view real-time
	- Support light HDR
	- The license...
</description></item><item><title>Download DBeaver Ultimate 25.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 22:40:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbeaver-6829.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbeaver-6829.html
</guid><description>
DBeaver is a comprehensive and efficient software solution aimed at developers and database administrators who need to manage and organize tables, triggers, views, and stored procedures from multiple databases. Regardless of the database you choose to work with, here referring to MySQL, SQLite, PostgreSQL, Oracle, Microsoft SQL Server, IBM DB2 and Firebird, the application comes in handy for users who need to handle a lot of connections, therefore Organize and edit various database...
</description></item><item><title>Download EASEUS Partition Master Server Edition 19.15.0 Build 202509051142</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 22:39:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-partition-master-server-edition-3457.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-partition-master-server-edition-3457.html
</guid><description>
EASEUS Partition Master Server Edition is a powerful program that allows you to solution delete, create, merge, resize / move, split the partition to use better the full capacity of the hard drive. EasUS Partition Master Server Edition is the partition manager packed full of features and includes three main functions: The recovery guide partition manager partition and wizard restore partition.
These tools will enhance the management of your hard drive and will help you to use disk space...
</description></item><item><title>Download EASEUS Partition Master Unlimited Edition 19.15.0 Build 202509051142</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 22:39:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-partition-master-unlimited-edition-3458.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-partition-master-unlimited-edition-3458.html
</guid><description>
EASEUS Partition Master Unlimited Edition is a partition solution all-in-one and tool kit, disk management PC &amp;amp; Server reliable, especially for large enterprise users. It allows unlimited usage within your company. Just a few clicks to re-partition your hard drive, SSD, USB, flash drive, memory card, SD card, memory card and many other storage devices in Windows 10, 8.1, 8, 7, Vista, XP and Windows Server 2016, 2012, 2008, 2003. EASEUS Partition Master Unlimited Edition extend...
</description></item><item><title>Download MobiKin Backup Manager for Android 2.0.19</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 22:38:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mobikin-backup-manager-for-android-4861.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mobikin-backup-manager-for-android-4861.html
</guid><description>
MobiKin Backup Manager for Android is tool is top ranking for Android to backup and restore flexible, files Android to avoid data loss. Restore function of MobiKin Backup Manager for Android providing assistance timely for a number of users lost Android phone, accidentally deleted phone data or restore their device to its original factory settings. With backup Android to PC using this software, you can restore the backup from PC to any Android device just by a click of the mouse.
There...
</description></item><item><title>Download Canvas X Pro 20.0.1010</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 22:38:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-acd-systems-canvas-x-821.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-acd-systems-canvas-x-821.html
</guid><description>
Canvas X is an environment fully integrated to illustrations, page layouts, images, presentations, and Web publishing. Canvas lets you work with vector objects, images, text and graphics are entered that do not have to switch to other apps. Whether you are a beginner or an experienced design, the tools and features in Canvas can make you more effective.
ACD Systems Canvas X - design, illustration, technical
ACD Systems Canvas X : illustration, design and share technical illustrations...
</description></item><item><title>Download AppCheck Anti-Ransomware 3.1.43.7</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 22:37:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-appcheck-anti-ransomware-1776.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-appcheck-anti-ransomware-1776.html
</guid><description>
"AppCheck Anti-Virus" is a software that is designed to prevent attacks ransomware file encryption of your files. Program monitoring your system and automatically blocked most of the software ransomware encryption while backup the original files in your folder are protected by drivers, lets you undo any changes have been made.
"AppCheck Anti-Virus" - Blocked Attack Ransomware
Other features include a warning if execution is blocked, automatic updates, the free Version will protect your...
</description></item><item><title>Download Zebra CardStudio Professional 2.5.35.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 22:37:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zebra-cardstudio-6424.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zebra-cardstudio-6424.html
</guid><description>
CardStudio is an easy-to-use software that allows you to easily create card designs from simple to complex design. CardStudio offers a new level that simplification the design and printing of all types of cards. The program comes with a very visual interface virtually no need for technical expertise and training so that you can use a single-faced monochet with advanced effects or thousands of printed double-colored prints, you can easily create and print cards.
CardStudio...
</description></item><item><title>Download FireAlpaca 2.13.23</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 22:36:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-firealpaca-2882.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-firealpaca-2882.html
</guid><description>
FireAlpaca is software painting Digital free available in 10 languages and is compatible with both Mac and Windows. The tools and simple controls allow you to draw a easy illustration. Convenient tool will be adding this one to the other! Download FireAlpaca right now! FireAlpaca is the utility to create and edit image files, add image overlays, as well as providing many other advanced features, bring an effective tool to help you draw a picture or edit a photo from the most basic...
</description></item><item><title>Download Software Ideas Modeler Ultimate 15.10</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 22:36:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-software-ideas-modeler-ultimate-10388.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-software-ideas-modeler-ultimate-10388.html
</guid><description>
Software Ideas Modeler Ultimate is a feature-rich CASE tool that can help you design software using various modeling tools and schematic notations. It will help you create a UML model, ERD designer, diagram generator, wireframing tool or BPMN editor.
Features of Software Ideas Modeler Ultimate
	Tools for UML diagrams, class diagrams, block diagrams, data flow diagrams, and other tools help you design your software or its key parts accurately.
	Handle user requests...
</description></item><item><title>Download ExplorerPatcher 26100.4946.69.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 22:35:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-explorerpatcher-7152.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-explorerpatcher-7152.html
</guid><description>
ExplorerPatcher is a patch for Windows 11. It helps you restore Windows 10 functionality on Windows 11, including most menus and taskbars, by using this simple and straightforward patch.
Features of ExplorerPatcher
	Choose between Windows 11 or Windows 10 taskbar (with support for labels, small icons, and lots of customization).
	Disable Windows 11 context menu and command bar in File Explorer and more.
	Open Start for all apps by default, choose how often apps to show, show on active...
</description></item><item><title>Download Type Pilot 3.9.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 22:34:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-type-pilot-5179.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-type-pilot-5179.html
</guid><description>
Type Pilot is a typing software automatically help you to quickly type phrases in document. You only need to specify the keyword (acronym) for piece of text, phrases, sentences or text passages often used. Whenever you enter one of these keywords in any program, Type Pilot automatically replace it with the required phrase or a paragraph.
In particular, Type Pilot operation in ANY text editor, like this: Notepad, MS Word, email apps, Gmail, web browser, HTML editor, fill in the login...
</description></item><item><title>Download KILHO ImageConverter 1.5.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 22:34:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kilho-imageconverter-12520.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kilho-imageconverter-12520.html
</guid><description>
ImageConverter is designed for ease of use, making it accessible to everyone, regardless of technical expertise. To get started, drag and drop the image you want onto the user interface. Once uploaded, you can explore different configuration options to suit your needs. These settings allow you to customize the output format, adjust resolution, and apply any necessary filters or enhancements. You can efficiently convert your images to your desired specifications in just a few...
</description></item></channel></rss>