<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 23:43:57 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 23:43:57 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download VLC Media Player 3.0.22 RC2</title><pubDate> Sat, 15 Nov 2025 01:00:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vlc-media-player-63.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vlc-media-player-63.html
</guid><description>
VLC Media Player is a multimedia player supporting many audio formats and video (MPEG-1, MPEG-2, MPEG-4, DivX, mp3, ogg, etc.) without the need for additional codecs , as well as DVDS, VCDS, and various streaming protocols different online.It also comes with a server, streaming allows you to stream media in unicast or multicast from your network.
VLC Media Player 
VLC Media Player provides a simple interface, with simple buttons control the playback standard and make the most of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download LosslessCut 3.67.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 15 Nov 2025 01:00:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-losslesscut-1789.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-losslesscut-1789.html
</guid><description>
LosslessCut is the video editor to trim and cut video without loss of quality. Just download the video file and use seal cutter start / stop to only the part you want to cut. Click the crop icon and the highlighted part will be exported to the file new video without any decoding or encoding whatsoever. LosslessCut using ffmpeg (included) to carry all the heavy stuff.
LosslessCut - Cut and edit videos
LosslessCut based on Chromium and uses the video player HTML5, so not all formats are...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare Recoverit 14.0.5.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 15 Nov 2025 00:57:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-recoverits-374.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-recoverits-374.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare Recoverit is a data recovery software that is easily lost at a rapid rate and is used by many people. You will do what happens if one day your data is suddenly lost due to the virus or deleted it, .. Wondershare Recoverit will provide you with an environment to protect important data.
Wondershare Recoverit has all the scanning processes that are divided into multiple types, from the typical recovery of the deleted files that are deleted to the recovery of missing files due...
</description></item><item><title>Download Any Video Downloader Pro 9.7.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 15 Nov 2025 00:57:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-video-downloader-pro-3731.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-video-downloader-pro-3731.html
</guid><description>
Any Video Downloader Pro is software support you can download video HD 720p, 1080p, 2K, 4K and 8K from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion, Vimeo, Metacafe and thousands of video sharing sites, other. It is a tool to speed up multi-threading can speed up your download faster up to 5 times. This helpful program support download at the same time. Any Video Downloader Pro lets you download multiple videos at the same time. Moreover, it allows you to pause and resume downloads if you need more...
</description></item><item><title>Download Edraw Max Ultimate 15.0.2.1409</title><pubDate> Sat, 15 Nov 2025 00:56:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-edraw-max-1121.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-edraw-max-1121.html
</guid><description>
Edraw Max is software draw professional looking diagrams help simplify creating diagrams, organization charts, network diagrams, business presentations, building plans, mind mapping, illustration, science, fashion designs, UML diagrams , workflows, program structure diagrams, web design diagrams, electrical engineering, directional maps, diagrams, databases, and more.
Edraw Max - Draw professional looking diagrams
EdrawSoft Edraw Max use software mapping best suits what you know and...
</description></item><item><title>Download WYSIWYG Web Builder 20.3.4</title><pubDate> Sat, 15 Nov 2025 00:56:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wysiwyg-web-builder-177.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wysiwyg-web-builder-177.html
</guid><description>
WYSIWYG Web Builder : The construction of the website from scratch using HTML code isn't a pleasant process, even when you know what you are doing. The website can be built using WYSIWYG Web Builder with using the element similar to the package published on the desktop: text and images placed in frames and tables on the page, so very little surprised when most of the efforts to make the web become a experience user-friendly than. the controls do you use to build your pages.
WYSIWYG Web...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinCatalog 2024.14.10.1103</title><pubDate> Sat, 15 Nov 2025 00:55:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wincatalog-615.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wincatalog-615.html
</guid><description>
WinCatalog 2018 is a software cataloguer multi-function for the disk, file, folder, and any objects not files. Not always easy to track the location of a number of files in your computer, especially if you have a huge collection of CD and DVD. If you are one of those users, then surely there will be appropriate tools to work with such a task. WinCatalog is a software utility designed to help you find documents and data from your computer by building an index that allows you immediate...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Character Animator 2025 v25.6.0 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Sat, 15 Nov 2025 00:54:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-character-animator-0014-1245.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-character-animator-0014-1245.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Character Animator is an animation and motion capture tool that provides everyone with a solution for visual 2D character animation, live animation, character sharing and publish. Turn any piece of art into a cartoon character using your webcam and the new character generator, powered by Adobe Sensei AI.
Using your webcam and microphone, Character Animator matches your expressions to animate your character in real time. The application is extremely fast and integrates with other...
</description></item><item><title>Download Aseprite 1.3.15.5</title><pubDate> Sat, 15 Nov 2025 00:49:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aseprite-6901.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aseprite-6901.html
</guid><description>
Aseprite is a pixel art tool that allows you to create 2D animations for video games using a variety of tools. Animations and visual effects are used to enhance nearly any form of multimedia, including video games. They are created by combining many images and effects, with countless applications at your disposal.
Aseprite supports files and smart drawing tools, resulting in an enhanced image or short animation for use in your project. In addition, you can completely change or enhance...
</description></item><item><title>Download ChessBase 26.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 15 Nov 2025 00:46:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chessbase-13889.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chessbase-13889.html
</guid><description>
ChessBase is the personal, independent chess database that has become the world standard. Everyone uses ChessBase, from World Champions to the amateur player next door. It is the program of choice for anyone who loves the game and wants to learn more about it. Start your personal success story with ChessBase and enjoy the game even more.
Whether it's preparing for an individual opponent or tournament, managing and analyzing your own games, developing training materials for self-study or...
</description></item><item><title>Download UPDF 2.0.13</title><pubDate> Sat, 15 Nov 2025 00:46:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-updf-14160.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-updf-14160.html
</guid><description>
UPDF for Windows is easy-to-use PDF software for Windows! Enjoy powerful editing tools for text, images, links, and more in your PDFs. Customize backgrounds, watermarks, and page sizes as easily as in Word. AI-powered PDF editor and manager that offers a wide range of features including editing, annotating, converting, OCR (Optical Character Recognition), organizing, protecting, sharing, printing, summarizing, translating, and interpreting PDF files.
Features of UPDF
Analyze PDFs with...
</description></item><item><title>Download Markdown Monster 4.0.0.17 Beta</title><pubDate> Sat, 15 Nov 2025 00:40:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-markdown-monster-2640.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-markdown-monster-2640.html
</guid><description>
Markdown Monster is the edit and view Markdown allows you to edit Markdown by syntax highlighting and fast text input. Live preview can collapse, synchronized allows you to see the output of when you enter. You can easily embed images, links, emoticons and code in text form or by using the support UI lightness of we to simplify many operations. You can also paste and drag images directly into the editor.
Markdown Monster is a solution comprehensive software designed to solve almost any...
</description></item><item><title>Download IsoBuster Pro 5.7 Beta</title><pubDate> Sat, 15 Nov 2025 00:39:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-isobuster-pro-146.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-isobuster-pro-146.html
</guid><description>
IsoBuster is a recovery tool, data CD and DVD is used, very professional and easy to use. It supports all disc formats CD and DVD, and all the system files CD and regular DVD... rescue lost files from CD or DVD is damaged or broken, save important documents, precious pictures, video from the family, the backup system your unique.
IsoBuster Pro
Salient features IsoBuster Pro
Download at from FileNugget Fast and secure download speed high Download and stream more than 10,000 movies,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Pazu Tidal Music Converter 1.7.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 15 Nov 2025 00:38:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pazu-tidal-music-converter-11450.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pazu-tidal-music-converter-11450.html
</guid><description>
Pazu Tidal Music Converter: The ultimate guide to downloading Tidal music
Tidal is a popular music streaming service that offers a wide variety of music, including exclusive content and high-quality audio. However, one of Tidal's disadvantages is that it does not allow users to download music for offline listening. This can be a major inconvenience for users who want to listen to music without using data or want to have a backup of their music library.
Pazu Tidal Music Converter is a...
</description></item><item><title>Download Geod Studio 3dSen VR 1.1.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 15 Nov 2025 00:38:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-3dsenvr-12203.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-3dsenvr-12203.html
</guid><description>
3dSenVR emulator offers beautifully handcrafted diorama versions of the most beloved classic NES 8-bit titles. Immerse yourself in the old game world, now magically transformed into a 3D space that will satisfy even the most devoted retro fans.
3DSenVR Features
	Growing list of supported classics and modern DIY games
	Including but not limited to Super Mario Bros, Duck Tale, Mega Man, Contra, Metroid, Legend of Zelda series, Final Fantasy, Duck Hunt, Dragon Warrior, Batman,...
</description></item><item><title>Download SysGauge Ultimate 12.2.16 + Pro + Server</title><pubDate> Sat, 15 Nov 2025 00:37:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sysgauge-1296.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sysgauge-1296.html
</guid><description>
SysGauge Ultimate / Server is software that provides the ability to display the chart type monitoring system, hosted report monitoring systems and results of monitoring system to a number of standard formats including HTML, PDF, Excel, text, CSV and XML. Advanced users and IT administrators are provided the ability to save recurring reports system status, set a limit specified by the user for the timer monitoring the system and then displayed error message or alert, play sound...
</description></item><item><title>Download HTML5Point 4.1.71</title><pubDate> Sat, 15 Nov 2025 00:37:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-html5point-5610.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-html5point-5610.html
</guid><description>
HTML5Point is the world's first PowerPoint to HTML5 converter that allows you to convert your PowerPoint presentation into interactive HTML5 content that can be viewed on iPad, iPhone, other mobile devices and on all modern browsers all in one click.
HTML5Point converts your PowerPoint content correctly into HTML5 preserving all animations, transitions, and other special effects associated with the original PowerPoint presentation. Developing an e-Learning package with support on all...
</description></item><item><title>Download Pazu StreamGet All-In-One Video Downloader 2.8.7</title><pubDate> Fri, 14 Nov 2025 21:48:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pazu-streamget-all-in-one-video-downloader-12037.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pazu-streamget-all-in-one-video-downloader-12037.html
</guid><description>
StreamGet All-In-One Video Downloader is the ultimate downloading solution for you. It supports downloading any movies and shows from the most popular streaming sites including Netflix, Prime Video, Disney Plus, Max, Hulu, and Apple TV Plus. The downloader is continuously updated to support more platforms in the future.
Download movies and shows from various streaming platforms to MP4/MKV on your Windows device and enjoy them anywhere you want.
Features of Pazu StreamGet All-In-One...
</description></item><item><title>Download ENGL Driver Manager 8.0.0.2023</title><pubDate> Fri, 14 Nov 2025 21:44:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-engl-driver-manager-14285.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-engl-driver-manager-14285.html
</guid><description>
ENGL Driver Manager is an enterprise software tool designed to manage drivers in Windows deployment and update scenarios. It supports task-based deployment solutions and is compatible with Windows 11, providing enterprise-grade driver management features. ENGL Driver Manager helps automate the installation, update, and management of device drivers across multiple systems, which is essential in IT environments to maintain system stability and performance.
This tool supports efficient...
</description></item><item><title>Download zplane Elastique Pitch 2 v2.5.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 14 Nov 2025 21:35:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zplane-elastique-pitch-14284.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zplane-elastique-pitch-14284.html
</guid><description>
zplane Elastique Pitch v2 delivers incredibly clear real-time pitch and formant transformations for every production need, from creative sound experimentation to precise frame rate conversion. Powered by the latest ELASTIQUEPRO engine, the trusted zplane technology used in many world-class DAWs, ELASTIQUE PITCH combines pristine sound quality with effortless control.
Independent pitch and formant correction for creative sound design, subtle vocal enhancement or powerful transitions....
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Audition 2025 v25.6.0 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Fri, 14 Nov 2025 19:01:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-0010-adobe-audition-1246.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-0010-adobe-audition-1246.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Autdition 2024 is a professional tool for professionals active in the field of audio processing and video, offering them the ability to almost unlimited. Ease of use combined with flexibility of work, allows you to create the main copy of the highest class, edit, mix, handle, impose more sound effects especially. In fact, users have to be on my computer a recording studio powerful full with the tool easy to use at the same time, the tool is quite professional.
Adobe autdition CC -...
</description></item><item><title>Download Chaos Corona 14 for 3ds Max 2018 - 2026</title><pubDate> Fri, 14 Nov 2025 19:00:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chaos-corona-2986.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chaos-corona-2986.html
</guid><description>
Corona Renderer is the name of the plug-in technique and dedicated powerful, but have high functionality for Autodesk software 3ds Max. Plug before you is a standalone application known to the CLI. In addition, users can use this tool to promote their business on software Maxon Cinema 4D is also used. The manufacturers of this product believe that working with this tool is very simple and in fact you only need to press the activities rendered. With this tool easier than ever can do the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Chaos Corona 14 for Cinema 4D R17 - 2026</title><pubDate> Fri, 14 Nov 2025 19:00:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-corona-renderer-for-cinema-4d-6499.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-corona-renderer-for-cinema-4d-6499.html
</guid><description>
Corona Renderer  is the name of a powerful, but highly functional engineering and dedicated plug-in for Autodesk 3ds Max software. Plug in before you are a known CLI standalone application. In addition, users can use this tool to advertise their business on Maxon Cinema 4D software which is also used. The manufacturers of this product firmly believe that working with this tool is very simple, and in fact you just need to hit render the rendering operations. With this tool it's easier...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Acrobat Reader DC 2025.001.20918</title><pubDate> Fri, 14 Nov 2025 18:57:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-acrobat-reader-3707.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-acrobat-reader-3707.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Acrobat Reader DC is a system of application software and Web services developed by Adobe Systems to view, create, manipulate, print and manage PDF files. With Adobe Acrobat Reader DC, you can create, export, edit, and track PDF files from anywhere - and maintain connection with the recent set of files on all your devices.
Adobe Acrobat Reader current DC is connected with Adobe Document Cloud - help working on the computers and mobile devices becomes easier than ever before. This is...
</description></item><item><title>Download Chaos Envision 1.3.1.588412</title><pubDate> Fri, 14 Nov 2025 18:57:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chaos-envision-14167.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chaos-envision-14167.html
</guid><description>
Chaos Envision is a standalone 3D visualization software designed for realistic real-time rendering combined with fast animation capabilities. The software is primarily aimed at architects, visualization professionals, and designers, providing a tool for creating professional, immersive presentations with animations, realistic crowds, and object manipulation.
Envision supports very large and complex scenes without compromising performance and integrates seamlessly with other Chaos tools...
</description></item></channel></rss>