<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 01:43:52 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 01:43:52 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download DriverMax Pro 16.22.0.25</title><pubDate> Fri, 24 Oct 2025 01:09:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-drivermax-pro-156.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-drivermax-pro-156.html
</guid><description>
DriverMax Pro : utility that allows to download the update the latest driver for your computer. In addition, DriverMax collects information about the drivers installed in system and prints a list of devices that use them. It scans and collects information about drivers installed in the system and create a list of the driver version, date, digital signature and many more.
DriverMax Pro offers information about the driver version, date, developer, number of files and you have digital...
</description></item><item><title>Download CyberLink PowerDirector Ultimate 2026 v24.0.1022.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 24 Oct 2025 01:08:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-powerdirector-ultimate-425.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-powerdirector-ultimate-425.html
</guid><description>
CyberLink PowerDirector Ultimate is software editor, edit video and make movies on the computer from a variety of templates are made available, complete with effects, transitions, animations, and music. CyberLink PowerDirector 17 is a combination of video editing software with advanced video editing features powerful. Cblowing need to add your clips into the time line and click on 'Production'!
The tool design video in CyberLink PowerDirector have the ability to customize helps you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ashampoo Photo Recovery 3.0.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 24 Oct 2025 01:07:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-photo-recovery-7133.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-photo-recovery-7133.html
</guid><description>
Ashampoo Photo Recovery is software to recover lost photos on your computer with just a few simple steps using modern search algorithms. The software supports the recovery of images lost due to various causes, allowing to recover many image formats, using many different search criteria, and returning the original image with no image quality. change.
Ashampoo Photo Recovery supports image recovery on various storage devices such as: your hard drives, USB drives and storage cards to find...
</description></item><item><title>Download Atlantis Word Processor 5.0.0.6</title><pubDate> Fri, 24 Oct 2025 01:02:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-atlantis-word-processor-585.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-atlantis-word-processor-585.html
</guid><description>
Atlantis Word Processor is a word processor app with features format, standard text, autocorrect, and spell check.  Atlantis is a word processor in accordance with most of the tasks handled daily text. The interface is very easy to use and offers the toolbars, hotkeys and sound effects thanh can customize (can turn off). It includes a clip library for quick access to the text or images used regular preview, font format and many other features aimed at improving the process of your...
</description></item><item><title>Download TechSmith Snagit 2025 v25.4.0.8498</title><pubDate> Fri, 24 Oct 2025 01:02:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-techsmith-snagit-01en-280.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-techsmith-snagit-01en-280.html
</guid><description>
TechSmith Snagit software screen capture anything on your screen, then easily add text arrows or effects and save the snapshot to a file or share it immediately by e-mail or IM. With TechSmith Snagit you can capture and share the article, photo or Web page directly from your screen.
TechSmith Snagit
TechSmith Snagit help you can take a photo screen in the form of roll, panoramic shooting, shooting photos of and easy photo editing after shooting. Besides it is feature - video recording...
</description></item><item><title>Download Far Manager 3.0 Build 6575</title><pubDate> Fri, 24 Oct 2025 01:01:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-far-manager-1609.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-far-manager-1609.html
</guid><description>
Far Manager is an application for managing files and archives in Windows operating systems. Far Manager works in text mode and provides a simple interface and intuitive to perform the action.
Far Manager - Manage file documents
The main features of Far Manager include:
	Viewing files and directories; editing, copying and renaming files; and many other actions.
	The function of Far Manager is significantly expanded by the module DLL outside - the plugin, created by a special...
</description></item><item><title>Download VovSoft VCF Editor 2.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 24 Oct 2025 01:00:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-vcf-editor-12583.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-vcf-editor-12583.html
</guid><description>
Vovsoft VCF Editor is a powerful, offline tool designed to manage and edit vCard (VCF) files on Windows. Running locally on the user's computer, the tool ensures privacy and security by processing all data offline without the need for an internet connection. This makes this tool ideal for users who prioritize keeping their communications private and secure.
Features of VovSoft VCF Editor
	This vCard editor software allows users to easily load, view and edit key contact fields such as...
</description></item><item><title>Download MiniTool Video Converter 4.5.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 24 Oct 2025 00:14:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minitool-video-converter-5358.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minitool-video-converter-5358.html
</guid><description>
MiniTool Video Converter is the most direct solution for converting audio and video files to a wide variety of formats. This free video converter is available to convert audio to video and convert video to audio. This free video converter supports over 1000 conversion formats including 4K / FHD / HD files MP4, MOV, MKV, AVI, WMV, M4V and audio formats like MP3, WAV, M4A, WMA High Quality, AAC, AC3.
MiniTool Video Converter allows you to convert batches of files at the same time. Just...
</description></item><item><title>Download MEmu Android Emulator 9.2.9</title><pubDate> Fri, 24 Oct 2025 00:09:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-memu-2975.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-memu-2975.html
</guid><description>
MEmu or also known as Android Emulator is the Android emulator light and free, allowing Windows users to enjoy Android experience the original on the computer and device Microsoft their. This app provides outstanding performance, allowing you to play on PC a series of games designed to run on Android devices. This app allows you to play the game favorite Android on larger screens, to bring you a better gaming experience.
MEmu - Android emulator, lightweight and free
Software MEmu also...
</description></item><item><title>Download Apowersoft Video Download Capture 6.6.1.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 24 Oct 2025 00:07:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-apowersoft-video-download-capture-1556.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-apowersoft-video-download-capture-1556.html
</guid><description>
Apowersoft Video Download Capture is a comprehensive tool with advanced technologies for media streaming to choice cost-effective to download videos from YouTube, Dailymotion, Vimeo, Yahoo Screen and Hulu, as well as millions of other websites. Apowersoft Video Download Capture is your download video powerful and effective this can download and save videos, movies, tv episodes and music videos online. It also has the switch function, supports convert any video to MP4, AVI, MKV, WMV and the...
</description></item><item><title>Download EaseUS Fixo Technician 4.0.0 Build 20251022</title><pubDate> Fri, 24 Oct 2025 00:06:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-fixo-9814.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-fixo-9814.html
</guid><description>
Video is corrupted or inaccessible after power failure and sudden blackout, whole system crash, update failure, wrong file handling or some other reason? EaseUS Fixo allows you to repair many different video file formats including MOV, MP4, M2TS, MKV, MTS, 3GP, etc. easier no matter how broken it is.
It can intelligently and intelligently repair damaged and damaged photos from computers or other external storage devices such as USB flash drives, memory cards, SD cards, digital cameras...
</description></item><item><title>Download Free YouTube Download 4.4.42.1021 Premium</title><pubDate> Fri, 24 Oct 2025 00:06:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-download-1177.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-download-1177.html
</guid><description>
Free YouTube Download Premium is the most popular application to download videos from YouTube. The program was released in 2006 and regularly updated since then. Use the program to download and convert YouTube videos to view offline anytime.
Free YouTube Download - added Support to download youtube
Download more videos! Save whole playlists and YouTube channels, videos from a playlist individually (history, video be favorite, favourites, Watch later), videos from many different...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube Downloader 3.9.17 (2210)</title><pubDate> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 23:58:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube Downloader  is a dedicated software that helps users  downloading youtube videos  Favorites on PC for offline viewing. With MediaHuman YouTube  Downloader  you can download videos from youtube website to your computer with  fast speed , with special software development technology that automatically receives videos from Websites, in addition to the ability to download videos from software websites, can convert downloaded video formats to various formats for the purpose...
</description></item><item><title>Download Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium 4.4.42.1021</title><pubDate> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 23:58:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-to-mp3-converter-premium-844.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-to-mp3-converter-premium-844.html
</guid><description>
Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium version is a software used to convert YouTube to MP3, extract audio from playlists YouTube, show listings, charts, video responses, channels, favorites of the user. With Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium, you can download and convert playlists, channels, stream original tv series and get them into iTunes at the same time.
Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium - convert YouTube to MP3
Features Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium from the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Apeaksoft Android Toolkit 2.1.52</title><pubDate> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 23:57:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-apeaksoft-android-toolkit-1712.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-apeaksoft-android-toolkit-1712.html
</guid><description>
Apeaksoft Android Toolkit can help you recover photos, videos, contacts, messages, call logs, apps, and documents from your phone, tablet and your SD card. The special thing is Apeaksoft Android Toolkit compatible with 5000+ devices, handheld Android.
Apeaksoft Android Toolkit - data Recovery for Android
The features of Apeaksoft Android Toolkit
	Restore and export the data deleted or lost from phone and Android tablets including Samsung, HTC, LG, Sony, Motorola, Huawei, Google,...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDF Annotator 9.0.0.928</title><pubDate> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 23:56:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-annotator-178.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-annotator-178.html
</guid><description>
PDF Annotator software user open any PDF file and add annotations, using the mouse or pen Tablet PC, directly on the Page of the PDF file. PDF Annotator allows users to perform editing operations on PDF files such as: add notes, edit signature, highlight, insert images or text... From the this useful tool, you can completely modify PDF files as you like in order to meet the different work.
PDF Annotator
With the PDF Annotator the document has annotations can then be saved directly back...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Downloader 9.17.12</title><pubDate> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 23:55:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html
</guid><description>
YTD Youtube Downloader is an application that reliable and intuitive, allowing you to quickly download YouTube videos and save them to your computer. You can also convert the media files to the format desired video or extract audio streams and save separately. YTD Youtube Downloader lets you save your favorite clips of yourself from Youtube, Facebook, Vimeo and Dailymotion to your desktop. The software supports URLS from many web site hosting, multimedia and allows you to download desired...
</description></item><item><title>Download OkMap Desktop 19.2.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 23:54:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-okmap-desktop-581.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-okmap-desktop-581.html
</guid><description>
OkMap Desktop is interactive software working on the computer with web maps or digital maps bought or scanned. OkMap can also import a data vector from the most common formats and data DEM related to information height.
Through the map you can organize your path by creating waypoints , routesand tracks on the screen your computer, and upload this data to your GPS . OkMap set data high speedautomatic and estimated moving time . Furthermore OkMap provides you also have autorouting and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Navicat Premium 17.3.6 Enterprise</title><pubDate> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 23:54:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-navicat-premium-87.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-navicat-premium-87.html
</guid><description>
Navicat Premium is a developer tool database allows you to connect simultaneously with the MySQL database, MariaDB, SQL Server, Oracle, PostgreSQL and SQLite from a single application. Navicat Premium is compatible with the database cloud such as Amazon RDS, Amazon Aurora, Amazon Redshift, SQL Azure, Oracle Cloud and Google Cloud. You can quickly and easily build, manage and maintain database of your.
Features, characteristics, Navicat Premium:
Move data seamlessly
Data transfer, data...
</description></item><item><title>Download AnyMP4 Android Data Recovery 2.1.52</title><pubDate> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 23:53:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anymp4-android-data-recovery-1256.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anymp4-android-data-recovery-1256.html
</guid><description>
AnyMP4 Android Data Recovery is software restore data Android provides the feature to restore data powerful for mobile and tablet Android. AnyMP4 Android Data Recovery can recover text content has been removed and lost, such as contacts, SMS, text messages, call history, notes, WhatsApp chat and more from your Android device. And the contact exported will be saved as VCF, CSV or HTML for you to use. Whether you've accidentally deleted Android data or lost data after restore factory, os...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter 3.9.17 (2210)</title><pubDate> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 23:52:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-to-mp3-converter-1744.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-to-mp3-converter-1744.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter is the software support download youtube video and convert video to mp3 format fast and most simple. MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter allows you download and convert videos from YouTube and other websites to MP3 format by pasting the YouTube URL into the application. When you paste the URL, the program will display thumbnails for videos and you have the option to customize the title information, artist and album before you begin the process of...
</description></item><item><title>Download MassTube 2026 v21.0.4.171 Ultra</title><pubDate> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 23:41:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-masstube-plus-461.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-masstube-plus-461.html
</guid><description>
MassTube Plus is a small utility used to download the favorite videos of you on youtube on your computer. This is a software compact, has a simple design with few options to download videos fastest. The you complete peace of mind because the software is easy to use, built exclusively for a single goal: to retrieve the video file from YouTube, so it doesn't pack the other useful features such as search engine integrated and a download audio file.
MassTube can work with multiple output...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sante PACS Server 4.3</title><pubDate> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 23:40:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sante-pacs-server-7541.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sante-pacs-server-7541.html
</guid><description>
Sante PACS Server is an HTTP (web) server for DICOM files and a CD/DVD Burn and Print server that offers high performance and reliability at an affordable price. It provides connectivity to all DICOM methods (CT, MR, US, CR, NM, XA, MG, DX, etc.). Reviewing of DICOM images can be done using the Sante PACS Viewer (the system's built-in, full-featured DICOM Viewer). The built-in web server can be used as a free cloud server for DICOM files!
Tools of Sante PACS Server
	The Migration Tool...
</description></item><item><title>Download Navicat for MySQL 17.0.3</title><pubDate> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 23:40:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-navicat-for-mysql-3802.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-navicat-for-mysql-3802.html
</guid><description>
Navicat for MySQL is a software management database comprehensive and powerful for MySQL and MariaDB, providing user interface graphics (GUI), advanced allows you to manage development and maintain database. This software also provides a set of powerful utilities, suitable for both developer MySQL / MariaDB, advanced and novice. Navicat for MySQL has the ability to connect with the MySQL and MariaDB server remotely or locally. For MySQL, the database server starting from version 3.21 is...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sante PACS Server PG 4.3</title><pubDate> Thu, 23 Oct 2025 23:39:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sante-pacs-server-pg-7540.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sante-pacs-server-pg-7540.html
</guid><description>
Sante PACS Server PG is an HTTP server (web) for DICOM files and a recorder and In CD/DVD with high performance and reliability. It provides connectivity with all the DICOM (CT, MR, US, CR, NM, XA, MG, DX, etc.). The review of the DICOM image can be done with the Sante PACS Viewer.
Integrated web servers can be used as a free cloud server for DICOM files!
</description></item></channel></rss>