<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 05:34:14 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 05:34:14 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download AnyDesk 9.6.6</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Dec 2025 01:40:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anydesk-1321.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anydesk-1321.html
</guid><description>
AnyDesk is software computer control remote, easy connection with remote computer management and manipulation on the computer. After installing the AnyDesk up 2 the computer then you can easily use the software to provide technical support for a friend or family member or you have access to your computer while you away from home or office.
AnyDesk - control your computer remotely
The process of using very simple software, want to allow access to his computer, only need to provide for...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Downloader 10.0.6</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Dec 2025 01:38:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html
</guid><description>
YTD Youtube Downloader is an application that reliable and intuitive, allowing you to quickly download YouTube videos and save them to your computer. You can also convert the media files to the format desired video or extract audio streams and save separately. YTD Youtube Downloader lets you save your favorite clips of yourself from Youtube, Facebook, Vimeo and Dailymotion to your desktop. The software supports URLS from many web site hosting, multimedia and allows you to download desired...
</description></item><item><title>Download PrintFab Pro XL 3.0.5</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Dec 2025 01:38:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-printfab-pro-xl-4083.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-printfab-pro-xl-4083.html
</guid><description>
PrintFab Pro XL software is targeted to advanced users and will allow for the prints, neutral balance. Of course, you can also affect the brightness of the color, adjust contrast, etc. using the option of different controls. PrintFab Pro XL allows you to print on any means accurate color possible - and even arbitrary use of special inks from the manufacturer side Tuesday. This is done for people by measuring color inexpensive (the 14.95 EUR) by service PrintFab or measurement technology of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Allavsoft Video Downloader Converter 3.28.6.9465</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Dec 2025 01:37:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allavsoft-video-downloader-converter-248.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allavsoft-video-downloader-converter-248.html
</guid><description>
Allavsoft Video Downloader Converter software supports download movies, music videos, playlist, sport videos from video sharing website for free like Facebook, Youtube and over 100 video sharing sites.
Allavsoft is many users favorite thanks to the combined features simultaneous transmission of multiple videos and speed limit download video. Besides, the program also supports pause and resume data transmission, to help you interfere with the process of transmitting download data to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Navicat Premium 17.3.7 Enterprise</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Dec 2025 01:37:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-navicat-premium-87.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-navicat-premium-87.html
</guid><description>
Navicat Premium is a developer tool database allows you to connect simultaneously with the MySQL database, MariaDB, SQL Server, Oracle, PostgreSQL and SQLite from a single application. Navicat Premium is compatible with the database cloud such as Amazon RDS, Amazon Aurora, Amazon Redshift, SQL Azure, Oracle Cloud and Google Cloud. You can quickly and easily build, manage and maintain database of your.
Features, characteristics, Navicat Premium:
Move data seamlessly
Data transfer, data...
</description></item><item><title>Download Hasleo Backup Suite 5.5.2.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Dec 2025 01:36:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hasleo-backup-suite-6588.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hasleo-backup-suite-6588.html
</guid><description>
Hasleo Backup Suite is a free backup and free Windows recovery, integration of backup features, recovery, and replication, it is designed for Windows operating system users and can be used on both Windows PC and Windows Server. The backup and recovery feature of Hasleo Backup Suite can help you backup and restore your Windows, disk and partition operating system to protect your Windows operating system and your personal data. The replication feature of Hasleo Backup Suite can help you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Edge Remover 18.43</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Dec 2025 01:36:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-edge-remover-7689.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-edge-remover-7689.html
</guid><description>
Edge Remover is our mini user interfaceless tool to permanently remove Microsoft Edge from your system. Easily remove Microsoft Edge browser from your system, with just one click, with this simple, no UI app.
Features of Edge Remover
	Remove MSEdge and its components
	Prevent reinstalling MSEdge on your system
Requirements:
Operating System: Microsoft Windows 7 or later
Framework: Microsoft .NET Framework 4.0
</description></item><item><title>Download Tenorshare 4DDiG File Repair 4.3.2.6</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Dec 2025 01:35:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tenorshare-4ddig-file-repair-5630.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tenorshare-4ddig-file-repair-5630.html
</guid><description>
Tenorshare 4DDiG File Repair is AI-powered software to repair damaged or damaged videos, photos, files and audios, improve their quality and add color to black media white. 4DDiG photo editing solves all photo problems like blurry photos, overexposed photos, etc. Powered by AI, it can dramatically improve image resolution and colorize black and white photos in seconds, not hours.
Features of Tenorshare 4DDiG File Repair
	Easily repair any blurry, overexposed and damaged videos, photos...
</description></item><item><title>Download SoftPerfect NetWorx 25.12</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Dec 2025 01:34:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-softperfect-networx-1592.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-softperfect-networx-1592.html
</guid><description>
SoftPerfect NetWorx is a software simple and effective way to manage traffic and bandwidth consumption in Windows. If we ignore traffic not regular, and occasionally of the operating system to update itself, as well as updates for the different drivers, one of the important factors in the job vacancy Internet soon is the use of the Internet is hidden by the software is installed on your system. . If you are the user settings clock software and you don't pay attention to it, the existence...
</description></item><item><title>Download ThinkAutomation Studio Professional 5.1.1100.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Dec 2025 01:34:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thinkautomation-studio-professional-9635.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thinkautomation-studio-professional-9635.html
</guid><description>
ThinkAutomation Studio Professional is software that automates on-premises and cloud-based business processes to cut costs and save time. Automate incoming communication channels, monitor databases, react to incoming webhooks, web forms and chat bots. Handles documents, attachments, local files, and other message sources.
Parse and extract data from incoming messages and take actions in business processes, such as outbound communications, updating on-premises and cloud databases,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Windows Firewall Control 6.24.0.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Dec 2025 01:33:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-firewall-control-3395.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-firewall-control-3395.html
</guid><description>
Windows Firewall Control is a application which help extend the functionality of the Microsoft Windows Firewall and provides quick access to the most common options of Windows firewall. It works in the system tray and allows users to adjust firewall simple root which does not have to lose time by navigating to the specific part of the firewall.
Windows Firewall Control - firewall App for windows
It runs in the system tray and allows user to control the firewall easily without having to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Advanced CSV Converter 7.86</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Dec 2025 01:32:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-csv-converter-4508.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-csv-converter-4508.html
</guid><description>
Advanced CSV Converter is a conversion tool CSV to DBF, Excel (XLS, XLSX), TXT, HTML, PRG, XML, SQL, RTF. To convert a file, the program provides an interface controlled by the wizard, guides you step by step conversion. Use the wizard, you select file input, select the format and destination folder. If necessary, you can set the filter switch according to the example and select columns you want to exclude from the process. When the conversion process is started, the program will extract...
</description></item><item><title>Download HE - Hardware Read and Write Utility 1.25.12.05</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Dec 2025 01:32:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-he-hardware-read-and-write-utility-4287.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-he-hardware-read-and-write-utility-4287.html
</guid><description>
HE - Hardware Read and Write Utility is a powerful utility intended for hardware engineer, engineer, BIOS developer, driver, engineer, QA engineers, performance test engineers, diagnostic, etc., this utility access almost all the computer hardware, including PCI (PCI Express), index / Data, PCI, memory, index memory / Data space I / O, Index I / O / Data, Super I / O, DIMM SPD, CPU The registers MSR, screen, SMART, physical area of the hard drive identification data, ATA, dump tables ACPI...
</description></item><item><title>Download Bitsum Process Lasso Pro 17.0.0.111 Beta</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Dec 2025 01:31:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bitsum-process-lasso-pro-289.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bitsum-process-lasso-pro-289.html
</guid><description>
Bitsum Process Lasso Pro is software compact statistics and troubleshoot computer systems, such as crashes by control CPU. Technological process Lassos ProBalance (process balance) adjust the smart priority of running programs so that the process works poorly or too active will not affect the ability to use your computer!
Software Process Lasso to help manage the program or application will be managed and controlled to not have the ability to monopolize the CPU. Process Lasso also...
</description></item><item><title>Download DipTrace 5.2.0.4</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Dec 2025 01:30:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-diptrace-4611.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-diptrace-4611.html
</guid><description>
DipTrace is EDA software / CAD to create schematics and printed circuit boards. The developer provides the interface and multi-language instructions (available in English and 22 other languages). DipTrace has 4 modules: The edit capture schematic editor layout PCB with features automatically based on shape and integrated preview &amp;amp; casting, 3D editing, composition and The edit template. DipTrace is a powerful software and intuitive aimed at the expert want to create the layout PCB,...
</description></item><item><title>Download ezPaycheck 3.15.23</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Dec 2025 01:30:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ezpaycheck-5319.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ezpaycheck-5319.html
</guid><description>
ezPaycheck is a payroll software easy to use is designed for the small business: simple, reliable and affordable. The developer of we have designed it to become a solution tax payroll internal for small businesses to calculate taxes, print paychecks for employees and contractors, generate reports and print tax forms.
The features of ezPaycheck
	Calculate payroll federal and state tax / deductions and local taxes (such as SDI tax, occupation tax, city)
	Print paychecks and tax...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sante DICOM Editor 10.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Dec 2025 01:29:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sante-dicom-editor-11760.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sante-dicom-editor-11760.html
</guid><description>
Sante DICOM Editor is a professional DICOM editor, viewer, anonymizer, converter, dicomizer, PACS client, mini PACS server, patient CD/DVD burner (with viewer) and more that too.
Sante DICOM Editor is the industry's leading post-processing application for editing, converting and processing DICOM files, it is used by most major corporations and medical device manufacturers and is DICOM drafting is chosen by the largest universities and colleges. hospitals around the world. Among other...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tenorshare 4DDiG 10.6.7.16</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Dec 2025 01:29:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tenorshare-4ddigs-pro-5629.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tenorshare-4ddigs-pro-5629.html
</guid><description>
Tenorshare 4DDiG is software to recover data from laptop / PC, external drive or USB flash disk. Recover Windows partitions, such as raw partitions, formatted partitions, damaged partitions, etc. Recover lost or deleted photos, videos, audio, videos, documents, etc.
With 4DDiG, you can recover many different types of data from this powerful Windows Data Recovery Tool feature. No matter what you have lost, 4DDiG is capable of recovering deleted files Windows 10 / 8.1 / 8/7 /...
</description></item><item><title>Download ChrisPC Win Experience Index 7.25.1205</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Dec 2025 01:28:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-win-experience-index-2338.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-win-experience-index-2338.html
</guid><description>
ChrisPC Win Experience Index helps to check performance of RAM, processor CPU to know that his machine still works fine with the program ChrisPC Win Experience Index brings back the Windows Experience Index are installed on windows 8.1 of you to take out only the number of hardware, after checking the software, return the original interface of your operating system.
ChrisPC Win Experience Index - performance test computer
ChrisPC Win Experience Index installed quickly, after launch,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Yellow Leads Extractor 9.3.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Dec 2025 01:28:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yellow-leads-extractor-3729.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yellow-leads-extractor-3729.html
</guid><description>
Yellow Leads Extractor is the software that allows users to make 100% custom search in the browser. When you have this program then you don't need to do more work to retrieve information from the yellow pages. You just need to enter the category and location. After entering the information when you will click on the option data get then all the information will be extracted.
Yellow Leads Extractor - custom Search on the browser
The features of the Yellow Leads Extractor
	You can save...
</description></item><item><title>Download Certificate Manager 18.43</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Dec 2025 01:26:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-certificate-manager-13958.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-certificate-manager-13958.html
</guid><description>
Certificate Manager provides an in-depth overview of your current certificates, allowing you to easily access detailed information. It also provides functions for both exporting existing certificates and importing new certificates, enhancing your certificate management capabilities.
Application certificates are often overlooked by most users until problems arise during application installation. For the average end user, there is little reason to focus on application certificates....
</description></item><item><title>Download Tixati 3.42.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Dec 2025 01:26:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tixati-2355.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tixati-2355.html
</guid><description>
A Bittorrent free, good have been updated, are designed for operating systems Microsoft Windows and Linux (for the OS Monday, you can download a version from the official website of the developer). The difference between a client and a large number of others is that users are provided a wide opportunity to control the torrent of them, they also write on your program that it consumes less memory than uTorrent and Halite famous.
Tixati - App download torrent
Tixati is also ready to...
</description></item><item><title>Download NTFS Permissions Auditor Pro 25.12.4</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Dec 2025 01:25:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-albusbit-ntfs-permissions-auditor-pro-7539.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-albusbit-ntfs-permissions-auditor-pro-7539.html
</guid><description>
NTFS Permissions Auditor Pro is a software to quickly and easily audit directory permissions in your Windows system. It allows you to quickly analyze, verify and review any NTFS folder permissions and provides additional features like powerful, customizable filtering, exporting to different formats, etc.
Features of NTFS Permissions Auditor Pro
	Get up and running with just one install.
	Instant and accurate details about NTFS permissions for all target folders.
	Filters combine many...
</description></item><item><title>Download Rainbow Analyst add-in Professional 25.12.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Dec 2025 01:25:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rainbow-analyst-add-in-professional-11122.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rainbow-analyst-add-in-professional-11122.html
</guid><description>
Rainbow Analyst add-in Professional is a powerful tool designed to enhance data analysis in Microsoft Excel. This add-on provides many advanced features and visualizations to help users gain valuable insights from their data.
One of the key features of Rainbow Analyst is the ability to create color-coded reports and charts. Users can assign specific colors to different data values, making it easier to identify patterns, trends, and outliers. This visual representation of data enhances...
</description></item><item><title>Download ezAccounting 3.15.17</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Dec 2025 01:24:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ezaccounting-5300.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ezaccounting-5300.html
</guid><description>
ezAccounting is accounting software designed for the small business: simple, reliable and affordable. ezAccounting is the solution internal accounting suitable for small businesses need to record and report on cash flow in and out including sales, incomes and expenses and purchases. It also supports payroll processing and print tax forms.
The features of ezAccounting
	Company accounts unlimited
	Custom format form
	Custom format Czech
	Support multiple tax code
	Support multiple...
</description></item></channel></rss>