<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 17:35:14 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 17:35:14 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download XMedia Recode 3.6.1.8</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 19:18:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xmedia-recode-919.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xmedia-recode-919.html
</guid><description>
XMedia Recode is software to change the quality for video files on windows operating system, it has the ability to change quality, video format. XMedia Recode supports the format conversion such as 3GP, 3GPP, 3GPP2, AAC, AC3, AIFF, AMR, ASF, AU, AVI, DIVX, DTS, DVR-MS, FLV, H. 261, H. 263, H. 264, M4A, M1V, M2V, M4V, MKV.
Parameters advanced
The user can step into the more advanced and modify bitrate, frame interval the frame rate, modes, speed control and many other settings regarding...
</description></item><item><title>Download ToDoList 9.1.0.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 18:39:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-todolist-1637.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-todolist-1637.html
</guid><description>
ToDoList is an application note and task management with multiple options, set up help you to easily split and track the progress of the work. Todolist helps millions of people feel in control of their lives more and be the leader in a number of organizations inspired the world to believe. Todolist keep all to-dos of I in one place and perfectly integrated with the other tools that I use. It helps me turn everything faster.
ToDoList - management software job
Every day you have to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Scale Photo Up 2.0.7</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 18:39:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-scale-photo-up-13763.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-scale-photo-up-13763.html
</guid><description>
Are you tired of low-resolution, pixelated footage that stifles your creativity? Say goodbye to grainy memories and say hello to Scale Photo Up – groundbreaking AI software that doubles resolution, enhances detail, and smooths out imperfections in your photos and videos with stunning clarity!
Why Scale Photo Up?
	Upscale 2x – No loss of quality! – Turn blurry, low-resolution photos and videos into sharp, high-resolution masterpieces. Perfect for breathing new life into old...
</description></item><item><title>Download Windows 11 Pro Lite 24H2 Build 26100.6584 Ghost Spectre</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 18:38:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-11-lite-6621.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-11-lite-6621.html
</guid><description>
Windows 11 Lite is a Windows 11 build that has been customisable to remove applications that do not need Windows 11 smoother operations, support for low-profile machines. The Windows 11 interface is quite similar to Windows 10X (a version of Windows 10 discontinued). Windows 11 will now place icons on the Start Menu bar, including the Start button and search button (Cortana) in the middle, rather than on the left as on the current version of Windows. Microsoft, however, allows users to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Windows 10 Pro (64-Bit) 22H2 v19045.6332 Multilingual Pre-activated</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 18:38:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-10-x64-bit-5460.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-10-x64-bit-5460.html
</guid><description>
Windows 10 is a Microsoft Windows operating system for PCs and workstations that is part of the Windows NT family of operating systems. This operating system was introduced on September 30, 2014 under the Build 2014 program and was officially released on July 29, 2015
Windows 10 x64 Bit is the most powerful version of windows that comes with Microsoft Edge, a brand new browser built to give you a better web experience. This is a version of Windows 10 Pro - Pre-activated providing the...
</description></item><item><title>Download IK Multimedia AmpliTube 5.10.6</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 18:37:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ik-multimedia-amplitube-1317.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ik-multimedia-amplitube-1317.html
</guid><description>
IK Multimedia AmpliTube 4 Complete is a music studio guitar and bass for Mac / PC works as a standalone application and as a plugin for DAW. AmpliTube recreates the entire signal chain guitar / bass from musical instruments to recording equipment, and made it a very practical and intuitive. But it's also doing it in ways you never dreamed possible. If you're not familiar with the use of the computer to get the guitar tone great, then you will be treated. If you are a master of sound...
</description></item><item><title>Download Revive Faces 2.0.7</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 18:36:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-revive-faces-13762.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-revive-faces-13762.html
</guid><description>
Have you ever looked at an old photo or video and wished you could see those faces clearly again? Time, blurriness, and pixels shouldn't steal the smiles, glances, or stories of the people you love. With Revive Faces, our breakthrough AI-powered restoration software, blurry, smudged, and pixelated faces can now shine with stunning clarity—as if they were taken yesterday.
Why Restore Faces?
	See the unseen again – Our advanced AI not only sharpens images, but also recreates lost...
</description></item><item><title>Download RapidRAW 1.3.13</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 18:36:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rapidraw-13957.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rapidraw-13957.html
</guid><description>
RapidRAW is a modern, high-performance, open-source RAW photo editor, designed to deliver a fast and clean editing experience with a lightweight footprint (under 30MB). Built with performance and usability in mind, the software is aimed at photographers who want a simple, efficient, and fun workflow without compromising performance.
Key Features
	GPU-accelerated processing: Uses a custom WGSL shader to process all image adjustments on the GPU, allowing for smooth, responsive editing...
</description></item><item><title>Download IK Multimedia Tonex Max 1.10.3</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 18:35:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ik-multimedia-tonex-max-7877.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ik-multimedia-tonex-max-7877.html
</guid><description>
TONEX software uses groundbreaking AI Machine Modeling technology to let you model the sound of any amp, cabinet, or combo and turn it into a plug-in, all with precision sounds are almost indistinguishable from reality. You can instantly play up to the more than 1,000 already available Melody Models along with browsing, performing, and downloading more and more Melody Models available on TONEX in ToneNET.
Features of IK Multimedia Tonex Max
	Modeled tone generator, player,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Minimal Firewall 2.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 18:35:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minimal-firewall-13877.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minimal-firewall-13877.html
</guid><description>
Minimal Firewall works in conjunction with Windows Firewall to block all unknown connections by default, prompting you to create application-based rules to mitigate malware, telemetry, and data leaks. Completely eliminate applications that call home without your knowledge. Minimal Firewall provides a more secure and integrated approach by interacting directly with the native Windows Firewall, eliminating the need for risky system modifications.
Core Features
	Lockdown Mode: The core...
</description></item><item><title>Download Let It Be Light 2.0.6</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 18:34:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-let-it-be-light-13761.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-let-it-be-light-13761.html
</guid><description>
Let It Be Light – Illuminate the Invisible, Unleash Infinite Content! Tired of dark, underexposed footage that could be your next viral hit? Say hello to Let It Be Light – revolutionary AI image and video processing software that turns dull clips into beautiful, well-lit masterpieces!
Why Let It Be Light?
	Unlock Hidden Content – ​​Turn dark, grainy, or underexposed footage from film, old archives, or social media into crisp, bright, and useful content. No more discarding...
</description></item><item><title>Download PCSX2 2.4.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 18:34:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pcsx2-4470.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pcsx2-4470.html
</guid><description>
PCSX2 is a software application copy your Playstation 2, allowing you to play the game on your computer. As a gaming machine, virtual PCSX2 can overcome the hardware limitations to bring you these important advantages such as the ability to use the memory card is not limited to save games, screen resolution, custom, game cheats, save game is loading at any time during your game - play, the ability to tom to use any controller compatible Windows operating system and HD recordings of your...
</description></item><item><title>Download TeamTalk 5.20</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 18:33:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-teamtalk-7663.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-teamtalk-7663.html
</guid><description>
TeamTalk is an application that allows users to have full control over their communication channel, it allows access to publicly available rooms (hosted on the machine). owner of TeamTalk) or create a fully customized, standalone server. TeamTalk is a cross-platform utility that supports connection to Windows OS, macOS and Linux distributions. That way, you can connect remotely with people from anywhere and from all backgrounds, and you can have the added benefit of flexibility.
With...
</description></item><item><title>Download CSI SAP2000 Ultimate 26.3.0.3220</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 18:32:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-csi-sap2000-1450.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-csi-sap2000-1450.html
</guid><description>
CSI SAP2000 is glad to announce the availability of version SAP2000 21.0.2. Those interesting new improvements have been implemented in SAP2000 v21 related to Download, analysis and design.
The models shown behavior convergence is slow in the previous version should be running again in the new version to verify results. The new results will be more accurate in case of observed significant difference between results of old and new. Moreover, the pattern of friction has been changed from...
</description></item><item><title>Download Betterbird 140.3.0esr-bb11</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 18:31:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-betterbird-8318.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-betterbird-8318.html
</guid><description>
Betterbird is a tweaked version of Mozilla Thunderbird, Thunderbird on steroids, if you will. It closely follows Thunderbird's Extended Support Releases (ESRs), thus avoiding the mistakes of other forks that cause it to quickly lose track of upstream Thunderbird, thus opening users to vulnerabilities. security.
Betterbird makes emailing safer, faster and easier than ever with the implementation of industry best features like smart spam filter, built-in spell checker , extension support,...
</description></item><item><title>Download TheAeroClock 9.12</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 18:31:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-theaeroclock-1145.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-theaeroclock-1145.html
</guid><description>
TheAeroClock is software that helps create and display accurate clock right on the screen of your computer. TheAeroClock is a simple clock time display current system of you in the form of analog clock display (with second option) on the desktop. You can adjust the size and opacity of the clock and choose from several textures to customize the clock screen.
TheAeroClock - clock on the Desktop
Features of TheAeroClock
	Display the correct time
	Beauty desktop background computer
	Uses...
</description></item><item><title>Download Picture Window Pro 8.0.530</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 18:30:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-picture-window-pro-7452.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-picture-window-pro-7452.html
</guid><description>
Picture Window Pro is a powerful image editing tool designed for serious photographers with strict creative and quality standards. Its comprehensive set of photo editing and editing tools let you control and shape every aspect of your images.
Picture Window Pro 8 is a complete rewrite of Picture Window Pro 7. It features non-destructive image editing through a novel interface based on an image tree. It also fully supports large, high-resolution displays and can be used in dual monitor...
</description></item><item><title>Download CSI Bridge Advanced with Rating 26.3.0.3324</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 18:28:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-csi-bridge-advanced-4363.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-csi-bridge-advanced-4363.html
</guid><description>
CSI Bridge Advanced - modeling, analysis and structural design requirements have been integrated into CSiBridge to create technical tools computer optimization. The ease with which all this work can do for gifted CSiBridge software programs flexible and effective available on the market today.
CSI Bridge Advanced - analysis and design of Bridges
Using CSI Bridge Advanced engineers can easily determine the shape complex requirements, boundary conditions and loading case. The model...
</description></item><item><title>Download Clementine Music Player 1.4.1-53</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 18:24:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-clementine-4762.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-clementine-4762.html
</guid><description>
Clementine is a tools multi-platform software which allows you to listen to music from hard drive, library, audio CDS or the Internet, as well as manage it, edit the card and see the lyrics. Clementine is inspired by Amarok 1.4, focusing on a easy to use interface for searching and playing your music.
Clementine also allows you can view track information such as length, bit rate, sample rate, size, file type, number of times played and your ranking, as well as complete the card...
</description></item><item><title>Download Explzh 9.85</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 18:23:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-explzh-2278.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-explzh-2278.html
</guid><description>
Explzh is software that originated from Japan. This program works with most formats, can extract the file directly to FTP server, split large files into multiple smaller size. I would like to note that the storage supports encryption of files compressed using AES algorithm, has a system of tabs in the main window, you can search for the information you need in the repository and work with files, batch mode is done.
Explzh - Compress and decompress file
The file is support work with the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Secret Video Downloader 1.0.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 18:22:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secret-video-downloader-13775.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secret-video-downloader-13775.html
</guid><description>
Secret Video Downloader is a free application designed to facilitate easy video downloading from various websites. It leverages the yt-dlp command line program to efficiently grab video content, allowing users to save videos in the highest quality available without complicated installation or configuration. The tool has a minimalist interface focused on simplicity: the user pastes the video URL into the built-in browser, clicks the Download button, and the video is added to the download...
</description></item><item><title>Download WindowTextExtractor 2.2.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 18:22:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windowtextextractor-6756.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windowtextextractor-6756.html
</guid><description>
WindowTextExtractor allows you to take the text from any window of the operating system including microsoft office programs, console windows, password text boxes, etc. It can restore the password stored after the flower sign (*******) from most windows applications. It also displays a detailed window and its process information and allows you to photograph the window screen.
Use:
	Launch WindowTextExtractor on your system.
	Now just drag the 'Find window' button to receive window...
</description></item><item><title>Download ClevCalc - Calculator 2.24.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 18:21:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-clevcalc-calculator-8333.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-clevcalc-calculator-8333.html
</guid><description>
ClevCalc - Calculator is a mobile application that provides calculator functionality for Android devices. This is a simple, easy-to-use calculator application that can perform basic mathematical operations such as addition, subtraction, multiplication and division as well as more advanced functions such as square roots, logarithms and trigonometric functions.&amp;lt; /p&amp;gt;
Features of ClevCalc - Calculator
	Basic math operations such as addition, subtraction, multiplication and...
</description></item><item><title>Download AndroVid Pro Video Editor 7.0.8.3</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 18:21:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-androvid-pro-video-editor-9268.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-androvid-pro-video-editor-9268.html
</guid><description>
AndroVid Pro Video Editor is a mobile application for Android devices that allows users to edit videos on their phones or tablets. It offers a wide range of editing tools and features that allow users to create professional-looking videos with ease. In addition to editing features, AndroVid Pro Video Editor also includes a series of video playback tools, such as the ability to play videos in slow motion or fast motion, loop videos, and create video collages.
AndroVid Pro Video Editor...
</description></item><item><title>Download 1Weather: Forecast &amp;amp; Radar 11.3.5</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 18:20:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-1weather-forecast-radar-8846.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-1weather-forecast-radar-8846.html
</guid><description>
1Weather is the most popular weather application on Google Play. Whether you want to check temperatures, forecast precipitation, Doppler radar, or simply track the current phases of the sun and moon, 1Weather has you covered. Plus, it's got an outstanding design that makes getting your weather information easy and fun.
Track current conditions and forecasts for your location and up to 12 locations of your choice. Access charts, precipitation forecasts, maps, weather information and...
</description></item></channel></rss>