<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 20:00:45 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 20:00:45 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download hashcat 7.0.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 02 Aug 2025 16:31:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hashcat-6759.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hashcat-6759.html
</guid><description>
hashcat is the world's fastest and most advanced password recovery utility, supporting five unique attack modes for over 300 highly-optimized hashing algorithms. hashcat currently supports CPUs, GPUs, and other hardware accelerators on Linux, Windows, and macOS and has facilities to help enable distributed password cracking.
Features of hashcat
	Open-Source (MIT License)
	Multi-OS (Linux, Windows, and macOS)
	Multi-Platform (CPU, GPU, APU, etc., everything that comes with an OpenCL...
</description></item><item><title>Download Privacy Eraser Free 6.21.0 Build 5321</title><pubDate> Sat, 02 Aug 2025 16:31:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-privacy-eraser-free-9160.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-privacy-eraser-free-9160.html
</guid><description>
Privacy Eraser is a software tool that helps protect user privacy by securely erasing or deleting unwanted data from their computer or device. This tool is designed to delete browsing history, cookies, cache, temporary files and other sensitive information that may be stored on the computer.
Privacy Eraser can be used to clear browsing history of popular web browsers such as Google Chrome, Mozilla Firefox and Microsoft Edge. It can also clear the history and cache of other applications,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Battery Notifier 3.1.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 02 Aug 2025 16:31:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-battery-notifier-7578.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-battery-notifier-7578.html
</guid><description>
Battery Notifier is a free and Open Source application that monitors the status of your battery charge and notifies you when the battery is full or you need to connect a charger. It also acts as a system information tool providing detailed information about the designed capacity and current and remaining battery life.
You can turn off full or low battery notification and define battery percentage to notify you in Settings. Other settings include custom sound, dark mode, and window...
</description></item><item><title>Download AVS Image Converter 7.1.1.181</title><pubDate> Sat, 02 Aug 2025 16:29:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs-image-converter-4021.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs-image-converter-4021.html
</guid><description>
AVS Image Converter is a comprehensive application and have the ability to allow you to switch quickly and easily the digital images of yourself between many formats, including RAW, JPEG, GIF, TGA, PNG, PDF, TIFF, RAS, JPEG 2000. and many other types . The application comes with a variety of presets to change image size will allow you to easily resize your photos to the different print formats. You can also use the presets this to adjust their images for slideshows can be shared on social...
</description></item><item><title>Download Hasleo Disk Clone 5.5.2.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 02 Aug 2025 16:29:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hasleo-disk-clone-6017.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hasleo-disk-clone-6017.html
</guid><description>
Hasleo Disk Clone is a free Windows copy software and all of one can help you move Windows to another disk, copy one disk to another or copy a partition to another.
The benefits of Hasleo Disk Clone:
1. Move Windows to SSD or HDD (smaller or larger) without reinstalling Windows and applications.
2. Copy one disc to another (smaller or larger) disk as backup.
3. Copy a partition to another location without losing any data.
Features of Hasleo Disk Clone
	System, Disk and...
</description></item><item><title>Download SolidCAM 2025 SP2 HF1 for SolidWorks 2018-2025</title><pubDate> Sat, 02 Aug 2025 16:28:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-solidcam-3151.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-solidcam-3151.html
</guid><description>
SolidCAM - The Leading Integrated CAM Solution with the Amazing iMachining Technology. Get the 'Best-in-Class' CAM Solution for Efficient &amp;amp; Profitable CNC-Programming Inside Your CAD
SolidCAM - SolidCAM for SolidWorks
Amazing iMachining technology..
SolidCAM provides the great value of the revolutionary and amazing iMachining technology.
iMachining saves 70% and more in CNC machining time
iMachining extends cutting tool life dramatically
The unique iMachining Technology Wizard,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Display Driver Uninstaller (DDU) 18.1.3.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 02 Aug 2025 16:26:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-display-driver-uninstaller-1999.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-display-driver-uninstaller-1999.html
</guid><description>
Display Driver Uninstaller (DDU) help to easily completely remove the packages and drivers graphics cards AMD, NVIDIA and Intel from your system without leaving any rest whatsoever. Display Driver Uninstaller will automatically detect your current GPU and allows you to delete drivers, registry and files related only by the click of a button. It will also prevent Windows automatically re-install drivers when you reboot your computer, leaving you a drivers graphics common until you install...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ultra Adware Killer 10.9.8</title><pubDate> Sat, 02 Aug 2025 16:25:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ultra-adware-killer-2137.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ultra-adware-killer-2137.html
</guid><description>
Ultra Adware Killer is a software dedicated to block and remove adware annoying, sluggish in performance of your operating system. Ultra Adware Killer interface is quite good-looking when the functions are arranged in tabs for easy control and use. App has the ability to scan the system and detect Adware on the browsers Internet Explorer, Chrome, FireFox. All the processes, the file contains Adware or doubt are software, ads are displayed for you to conduct screening and removal.
Ultra...
</description></item><item><title>Download Universal Media Server 14.13.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 02 Aug 2025 16:25:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-universal-media-server-2364.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-universal-media-server-2364.html
</guid><description>
Universal Media Server is a media server UPnP compatible multi-platform DLNA. The purpose of this software is to give you a chance to stabilize to make the exchange quick and convenient files necessary. Server the device supports the different output and facilitate the process of exchanging information between a computer and necessary equipment. The development is based on PS3 Media Server, which means you can interact with the Playstation 3, Xbox 360, as well as TV Samsung or...
</description></item><item><title>Download Scale Photo Up 2.0.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 02 Aug 2025 16:24:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-scale-photo-up-13763.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-scale-photo-up-13763.html
</guid><description>
Are you tired of low-resolution, pixelated footage that stifles your creativity? Say goodbye to grainy memories and say hello to Scale Photo Up – groundbreaking AI software that doubles resolution, enhances detail, and smooths out imperfections in your photos and videos with stunning clarity!
Why Scale Photo Up?
	Upscale 2x – No loss of quality! – Turn blurry, low-resolution photos and videos into sharp, high-resolution masterpieces. Perfect for breathing new life into old...
</description></item><item><title>Download ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro 15.25.0801</title><pubDate> Sat, 02 Aug 2025 16:24:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-videotube-downloader-pro-1276.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-videotube-downloader-pro-1276.html
</guid><description>
ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro is the professional version support download videos and playlists from YouTube, videos from Dailymotion, BBC iPlayer, ITV Player, ABC,  FOX,CBS.com Vimeo, Prosieben, Metacafe, Blip.tv CBC.ca many more video sites. After the video is downloaded, you can convert them to the formats compatible with iPad, iPhone, iPod, MPEG-4, H. 264, MP3, AC3.
ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro - Download videos on Youtube
This is one of the software download the most...
</description></item><item><title>Download MCBoot VN 2025 Pro 11.0 build 270625</title><pubDate> Sat, 02 Aug 2025 16:24:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mcboot-vn-7284.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mcboot-vn-7284.html
</guid><description>
Windows PE (WinPE) is a small operating system used to install, deploy, and repair desktop versions of Windows, Windows Server, and other Windows operating systems. MCBoot VN is a set of tools to create bootable USB-HDD for two MBR legacy and UEFI-GPT standards. The purpose of MCBoot VN is to provide users with a BOOT with all the necessary tools and with the simplest operation, but still have to have a versatile and professional computer rescue usb.
Features of MCBoot VN
	This is the...
</description></item><item><title>Download R-Studio 9.5 Build 191580 Network / Technician</title><pubDate> Sat, 02 Aug 2025 16:23:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-studio-1415.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-studio-1415.html
</guid><description>
R-Studio is a group of software data recovery and data recovery powerful and effective. -STUDIO is the solution to recover most comprehensive data for the file restored from the variants NTFS, NTFS5, ReFS, FAT12 / 16/32, exFAT, HFS / HFS + (Macintosh), Little and Big Endian of UFS1 / UFS2 (FreeBSD / OpenBSD / NetBSD / Solaris) and Ext2 / Ext3 / Ext4 partition FS (Linux).
R-Studio is also used to recover file raw (scan known file types) for the file system is damaged or not determined. It...
</description></item><item><title>Download Revive Faces 2.0.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 02 Aug 2025 16:22:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-revive-faces-13762.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-revive-faces-13762.html
</guid><description>
Have you ever looked at an old photo or video and wished you could see those faces clearly again? Time, blurriness, and pixels shouldn't steal the smiles, glances, or stories of the people you love. With Revive Faces, our breakthrough AI-powered restoration software, blurry, smudged, and pixelated faces can now shine with stunning clarity—as if they were taken yesterday.
Why Restore Faces?
	See the unseen again – Our advanced AI not only sharpens images, but also recreates lost...
</description></item><item><title>Download IK Multimedia T-RackS 6 MAX 6.3.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 02 Aug 2025 16:21:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ik-multimedia-t-racks-1781.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ik-multimedia-t-racks-1781.html
</guid><description>
IK Multimedia T-RackS: World-class mixing and mastering plug-ins on demand, Close your eyes and picture a store full of cool, powerful processing gear including compressors, limiters, reverbs can, de-essers, multiband processors, and a shelf full of vintage, legendary gear emulations. In short, a dream store for recording musicians, engineers and producers.
IK Multimedia T-RackS 5 Complete
Features available by upgrading to T-RackS 5, T-RackS 5 Deluxe or T-RackS 5 MAX. T-RackS 5 CS...
</description></item><item><title>Download XYplorer 27.10.0300</title><pubDate> Sat, 02 Aug 2025 16:16:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-533.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-533.html
</guid><description>
XYplorer - File Manager for Windows is software that supports users to manage files on the Window quickly and to arrange the folder tidy. XYplorer features tabbed browsing, search, files, powerful, preview, flexible, highly customizable interface, dual frame options and a variety of unique ways to automate effective tasks often repeat. It's fast, lightweight, and portable.
Features XYplorer
	XYplorer is a file manager mobile. It does not require any settings, store all configuration...
</description></item><item><title>Download Let It Be Light 2.0.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 02 Aug 2025 16:16:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-let-it-be-light-13761.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-let-it-be-light-13761.html
</guid><description>
Let It Be Light – Illuminate the Invisible, Unleash Infinite Content! Tired of dark, underexposed footage that could be your next viral hit? Say hello to Let It Be Light – revolutionary AI image and video processing software that turns dull clips into beautiful, well-lit masterpieces!
Why Let It Be Light?
	Unlock Hidden Content – ​​Turn dark, grainy, or underexposed footage from film, old archives, or social media into crisp, bright, and useful content. No more discarding...
</description></item><item><title>Download Freeplane 1.12.12</title><pubDate> Sat, 02 Aug 2025 16:15:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-freeplane-2823.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-freeplane-2823.html
</guid><description>
Freeplane is a program free, open-source, allowing you to express his thoughts, which allows you to exchange information, useful for both students and at work. If you have an idea or plan, you can bring all this into the edit form of maps and diagrams. The software will work correctly on any operating system that supports Java. There is a mobile version can be run from removable media.
Freeplane - Create mapping
Can extend the functionality of Freeplane using Add-ons and scripts. You...
</description></item><item><title>Download Karaosoft Karma 2026.0.7</title><pubDate> Sat, 02 Aug 2025 16:08:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-karma-2379.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-karma-2379.html
</guid><description>
Karma is an enhancement program that helps you tune, karaoke can view the text of the files sound different. At first glance, after launch, the layout may seem complicated, unclear where to start. You can customize the display prompts to understand the function of each parameter is highlighted integrated.
Management program your karaoke a easy way. Search no need to click, drag and drop feature and many other unique features designed to bring you the easiest management for the program...
</description></item><item><title>Download InventorCAM 2025 SP2 HF1 for Autodesk Inventor 2018-2025</title><pubDate> Sat, 02 Aug 2025 16:08:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-inventorcam-1859.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-inventorcam-1859.html
</guid><description>
InventorCAM is a CAD / CAM system the new generation developed by company SolidCAM Ltd of Israel (official distributor in Russia - software consistency). This system is a complete solution to automate production of machining metal. With the use of a variety of strategies is provided by InventorCAM for lathe, milling, turn-milling and machining, electrical erosion, a technician can quickly prepare the necessary set of control programs for machining products. InventorCAM provides a wide...
</description></item><item><title>Download SolidCAM 2025 SP2 HF1 for Solid Edge 2020-2025</title><pubDate> Sat, 02 Aug 2025 16:06:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-solidcam-for-solid-edge-10117.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-solidcam-for-solid-edge-10117.html
</guid><description>
SolidCAM is renowned computer-aided manufacturing (CAM) software that integrates directly into various CAD systems, including SolidWorks. It provides the tools to create efficient and accurate toolpaths for CNC machining operations. SolidCAM aims to streamline the process of turning a computer-generated design into a physical part by generating toolpaths that control the movement of a CNC machine.
This system is a comprehensive solution for the automation of metalworking production....
</description></item><item><title>Download Stardock Start11 2.5.5 Beta</title><pubDate> Sat, 02 Aug 2025 16:05:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stardock-start11-7029.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stardock-start11-7029.html
</guid><description>
Start11 is an application capable of customizing the Start Menu and Taskbar on Windows 11 and Windows 10. This is an application that allows users to customize Windows 11 to suit their preferences. his personal. Start11 will help you bring the new Start Menu of Windows 11 to Windows 10. And vice versa, Start11 also helps you to bring the Start Menu of Windows 10 to Windows 11.
Start11 also helps users bring some functions of Windows 10 to Windows 11 through customizing the Taskbar such...
</description></item><item><title>Download Scientific Toolworks Understand 7.1 Build 1232</title><pubDate> Sat, 02 Aug 2025 16:05:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-scientific-toolworks-understand-1532.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-scientific-toolworks-understand-1532.html
</guid><description>
Scientific Toolworks Understand is a tool of static analysis to management, measurement and analysis, ability to program. This tool can measure multiple metrics and give you the clear chart about the indicator code different. For example: number of layers, number of project files, number of methods, number of lines, blank lines, comments, dead code, rate, comment on code, complexity in the cycle and the level of trouble of the code, the level of dependence of code together, the rate of...
</description></item><item><title>Download CoolUtils Total Audio Converter 6.1.0.284</title><pubDate> Sat, 02 Aug 2025 16:03:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-total-audio-converter-807.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-total-audio-converter-807.html
</guid><description>
CoolUtils Total Audio Converter is the convert audio files of various extensions, various as MP3, WAV, RMVB, MIDI, AMR, FLAC and M4A. Total Audio Converter is a program interface is quite easy and convenient combined control panel in which you can select the installation size and source.
Total Audio Converter supports batch conversion. This is a very good tool for those who love music. The program supports ID3 tags and CUE, convert the audio clips that don't create WAV files intermediate...
</description></item><item><title>Download S.O.S Security Suite 2.9.8</title><pubDate> Sat, 02 Aug 2025 15:58:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sos-security-suite-6227.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sos-security-suite-6227.html
</guid><description>
S.O.S Security Suite is a free, user-friendly app that helps you remove malware, ad software, and spy software, and also prevent infection. There is also a hardware error detection and security error detection and system optimization module. All these features combine to bring you what stands for the application: A more secure and optimal system.
S.O.S Security Suite is a successor to UVK and is designed to help you remove malware, ad software, and spy software, and help you not get...
</description></item></channel></rss>