<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 05:40:59 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 05:40:59 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download KMPlayer (KMP) 2025.7.28.15 x64 / 4.2.3.22 x86</title><pubDate> Mon, 28 Jul 2025 20:50:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kmplayer-kmp-902.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kmplayer-kmp-902.html
</guid><description>
KMPlayer (KMP) is software watch movies listen to music multi-function for video enthusiasts. KMPlayer development is many types of the format different. KMPlayer has improved on sound quality, images when listening to music and watching movies, the playback speed of video is faster, more codec player is added to the software video decoder is optimized.
KMPlayer also supports a variety of audio formats and video and offers a the interface can be customized with the preview coverflow and...
</description></item><item><title>Download 3uTools 3.27.015</title><pubDate> Mon, 28 Jul 2025 20:50:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-3utools-4336.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-3utools-4336.html
</guid><description>
3uTools is tool data management and file iOS the most effective. 3uTools help easily manage the apps, photos, music, ringtones, video files and other multimedia. Watch full the different status of iOS devices, including activating, unlocking, status, pin lock and iCloud, as well as detailed information about iOS &amp;amp; iDevice. 3uTools can automate the hardware available for iOS devices. iOS flashing in normal mode, DFU mode and recovery mode are supported. Unlocking with a click of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe DNG Converter 17.4.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 28 Jul 2025 20:49:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-dng-converter-2452.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-dng-converter-2452.html
</guid><description>
Adobe DNG Converter, a free utility that converts files from more than 350 cameras to DNG, enables you to easily convert the files raw exclusively for camera file raw DNG more universal. A program strong enough which allows you to convert the source files RAW to DNG format popular and more convenient with a few clicks of the mouse.
DNG allows photographers to archive files, raw images of them in a single format for easy cataloging and access in the future. With specification formats are...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe DNG Converter for macOS 17.4.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 28 Jul 2025 20:49:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/mac/download-adobe-dng-converter-for-mac-3708.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/mac/download-adobe-dng-converter-for-mac-3708.html
</guid><description>
Adobe DNG Converter for Mac (DNG) is a publicly available storage format for raw files created by various digital cameras. This addresses the lack of an open standard for raw files created by individual camera models and ensures that photographers have easy access to their files. Hundreds of software manufacturers such as Apple and Google have developed support for DNG. And venerable camera manufacturers like Leica, Casio, Ricoh, Samsung, and Pentax have introduced cameras that offer...
</description></item><item><title>Download AB Download Manager 1.6.8</title><pubDate> Mon, 28 Jul 2025 20:48:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ab-download-manager-12399.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ab-download-manager-12399.html
</guid><description>
With this application, you can easily download files from anywhere. Enjoy fast, free downloads with seamless browser extension support. It is built to be a desktop application that allows you to manage and organize your downloads better than before.
AB Download Manager features
	Simple and modern UI: Simple UI and dark mode by default
	Faster download speeds: Download files using multiple connections to increase your download speed by up to 500%
	Download Queue: Create and manage your...
</description></item><item><title>Download XYplorer 27.10.0100</title><pubDate> Mon, 28 Jul 2025 20:47:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-533.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-533.html
</guid><description>
XYplorer - File Manager for Windows is software that supports users to manage files on the Window quickly and to arrange the folder tidy. XYplorer features tabbed browsing, search, files, powerful, preview, flexible, highly customizable interface, dual frame options and a variety of unique ways to automate effective tasks often repeat. It's fast, lightweight, and portable.
Features XYplorer
	XYplorer is a file manager mobile. It does not require any settings, store all configuration...
</description></item><item><title>Download Omidsoft Red Burner 18.20</title><pubDate> Mon, 28 Jul 2025 20:46:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-red-burner-10119.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-red-burner-10119.html
</guid><description>
Red Burner is a lightweight burning software based on Blue Burner with full functionality to work with ISO/CUE images and drives. Start the move to a lightweight, yet powerful, and time-saving standalone optical disc burner with the simplest user interface and fastest possible burning algorithm.
Features of Red Burner
	Fastest possible CD/DVD/BD burning algorithm
	Standard, dual-layer and high-capacity media recording
	Browse ISO/CUE images via internal image browser
	Writable M-Disc,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Auslogics BoostSpeed 14.0.1.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 28 Jul 2025 20:46:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-auslogics-boostspeed-140.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-auslogics-boostspeed-140.html
</guid><description>
Auslogics BoostSpeed is software support speed up an Internet connection for the computer with Auslogics BoostSpeed restrictions on your Internet speed will be corrective and limited to the lowest level to bring high efficiency in work as well as in their learning. Auslogics BoostSpeed improves the speed surfing the web for the computer through the way in data compression and image to gảm capacity when participating online, with the mechanism and how it works so users also software feel...
</description></item><item><title>Download Any Video Downloader Pro 9.3.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 28 Jul 2025 20:45:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-video-downloader-pro-3731.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-video-downloader-pro-3731.html
</guid><description>
Any Video Downloader Pro is software support you can download video HD 720p, 1080p, 2K, 4K and 8K from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion, Vimeo, Metacafe and thousands of video sharing sites, other. It is a tool to speed up multi-threading can speed up your download faster up to 5 times. This helpful program support download at the same time. Any Video Downloader Pro lets you download multiple videos at the same time. Moreover, it allows you to pause and resume downloads if you need more...
</description></item><item><title>Download Systweak PDF Editor 1.0.0.7957</title><pubDate> Mon, 28 Jul 2025 20:45:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-systweak-pdf-editor-11484.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-systweak-pdf-editor-11484.html
</guid><description>
Systweak PDF Editor is a fast and simple solution to edit, convert, sign, protect, compress PDF files and make scanned PDF files searchable and can choose. With Systweak PDF Editor, quickly convert your PDF files into a variety of editable formats. Converting PDF files to and from any MS Office files, images, ebooks, web pages, and other formats just got easier.
For working and editing PDF files, Systweak PDF editor offers many features and tools. Using them, you can mark text for...
</description></item><item><title>Download Garden Planner 3.8.76</title><pubDate> Mon, 28 Jul 2025 20:45:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-garden-planner-186.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-garden-planner-186.html
</guid><description>
Garden Planner : If you want to create a garden plan, create a landscape by activity or simply be curious, then you can download Garden Planner .   Garden Planner is a program that helps the user to design a dream garden through the layout and arrangement of plants, plants, buildings and objects, creating living spaces. style is consistent with the user's criteria and standards.
Garden Planner application is very simple, just select bushes, other plants, trees, pond and drag them into...
</description></item><item><title>Download DiskMax 7.25</title><pubDate> Mon, 28 Jul 2025 20:40:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-diskmax-5940.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-diskmax-5940.html
</guid><description>
Using DiskMax to periodically make a robust drive cleaner and optimize performance to keep your PC healthy. After using DiskMax, you will notice that your system will work better, the apps will start faster, the files will open faster and the games will run better. Just run DiskMax over time to keep your system steady.
Even if you are an advanced user, DiskMax will be useful to you because it automate all the tasks needed to keep your system clean and quickly, helping you enjoy the...
</description></item><item><title>Download PPTube 10.5.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 28 Jul 2025 20:39:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pptube-12556.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pptube-12556.html
</guid><description>
PPTube Video Downloader allows you to download HD videos easily, from 720p, 1080p, 2K, 4K and 8K. You can save multiple videos at the same time. Just copy multiple video URLs from various websites and paste them into PPTube Downloader, then you can download multiple videos in seconds.
In addition, you can download HD videos from Instagram, TikTok, Facebook, Apple Music, Vimeo, adult websites, etc. and convert them to MP4, MP3, MOV, AAC and more than 20 other output formats. PPTube...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinCatalog 2024.14.1.728</title><pubDate> Mon, 28 Jul 2025 20:39:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wincatalog-615.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wincatalog-615.html
</guid><description>
WinCatalog 2018 is a software cataloguer multi-function for the disk, file, folder, and any objects not files. Not always easy to track the location of a number of files in your computer, especially if you have a huge collection of CD and DVD. If you are one of those users, then surely there will be appropriate tools to work with such a task. WinCatalog is a software utility designed to help you find documents and data from your computer by building an index that allows you immediate...
</description></item><item><title>Download Simple Sticky Notes 6.8</title><pubDate> Mon, 28 Jul 2025 20:39:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-simple-sticky-notes-2180.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-simple-sticky-notes-2180.html
</guid><description>
Simple Sticky Notes is software that creates sticky notes on screen Desktop computer help you easily remember the schedule of his. Simple Sticky Notes allow users to fashion digital sticky / post it notes and almost "sticky" notes on a desktop operation Windows. It is completely ideal for the kind of users who need to write everything down with pen and paper to avoid the discomfort of forget everything. This program of articles simple digital notes, it certainly will prove to be of great...
</description></item><item><title>Download RapidRAW 1.3.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 28 Jul 2025 20:38:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rapidraw-13957.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rapidraw-13957.html
</guid><description>
RapidRAW is a modern, high-performance, open-source RAW photo editor, designed to deliver a fast and clean editing experience with a lightweight footprint (under 30MB). Built with performance and usability in mind, the software is aimed at photographers who want a simple, efficient, and fun workflow without compromising performance.
Key Features
	GPU-accelerated processing: Uses a custom WGSL shader to process all image adjustments on the GPU, allowing for smooth, responsive editing...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ahnenblatt 4.32.0.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 28 Jul 2025 20:38:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ahnenblatt-3844.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ahnenblatt-3844.html
</guid><description>
Ahnenblatt is a genealogy software full-featured, easy to use suitable for beginners and even pedigree has the experience to organize genealogy research by you. Use plausibility checks to find out the inaccuracies in your family and create the chart impressive with just a few mouse clicks.
Ahnenblatt - Create family tree,
Recently, there has been strong increase of the general interest of the public for genealogical tree. Users who desire to track their heritage have many tools at...
</description></item><item><title>Download iDownerGo Pro 10.5.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 28 Jul 2025 20:37:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idownergo-12439.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idownergo-12439.html
</guid><description>
iDownerGo is the best tool that allows users to download videos, music and playlists from more than 10,000 streaming sites. It can easily convert videos to MP4, MOV, MKV, 3GP, AAC, WAV, FLAC and other formats on PC and Mac. With this amazing program, users can enjoy their favorite media content without restrictions.
iDownerGo Features
	Download any video up to 8K resolution
	Download 1080p videos online from over 10,000 popular streaming sites easily.
	Save any video in various...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Downloader 9.15.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 28 Jul 2025 20:37:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html
</guid><description>
YTD Youtube Downloader is an application that reliable and intuitive, allowing you to quickly download YouTube videos and save them to your computer. You can also convert the media files to the format desired video or extract audio streams and save separately. YTD Youtube Downloader lets you save your favorite clips of yourself from Youtube, Facebook, Vimeo and Dailymotion to your desktop. The software supports URLS from many web site hosting, multimedia and allows you to download desired...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Video Downloader 11.26</title><pubDate> Mon, 28 Jul 2025 20:36:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-video-downloader-9636.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-video-downloader-9636.html
</guid><description>
YT Video Downloader is software used to easily and quickly download any video or audio content from any website in HD quality using video downloader online. Save videos from almost any website supported by a video downloader on your local hard drive. Media search is a convenient way to do this.
Features of YT Video Downloader
	Download videos from hundreds of video sites.
	Really increase your download speed by up to 500% or even more!
	Download 8K, 5K, 4K Ultra HD, 2K Quad HD, 1080p...
</description></item><item><title>Download WindowTop Pro 5.28.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 28 Jul 2025 20:36:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windowtop-6955.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windowtop-6955.html
</guid><description>
WindowTop is a program that pins windows on Desktop, in other words it sets the window to float above all other program windows, creating transparency for the windows. that window via a dedicated slider, which supports adjusting transparency, changing the color of application windows or similar programs with the dark theme of the Windows 10 operating system, creating contrast and reducing tension straight, painful for the eyes.
Features of WindowTop
	Put window on top
	Set window to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Hybrid 2025.07.27.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 28 Jul 2025 20:35:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hybrid-2233.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hybrid-2233.html
</guid><description>
Hybrid is a multifunctional program that allows you to record videos on media Blu-ray or AVCHD, also you can convert data in formats x264, Xvid, VP8, ac3, ogg, mp3, aac and flac formats mp4, m2ts, mkv, webm. You can download Hybrid below. Please note that after conversion, you can write the result right into the media. That's not all, you also can use the edit program and the card, you can work with subtitles. You will get a large number of installation, a simple interface, in that it's...
</description></item><item><title>Download PC Assist Software PDF Assist 2.5.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 28 Jul 2025 20:35:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pc-assist-software-pdf-assist-12798.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pc-assist-software-pdf-assist-12798.html
</guid><description>
One of the most widely used file formats today is PDF, due to its many advantages. Not only because it is cross-platform, but also because it is compact, secure and ensures the integrity of graphics, displaying identical content regardless of the device it is viewed on. PDF Assist is a full-featured PDF processing tool that not only acts as a PDF viewer but also comes with options to annotate documents, sort pages, hide sensitive content or completely encrypt a file, convert, merge and...
</description></item><item><title>Download DroidKit 2.3.6.20250728</title><pubDate> Mon, 28 Jul 2025 20:35:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-droidkit-6578.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-droidkit-6578.html
</guid><description>
DroidKit is data recovery software for your mobile device, it will quickly scan your phone memory and save photos, WhatsApp chats and files, messages Messages, contacts and more essential data up to 13 categories, covering almost everything you need every day. All Android phones and tablets are supported. Without rooting your device. No tech skills required. No need to wait many days. You can get back what you've lost with just a few simple clicks, instantly.
Besides, DroidKit also has...
</description></item><item><title>Download EarthTime 6.30.6</title><pubDate> Mon, 28 Jul 2025 20:34:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-earthtime-185.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-earthtime-185.html
</guid><description>
EarthTime is software that displays the time and date local time of any place in the world. This application has database integration good for 3000 city, users can manually add, download at EarthTime if you want to. EarthTime allows you to install for the time zone and current local time.EarthTime displays the Earth according to the view night and day, you can view the map in full screen mode.
EarthTime
The feature on EarthTime
	EarthTime allows users to interact with visualization...
</description></item></channel></rss>