<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 13:47:43 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 13:47:43 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Notepad++ 8.9 + Portable</title><pubDate> Sun, 28 Dec 2025 16:29:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-notepad-1062.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-notepad-1062.html
</guid><description>
Notepad++ is software editor programming editor and edit source code support on Windows platform, working with many other programming languages like ASP, PHP, Java, C#, Python, Jsp... Notepad++ is a source code editor is many programmers choice with many functions than men of it is Notepad.
Notepad++ - tool editor programming
Notepad++ has many features, simple interface, and can combine with many programming languages different. Notepad++ supports you to automatically perform various...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube Downloader 3.9.18 (2512)</title><pubDate> Sun, 28 Dec 2025 16:20:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube Downloader  is a dedicated software that helps users  downloading youtube videos  Favorites on PC for offline viewing. With MediaHuman YouTube  Downloader  you can download videos from youtube website to your computer with  fast speed , with special software development technology that automatically receives videos from Websites, in addition to the ability to download videos from software websites, can convert downloaded video formats to various formats for the purpose...
</description></item><item><title>Download Kotato All Video Downloader Pro 10.0.9</title><pubDate> Sun, 28 Dec 2025 16:19:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kotato-all-video-downloader-pro-5228.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kotato-all-video-downloader-pro-5228.html
</guid><description>
Kotato All Video Downloader Pro is a Windows application professional to download and convert your favorite videos from the video sharing website. It speeds up your downloads up to 5 times! Kotato All Video Downloader Pro can download videos from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion and hundreds of video sharing sites, other. After downloading, you will be able to play them smoother on your PC or your mobile device, even when you don't have Internet access.
The main features of Kotato All...
</description></item><item><title>Download Network LookOut Administrator Pro 5.3.8</title><pubDate> Sun, 28 Dec 2025 16:19:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-network-lookout-administrator-pro-1414.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-network-lookout-administrator-pro-1414.html
</guid><description>
Network LookOut Administrator Pro is application software to control the screen of the computer on the network to help full the right to monitor your computer remotely. Network LookOut Administrator use the most appropriate for LAN network, the benefits that it brought back really great, you can control the computer remotely using the mouse and keyboard , without the need to use these tools other troubles. When employees get into trouble, you only have to help from far away that still...
</description></item><item><title>Download ToolsToo Pro 12.0.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 28 Dec 2025 16:09:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-toolstoo-4430.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-toolstoo-4430.html
</guid><description>
ToolsToo - enhance the capabilities of PowerPoint with the help of additional yield useful and simple this comes with more than 85 powerful tool. Although it may be considered somewhat limiting and likely even too complicated for some people, the PowerPoint, without a doubt, is one of the best options when creating presentations and illustrations. Among other things, the effect of it stems from the fact that it managed to pack a lot of useful features wrapped around a Office UI...
</description></item><item><title>Download WildBit Viewer Pro 6.19 Commercial</title><pubDate> Sun, 28 Dec 2025 16:09:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wildbit-viewer-pro-1694.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wildbit-viewer-pro-1694.html
</guid><description>
WildBit Viewer is compact photo viewer and quick with slideshow and editor. Look in the folder fast, the file list and the thumbnail view. Viewer includes also image info with meta data EXIF support for JPEG and TIFF information and IPTC (IIMV4) (such as information file PhotoShop) from JPEG and TIFF, Thumbview can change the view mode, sorting and thumbnail size is predefined to set thumbnail size quickly.
WildBit Viewer Pro
WildBit Viewer also includes a toolbar shell, you can drop...
</description></item><item><title>Download Net Monitor for Employees Professional 6.4.14</title><pubDate> Sun, 28 Dec 2025 16:08:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-network-lookout-net-monitor-for-employees-professional-2098.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-network-lookout-net-monitor-for-employees-professional-2098.html
</guid><description>
Network LookOut Net Monitor for Employees Professional is a software platform to help manage user activity, gives the ability to inspect and control computer activities, as well as record activity on the screen as AVI file. Net Monitor for Employees Professional allows access from remote computers. This feature proved particularly useful when you want to see the activity of each user on the computer, or assist them perform the work on the computer with the mouse manipulation or the...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter 3.9.18 (2612)</title><pubDate> Sun, 28 Dec 2025 16:01:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-to-mp3-converter-1744.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-to-mp3-converter-1744.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter is the software support download youtube video and convert video to mp3 format fast and most simple. MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter allows you download and convert videos from YouTube and other websites to MP3 format by pasting the YouTube URL into the application. When you paste the URL, the program will display thumbnails for videos and you have the option to customize the title information, artist and album before you begin the process of...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinScan2PDF 9.49 + Portable</title><pubDate> Sun, 28 Dec 2025 16:00:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winscan2pdf-2117.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winscan2pdf-2117.html
</guid><description>
WinScan2PDF is a simple tool that allows you to scan documents from scanner and save them as PDF files. The program also supports multi-page scanning, then will be combined into one PDF document. Useful if your scanning software does not provide PDF conversion.
WinScan2PDF - Scan document to computer
WinScan2PDF allows users to perform scans the entire text or document at the same time to serve for the saved PDF format. Not only that, you also can choose the page any of a text to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Classroom Spy Professional 5.4.13</title><pubDate> Sun, 28 Dec 2025 16:00:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-classroom-spy-professional-916.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-classroom-spy-professional-916.html
</guid><description>
Classroom Spy Professional is a software classroom management effective. Manage and track activities of all the computers of students remotely. Plus, you can share your screen with the activity record of the student, the computer controls for performance, limit the use of the Internet, the application blocks and more.
Classroom Spy Professional - software classroom management
The main features of Classroom Spy Professional
	Display live images of the remote computer.
	You can control...
</description></item><item><title>Download Nero Video 27.0.0.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 28 Dec 2025 15:59:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nero-video-1889.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nero-video-1889.html
</guid><description>
Professional Video for everyone! Nero Video 2019't have anything to look forward to when creating videos and slideshows quickly, easily and professionally. Nero Video out there entire the special features ready for you. With more than 1000 themes and film effect, almost no limits for your creativity. Discover the benefits of Nero Video 2019 today.
Nero Video - Editor, create professional video
Features of Nero Video
	Easily transfer videos and photos from mobile devices, external...
</description></item><item><title>Download TubeMate Downloader 6.0.16</title><pubDate> Sun, 28 Dec 2025 15:58:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubemate-downloader-4250.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubemate-downloader-4250.html
</guid><description>
TubeMate Downloader is a smart application that lets you download any clip you want from the website hosting the main video and convert them in when download at or then. If you need a simple and effective tool to download videos, you can give it a try. With TubeMate Downloader, you can directly drag and drop video link from your browser into the drop-down box or application window to start downloading. You don't even need to copy and paste the video URL.
TubeMate Downloader - Support...
</description></item><item><title>Download Rename Master 4.01</title><pubDate> Sun, 28 Dec 2025 15:58:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rename-master-4524.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rename-master-4524.html
</guid><description>
Rename Master is a powerful application and effectively allow you to easily and quickly rename multiple files just by a click of the mouse. The program can delete, add or replace parts of the filename and also supports renaming files using EXIF tags, and JPEG, MP3 tags, text files, video tag and attribute files.
Rename Master - rename files batch
Neat interface, smart arrangement
Rename Master includes a feature arranged smartly will help you keep your files in order. Unicode support...
</description></item><item><title>Download FreeCommander XE 2026 Build 940</title><pubDate> Sun, 28 Dec 2025 15:57:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-freecommander-xe-2746.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-freecommander-xe-2746.html
</guid><description>
FreeCommander XE is an alternative easy-to-use for manager file windows standard. The program helps you to do daily work in Windows. Here you can find all the necessary functions to manage the database of his. You can take FreeCommander anywhere - just copy the installation directory on a CD or USB-Stick - and you can work with this program on the computer foreign.
FreeCommander XE - a file Manager replacement for windows default
The features of FreeCommander
	Technology board dual -...
</description></item><item><title>Download GSoft4U Music Collection 3.9.5.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 28 Dec 2025 15:56:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gsoft4u-music-collection-2437.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gsoft4u-music-collection-2437.html
</guid><description>
GSoft4U Music Collection is a free software to help you fully organized music collection of an archive can search quality. Archiving process is very simple; put on details related to format, genre, release date, record label, as well as rating the 'why' of it. The artists will be divided up alphabetically for easy access.
GSoft4U Music Collection - Manage music collection
The app will allow you to add additional information into its music, as this of course you must have an Internet...
</description></item><item><title>Download VovSoft Collect URL 4.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 28 Dec 2025 15:48:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-collect-url-7395.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-collect-url-7395.html
</guid><description>
VovSoft Collect URL is an internet scanner like a search engine bot. Starting from the URL the user entered, it lists all the links on the URL. Then it recursively scans all the links in the list. Users can limit URL Crawl to only one domain name. The file extension ignore list can be edited. Connection and response timeout values ​​are editable. Additionally, the user can change the user agent value for HTTP and HTTPS connections.
Features of VovSoft Collect URL
	Scan the...
</description></item><item><title>Download thilmera7 0b184 Rev.7</title><pubDate> Sun, 28 Dec 2025 15:47:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thilmera7-2918.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thilmera7-2918.html
</guid><description>
thilmera7 is an application capable of performing this task and perform it quite well. This is an app that tracks real-time which you can put anywhere on the screen of his computer application and to forward detailed information about memory, disk, network, CPU, GPU, processes, sound and other aspects miscellaneous.
All the controls and options for the application is provided from the context menu right-click. There you can find the table 'properties' from where you can switch and see all...
</description></item><item><title>Download SecretDNS 3.8.3</title><pubDate> Sun, 28 Dec 2025 15:47:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secretdns-12481.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secretdns-12481.html
</guid><description>
SecretDNS provides a quick means to deploy DNS over HTPS, meaning it allows DNS (short for Domain Name Server) resolution to be performed remotely using the HTTPS protocol to encrypts data between the client and the DNS resolver. Its purpose, obviously, is related to data security and user privacy, to prevent unauthorized interception and manipulation of DNS data.
Default DNS settings in SecretDNS use CloudFlare to ensure security. You can change DNS configuration in the dedicated tab...
</description></item><item><title>Download Eventide Ensemble Bundle 2.23.5</title><pubDate> Sun, 28 Dec 2025 15:46:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-eventide-ensemble-bundle-001-9103.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-eventide-ensemble-bundle-001-9103.html
</guid><description>
Eventide Ensemble Bundle is a collection of over 30 high-quality audio processing plugins designed for music production, mixing, and mastering. Each plugin is modeled after a classic hardware processor from the famous Eventide brand and offers a wide range of effects and processing options.
In addition, to truly experience the unique sound of vintage equipment, plug-ins need to be carefully designed to faithfully emulate the nuances of classic analog and digital circuits. Extras in the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Danil Pristupov Fork 2.15.4</title><pubDate> Sun, 28 Dec 2025 15:46:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fork-6879.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fork-6879.html
</guid><description>
Fork is a great Git client app that allows you to keep tabs on every file line so you can know who is the last person to make changes. The simple and intuitive design of this app helps the management of all of your warehouses much easier. The Fork interface is extremely friendly to users. There is a long list of repositories, branches, origins, tags and archives on the left side of the screen.
With Fork, you can also search and open any of the repositories quickly, from the top of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Video Downloader 12.0.15</title><pubDate> Sun, 28 Dec 2025 15:45:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-video-downloader-9636.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-video-downloader-9636.html
</guid><description>
YT Video Downloader is software used to easily and quickly download any video or audio content from any website in HD quality using video downloader online. Save videos from almost any website supported by a video downloader on your local hard drive. Media search is a convenient way to do this.
Features of YT Video Downloader
	Download videos from hundreds of video sites.
	Really increase your download speed by up to 500% or even more!
	Download 8K, 5K, 4K Ultra HD, 2K Quad HD, 1080p...
</description></item><item><title>Download MPV-EASY Player 0.41.0.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 28 Dec 2025 15:45:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mpv-easy-player-3110.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mpv-easy-player-3110.html
</guid><description>
MPV-EASY Player is movies player based on mpv. It comes with easy to use interface, you can quickly adjust many parameters, the default settings are carefully adjusted will be able to stimulate all the performance of the mpv, so use mpv player simple than before a lot.
Basically, MPV-EASY Player is the assembly and combination of MPV, configuring mpv files, the command lua (including all scripts to be shared by other people on github), and the command js with the to read and fully...
</description></item><item><title>Download RAR for Android 7.20 build 130</title><pubDate> Sun, 28 Dec 2025 15:19:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-rar-for-android-8780.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-rar-for-android-8780.html
</guid><description>
RAR for Android is an application that allows users to create, manage and extract compressed files in RAR and ZIP formats on their Android devices. This application is developed by RARLAB, the same company that created the popular WinRAR software for Windows.
RAR can create RAR and ZIP and decompress RAR, ZIP, TAR, GZ, BZ2, XX, 7z, ISO, ARJ archives. List of functions includes command to repair damaged ZIP and RAR files, benchmarking function compatible with RARLAB's WinRAR benchmark,...
</description></item><item><title>Download ProShot 8.32.5.1 build 542</title><pubDate> Sun, 28 Dec 2025 15:19:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-proshot-8195.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-proshot-8195.html
</guid><description>
ProShot is a camera app for Android devices that offers advanced manual controls for photography enthusiasts. It allows users to manually adjust settings such as shutter speed, ISO, white balance, and focus. It also offers a level of integration, a powerful time-lapse mode, and many other features for advanced photography. It's designed for advanced users who want more control over their photos than the default camera app offers.
Camera features of ProShot
	Auto, Program, Manual and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Night Mode Camera Photo Video 3.3.5</title><pubDate> Sun, 28 Dec 2025 15:18:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-night-mode-camera-photo-video-11584.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-night-mode-camera-photo-video-11584.html
</guid><description>
The camera in night mode captures 6 times more light. The best photos and videos can be taken in low light conditions. Fast and simple app for taking bright photos and videos. Even though your images may not illuminate the exotic beauty of nature, or the moon and stars in the sky, or the beautiful ocean waves, or flowers at night: Night Mode Camera ready to do it at the lowest brightness without any additional equipment.
With low light support during photo/video recording, you can...
</description></item></channel></rss>