<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 23:38:37 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 23:38:37 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Adobe Acrobat Reader DC 2025.001.20756</title><pubDate> Wed, 01 Oct 2025 23:50:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-acrobat-reader-3707.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-acrobat-reader-3707.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Acrobat Reader DC is a system of application software and Web services developed by Adobe Systems to view, create, manipulate, print and manage PDF files. With Adobe Acrobat Reader DC, you can create, export, edit, and track PDF files from anywhere - and maintain connection with the recent set of files on all your devices.
Adobe Acrobat Reader current DC is connected with Adobe Document Cloud - help working on the computers and mobile devices becomes easier than ever before. This is...
</description></item><item><title>Download anyPDF 1.4.3.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 01 Oct 2025 23:47:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anypdf-11943.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anypdf-11943.html
</guid><description>
AnyPDF is an integrated PDF viewer and manager as it facilitates viewing and editing of PDF files in a user-friendly manner where users can merge multiple documents, protect and compress important data, etc. This program aims to be a more or less general tool for PDF workflow. That said, it doesn't necessarily specialize in anything specific as it has a number of uses related to working with PDF files.
Features of anyPDF
	User-friendly user interface
	Convert from JPG to...
</description></item><item><title>Download VueScan Pro 9.8.48</title><pubDate> Wed, 01 Oct 2025 23:47:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vuescan-pro-75.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vuescan-pro-75.html
</guid><description>
VueScan Pro l  is one of the software  Scan quality pictures  First and appeared quite soon,  VueScan Pro  always asserted its No. 1 position on the technology pages, awards as well as user reviews. Through many versions, VueScan Pro 9 is greatly improved in terms of interface and features. Supporting most popular image formats today, this software will help you scan images quickly, easy to use and high quality output. With the color balance mode, you won't have to worry about blurring the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Textadept 12.9</title><pubDate> Wed, 01 Oct 2025 23:46:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-textadept-2878.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-textadept-2878.html
</guid><description>
Textadept is a text editor multi-platform, fast, minimalist, and can expand significantly. The user interface of Textadept is sleek and simple. Optimized non-stop for speed and minimalism over the years, the editor consists of less than 2000 lines of C code and less than 4000 lines of code.
Textadept - source code editor
Textadept runs on Windows, Mac OSX, Linux and BSD. It also has a the top-end version, ideal for work on the remote machine. Textadept is an editor, ideal for...
</description></item><item><title>Download CyberLink PhotoDirector Ultra 2026 v17.0.0922.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 01 Oct 2025 23:46:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-photodirector-ultra-129.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-photodirector-ultra-129.html
</guid><description>
Cyberlink PhotoDirector Ultra is known to be photo editing tools and videos with the effect is extremely rich, help you to change the style for the individual images or the videos of his favorite. This software integrated the 3D engine helps to speed up Video processing, which allows accessing the repository effect online and extract the Videos into the movies 3D Bru-ray, 3D AVCHD.
Cyberlink PhotoDirector Ultra to offer users a more professional tool to handle their images, remove...
</description></item><item><title>Download Free Download Manager 6.30.1 Build 6474</title><pubDate> Wed, 01 Oct 2025 23:45:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-download-manager-3105.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-download-manager-3105.html
</guid><description>
Free Download Manager is free application download manager, Free Download Manager will significantly increase downloads by splitting the files into several smaller parts and then downloads at the same time. Speed your download will be significantly increased. Manager download free can also continue to download at broken or not responding, so you don't need start downloading from the beginning after occasionally interrupted.
Free Download Manager - Manage and speed up downloads
You can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Hard Disk Sentinel Pro 6.30.4 Beta</title><pubDate> Wed, 01 Oct 2025 23:45:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hard-disk-sentinel-pro-562.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hard-disk-sentinel-pro-562.html
</guid><description>
Hard Disk Sentinel Pro is a tool for monitoring and optimal performance for hard drive HDD and help diagnose the HDD as well as SSD. Version of Hard Disk Sentinel Pro is a professional version, the most advanced of Hard Disk with many advanced features that meet basic needs, check the hard drive for the user.
The goal of it is to find, test, diagnose and repair the malfunction, hard drive, report and display the health status of the SSD and hard drive failure, decreased performance and...
</description></item><item><title>Download GPU Monitor 13.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 01 Oct 2025 23:44:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gpu-monitor-4160.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gpu-monitor-4160.html
</guid><description>
GPU Monitor is a free software allows you to track the statistics, the most recent of graphics Card desktop, NVIDIA or AMD / ATI of you. GPU Monitor including vendor, Model, GPU (clock Speed, Temperature, usage), memory (clock Speed, size, usage), Fan (Speed, usage), clock Speed, Shader, Temperature PCB, and PCI Express. GPU Monitor does not require any application of 3rd party. Just drivers features full latest from suppliers graphics card to your specific is required. Change the size!...
</description></item><item><title>Download SIW Technicians 2025 v15.8.0817</title><pubDate> Wed, 01 Oct 2025 23:43:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-siw-technicians-3584.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-siw-technicians-3584.html
</guid><description>
SIW Technicians is an information tool complex system, for Microsoft Windows, check your PC and collect detailed data about the properties and system settings and displays it in a way very easy to understand. SIW Technicians can create a report file (JSON, HTML, TXT, CSV or XML) and you can use that file in batch mode (for Inventory computer inventory of hardware and software, asset inventory, security audit, license Management software, configuration Management server).
SIW Technicians...
</description></item><item><title>Download Betterbird 140.3.1esr-bb12</title><pubDate> Wed, 01 Oct 2025 23:43:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-betterbird-8318.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-betterbird-8318.html
</guid><description>
Betterbird is a tweaked version of Mozilla Thunderbird, Thunderbird on steroids, if you will. It closely follows Thunderbird's Extended Support Releases (ESRs), thus avoiding the mistakes of other forks that cause it to quickly lose track of upstream Thunderbird, thus opening users to vulnerabilities. security.
Betterbird makes emailing safer, faster and easier than ever with the implementation of industry best features like smart spam filter, built-in spell checker , extension support,...
</description></item><item><title>Download System Utilities 1.3.7.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 01 Oct 2025 23:43:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-system-utilities-10394.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-system-utilities-10394.html
</guid><description>
System Utilities as its name suggests, contains a collection of tools that can help you maintain your system easily. It can scan your drive for storage, help you quickly uninstall programs, as well as manage startup applications and clean up unnecessary data.
Features of System Utilities
	Scan and organize all the folders on your PC to create more space.
	Uninstall all programs that you do not use. Get rid of data junk on your computer.
	Determine which programs should start...
</description></item><item><title>Download Steinberg Dorico Pro 6.1.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 01 Oct 2025 23:42:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-steinberg-dorico-4929.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-steinberg-dorico-4929.html
</guid><description>
Steinberg Dorico help you write musical notation, automatically generated results are printed with exceptional quality - and playback with realism spectacular. Steinberg Dorico easy enough for anyone to learn, but there are hundreds of symbols, features, options and advanced audio to satisfy even the most demanding professionals.
With the user interface itself is streamlined, students and those less experienced in recording scores can be composed and arranged straight into Dorico, help...
</description></item><item><title>Download MP3Studio YouTube Downloader 2.0.28.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 01 Oct 2025 23:40:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mp3studio-youtube-downloader-6778.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mp3studio-youtube-downloader-6778.html
</guid><description>
MP3Studio YouTube Downloader is an efficient and user-friendly software developed to provide you with an easy means of getting all your favorite videos from the web and store them on your PC, in one of the available formats. With MP3Studio YouTube Downloader, you can download up to 99 songs at once in the background as you start your business.
Use this media editor to preload various songs via YouTube and other services. It will provide you with good quality music that you can listen to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Explzh 9.87</title><pubDate> Wed, 01 Oct 2025 23:39:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-explzh-2278.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-explzh-2278.html
</guid><description>
Explzh is software that originated from Japan. This program works with most formats, can extract the file directly to FTP server, split large files into multiple smaller size. I would like to note that the storage supports encryption of files compressed using AES algorithm, has a system of tabs in the main window, you can search for the information you need in the repository and work with files, batch mode is done.
Explzh - Compress and decompress file
The file is support work with the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Vivaldi Browser 7.6.3797.58</title><pubDate> Wed, 01 Oct 2025 23:39:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vivaldi-159.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vivaldi-159.html
</guid><description>
Vivaldi is a browser designed for users who have power and offer the option to customize high. You can choose the location of the tabs and the address bar, put the hotkeys for the common tasks and many other features. Also, Vivaldi also provides a number of improvements such as Tab Stacks to group multiple open tabs into a tab, leads to interface less cluttered. Can notes and added a screenshot of a web page while browsing, storing an attachment, and add the URL to easily sort and locate...
</description></item><item><title>Download LibreWolf 143.0.3-1</title><pubDate> Wed, 01 Oct 2025 23:38:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-librewolf-11967.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-librewolf-11967.html
</guid><description>
LibreWolf is a customized and independent version of Firefox, with the main goals being user privacy, security and freedom. LibreWolf is designed to provide increased protection against tracking and fingerprinting techniques and includes a number of security enhancements. This is achieved through our security and privacy oriented settings and patches. LibreWolf also aims to remove all telemetry, data collection and annoyances, as well as disable anti-free features like DRM.
LibreWolf...
</description></item><item><title>Download MusicBee 3.6.9403</title><pubDate> Wed, 01 Oct 2025 23:38:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musicbee-2980.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musicbee-2980.html
</guid><description>
MusicBee is a free software that lets you find, organize, and play music on the PC, on the Web or on mobile devices. The program supports all audio formats popular and will also allow you to switch between them. The rules Auto DJ will allow you to automatically fill in the row Are released and find new music on the Internet by streaming similar artists from Last.fm. Using MusicBee, you will be able to easily create and manage playlists static playlists, auto-playlists and radio. You can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Zoom Player Max 22.0 Beta 2</title><pubDate> Wed, 01 Oct 2025 23:36:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zoom-player-max-104.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zoom-player-max-104.html
</guid><description>
Zoom Player MAX help you to see the film on DVD, Blu-ray, Flash movies and HD format with high quality and the ability to display subtitles in English very well. The advantage of software is that takes up very little system resources to play the movie with quick speed, change the wallpaper options while viewing movies.
Zoom Player MAX is the movies, browse high-quality photos on the computer with the advantages such as compact size, quick start, built-in codec. The application supports...
</description></item><item><title>Download FanCtrl 1.7.7</title><pubDate> Wed, 01 Oct 2025 23:36:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fanctrl-5779.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fanctrl-5779.html
</guid><description>
FanCtrl is software that allows you to automatically control the fan speed on your PC. FanCtrl is easy to use, although the app is best for high-end users. You can cause damage to your computer due to overheating or conflict with other processors or other monitoring software. As an independent developed application, not all motherboards are or may be supported.
The application is well positioned and is located in the system tray with the name of the motherboard, every fan and control...
</description></item><item><title>Download Audified GK Amplification 3 Pro 3.1.6</title><pubDate> Wed, 01 Oct 2025 23:36:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-audified-gk-amplification-pro-10392.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-audified-gk-amplification-pro-10392.html
</guid><description>
Audified GK Amplification 3 Pro includes three precision-engineered amplifiers, enhanced with Smart Ports and Compressors. Reworked user interface ensures effortless creativity.
Three amps included:
	800 RB: Launched in 1982, the 800RB is part of the rock legacy of the 1980s. The advent of Bi-amp technology fundamentally changed the amp game of the era.
	MB 150: Small but powerful. Across all genres, from jazz to rock, the MB150's mid-parametric EQ puts your ideal mix-ready tone at...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cullen Kelly Color Genesis Pro 1.3.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 01 Oct 2025 23:35:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cullen-kelly-color-genesis-pro-14197.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cullen-kelly-color-genesis-pro-14197.html
</guid><description>
Cullen Kelly Color Genesis Pro is an advanced photochemical film simulation plugin designed for colorists and filmmakers. It shapes images with real photochemical prints, bringing authentic film-like colors and textures to the digital environment. It includes advanced features such as grain and halo optimization algorithms, and provides a powerful, customizable editor for creating photochemical textures and color effects. This plugin is used not only by colorists but also by directors of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Karaosoft Karma 2026.0.11</title><pubDate> Wed, 01 Oct 2025 23:35:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-karma-2379.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-karma-2379.html
</guid><description>
Karma is an enhancement program that helps you tune, karaoke can view the text of the files sound different. At first glance, after launch, the layout may seem complicated, unclear where to start. You can customize the display prompts to understand the function of each parameter is highlighted integrated.
Management program your karaoke a easy way. Search no need to click, drag and drop feature and many other unique features designed to bring you the easiest management for the program...
</description></item><item><title>Download Fast Video Cutter Joiner 6.9.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 01 Oct 2025 23:34:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fast-video-cutter-joiner-7542.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fast-video-cutter-joiner-7542.html
</guid><description>
Fast Video Cutter Joiner is a fast video cutter and joiner with an easy to use interface. It allows users to trim parts of a video quickly while maintaining the quality of the original video. It supports various formats like AVI, MPEG, MP4, WMV, 3GP, FLV...
This tool helps you to cut video files into small parts, to keep only the parts you need and remove unwanted parts like trailers and advertisements in a movie. The clips you cut can then be used for other video productions or for a...
</description></item><item><title>Download TeamViewer 15.70.3 + Portable</title><pubDate> Wed, 01 Oct 2025 23:34:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-teamviewer-528.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-teamviewer-528.html
</guid><description>
TeamViewer is software that functions to connect and control the remote computer, the ability to connect with any system anywhere from all over the place. This is a support tool users is very convenient. TeamViewer to help users control remote computer becomes much more simple, help you interact and collaborate with others in the exchange and share of information, instruction manual, application software or fix the computer.
TeamViewer as a revolution of computer science. when you have...
</description></item><item><title>Download TeamViewer QuickSupport 15.70.3</title><pubDate> Wed, 01 Oct 2025 23:33:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-teamviewer-quicksupport-1933.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-teamviewer-quicksupport-1933.html
</guid><description>
A different version of TeamViewer is TeamViewer QuickSupport is a solution easy to use allows you to share your desktop with a users TeamViewer other to receive technical support or other support. All what you need to do is run the TeamViewer QuickSupport and provides for the remote user ID and your password to grant access to the computer to your desk. Only people you trust can connect to your computer and access password will automatically change after each session.
The software also...
</description></item></channel></rss>