<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 01:46:39 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 01:46:39 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Find.Same.Images.OK 5.88</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Dec 2025 23:06:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-find-same-images-ok-113.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-find-same-images-ok-113.html
</guid><description>
Find.Same.Images.OK lets find the images identical or similar in the folder of you, even if they were to rotate, change size or change.
Just select one or more folders that you want the program to scan and it will return a list of all the duplicate images or very similar, as indicated by the percent the same and the preview is built.Then, you can select images from the list and then copy, move or delete them.
Find.Same.Images.OK
In addition, there are other options smart option allows...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mirillis Action! 4.47.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Dec 2025 22:56:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mirillis-action-213.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mirillis-action-213.html
</guid><description>
Mirillis Action! is a game video recording software,  screen recording, take screenshot with impressive sharpness and 4K quality. It's a simple, reliable and effective software solution that's worth it when you need to access features like streaming and recording and work on desktop with unique HD video quality.
Mirillis Action makes exporting and uploading your recordings to popular services and social networks like YouTube and Facebook very easy. Work! provides predefined export...
</description></item><item><title>Download AIMP 5.40 Build 2703 + Portable</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Dec 2025 22:56:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aimp-1302.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aimp-1302.html
</guid><description>
AIMP is a free audio with support for large number of formats and playlists. It works with multiple playlists immediately, allows creation of bookmarks and also has the playback queue.
AIMP - audio player
Features of AIMP
	Clear sound, technology of re-creating fundamentally different from Winamp and WMP
	The balance sensitivity
	Maximum functions from minimal resource
	Minimum consumption of system resources
	Multi-language support
	Support the audio format
	Adjust the hot keys for...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare Recoverit 14.0.11.7</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Dec 2025 22:55:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-recoverits-374.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-recoverits-374.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare Recoverit is a data recovery software that is easily lost at a rapid rate and is used by many people. You will do what happens if one day your data is suddenly lost due to the virus or deleted it, .. Wondershare Recoverit will provide you with an environment to protect important data.
Wondershare Recoverit has all the scanning processes that are divided into multiple types, from the typical recovery of the deleted files that are deleted to the recovery of missing files due...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ventoy 1.1.10 + LiveCD</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Dec 2025 22:55:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ventoy-4578.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ventoy-4578.html
</guid><description>
Ventoy is an open source tool for creating bootable USB drives for ISO files. With ventoy, you don't need to format the disk multiple times, you just need to copy the iso file to the USB drive and boot it. You can copy multiple iso files at once and ventoy will give you a boot menu to select them.
Features of Ventoy
100% Open Source
Simple to Use
Fast (limited only by iso file copy speed)
Boot directly from iso file, no extraction required
Legacy + UEFI supported in the same...
</description></item><item><title>Download iToolab WatsGo 8.9.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Dec 2025 22:54:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-itoolab-watsgo-7822.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-itoolab-watsgo-7822.html
</guid><description>
iToolab WatsGo is a software that supports transferring WhatsApp messages between Android and iPhone quickly and easily. It supports a wide range of data types including WhatsApp messages, pictures, videos, contacts, etc. Backup WhatsApp on Android &amp;amp; iOS to your computer and completely free up device space. Backup WhatsApp (Business) data without Google Drive, iTunes or iCloud. Fully compatible with Android 12 and iOS 16.
Also, it allows you to view a list of backup history and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cockos REAPER 7.57</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Dec 2025 22:54:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cockos-reaper-889.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cockos-reaper-889.html
</guid><description>
Cockos REAPER is a powerful software for for windows, chp lets you record, arrange, edit, and display the audio waveform multi-track. Cockos REAPER offers an extensive feature set includes many effects and a sample project. REAPER supports ASIO, Kernel Streaming, WaveOut, and DirectSound for playback and recording. It reads the files in WAV, OGG and MP3 files and records WAV files. You can arrange any number of items in any number of tracks and use plug-in sound processing (DirectX and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Atlantis Word Processor 5.0.0.15</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Dec 2025 22:53:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-atlantis-word-processor-585.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-atlantis-word-processor-585.html
</guid><description>
Atlantis Word Processor is a word processor app with features format, standard text, autocorrect, and spell check.  Atlantis is a word processor in accordance with most of the tasks handled daily text. The interface is very easy to use and offers the toolbars, hotkeys and sound effects thanh can customize (can turn off). It includes a clip library for quick access to the text or images used regular preview, font format and many other features aimed at improving the process of your...
</description></item><item><title>Download Gilisoft AI Toolkit 10.6</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Dec 2025 22:53:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-ai-toolkit-9520.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-ai-toolkit-9520.html
</guid><description>
Gilisoft AI Toolkit is a comprehensive software package that can be useful for businesses and individuals who want to integrate AI technology into their workflow. Gilisoft AI Toolkit is a software package that includes various tools for working with artificial intelligence, including chatbots, OCR (optical character recognition), TTS (text-to-speech) software, and ASR (automatic speech recognition). The chatbot tool allows users to create their own chatbots and customize them to their...
</description></item><item><title>Download AdwCleaner 8.7.0.619</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Dec 2025 22:52:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-malwarebytes-adwcleaner-1132.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-malwarebytes-adwcleaner-1132.html
</guid><description>
Malwarebytes AdwCleaner is ad blocking software on the browser, which helps you completely remove the annoying stuff every time Internet access. The software is completely free for users, also AdwCleaner can remove unwanted software or virus on your computer.
When on the website is not secure, appearance various types of advertising PUP. Very can will appear on the website contain malicious code that when you click on the sensitive area, the virus infected computer very likely to happen....
</description></item><item><title>Download VirtualDJ Home 2026 Build 8978</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Dec 2025 22:51:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-virtual-dj-home-4801.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-virtual-dj-home-4801.html
</guid><description>
Virtual DJ Home is software compiled and mix of tracks with many music formats various. It has the features as there are 2 installation mode for the program is automatically or manually transformed the structure of music has to arrange after the claim theft of Remix music, record your mixes, burn a CD, rip DVD, vinyl rip, create radio on the Internet.
Although VirtualDJ is integrated with many features but still very easy to learn. You can start with the basics and advance as you learn...
</description></item><item><title>Download XMPlay 4.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Dec 2025 22:51:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xmplay-2666.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xmplay-2666.html
</guid><description>
XMPlay is an audio player software free for Windows. Originally released in 1998, it created the difference compared with the competitors by providing a special copy authentication of the audio file track. XMPlay is an audio player, supporting audio formats OGG / MP3 / MP2 / MP1 / WMA / AAC / MP4 / WAV / AIFF / CDA / MO3 / IT / XM / S3M / MTM / MOD / UMX, PLS / M3U / ASX / playlist WAX / CUE and ZIP archives. Download more audio file formats, and file storage is also supported via...
</description></item><item><title>Download RapidRAW 1.4.7</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Dec 2025 22:50:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rapidraw-13957.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rapidraw-13957.html
</guid><description>
RapidRAW is a modern, high-performance, open-source RAW photo editor, designed to deliver a fast and clean editing experience with a lightweight footprint (under 30MB). Built with performance and usability in mind, the software is aimed at photographers who want a simple, efficient, and fun workflow without compromising performance.
Key Features
	GPU-accelerated processing: Uses a custom WGSL shader to process all image adjustments on the GPU, allowing for smooth, responsive editing...
</description></item><item><title>Download AB Download Manager 1.8.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Dec 2025 22:50:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ab-download-manager-12399.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ab-download-manager-12399.html
</guid><description>
With this application, you can easily download files from anywhere. Enjoy fast, free downloads with seamless browser extension support. It is built to be a desktop application that allows you to manage and organize your downloads better than before.
AB Download Manager features
	Simple and modern UI: Simple UI and dark mode by default
	Faster download speeds: Download files using multiple connections to increase your download speed by up to 500%
	Download Queue: Create and manage your...
</description></item><item><title>Download Time Boss Pro 3.38.009</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Dec 2025 22:43:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-time-boss-pro-7836.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-time-boss-pro-7836.html
</guid><description>
Time Boss Pro is a popular time management tool that performs a wide range of functions from setting PC work time limits to collecting usage statistics, display the remaining time and manage the list of prohibited or allowed programs and websites. By using this program you can manage the usage of any computer by any user in the Windows local network from a remote PC.
Time Boss Pro gives you full control over the remote Time Boss control panel. If you want to manage Time Boss Pro on...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinUAE 6.0.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Dec 2025 22:43:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winuae-4960.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winuae-4960.html
</guid><description>
WinUAE is a port to Windows of emulator Amiga UAE are designed to simulate cargo Amore 500, 1000 and 2000. WinUAE is easily one of the emulator most complex that we have seen with more options than you can use. You will need to know where to find the resources to use it properly. It also supports multi-CPU simulation, drive, etc.
The characteristics of WinUAE
	The chips original (OCS), The chip enhanced (ECS) and architecture, advanced graphics (AGA)
	Device I / O: ( floppy drive ,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Opera GX (Gaming Browser) 125.0.5729.58</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Dec 2025 22:41:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-gx-3170.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-gx-3170.html
</guid><description>
Opera GX is a special version of the Opera browser is built to complement gamers avid. Browser this game comes with the unique features to help users make maximum use of both the game and their browser. Opera GX is built specifically to support the game. This browser includes the unique features to help users have the best experience when gaming and surfing the web.
Opera GX - special browser for gamers
GX Control allows you to set a limit on the level of use RAM, CPU and network where...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinShift Forge 0.5.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Dec 2025 20:03:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winshift-forge-14401.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winshift-forge-14401.html
</guid><description>
What is WinShift Forge?
WinShift Forge is a lightweight utility built to enhance the performance of Windows 11. WinShift Forge allows you to easily remove them, free up space, and speed up your system. WinShift Forge lets you instantly refresh your computer screen by customizing the most important icons. No more fumbling through complex system settings—easily take direct control of the core Windows visuals and make your PC truly your own.
Key Features:
Personalize Your PC
	Replace...
</description></item><item><title>Download DelFast 1.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Dec 2025 19:48:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-delfast-14400.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-delfast-14400.html
</guid><description>
DelFast is a lightweight utility for Windows that instantly deletes files and folders without the delays caused by Windows Explorer's calculations and animations. It's designed to be fast, simple, and easy to carry.
Features of DelFast
	Instantly deletes files and folders
	Supports multiple selection (delete multiple items at once)
	No installer needed, just a single EXE file
	Extremely small size (approximately 188 KB)
	Minimal CPU usage
	Clean and simple user interface
	Permanent...
</description></item><item><title>Download Intel Ethernet Adapter Complete Driver Pack 30.6</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Dec 2025 17:10:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intel-ethernet-adapter-complete-driver-pack-7424.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intel-ethernet-adapter-complete-driver-pack-7424.html
</guid><description>
Intel Ethernet Adapter Complete Driver Pack contains all Intel® Ethernet networking software and drivers for Windows, Linux and FreeBSD versions currently supported for most Intel Ethernet Adapters. Not all Intel Ethernet Adapters and Intel Ethernet Controllers are supported in all versions of Windows, Linux, or FreeBSD.
What's new in this release:
In this point release, NVM Update Package 3.20 has been updated. If you currently have the 3.20 update package installed and are running...
</description></item><item><title>Download Android Studio 2025.2.2.8</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Dec 2025 17:10:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-android-studio-3890.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-android-studio-3890.html
</guid><description>
Android Studio is an Android development environment, completely new, provides many improvements and new features compared to Eclipse ADT. This software solution will is IDE the official Android when is finishing. This tool provides many tools and features such as editing, layout, rich set of tools to capture usability, compatibility version, performance and other issues, create a lot APK, build system based on Gradle flexibility, extended support for Google Services, integrated support...
</description></item><item><title>Download Auslogics BoostSpeed 14.1.0.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Dec 2025 17:08:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-auslogics-boostspeed-140.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-auslogics-boostspeed-140.html
</guid><description>
Auslogics BoostSpeed is software support speed up an Internet connection for the computer with Auslogics BoostSpeed restrictions on your Internet speed will be corrective and limited to the lowest level to bring high efficiency in work as well as in their learning. Auslogics BoostSpeed improves the speed surfing the web for the computer through the way in data compression and image to gảm capacity when participating online, with the mechanism and how it works so users also software feel...
</description></item><item><title>Download Luminar Neo 1.26.0 (16162)</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Dec 2025 17:07:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-luminar-neoo-7194.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-luminar-neoo-7194.html
</guid><description>
Luminar Neo is an innovative image editor powered by futuristic AI technologies that simplifies complex editing workflows and allows creators to turn their boldest ideas into reality. Luminar Neo calculates image depth and generates 3D maps, allowing you to naturally scatter light in 3D across a 2D image. This opens the door to unleash your creativity to bring your artistic vision to life.
MaskAI automates the masking process by identifying objects in the image and creating the correct...
</description></item><item><title>Download AnyTrans for iOS 8.9.14.20251223</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Dec 2025 17:07:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anytrans-for-ios-755.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anytrans-for-ios-755.html
</guid><description>
AnyTrans for iOS is content manager essential fully managed iPhone, Android and content of your cloud. Including all mobile devices, all cloud drives from your iPhone, iPad, iPod touch to phones and tablets. From local disk to cloud storage. AnyTrans has protected them all, providing you convenient management for all data and your files, regardless of whether they are stored where.
AnyTrans is the one stop solution to meet all the management needs of your data. For the first time, you can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Auslogics Registry Cleaner Pro 11.1.0.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Dec 2025 17:06:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-auslogics-registry-cleaner-pro-1892.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-auslogics-registry-cleaner-pro-1892.html
</guid><description>
Auslogics Registry Cleaner Pro is the most advanced Version of the software cleans the registry stable help users delete the outdated Registry to speed up your pc. Auslogics Registry Cleaner Pro contains all the features of Auslogics Registry Cleaner Free. User easy download Auslogics Registry Cleaner on the website taiwebs.com with many new features. The software will fix all the errors in the registry of your Windows and clean it from obsolete entries. With Auslogics Registry Cleaner you...
</description></item></channel></rss>