<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 01:49:29 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 01:49:29 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Mp3Tag 3.30f</title><pubDate> Fri, 01 Aug 2025 23:51:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mp3tag-150.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mp3tag-150.html
</guid><description>
Mp3tag is a powerful tool and easy to use to edit ID3 tags and OGG comments about the files MP3 - and Ogg Vorbis. It can rename files based on the tag information, replace characters or words from tags and filenames. Help users create and add the tag information for MP3 files to manage the information that is reasonable.
The program supports lookup database freedb online for the selected files, allowing you to automatically gather tag information appropriate for the files or CD selection....
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare PDFelement Pro 11.4.26.3648</title><pubDate> Fri, 01 Aug 2025 23:50:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-pdfelement-pro-105.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-pdfelement-pro-105.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare PDFelement Pro support users to convert PDF to office documents for easier use, modify in every situation. Is one of the software conversion material is rated best today, integrated with many features. We recommend that you should use experience software many useful features this.
Wondershare PDFelement Pro - conversion Fie PDF more features, multi-language
Wondershare PDFelement Pro what?
Convert PDF into Word, Excel, PowerPoint...
• Convert PDF and protected PDF into...
</description></item><item><title>Download n-Track Studio Suite 10.2.2.10168</title><pubDate> Fri, 01 Aug 2025 23:49:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-n-track-studio-2991.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-n-track-studio-2991.html
</guid><description>
n-Track Studio is a recording software allows you record and create MIDI music and sounds top quality. The software allows you to add effects, VST3, DirectX, AU (Mac), VST and ReWire different on each track or channel. This program also allows you to automatically fade out, fade in and fade out or increase the volume of the music to indicate the voice of the singer.
n-Track Studio can record and playback the number of audio, MIDI and sound unlimited. In addition, you can handle the...
</description></item><item><title>Download AVS Media Player 6.1.1.181</title><pubDate> Fri, 01 Aug 2025 23:49:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs-media-player-1890.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs-media-player-1890.html
</guid><description>
AVS Media Player is software media player brings you a space to enjoy music, video, vivid. AVS Media Player supports all audio formats, different image is a necessity. AVS Media Player allows you can open to near 100 format sounds, different images from common to most rare. Name the audio format, video, audio that programs can read, including: .AVI, .MPEG, .MP3, or .FLV, .JPG, .PNG ... and so very many other formats again.
AVS Media Player - The Media player
Features of AVS Media...
</description></item><item><title>Download Picture Window Pro 8.0.521</title><pubDate> Fri, 01 Aug 2025 23:48:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-picture-window-pro-7452.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-picture-window-pro-7452.html
</guid><description>
Picture Window Pro is a powerful image editing tool designed for serious photographers with strict creative and quality standards. Its comprehensive set of photo editing and editing tools let you control and shape every aspect of your images.
Picture Window Pro 8 is a complete rewrite of Picture Window Pro 7. It features non-destructive image editing through a novel interface based on an image tree. It also fully supports large, high-resolution displays and can be used in dual monitor...
</description></item><item><title>Download Systweak PDF Editor 1.0.0.8012</title><pubDate> Fri, 01 Aug 2025 23:48:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-systweak-pdf-editor-11484.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-systweak-pdf-editor-11484.html
</guid><description>
Systweak PDF Editor is a fast and simple solution to edit, convert, sign, protect, compress PDF files and make scanned PDF files searchable and can choose. With Systweak PDF Editor, quickly convert your PDF files into a variety of editable formats. Converting PDF files to and from any MS Office files, images, ebooks, web pages, and other formats just got easier.
For working and editing PDF files, Systweak PDF editor offers many features and tools. Using them, you can mark text for...
</description></item><item><title>Download WebMinds Hard Drive Optimizer 1.8.0.10</title><pubDate> Fri, 01 Aug 2025 23:47:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hard-drive-optimizer-7835.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hard-drive-optimizer-7835.html
</guid><description>
Hard Drive Optimizer is a software that optimizes your hard drive, with it you will quickly recover free disk space! The job of this program is to find the biggest files on your hard drive and delete the ones you don't need easily.
Features of Hard Drive Optimizer
	Hard Drive Optimizer provides the fastest and easiest way to free up your hard drive and free up precious space.
	Scan your hard drive or any folder on your computer for large files that are eating up disk space.
	Review...
</description></item><item><title>Download WYSIWYG Web Builder 20.2.3</title><pubDate> Fri, 01 Aug 2025 23:46:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wysiwyg-web-builder-177.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wysiwyg-web-builder-177.html
</guid><description>
WYSIWYG Web Builder : The construction of the website from scratch using HTML code isn't a pleasant process, even when you know what you are doing. The website can be built using WYSIWYG Web Builder with using the element similar to the package published on the desktop: text and images placed in frames and tables on the page, so very little surprised when most of the efforts to make the web become a experience user-friendly than. the controls do you use to build your pages.
WYSIWYG Web...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Bridge 2025 v15.1.1.729 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Fri, 01 Aug 2025 23:46:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-bridge-0003-1338.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-bridge-0003-1338.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Bridge is a versatile digital asset management application developed by Adobe Inc., first released in 2005 as part of the Adobe Creative Suite. It acts as a powerful tool for organizing, previewing, and managing creative assets across various Adobe applications. By downloading the program on taiwebs.com, you can easily edit elements in batch mode, add watermarks and even set color options centrally - Adobe Bridge CC will simplify your work and help maintain order.
Adobe Bridge...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Downloader 9.15.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 01 Aug 2025 23:45:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html
</guid><description>
YTD Youtube Downloader is an application that reliable and intuitive, allowing you to quickly download YouTube videos and save them to your computer. You can also convert the media files to the format desired video or extract audio streams and save separately. YTD Youtube Downloader lets you save your favorite clips of yourself from Youtube, Facebook, Vimeo and Dailymotion to your desktop. The software supports URLS from many web site hosting, multimedia and allows you to download desired...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Substance 3D Modeler 1.22.3.1212 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Fri, 01 Aug 2025 23:44:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-substance-3d-modeler-7876.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-substance-3d-modeler-7876.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Substance 3D Modeler is a 3D sculpting and modeling application that helps you create on both desktop and VR. Modelers aim to make working in 3D as intuitive as working with clay in real life. To help achieve this, with Adobe Substance 3D Modeler you don't have to worry about adjusting vertices or managing UVs, you can instead focus on the creative process.
With its intuitive design, Adobe Substance 3D Modeler frees you from the technical constraints of traditional 3D modeling....
</description></item><item><title>Download Coolutils Total Movie Converter 4.1.0.70</title><pubDate> Fri, 01 Aug 2025 23:43:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-total-movie-converter-915.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-total-movie-converter-915.html
</guid><description>
Coolutils Total Movie Converter is software to convert video files in any popular formats such as AVI, MPG, WMV, MPEG, FLV. At the same time, the program can prepare video for a variety of devices - iPod, iPhone, Zune, Apple TV, Archos, Creative Zen Vision, XBox and many other devices. Provides the ability to batch convert a group of files.
Coolutils Total Movie Converter 4 - convert video formats
Total Movie Converter supports 3GP format this is suitable for those who are still using...
</description></item><item><title>Download Textadept 12.8</title><pubDate> Fri, 01 Aug 2025 23:43:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-textadept-2878.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-textadept-2878.html
</guid><description>
Textadept is a text editor multi-platform, fast, minimalist, and can expand significantly. The user interface of Textadept is sleek and simple. Optimized non-stop for speed and minimalism over the years, the editor consists of less than 2000 lines of C code and less than 4000 lines of code.
Textadept - source code editor
Textadept runs on Windows, Mac OSX, Linux and BSD. It also has a the top-end version, ideal for work on the remote machine. Textadept is an editor, ideal for...
</description></item><item><title>Download Fort Firewall 3.18.10</title><pubDate> Fri, 01 Aug 2025 23:42:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fort-firewall-6439.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fort-firewall-6439.html
</guid><description>
Fort Firewall is a network security system that monitors and controls network traffic and goes based on predefined security rules. A firewall often establishes a barrier between a trusted internal network and untrusted external networks, such as the Internet.
Features of Fort Firewall
	Filter by network address, application group
	Support of representative characters in the name path name
	Application group speed limit
	Access Traffic Statistics
	Display bandwidth
	Based on the...
</description></item><item><title>Download FakeDriveCheck 4.56</title><pubDate> Fri, 01 Aug 2025 23:42:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fakedrivecheck-11322.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fakedrivecheck-11322.html
</guid><description>
FakeDriveCheck is a simple utility you can run to verify if your USB stick or MicroSD card is fake. It's easy to get and use, making it a good choice for anyone skeptical about the authenticity of their external storage.
FakeDriveCheck Features
	Existing files will not be destroyed while the USB drive is verified.
	Super fast verification.
	No need to unplug and plug in.
	Hot Plug: FakeDriveCheck detects USB drives
	inserted after FakeDriveCheck is started.
</description></item><item><title>Download DroidKit 2.3.6.20250801</title><pubDate> Fri, 01 Aug 2025 23:42:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-droidkit-6578.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-droidkit-6578.html
</guid><description>
DroidKit is data recovery software for your mobile device, it will quickly scan your phone memory and save photos, WhatsApp chats and files, messages Messages, contacts and more essential data up to 13 categories, covering almost everything you need every day. All Android phones and tablets are supported. Without rooting your device. No tech skills required. No need to wait many days. You can get back what you've lost with just a few simple clicks, instantly.
Besides, DroidKit also has...
</description></item><item><title>Download TubeMate Downloader 5.21.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 01 Aug 2025 23:41:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubemate-downloader-4250.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubemate-downloader-4250.html
</guid><description>
TubeMate Downloader is a smart application that lets you download any clip you want from the website hosting the main video and convert them in when download at or then. If you need a simple and effective tool to download videos, you can give it a try. With TubeMate Downloader, you can directly drag and drop video link from your browser into the drop-down box or application window to start downloading. You don't even need to copy and paste the video URL.
TubeMate Downloader - Support...
</description></item><item><title>Download SQLite Expert Professional 5.5.37.648</title><pubDate> Fri, 01 Aug 2025 23:40:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sqlite-expert-professional-109.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sqlite-expert-professional-109.html
</guid><description>
SQLite Expert Professional  is a powerful program that allows you to manage and  organize  SQLite databases, visually display you tables and working classes. The user interface is convenient, but due to the lack of Russian support and a lot of customization, not everyone can figure it out, although if you work with the database I think you can understand where and click. In the main window, you can see all your databases, and if you want you can execute the   SQL   using the  SQL ...
</description></item><item><title>Download priPrinter Professional 7.0.0.2591 Beta</title><pubDate> Fri, 01 Aug 2025 23:40:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-priprinter-professional-633.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-priprinter-professional-633.html
</guid><description>
priPrinter Professional is the printer driver allows you to manipulate the output of the printer before being printed. PriPrinter is installed and select the same as the printer driver other. After printing it automatically displays the preview in where you can preview his print, change the layout, page position back, cut them, and much more. Then, you print it to printer or save your document for later use. With PriPrinter you will always be sure his prints will look like. You can measure...
</description></item><item><title>Download Steelray Project Analyzer 7.20.4</title><pubDate> Fri, 01 Aug 2025 23:39:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-steelray-project-analyzer-607.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-steelray-project-analyzer-607.html
</guid><description>
Steelray Project Analyzer is software reviews schedules and resources for multiple projects and create reports to improve quality and performance. Steelray Project Analyzer is software that eases the creation, maintenance and provide schedule quality. With The analysis, you can evaluate the progress of your project in terms of quality and performance in minutes and produce results easy to understand. The schedule can be analyzed against the best practices of project management best...
</description></item><item><title>Download Advanced Disk Recovery 2.9.1300.18693</title><pubDate> Fri, 01 Aug 2025 23:39:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-disk-recovery-4350.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-disk-recovery-4350.html
</guid><description>
Advanced Disk Recovery is one stop solution for all the problems of losing your data. Recover photo, video, audio and other documents deleted in a few clicks. The problem is, when you delete data from your system, it's not really deleted immediately. You won't find it on your system, but it's still in there and soon you try to restore it, the more likely full recovery of it.
Advanced Disk Recovery - Restore deleted files
Advanced Disk Recovery scan effective PC Windows to delete your...
</description></item><item><title>Download Simple System Font Changer 1.0.0.14</title><pubDate> Fri, 01 Aug 2025 23:38:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wintools-advanced-system-font-changer-3881.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wintools-advanced-system-font-changer-3881.html
</guid><description>
Simple System Font Changer is a lightweight application and easy to use, gives you the possibility to modify the size of the fonts used by your operating system. This app is useful for users of Windows 10 because the system does not have this option comes.
Simple System Font Changer - change the font of the operating System
Simple System Font Changer allows you to change the font size according to your desire. App helps you make the font easy to read while using the display settings in...
</description></item><item><title>Download X-Ability Winmostar 11.13.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 01 Aug 2025 23:38:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-x-ability-winmostar-11156.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-x-ability-winmostar-11156.html
</guid><description>
Winmostar is an integrated GUI software designed for simulation programs such as GAMESS, MOPAC, LAMMPS, Gromacs and Quantum ESPRESSO. Winmostar serves as an integrated software solution, using programs (solvers) for MO, DFT and MD calculations as its backend. It provides pre- and post-processing capabilities, as well as file and process management functions. Software supported solvers include GAMESS, MOPAC, LAMMPS, Gromacs and Quantum ESPRESSO. Winmostar is designed to be installed and...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinTools System Font Size Changer 2.2.1.22</title><pubDate> Fri, 01 Aug 2025 23:36:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wintools-system-font-size-changer-6143.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wintools-system-font-size-changer-6143.html
</guid><description>
WinTools System Font Size Changer allows you to set the system font in Windows 10. It allows you to set the system font used by Windows 10 easily and make the text more easily read. It can modify the system font without having to restart the computer. It supports the conversion between the system fonts with the configuration and the hot key.
This software is part of the software family that changes the system font. The terms of use and all other information related to the software...
</description></item><item><title>Download MAME 0.279</title><pubDate> Fri, 01 Aug 2025 23:36:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mame-3320.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mame-3320.html
</guid><description>
MAME is an emulator of open source and free are designed to recreate the hardware of the game system arcade in software on the personal computer modern and other platforms. The goal is to preserve gaming history by preventing classic games from being lost or being forgotten.
MAME - emulator classic game
MAME (Multiple Arcade Machine Emulator) is a software that has the ability to simulate an arcade machine, allowing you to play the classic arcade game on his computer. This tool can...
</description></item></channel></rss>