<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 05:38:54 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 05:38:54 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Adobe Premiere Pro 2026 v26.0.0 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Sun, 25 Jan 2026 00:41:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-premiere-pro-0022-1361.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-premiere-pro-0022-1361.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Premiere Pro is the leading video editing software for film, TV, and the web. Creative tools, integration with other Adobe apps and services, and the power of Adobe Sensei help you turn footage into finished movies and videos in a seamless workflow. It offers high-quality video editing at 4K x 4K resolution and beyond, with 32-bit color, in both RGB and YUV color spaces. Edit audio samples, support for VST audio plug-ins (plug-ins), and 5.1 surround sound tracks. The Premiere Pro...
</description></item><item><title>Download Topaz Gigapixel Pro 1.1.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 25 Jan 2026 00:39:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-ai-gigapixel-1318.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-ai-gigapixel-1318.html
</guid><description>
Topaz ONE Gigapixel is the first app and only use the power of artificial intelligence to enhance your photos, add natural details, for great results. Use technology to learn deep, AIGigapixel ™ can zoom in and fill in the details that the products change in size other are not included. The traditional method this created blurred image, a non-realistic and do not have the detail present in the image have high resolution.
Topaz A.I. Gigapixel - enhance image quality
The content of...
</description></item><item><title>Download ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro 15.26.0124</title><pubDate> Sun, 25 Jan 2026 00:38:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-videotube-downloader-pro-1276.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-videotube-downloader-pro-1276.html
</guid><description>
ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro is the professional version support download videos and playlists from YouTube, videos from Dailymotion, BBC iPlayer, ITV Player, ABC,  FOX,CBS.com Vimeo, Prosieben, Metacafe, Blip.tv CBC.ca many more video sites. After the video is downloaded, you can convert them to the formats compatible with iPad, iPhone, iPod, MPEG-4, H. 264, MP3, AC3.
ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro - Download videos on Youtube
This is one of the software download the most...
</description></item><item><title>Download Topaz Video AI Pro 1.2.1 RC</title><pubDate> Sun, 25 Jan 2026 00:38:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-video-enhance-ai-3733.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-video-enhance-ai-3733.html
</guid><description>
Topaz Video Enhance AI is a tool to increase video quality with this great technology ONE. Topaz Video Enhance WHO wide open your video to resolutions up to 8K with the details and consistency of motion. Until the present, there is no way to re-create a perfect high resolution video from the footage is low resolution. From the family film to SD low quality to DVD quality and more than that, Video Enhance WHO will convert your video into the footage is upgrade clear with resolutions up to...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinShift Forge 0.7.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 25 Jan 2026 00:37:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winshift-forge-14401.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winshift-forge-14401.html
</guid><description>
What is WinShift Forge?
WinShift Forge is a lightweight utility built to enhance the performance of Windows 11. WinShift Forge allows you to easily remove them, free up space, and speed up your system. WinShift Forge lets you instantly refresh your computer screen by customizing the most important icons. No more fumbling through complex system settings—easily take direct control of the core Windows visuals and make your PC truly your own.
Key Features:
Personalize Your PC
	Replace...
</description></item><item><title>Download Zero Install 2.28.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 25 Jan 2026 00:37:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zero-install-1632.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zero-install-1632.html
</guid><description>
Zero Install is a system, install the software distribution cross africa focus. Other features include full support for shared libraries (with the SAT for resolution dependent), share between users, and integration with the package manager original foundation. Zero Install supports both binary packages and source and works on Linux systems , OS X , Unix and Windows. It is completely open source.
Zero Install - System software installation
Zero Install also has a number of interesting...
</description></item><item><title>Download Security Task Manager 3.2c</title><pubDate> Sun, 25 Jan 2026 00:36:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-security-task-manager-493.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-security-task-manager-493.html
</guid><description>
Security Task Manager is management software task program window for you to know the performance is the use of the software. Security Task Manager provides ratings, risk, security, process description, file path, chart, CPU usage, start time, hidden functions embedded. The software also lets you know the ability to the process is the spyware potential malware, Trojan or keylogger.
Security Task Manager also delete traces of Internet activity and your computer, stop monitoring keyboard...
</description></item><item><title>Download Hasleo Backup Suite 5.6.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 25 Jan 2026 00:36:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hasleo-backup-suite-6588.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hasleo-backup-suite-6588.html
</guid><description>
Hasleo Backup Suite is a free backup and free Windows recovery, integration of backup features, recovery, and replication, it is designed for Windows operating system users and can be used on both Windows PC and Windows Server. The backup and recovery feature of Hasleo Backup Suite can help you backup and restore your Windows, disk and partition operating system to protect your Windows operating system and your personal data. The replication feature of Hasleo Backup Suite can help you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Muziza YouTube Downloader Converter 9.1.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 25 Jan 2026 00:35:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-muziza-youtube-downloader-converter-3972.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-muziza-youtube-downloader-converter-3972.html
</guid><description>
Muziza YouTube Downloader Converter is a tool to create conditions for an attractive interface and many features to help you to download video clips from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion, Instagram and other sites. Muziza YouTube Downloader Converter can also download the video UHD 8K, 5K, 4K, QHD 2K, HD 1080p and 720p from YouTube. The app allows you download only audio stream from YouTube and save as MP3. You don't need to download the entire video file.
Muziza YouTube Downloader...
</description></item><item><title>Download FRITZ 20.10</title><pubDate> Sun, 25 Jan 2026 00:35:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fritz-14060.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fritz-14060.html
</guid><description>
FRITZ 20 is more than just a chess engine – it’s a training revolution for aspiring players and professionals. Whether you’re taking your first steps into the world of professional chess training, or are already playing at tournament level, FRITZ 20 will help you train more efficiently, intelligently and personally than ever before.
Simulate playing styles at the highest level
FRITZ 20 analyzes your next opponent – and plays just like them!
Use the style analysis feature in...
</description></item><item><title>Download Karaosoft Karma 2026.1.20</title><pubDate> Sun, 25 Jan 2026 00:34:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-karma-2379.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-karma-2379.html
</guid><description>
Karma is an enhancement program that helps you tune, karaoke can view the text of the files sound different. At first glance, after launch, the layout may seem complicated, unclear where to start. You can customize the display prompts to understand the function of each parameter is highlighted integrated.
Management program your karaoke a easy way. Search no need to click, drag and drop feature and many other unique features designed to bring you the easiest management for the program...
</description></item><item><title>Download RS File Manager File Explorer 2.2.6.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 24 Jan 2026 23:11:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-rs-file-manager-file-explorer-10933.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-rs-file-manager-file-explorer-10933.html
</guid><description>
RS File Manager - RS File Explorer is the ultimate File Manager for Android. Free, Safe, Simple, Manage your files efficiently and easily with RS File Manager. RS File Manager - RS File Explorer is an easy and powerful file explorer for Android devices. This app is free, fast and full-featured. Manage your files just like you do on your desktop or laptop using various functions Select, Cut, Copy, Paste, Move, Create, Delete, Rename, Search, Share, Send, Hide, Compress, Unzip and Bookmark...
</description></item><item><title>Download Silent Camera [High Quality] 8.16.9</title><pubDate> Sat, 24 Jan 2026 23:11:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-silent-camera-10536.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-silent-camera-10536.html
</guid><description>
Introducing the best silent camera! Without the shutter sound, photos can be taken in complete silence! It also ranks number 1 among many silent cameras thanks to its high image quality! Take high-quality photos with the silent camera! You won't disturb anyone around you because the shutter sound can't be heard. You can take high-quality photos of any situation, such as your baby's cute sleeping face, your pet's natural behaviors, and words written on a blackboard!
Silent Camera...
</description></item><item><title>Download Psiphon VPN: Freedom Online v448</title><pubDate> Sat, 24 Jan 2026 23:11:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-psiphon-pro-8479.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-psiphon-pro-8479.html
</guid><description>
Psiphon Pro is a VPN application for Android that allows users to access the Internet freely and securely. It uses a combination of VPN, SSH and HTTP proxy technologies to bypass censorship and firewalls, providing users with unrestricted internet access. It gives you unprecedented access to your favorite news broadcast or social media platforms. In essence, Psiphon Pro also protects you when accessing WiFi hotspots by creating a secure, private tunnel between you and the Internet....
</description></item><item><title>Download radio.net PRIME 5.18.1.2-app build 100125</title><pubDate> Sat, 24 Jan 2026 23:10:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-radionet-prime-8335.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-radionet-prime-8335.html
</guid><description>
radio.net PRIME is a mobile application that allows users to listen to a variety of radio stations on their Android devices. This app provides access to more than 30,000 radio stations around the world, including local and international stations in a variety of genres and formats.
Features of radio.net PRIME
	Access to more than 30,000 radio stations around the world
	Supports multiple genres and formats, including news, music, sports, and chat
	Option to create a list of favorite...
</description></item><item><title>Download TickTick:To Do List &amp;amp; Calendar 8.0.1.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 24 Jan 2026 23:10:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ticktick-to-do-list-tasks-8702.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ticktick-to-do-list-tasks-8702.html
</guid><description>
TickTick is a simple and effective task management and to-do list application that helps you schedule, manage time, remind about deadlines and organize your life at work, at home. home and everywhere else. TickTick is here to help you make the most of your day and get things done (gtd). Whether there's an idea you want to capture, a personal goal to achieve, a job to complete, or collaborating with other colleagues, even create a shopping list (with the help of a list creator). book)....
</description></item><item><title>Download Video Converter, Compressor 17.0.10</title><pubDate> Sat, 24 Jan 2026 23:10:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-video-converter-compressor-13301.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-video-converter-compressor-13301.html
</guid><description>
The fastest video converter and compressor on the market supports almost all video formats: MP4, MKV, AVI, 3GP, MOV, MTS, MPEG, MPG, WMV, M4V, VOB, FLV, etc. This converter and compressor supports converting, compressing, changing resolution, Frame Rate (FPS), bitrate of video files. It can also convert video files to audio formats like MP3, AAC, AC3, OGG, M4A, WAV, etc.
Key Features
	Convert and compress your videos to almost any video and audio format. Choose from predefined 4K to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Textra SMS 4.83 build 48361</title><pubDate> Sat, 24 Jan 2026 23:09:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-textra-sms-8697.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-textra-sms-8697.html
</guid><description>
Want a beautiful, super-fast, and highly customizable alternative to your stock Android messaging app? Well today is your day. Textra is simply outstanding! Comes with a bunch of great features, especially over 180 material design themes, bubble and app icon colors. Dark, light and auto night modes, multiple bubble styles, scheduled SMS &amp;amp; MMS (future), stop while sending, slide to delete, slide to call, snapshot camera, multi-select photo gallery select, quick reply SMS popup, great...
</description></item><item><title>Download Piktures: All-In-One Gallery 2.24 build 950</title><pubDate> Sat, 24 Jan 2026 23:09:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-piktures-gallery-photo-video-9523.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-piktures-gallery-photo-video-9523.html
</guid><description>
Piktures is a simple photo gallery app with very advanced features. It supports dozens of cloud services like Google Drive and Microsoft Onedrive, your personal cloud server (WebDav), SD Cards, USB drives and even your computer! Piktures allows you to view your photos in grid, mosaic and list views. Organize them the way you like.
Features of Piktures
	Fast: Piktures has its own rendering engine so you can view photos very quickly.
	Secret Space: The secure space protects your most...
</description></item><item><title>Download The Guardian - Live World News 6.206.22417</title><pubDate> Sat, 24 Jan 2026 23:09:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-the-guardian-news-sport-8572.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-the-guardian-news-sport-8572.html
</guid><description>
Read the best news stories, hot news &amp;amp; comments along the way. The Guardian app gives you access to the latest politics, business and sports news through award-winning journalism.
World news, live updates &amp;amp; opinion - take your news feed with you wherever you go. Explore US stories, headlines, content and media on a variety of topics; from business to music, politics, sports, culture &amp;amp; more.
5 reasons to download The Guardian App
	Breaking news alerts, sent straight to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Lucky Patcher 12.0.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 24 Jan 2026 23:08:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-lucky-patcher-11914.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-lucky-patcher-11914.html
</guid><description>
Lucky Patcher is a free Android app that can modify many apps and games, Block ads, remove unwanted system apps, backup apps before and after modification, Move apps apps to SD card, remove license verification from paid apps and games, etc.
Lucky Patcher features and details:
	Remove or block ads on Android apps and games. You can easily block ads with Lucky Patcher.
	Block in-app purchase verification with the app. You can use premium apps and games for free by removing in-app...
</description></item><item><title>Download Business Calendar 2 Pro 2.53.8 build 253801</title><pubDate> Sat, 24 Jan 2026 23:08:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-business-calendar-8433.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-business-calendar-8433.html
</guid><description>
Business Calendar 2 Pro is the premium version of our popular calendar app. It provides a great overview of your appointments, is easy to use, and gives you powerful tools to plan and schedule your events and tasks.
Features of Business Calendar
Your personal organizer
	calendar, planner and tasks in one app
	6 clearly designed main views: month, week, day, agenda, year and tasks
	popup with live event details in month view
	flexible daily and weekly planning that can be adjusted...
</description></item><item><title>Download Fing - Network Tools 12.11.6 build 121106003</title><pubDate> Sat, 24 Jan 2026 23:08:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-fing-network-tools-8540.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-fing-network-tools-8540.html
</guid><description>
Fing is a popular network scanning application that allows users to discover devices connected to the local network, view their IP and MAC addresses, and perform various network tests. Fing is the #1 Network Scanner: detects all devices connected to your WiFi and identifies them with our patented technology that is also used by router manufacturers and companies antivirus used worldwide.
Features of Fing for Android
	Network Scan: Quickly find all devices connected to your Wi-Fi...
</description></item><item><title>Download Audiomack: Music Downloader 7.11.1 build 31455</title><pubDate> Sat, 24 Jan 2026 23:07:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-audiomack-music-downloader-11192.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-audiomack-music-downloader-11192.html
</guid><description>
Stream and download the best new trending music (full tracks offline data-free) and listen to your local MP3s!&amp;nbsp;Browse music from the best artists in top categories like Hip-Hop, Rap, R&amp;amp;B, EDM, Afropop, and Reggae on the Audiomack music app. Download songs and listen offline, without using your data, or listen to your personal MP3 collection! Audiomack provides download access and unlimited streaming to the newest and hottest tracks, right at your fingertips. Our music download...
</description></item><item><title>Download YoWindow Weather - Unlimited 2.55.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 24 Jan 2026 23:07:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-yowindow-weather-unlimited-8421.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-yowindow-weather-unlimited-8421.html
</guid><description>
YoWindow is a unique new weather app. The magic of YoWindow is a living landscape that reflects your real-life weather. For example, if it rains - it will rain in YoWindow. Sunset and sunrise in YoWindow take place at the same time as in real life. But the cool thing is you can roll time forward. Just swipe the screen and you'll see how the weather changes throughout the day.
YoWindow Weather Features - Unlimited
	All the weather at your fingertips. You see the current weather,...
</description></item></channel></rss>