<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 15:42:47 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 15:42:47 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download PhotoStage Slideshow Producer Professional 12.15</title><pubDate> Tue, 26 Aug 2025 17:34:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photostage-slideshow-producer-professional-942.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photostage-slideshow-producer-professional-942.html
</guid><description>
PhotoStage Slideshow Producer Professional is a software to create the slideshow using image files, audio and video. This is a program that allows you to create slideshows from images, by providing you a number of simple tools to use.
PhotoStage Photo slideshow Maker has the ability to add effects (e.g. brightness, crop, rotate, speed, zoom) and transitions (e.g. fade, reveal, wipe, circle, heart, diamond). This can be done through the dedicated menu or visual tab also provides the option...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDF-XChange Editor Plus 10.7.1.399.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 26 Aug 2025 17:34:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-xchange-editor-plus-645.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-xchange-editor-plus-645.html
</guid><description>
PDF-XChange Editor Plus is the editor, PDF viewer, compact, fast with many features, add-ons, professional. When using the PDF-XChange Editor Plus, easy for users to create, view, edit, annotate, OCR and digital signing PDF files, plus much more.
PDF-XChange Editor is a PDF editing full-featured. With the help of it, you can edit, fix, add, or delete text easily. Graphics can also be moved, resized or removed.
Features PDF-XChange Editor Plus
Edit documents
	Use a variety of editing...
</description></item><item><title>Download MyLanViewer Enterprise 6.5.6</title><pubDate> Tue, 26 Aug 2025 17:33:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mylanviewer-enterprise-1274.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mylanviewer-enterprise-1274.html
</guid><description>
MyLanViewer is a program for scanning IP address, Netbios and LAN / Network powerful for Windows tool whois and traceroute, remote shutdown and process management Wake On LAN (WOL), scan and monitor wireless networks. This app will help you find all IP addresses, MAC addresses and shared folders of computers on the network wired or wireless (Wi-Fi).
MyLanViewer Enterprise - Scan IP address LAN/Network
The program scans network and displays the computer network in your window, friends...
</description></item><item><title>Download Opera One 120.0.5543.201</title><pubDate> Tue, 26 Aug 2025 17:33:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-972.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-972.html
</guid><description>
Opera is a fast, safe, configurable and compliant intranet web browser, which includes both the reader and the application. The Opera browser supports web browsing, listening to music, watching high speed movies, you can open many tabs on the Opera without affecting your browsing speed. Opera now supports almost all devices and operating systems such as windows, IOS, Android, linux, MacOS ...
Opera is a beautiful interface and many interesting features, operating on both PCs and mobile,...
</description></item><item><title>Download StartAllBack 3.9.13.5300</title><pubDate> Tue, 26 Aug 2025 17:32:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-startallback-6857.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-startallback-6857.html
</guid><description>
With the official release of Windows 11, chances are that most of you want to try it out. As the name suggests, StartAllBack is a small, lightweight tool that can help you enjoy the power of the new operating system while keeping the look and feel, especially because main work area, desktop of Windows 7, Windows 10 as taskbars and start menu styles.
StartAllBack is specially designed for Windows 11 and will not work on any older operating systems. If you want to get the start menu back...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDF-XChange Pro 10.7.1.399.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 26 Aug 2025 17:32:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-xchange-editor-pro-3422.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-xchange-editor-pro-3422.html
</guid><description>
PDF-XChange Editor Pro is an application to manipulate and create PDF versatile, offering a wide range of useful features and powerful will help you to easily work with PDF files. This application is very flexible and allows you to easily create and modify PDF files. PDF-XChange Editor Pro provides a powerful set of tools and flexibility to work with PDF files, such as editor PDF-XChange new, utilities series, OFFice2PDF and the Addin tool Bar allows you to easily convert multiple file...
</description></item><item><title>Download MiniTool Video Converter 4.4.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 26 Aug 2025 17:31:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minitool-video-converter-5358.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minitool-video-converter-5358.html
</guid><description>
MiniTool Video Converter is the most direct solution for converting audio and video files to a wide variety of formats. This free video converter is available to convert audio to video and convert video to audio. This free video converter supports over 1000 conversion formats including 4K / FHD / HD files MP4, MOV, MKV, AVI, WMV, M4V and audio formats like MP3, WAV, M4A, WMA High Quality, AAC, AC3.
MiniTool Video Converter allows you to convert batches of files at the same time. Just...
</description></item><item><title>Download Advanced Installer Architect 22.9.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 26 Aug 2025 17:31:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-installer-128.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-installer-128.html
</guid><description>
Advanced Installer is a Windows utility designed to help you build the package Windows Installer in a working environment clean and intuitive.
Although it has many parameters dedicated but the user interface is very simple and gives users the ability to create new projects by selecting the type, namely installer (for example: application Visual Studio or .NET, pack 32/64-bit mixture), Java , updates, support, mobile devices, and other things.
Advanced Installer - An environment for...
</description></item><item><title>Download Lumina Analytica Optimizer 6.5.11.266</title><pubDate> Tue, 26 Aug 2025 17:30:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lumina-analytica-optimizer-10353.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lumina-analytica-optimizer-10353.html
</guid><description>
Lumina Analytica Optimizer is the highest version that includes all the Enterprise features, plus the addition of powerful resolution tools. It discovers decision values that minimize or maximize any quantitative objective, subject to constraints. Or, in the absence of an objective quantity, it finds a feasible solution within the constraints. It handles Linear Programming, Quadratic Programming and Non-Linear Programming in general and automatically differentiates between all of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Renee PDF Aide 2025.08.24.183</title><pubDate> Tue, 26 Aug 2025 17:30:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-renee-pdf-aide-2042.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-renee-pdf-aide-2042.html
</guid><description>
Renee PDF Aide is versatile software support to convert and edit PDF like you are edit Word, Excel, Power Point (PPT), Image, HTML,. PDF is the file format most popular commercial but difficult to edit. That's how Renee PDF support: it helps users to convert PDF documents into files that can edit like Word, Excel, Power Point (PPT), Image, HTML, EPUB and txt document. In addition, Renee PDF Aide is equipped with cutting-edge OCR technology can recognize the characters in image PDF or...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Acrobat Reader DC 2025.001.20643</title><pubDate> Tue, 26 Aug 2025 17:29:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-acrobat-reader-3707.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-acrobat-reader-3707.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Acrobat Reader DC is a system of application software and Web services developed by Adobe Systems to view, create, manipulate, print and manage PDF files. With Adobe Acrobat Reader DC, you can create, export, edit, and track PDF files from anywhere - and maintain connection with the recent set of files on all your devices.
Adobe Acrobat Reader current DC is connected with Adobe Document Cloud - help working on the computers and mobile devices becomes easier than ever before. This is...
</description></item><item><title>Download WizTree 4.27 Enterprise</title><pubDate> Tue, 26 Aug 2025 17:23:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wiztree-3529.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wiztree-3529.html
</guid><description>
WizTree is a tool to analyze hard drive space similar to WinDirStat, but much faster. WizTree works well on all version 32 and 64 bit of Windows XP, Vista, Windows 7, 8 and 10. WizTree will quickly scan the drive and displays the name and location of the file largest. Scan results are presented in the form of tree or list on the tab 1000 file largest. To delete a file, right-click on it and select Delete from the context menu. Analyzer WizTree mark the file system in grey, thus protecting...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaMonkey Gold 2024.2.0.3165 Beta</title><pubDate> Tue, 26 Aug 2025 17:23:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediamonkey-gold-231.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediamonkey-gold-231.html
</guid><description>
MediaMonkey Gold is music manager and music player multimedia for the music collection and iPod users. MediaMonkey lists the audio file of you as CD, OGG, WMA, MPC, FLAC, APE, WAV and MP3 and includes the edit smart card and an automatic file and folder to arrange your music library.
MediaMonkey Gold also has CD ripper, CD / DVD Burner, and audio converter for saving music, and manual or editor list automatically to create mixed music.
Features MediaMonkey Gold
	Automatically find...
</description></item><item><title>Download MixPad Masters Edition 13.36</title><pubDate> Tue, 26 Aug 2025 17:22:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mixpad-masters-edition-505.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mixpad-masters-edition-505.html
</guid><description>
MixPad Masters Edition is software mixing many different songs, mix music files available, or the recording is completed and combine them. MixPad Masters Edition is software recording and mixing music is designed to produce sounds easily. Mix music, vocal and audio, adjust the volume, pan, fade and more with MixPad as your digital mixing your.
MixPad Masters Edition will save the sound under the popular formats such as MP3,WAV, AIF, WMA, VOX, M4A, GSM,... user can create, add and remove...
</description></item><item><title>Download VideoPad Video Editor Pro 17.36</title><pubDate> Tue, 26 Aug 2025 17:22:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-videopad-video-editor-pro-268.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-videopad-video-editor-pro-268.html
</guid><description>
VideoPad Video Editor Pro is software edit video from any camcorder, DV camcorder, VHS player or webcam for best quality. The interface of this utility is divided into several parts (for example: list of multi-media, Effects, transitions, Files, Clips, video track, audio track, overlay), which makes everything seem difficult to operate. You can capture videos from camcorder or other devices like webcam or capture card TV and after you have added files and sequence clips to the queue, you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Phoenix Customizer 1.1.9 Beta</title><pubDate> Tue, 26 Aug 2025 17:21:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-phoenix-customizer-12580.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-phoenix-customizer-12580.html
</guid><description>
Phoenix Customizer provides you with various settings that allow you to customize your Windows 11 or Windows 10 system. You can easily customize Windows folders with various colors and effects, add a custom taskbar that you can change to your liking, have a floating widget with access to shortcuts, and favorites or modify the Windows context menu.
Main features
	Customize Windows folders: Customize your Windows folder icons easily. It's simple, select the Windows folder for which you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft Edge 139.0.3405.119</title><pubDate> Tue, 26 Aug 2025 17:20:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-edge-3940.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-edge-3940.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft Edge is web browser developed specifically for Windows operating system 10 alternatives to Internet Explorer is the default browser on Windows. Browser Microsoft Edge built-in assistant Cortana brings content and website based on the user's preferences, there are also system utilities quite extensive help you to customize according to individual. Microsoft Edge has the similarity with Google Chrome quite large, except the target is marked more of the interface and the rounded...
</description></item><item><title>Download Twenty 2nd Century Lightcube 1.2.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 26 Aug 2025 17:20:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-twenty-2nd-century-lightcube-12253.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-twenty-2nd-century-lightcube-12253.html
</guid><description>
Lightcube is a pixel art editing tool for game developers and artists, with many features including multiple layers, animation frames, and many tools including pen, eraser, wand selection spirit, paint bucket, line drawing and pattern brush. Lightcube has everything you need to easily turn your game development assets or creative visions into reality.
Whether you're a pixel artist or a game developer, the intuitive interface makes creating stunning pixel art easy. Immerse yourself in a...
</description></item><item><title>Download PilotEdit Pro 20.2.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 26 Aug 2025 17:20:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pilotedit-979.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pilotedit-979.html
</guid><description>
PilotEdit is software edit the textfile to help you execute scripts, extract strings and edit large files. PilotEdit is the editing file will help you search and replace multi-line text, edit files, FTP or even download and upload files and folders FTP. With edit file PilotEdit becomes easier.
PilotEdit - edit text files
PilotEdit is a hex-editor and advanced text support opening files larger than 4GB. It provides syntax to customize and highlight keywords, advanced search and replace...
</description></item><item><title>Download Fast Screen Recorder 2.1.0.14</title><pubDate> Tue, 26 Aug 2025 17:19:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fast-screen-recorder-7132.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fast-screen-recorder-7132.html
</guid><description>
With the Fast Screen Recorder app, you can capture any moment on your screen. Fast Screen Recorder helps capture your online conferences, meetings, tutorials, gaming moments and more. You can only record audio, video and both with or without a voice mic.
Fast Screen Recorder provides an option to enable/disable your microphone before recording begins. So you can make videos with your voice. This is useful for recording tutorials and presentations. After recording video or audio from...
</description></item><item><title>Download Outline Client VPN 1.16.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 26 Aug 2025 17:19:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-outline-client-vpn-7913.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-outline-client-vpn-7913.html
</guid><description>
Outline Client VPN is a simple, easy-to-use application that allows you to share access to a VPN with anyone on your network. It provides greater control over a user's online anonymity. It is a free service that allows users to create their own virtual private network, allowing them to share access with anyone on their network.
Outline Client VPN uses services from DigitalOcean, Google Cloud Platform, and Amazon Lightsail. These options are intended to make the process simpler, you can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Gilisoft Copy Protect 8.1.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 26 Aug 2025 17:18:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-copy-protect-8047.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-copy-protect-8047.html
</guid><description>
Gilisoft Copy Protect is software that helps you protect audio, video, PDF, DOC, PPT, XLS and image files so that they cannot be copied or distributed by illegal means. Users can play from, video encoded on macOS, android using Gilisoft's GCP reader.
Features of Gilisoft Copy Protect
	A document security tool that creates shareless GCP files to protect your Video, Photo, DOC, PDF, XLS, PPT files from unauthorized sharing, editing, copying or viewing .
	Protect document files from...
</description></item><item><title>Download Metasequoia 4.9.0c</title><pubDate> Tue, 26 Aug 2025 17:18:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tetraface-inc-metasequoia-1479.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tetraface-inc-metasequoia-1479.html
</guid><description>
Metasequoia is software designed three-dimensional model and create the characters the same person or animal, requires some knowledge in this field and most important is a set of tools suitable for the job. For those who have created a number of innovative 3D solutions dedicated software different and need to work with them without have to re-install each program, a utility like Metasequoia can be the right choice.
Tetraface Inc Metasequoia - designed three-dimensional model
This app...
</description></item><item><title>Download EverNote 10.152.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 26 Aug 2025 17:17:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-evernote-3261.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-evernote-3261.html
</guid><description>
EverNote is the all in one tool allows you to track notes, todo items, memos, outlines, excerpts, websites, ideas and other things and automatically synchronize them between multiple computers and mobile devices (iPhone, Android, etc.). You can choose to sort their notes into categories, password protect them, export them to XML and more. EverNote supports a number of pattern notes allow you to add to-do list, spreadsheet like Excel to calculate costs (automatic sum), notes, phone, contact...
</description></item><item><title>Download DP Animation Maker 3.5.42</title><pubDate> Tue, 26 Aug 2025 17:16:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dp-animation-maker-2860.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dp-animation-maker-2860.html
</guid><description>
DP Animation Maker - 2D animation software smart allows you to turn static images into motion directly. The world is a living, breathing from your still images with minimal effort. DP Animation Maker lets you make natural scenes burst with vibrancy and bring out the motion to people and objects.
DP Animation Maker - Create and edit animated GIF
Animation Maker has the tools rich that you need to put all the pieces together. When you select pictures of yourself, it's easy to move from...
</description></item></channel></rss>