<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 20:09:56 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 20:09:56 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download EaseUS Data Recovery Wizard Professional WinPE 19.6.5 Build 20250721</title><pubDate> Thu, 07 Aug 2025 18:05:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-data-recovery-wizard-winpe-4379.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-data-recovery-wizard-winpe-4379.html
</guid><description>
EaseUS Data Recovery Wizard WinPE - recovery software best data to restore data deleted, formatted or lost from PC, laptop or mobile device easily and quickly. Help get back the lost files or deleted photos, music, sounds, emails, etc. from hard drive, memory card, USB, digital cameras, mobile devices, and other storage media. Program recover data this recover files lost or deleted 100% safe from losing cases different data on different devices without overwriting original data.
EaseUS...
</description></item><item><title>Download Screenpresso Pro 2.1.38</title><pubDate> Thu, 07 Aug 2025 18:04:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-screenpresso-pro-1362.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-screenpresso-pro-1362.html
</guid><description>
Screenpresso Pro is a program easy to take great photos on your screen! Screenpresso blocked Print Screen key and screen capture the best in a few seconds. Allows you to capture windows and screen area, roll the part of the screen, edit the images obtained, add effects, resize a group of images, send screenshots by email and post them to Web resources.
Screenpresso Pro - Shooting the computer screen
Features of Screenpresso Pro
	Take the window and screen area. Take a partial screen...
</description></item><item><title>Download Final Draft 13.2.5 Build 94</title><pubDate> Thu, 07 Aug 2025 18:04:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-final-draft-1241.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-final-draft-1241.html
</guid><description>
Final Draft is a professional program to write scripts for movies, tv shows and performances. This program is a word processor text window with a lot of ability to script specialized. To use the program, you absolutely do not need to know the rules to design the scenario - draft ultimate will automatically convert scripts you write by world standards.
Final Draft - script Writing professional
The features of Final Draft
	Send a copy of the index cards with the summary directly to...
</description></item><item><title>Download XYplorer 27.10.0400</title><pubDate> Thu, 07 Aug 2025 18:03:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-533.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-533.html
</guid><description>
XYplorer - File Manager for Windows is software that supports users to manage files on the Window quickly and to arrange the folder tidy. XYplorer features tabbed browsing, search, files, powerful, preview, flexible, highly customizable interface, dual frame options and a variety of unique ways to automate effective tasks often repeat. It's fast, lightweight, and portable.
Features XYplorer
	XYplorer is a file manager mobile. It does not require any settings, store all configuration...
</description></item><item><title>Download Viber for PC 25.9.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 07 Aug 2025 17:53:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-viber-2406.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-viber-2406.html
</guid><description>
Viber is a software of instant messaging, based on VoIP protocols, multi-platform due to the Viber Media development for smart phones used to send sms and make calls over the internet. Along with text messaging, users can exchange images, video and audio.
Viber - software news message, chat online
This is a program that is quite popular is mainly designed for mobile phones, but now we are talking about the version for Windows, so immediately. It will allow you to send messages to other...
</description></item><item><title>Download OpenVPN 2.6.14</title><pubDate> Thu, 07 Aug 2025 17:53:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-openvpn-4245.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-openvpn-4245.html
</guid><description>
OpenVPN provides the VPN solution flexible to secure communication of your data, whether it is the right to privacy on the Internet, remote access for employees, security, IoT, or for the data center cloud. Solution VPN software, our Server can be deployed in place by standard server or virtual device or on the cloud.
OpenVPN - VPN Solution flexible
Though built with the open source OpenVPN, the solution of our additional functionality to meet the needs of business customers, the...
</description></item><item><title>Download OCCT 14.2.4.99</title><pubDate> Thu, 07 Aug 2025 17:52:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-occt-perestroika-1680.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-occt-perestroika-1680.html
</guid><description>
OCCT is a free application designed to benchmark and overclock system components. Test tool OverClock includes 4 different tests to assess the stability of your computer. CPU and CPU: Linpack to test the processor, GPU: 3D to check stability of the graphics processor and power supply combination of CPU: Linpack and GPU: 3D to download power of you up to the maximum.
OCCT - Measuring system components
The features of OCCT
	Support is enabled for a maximum of 16 cores.
	All the tests...
</description></item><item><title>Download Freemake Video Converter Gold 5.0.0.10</title><pubDate> Thu, 07 Aug 2025 17:52:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-freemake-video-converter-gold-167.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-freemake-video-converter-gold-167.html
</guid><description>
Freemake Video Converter Gold is a software to help convert tail high quality videos with many different formats on many devices. Freemake Video Converter - convert video to AVI, MP4, WMV, MKV, 3GP, DVD, MP3, iPad, iPhone, PSP, Android phone. Video to MP3 just with one click! Rip and burn DVD. Convert YouTube to MP4, AVI, etc. with Freemake! Results guaranteed. Freemake Video Converter has fast conversion speed, guarantee the output quality,support create HTML5 videos have the embed code...
</description></item><item><title>Download SoftPerfect RAM Disk 25.8</title><pubDate> Thu, 07 Aug 2025 17:51:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-softperfect-ram-disk-4359.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-softperfect-ram-disk-4359.html
</guid><description>
SoftPerfect RAM Disk is a program disk, RAM performance is designed to help you have a disk on the computer is stored completely in memory. Because memory is much faster than physical hard disk, should store temporary data on disk in fast memory to achieve higher performance. Whether your job is what, keep reading to find out if a RAM disk can offer you what. The program creates a virtual disk located in the computer RAM accessible in Windows Explorer and other applications, allowing you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Chris-PC RAM Booster 7.25.0711</title><pubDate> Thu, 07 Aug 2025 17:51:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chris-pc-ram-booster-1181.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chris-pc-ram-booster-1181.html
</guid><description>
ChrisPC RAM Booster is software speed up your system by managing and acceleration of the RAM in the operating system. RAM Booster will monitor the RAM usage (memory random access) and upon reaching the threshold memory certain low, it will trigger the process of freeing up memory for the new program open while moving at the same time the old programs from the RAM memory into virtual memory on disk.
Chris-PC RAM Booster - speed up processing RAM
Certainly this is a slower process...
</description></item><item><title>Download ExtraMAME 25.8</title><pubDate> Thu, 07 Aug 2025 17:50:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-extramame-2608.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-extramame-2608.html
</guid><description>
ExtraMAME is a simple tool that allows simulation of the arcade game from the most popular platform but is long forgotten, thanks to which the game industry has reached the current level. After launch, you will get 11 games pre-installed, among which are: Super Mario Bros, Pac-Man Plus, Space Invaders II and other games.
The simulation of multiple machine arcade is authored by Nicola Salmoria and team MAME. MAME lets you play thousands of arcade game old school on your computer. ExtraMAME...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Master Collection 2025 v8</title><pubDate> Thu, 07 Aug 2025 17:50:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-master-collection-0001-8036.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-master-collection-0001-8036.html
</guid><description>
You may already know that Adobe Master Collection 2025 does not officially exist and Adobe has never released it. But now that it's here, we also need to give thanks to m0nkrus and PainteR (who put a lot of effort into creating it). Adobe Master Collection 2025 is a collection of applications from the Creative Cloud 2025 line, united by a multilingual installer with the ability to choose the installation path and interface language of installed programs. In terms of functionality,...
</description></item><item><title>Download TechSmith Snagit 2025 v25.3.0.7627</title><pubDate> Thu, 07 Aug 2025 17:48:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-techsmith-snagit-01en-280.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-techsmith-snagit-01en-280.html
</guid><description>
TechSmith Snagit software screen capture anything on your screen, then easily add text arrows or effects and save the snapshot to a file or share it immediately by e-mail or IM. With TechSmith Snagit you can capture and share the article, photo or Web page directly from your screen.
TechSmith Snagit
TechSmith Snagit help you can take a photo screen in the form of roll, panoramic shooting, shooting photos of and easy photo editing after shooting. Besides it is feature - video recording...
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 7.0.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 07 Aug 2025 17:47:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-11-7760.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-11-7760.html
</guid><description>
TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 is a program that allows users to discover hidden settings in Windows 11. This application is specially designed for Windows 11, groups many registry settings and distribute them from the easy and secure user interface. With TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 you can move the Windows taskbar to the top and resize the taskbar by editing the registry value. With any application that modifies the registry, we recommend that you have a backup copy...
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 7.0.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 07 Aug 2025 17:47:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-10-7759.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-10-7759.html
</guid><description>
TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 is a utility that allows users to discover hidden settings in Windows 10. This application is specially designed for Windows 10, groups many registry settings and provide them from an easy and secure user interface. With TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 you can move the Windows taskbar to the top and resize the taskbar by editing the registry value. With any application that modifies the registry, we recommend that you have a backup copy to...
</description></item><item><title>Download 4KSoftware 4K Downloader 5.16.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 07 Aug 2025 17:47:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-downloader-3858.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-downloader-3858.html
</guid><description>
4K Downloader is a Windows application small but powerful to download and convert video in 4K and 8K Ultra HD from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion and thousands of other video-based websites. It speeds up your download by up to 5 times. Consider that most smart phones, TVS, computers, and tablets all support the high definition format, don't be surprised when many users want to enjoy quality content on their device. 4K Downloader is a lightweight software designed to help you grab videos...
</description></item><item><title>Download Secret Disk Pro 2025 v311</title><pubDate> Thu, 07 Aug 2025 17:46:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secret-disk-pro-933.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secret-disk-pro-933.html
</guid><description>
Secret Disk Pro 4 is a software to create a virtual disk can be hidden and password protected to keep your data private and safe. You can store any file and folder on the disk. Disc secret works like a hard disk typically, and is compatible with any any other program that you have installed. You can have more than one disk secret, and you can also choose disk letter.
Secret Disk Pro 4 - Create and secure drive
Secret Disk does not encrypt any files, it just limits access to your files...
</description></item><item><title>Download XL-Connector 3.6.6.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 07 Aug 2025 17:46:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xl-connector-12415.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xl-connector-12415.html
</guid><description>
XL-Connector is a popular plugin that securely integrates Excel and Salesforce to export, import, refresh and transform data seamlessly with ultra-fast api connection. It provides Salesforce administrators with a comprehensive toolbox that easily performs data and metadata management activities in a familiar Excel environment.
Features
Export from Salesforce to Excel
	Get data from existing Salesforce reports or build your own SOQL queries directly into Excel.
Import data into...
</description></item><item><title>Download QueueExplorer Professional 5.0.53</title><pubDate> Thu, 07 Aug 2025 17:45:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-queueexplorer-professional-4823.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-queueexplorer-professional-4823.html
</guid><description>
QueueExplorer is a tool indispensable to work with queues and messages: understand and manage your system, find the error and fix it. Or you can use QueueExplorer to sort them by any field available. Because of the sort display the messages in another order with them will be handled, QueueExplorer more columns of Ms Ms # # so you can still see what is processed first.
The features of QueueExplorer
Move, copy or delete messages
	Messages can be handled the same as in process explorer,...
</description></item><item><title>Download MaxCut Business Edition 2.9.5.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 07 Aug 2025 17:45:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-maxcut-business-edition-3912.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-maxcut-business-edition-3912.html
</guid><description>
MaxCut Business Edition is a software to create cutting diagrams, accurate, and cost estimate for the wood industry, cabinets and metal,.. You enter the size and material, MaxCut will do the rest! Produce optimized cutting diagrams, create estimates, orders, and labels - it's just a click. Run the application MaxCut Business Edition brings a pretty clean interface and slick quickly get you up and running. Most space represents the editing area, with the main function are stored cleverly in...
</description></item><item><title>Download Exportizer Enterprise 10.1.9.590</title><pubDate> Thu, 07 Aug 2025 17:45:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-exportizer-pro-470.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-exportizer-pro-470.html
</guid><description>
Exportizer Pro is software export base, robust data that allows view, edit and export the database to a data file, text, clipboard. Exportizer Pro is a software tool effective and simple, can be used to help individuals view, filter and copy an entire database to clipboard or convert it to another format.
Simple interface and no complex also indicates that Exportizer Pro meet the system requirements, the application can run on most operating systems.
The main window of Exportizer Pro...
</description></item><item><title>Download ezPaycheck 3.15.18</title><pubDate> Thu, 07 Aug 2025 17:44:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ezpaycheck-5319.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ezpaycheck-5319.html
</guid><description>
ezPaycheck is a payroll software easy to use is designed for the small business: simple, reliable and affordable. The developer of we have designed it to become a solution tax payroll internal for small businesses to calculate taxes, print paychecks for employees and contractors, generate reports and print tax forms.
The features of ezPaycheck
	Calculate payroll federal and state tax / deductions and local taxes (such as SDI tax, occupation tax, city)
	Print paychecks and tax...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinTools Zip Express 2.19.7.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 07 Aug 2025 17:44:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wintools-zip-express-2201.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wintools-zip-express-2201.html
</guid><description>
Zip Express is a good program helps you to search zip code and the city related of they, provide you with additional information such as timezone or area code. After installed and quick launch, a window quite compact will open in front of us, but the size of it can be changed to get clearer picture about what is happening. The top toolbar provides quick access to the main menu and a number of search criteria, all depends on the knowledge of your search, you can search by city or by state,...
</description></item><item><title>Download ezCheckPrinting for Quickbook 9.1.13</title><pubDate> Thu, 07 Aug 2025 17:43:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ezcheckprinting-5204.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ezcheckprinting-5204.html
</guid><description>
Software ezCheckPrinting for any business need design and in Czech republic professional. The big business and start-up companies are able to organize payments and print checks, customized from any laser printer or MICR how. Professional has never been so easy.
ezCheckPrinting can support the account and check the unlimited without paying an additional fee. It also allows users to QuickBooks / Quicken print checks on the blank through the virtual printer ezCheckPrinting options (only...
</description></item><item><title>Download Monkeys Audio 11.30</title><pubDate> Thu, 07 Aug 2025 16:45:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-monkeys-audio-949.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-monkeys-audio-949.html
</guid><description>
Monkey\'s Audio is software that compresses digital music without loss of quality. Supports high quality WAV files and CD ripping. Monkeys Audio will compress .wav tracks into .ape files to reduce their size without loss of sound quality, decompress .ape, convert files, check file integrity and manage tags.
Unlike traditional methods like MP3 and OGG, which permanently remove quality to save space, Monkey\'s Audio only creates perfect copies with the same sound quality as the originals....
</description></item></channel></rss>