<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 17:32:59 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 17:32:59 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download HFS: HTTP File Server (version 3) 0.57.26</title><pubDate> Sun, 02 Nov 2025 19:38:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hfs-http-file-server-11851.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hfs-http-file-server-11851.html
</guid><description>
HFS is a web file server to run on your computer. Share a folder or even a file thanks to the virtual file system. Essentially, this application turns your computer into an HTTP server and all users who want to connect and download files can do so by loading a simple website in their browser. HFS includes many configuration settings, so you can basically change each part of the application, starting with how users download files and ending with the appearance of the created website.
HFS...
</description></item><item><title>Download iDefender 5.2.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 02 Nov 2025 19:33:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idefender-13959.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idefender-13959.html
</guid><description>
iDefender is an advanced security solution designed for the home, providing both a High-Performance Intrusion Prevention System (HIPS) and Real-Time Endpoint Detection and Response (EDR). This integrated system protects against potential threats, ensuring the safety and integrity of your devices by proactively monitoring and responding to suspicious activity.
Why iDefender?
Ransomware Prevention
	Detects and blocks ransomware in real time to protect important files from malicious...
</description></item><item><title>Download Windows 11 Pro 25H2 v26200.6899 NoTPM Multilingual Preactivated</title><pubDate> Sun, 02 Nov 2025 19:31:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-11-6618.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-11-6618.html
</guid><description>
Windows 11 is officially leaked to a developer version. Previously, when Windows 10 was released, Microsoft once stated that Windows 10 would be the last version of Windows for users. Clearly, with the arrival of Windows 11, Microsoft needed a major reason to reverse its previous claims and still remove Windows 10 by introducing some new operating systems.
About the interface of Windows 11 is quite similar to Windows 10X (a version of Windows 10 has stopped growing). The logo image of...
</description></item><item><title>Download ImgDrive 2.2.5</title><pubDate> Sun, 02 Nov 2025 19:30:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-imgdrive-7453.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-imgdrive-7453.html
</guid><description>
ImgDrive is an application for users who need a simple, reliable drive emulator that allows them to mount disk image files saved in various formats . It is easy to use and does your job well, as it sits in the system tray and is integrated into the Windows context menu.
Features of ImgDrive
	One-click mounting of ISO, CUE, NRG, MDS/MDF, CCD, ISZ images
	Runs on 32-bit and 64-bit versions of Windows from 2000 to Windows 10/11.
	Mount APE, FLAC, M4A, WAV, WavPack, TTA files as AUDIO CD...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mocha Pro for Adobe 2025.5 v12.5.3</title><pubDate> Sun, 02 Nov 2025 19:30:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mocha-pro-1029.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mocha-pro-1029.html
</guid><description>
Mocha Pro 2019 is the tool for visual effects and postproduction. Tool Tracking and VFX and is plugins for Adobe. Mocha is the artist and editor effects appreciate about the unique ability of his to reduce the time using keyframing related to VFX and premium finishing.
Mocha Pro 2019
Mocha Pro 2019 features track and remove objects that are GPU acceleratedtools, rotoscoping, advanced, stable, solved 3D camera, supports stereo 360 / VR, etc. Using Mocha AE CC in Adobe After Effects? See...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mocha Pro Standalone 2025.5 v12.5.3</title><pubDate> Sun, 02 Nov 2025 19:30:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mocha-pro-standalone-4302.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mocha-pro-standalone-4302.html
</guid><description>
Mocha Pro Standalone is the tracking tool flat the world's most powerful for VFX and postproduction. With the tracking feature and remove objects that are GPU accelerated, mask advanced with snapshot feature edge, stable, corrective lens, the 3D camera, supports stereo 360 / VR, v. v. Mocha Pro Standalone is a plugin for Adobe Premiere Pro &amp;amp; After Effects, servers Avid Media Composer &amp;amp; OFX as Flame, Nuke, Fusion, HitFilm, and VEGAS Pro.
Mocha Pro Standalone 2020
New features in...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mocha Pro for OFX 2025.5 v12.5.3</title><pubDate> Sun, 02 Nov 2025 19:27:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mocha-pro-for-ofx-4303.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mocha-pro-for-ofx-4303.html
</guid><description>
Mocha Pro for OFX is the tracking tool flat the world's most powerful for VFX and postproduction. With the tracking feature and remove objects that are GPU accelerated, mask advanced with snapshot feature edge, stable, corrective lens, the 3D camera, supports stereo 360 / VR, v. v. Mocha Pro for OFX is a plugin for Adobe Premiere Pro &amp;amp; After Effects, servers Avid Media Composer &amp;amp; OFX as Flame, Nuke, Fusion, HitFilm, and VEGAS Pro.
Mocha Pro for OFX 2020
New features in version...
</description></item><item><title>Download Boris FX Mocha Pro for AVX 2025.5 v12.5.3</title><pubDate> Sun, 02 Nov 2025 19:27:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-boris-fx-mocha-pro-for-avx-13995.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-boris-fx-mocha-pro-for-avx-13995.html
</guid><description>
Boris FX Mocha Pro for AVX is the industry-leading version of the plane tracking and visual effects software, designed to work as a plugin supporting AVX (Avid Video Extensions) servers such as Avid Media Composer. Mocha Pro integrates advanced plane tracking, rotoscoping, 3D camera resolution, object removal, image stabilization, and masking tools into supported hosts, including AVX-based editing software.
Key points about Boris FX Mocha Pro for AVX:
	This is part of the Boris FX...
</description></item><item><title>Download Daemon Tools Lite 12.3.0.2363</title><pubDate> Sun, 02 Nov 2025 19:26:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-daemon-tools-lite-3391.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-daemon-tools-lite-3391.html
</guid><description>
DAEMON Tools Lite is based on two key features, simulation of virtual disks and building the file disk image as iso. DAEMON Tools Lite can emulate up to 4 virtual drives, DVD, CD or Blu-ray on your computer. The virtual units will be present in your system the same as the unit. After you select the virtual drive you want, you will choose a disc image (nrg, iso, mdf, bin, cue, etc.) that you want to mount. Visit My Computer at the device have The mobile storage and you will find the disk...
</description></item><item><title>Download Derivative TouchDesigner Pro 2025.31550</title><pubDate> Sun, 02 Nov 2025 19:24:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-derivative-touchdesigner-pro-3916.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-derivative-touchdesigner-pro-3916.html
</guid><description>
Derivative TouchDesigner Pro is a development platform visual equip you with the tools you need to create the project real-time stunning user experience and rich. Whether you are creating the system, media interaction, project architecture, photos, live music, or simply rapid-prototyping creative impulses your latest Derivative TouchDesigner Pro is platform can do it all.
Derivative TouchDesigner Pro - creation Support project, application
Derivative TouchDesigner Pro works well with...
</description></item><item><title>Download Graitec Advance Design 2026.1 build 21258</title><pubDate> Sun, 02 Nov 2025 19:23:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-graitec-advance-design-7526.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-graitec-advance-design-7526.html
</guid><description>
Glad to announce the release of Advance Design 2023 version. This 2023 version of Advance Design is enhanced with lots of new user-centric functions, with premium benefits, clearly presented. Advance Design is a complete solution for analyzing complex structures using the finite element method. To ensure a high standard of excellence for users, it provides a wide range of advanced CAD modeling, meshing, calculation, expert design and post-processing functions.
Advance Design is...
</description></item><item><title>Download EIVA NaviPac 4.11.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 02 Nov 2025 19:22:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-eiva-navipac-7848.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-eiva-navipac-7848.html
</guid><description>
NaviPac provides navigation and navigation features for vehicles on the water or on the seabed. With NaviPac Pro you get the most complex of the four and can therefore benefit from the full range of features offered by NaviPac for surveys conducted with a multi-channel echo meter. beams, side-scan sonars or lasers.
Features of EIVA NaviPac
	General visualization tools
	Navigation and routes
	Sensor and Recording Interface
	Sensor handling
	Point Cloud
	Engineering/Construction...
</description></item><item><title>Download NoScript 13.4 Chrome + Firefox</title><pubDate> Sun, 02 Nov 2025 19:22:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-noscript-116.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-noscript-116.html
</guid><description>
NoScript is an add-ons extension Firefox , Google Chrome allows you to interactively block Java, JavaScript, Flash a one-click button.
You can choose to temporary block or allow scripts on the current web page and also allows the reliable site by you is excluded from any action to block any.
Whenever you visit a website, all content scripts potential invasive are blocked by default and you can select it on the basis of each script from the status bar of browsers like Google Chrome,...
</description></item><item><title>Download DoNotSpy11 1.3.0.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 02 Nov 2025 19:21:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-donotspy11-7498.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-donotspy11-7498.html
</guid><description>
DoNotSpy11 is an updated antispyware tool for Windows 10 and 11 by the author of DoNotSpy10. DoNotSpy11 takes tweaks that aren't easily accessible through the apps Windows provides and combines them all in one app so you can effectively protect your privacy.
DoNotSpy11 takes tweaks that aren't easily accessible through the apps Windows provides and combines them all in one app so you can effectively protect your privacy. Manage settings including Ads, Apps, Windows Defender, Microsoft...
</description></item><item><title>Download HashiCorp Vault Enterprise 1.21.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 02 Nov 2025 19:21:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hashicorp-vault-enterprise-8618.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hashicorp-vault-enterprise-8618.html
</guid><description>
HashiCorp Vault Enterprise is a secret management solution that provides organizations with a centralized platform to store, manage and control access to sensitive information, such as passwords, certificates, and API keys.
HashiCorp Vault Enterprise provides organizations with a powerful solution to manage their secrets. The platform's combination of secret management, encryption, and role-based access control makes it a valuable tool for organizations looking to secure their sensitive...
</description></item><item><title>Download Elasticsearch Enterprise 9.2.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 02 Nov 2025 19:20:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-elasticsearch-enterprise-12537.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-elasticsearch-enterprise-12537.html
</guid><description>
Elasticsearch Enterprise is a suite of products and services designed to enhance the search capabilities of applications and websites, primarily through the use of Elastic Enterprise Search and Elastic Cloud Enterprise (ECE). These tools provide advanced features to manage and optimize search functionality across different platforms.
Features
	Elastic Search AI Platform: Get relevant results at unprecedented speed with open and flexible enterprise solutions. Accelerate business...
</description></item><item><title>Download HashiCorp Consul Enterprise 1.22.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 02 Nov 2025 19:20:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hashicorp-consul-enterprise-8616.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hashicorp-consul-enterprise-8616.html
</guid><description>
HashiCorp Consul Enterprise is a software solution for service discovery, configuration management, and network segmentation. It provides organizations with a centralized platform to manage and secure their infrastructure and applications across multi-cloud and multi-datacenter environments.
HashiCorp Consul Enterprise provides organizations with a powerful solution to manage and secure their infrastructure and applications. The platform's combination of service discovery, configuration...
</description></item><item><title>Download HashiCorp Boundary Enterprise 0.20.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 02 Nov 2025 19:20:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hashicorp-boundary-enterprise-9715.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hashicorp-boundary-enterprise-9715.html
</guid><description>
HashiCorp Boundary Enterprise centralizes remote access management and ensures access to infrastructure resources located on any public or private cloud environment. Easily integrates with leading identity providers such as Okta, Ping, and Azure Active Directory, and supports multiple service registries to automatically discover and maintain an up-to-date repository of servers and target service.
Features of HashiCorp Boundary Enterprise
	Authenticate with whatever trusted identity...
</description></item><item><title>Download Jailer 16.10</title><pubDate> Sun, 02 Nov 2025 19:18:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jailer-3196.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jailer-3196.html
</guid><description>
Jailer is a tool to reset the database, schema and browse data. It the sets of continuous, intact reference from the database relations. It removes outdated data without violating integrity. Theory is that force majeure DBMS (using JDBC), platform-independent and tạobộ data DbUnit , XML has hierarchical structure and SQL-DML is arranged in the link structure.
Jailer - Installed back to the database
Database Jailer is growing both in scale and complexity to meet the growing needs of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Broot 1.52.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 02 Nov 2025 19:18:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-broot-8588.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-broot-8588.html
</guid><description>
Broot is an open source command line tool for browsing and navigating file systems. Broot provides a fast and intuitive way to navigate the file system with a tree-like interactive interface. It provides various features like searching for files, opening files and folders, copying file paths to clipboard, etc. It also supports customizing keys and color themes.
Features of Broot
	Fast file browsing: Lets you quickly navigate through large directory structures with a tree-like...
</description></item><item><title>Download Scientific Toolworks Understand 7.2 Build 1239</title><pubDate> Sun, 02 Nov 2025 19:17:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-scientific-toolworks-understand-1532.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-scientific-toolworks-understand-1532.html
</guid><description>
Scientific Toolworks Understand is a tool of static analysis to management, measurement and analysis, ability to program. This tool can measure multiple metrics and give you the clear chart about the indicator code different. For example: number of layers, number of project files, number of methods, number of lines, blank lines, comments, dead code, rate, comment on code, complexity in the cycle and the level of trouble of the code, the level of dependence of code together, the rate of...
</description></item><item><title>Download ThermoSientific AMIRA/AVIZO 3D 2025.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 02 Nov 2025 16:19:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thermosientific-amiraavizo-3d-12598.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thermosientific-amiraavizo-3d-12598.html
</guid><description>
Analyzing and visualizing your image data enables a better understanding of the structure, properties and performance of materials. Regardless of the scale and data method you use, your organizational profile (large industrial company, core imaging facility, national or local service laboratory, academic institution) , Thermo Scientific's Avizo software provides optimized workflows for advanced materials characterization and quality control from a single environment. Avizo software is a...
</description></item><item><title>Download Voyis VSLAM powered by EIVA NaviSuite 1.4.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 02 Nov 2025 16:16:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-voyis-vslam-powered-by-eiva-navisuite-14267.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-voyis-vslam-powered-by-eiva-navisuite-14267.html
</guid><description>
Voyis VSLAM powered by EIVA NaviSuite is a computer vision software product that generates real-time QC displays of area coverage such as 3D point clouds and trajectory charts - using only your Discovery Stereo camera as input. The result is improved survey quality during acquisition, as well as improved ROV visual inspection results by linking high-quality still images to a true-scale 3D point cloud in real time.
Optimized acquisition with enhanced ROV control
To minimize the risk of...
</description></item><item><title>Download ASCOMP PDF-compress 1.012 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Sun, 02 Nov 2025 00:10:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ascomp-pdf-compress-7415.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ascomp-pdf-compress-7415.html
</guid><description>
ASCOMP PDF-compress provides PDF compression so you can optimize your PDF files so that they don't take up more storage space than necessary. Depending on the structure and content of the PDF document, up to 95% compression can be achieved. In a test with more than 1,000 randomly selected PDF files from different sources, an average compression ratio of close to 50% was achieved.
ASCOMP PDF-compress uses different approaches to compression. For example, images contained in a document...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDF-compress Professional 1.012</title><pubDate> Sun, 02 Nov 2025 00:10:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-compress-professional-10856.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-compress-professional-10856.html
</guid><description>
The PDF format is ideal for presenting and sharing complex documents, diagrams, graphics, and forms. However, as a result, PDFs are often very extensive, so it's really a knockout criterion for sharing. PDF-compress Professional is a solution that compresses your PDF files reliably and in the best possible way.
With PDF compression, you can optimize your PDF files so they don't take up more storage space than is absolutely necessary. Depending on the structure and content of the PDF...
</description></item></channel></rss>