<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 15:42:21 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 15:42:21 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download PDF Annotator 9.0.0.930</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 17:32:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-annotator-178.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-annotator-178.html
</guid><description>
PDF Annotator software user open any PDF file and add annotations, using the mouse or pen Tablet PC, directly on the Page of the PDF file. PDF Annotator allows users to perform editing operations on PDF files such as: add notes, edit signature, highlight, insert images or text... From the this useful tool, you can completely modify PDF files as you like in order to meet the different work.
PDF Annotator
With the PDF Annotator the document has annotations can then be saved directly back...
</description></item><item><title>Download Apache OpenOffice 4.1.16</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 17:32:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-openoffice-4220.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-openoffice-4220.html
</guid><description>
OpenOffice is a replacement tool for free and mobile for productivity tools Office provides many utilities, such as text processing, spreadsheet, presentation, graphics, editor, recipe and program management database. OpenOffice can be installed and used on all popular platforms and provides support for many different languages. The app will store your data in ODF format, but also can read and write files in many other formats. The file formats used by the software most popular Office...
</description></item><item><title>Download StartAllBack 3.9.17.5334</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 17:30:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-startallback-6857.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-startallback-6857.html
</guid><description>
With the official release of Windows 11, chances are that most of you want to try it out. As the name suggests, StartAllBack is a small, lightweight tool that can help you enjoy the power of the new operating system while keeping the look and feel, especially because main work area, desktop of Windows 7, Windows 10 as taskbars and start menu styles.
StartAllBack is specially designed for Windows 11 and will not work on any older operating systems. If you want to get the start menu back...
</description></item><item><title>Download Digiarty AIArty Image Matting 2.6</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 17:30:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-digiarty-aiarty-image-matting-12567.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-digiarty-aiarty-image-matting-12567.html
</guid><description>
Digiarty's Aiarty Image Matting is an advanced AI-based software designed to accurately remove image backgrounds and seamlessly integrate foreground objects into new backgrounds. Recently launched, the tool is especially beneficial for e-commerce, photographers, and digital creators looking to enhance their visual content effectively. It offers precise background removal, advanced alpha blending for hair, fur, and detailed transparent objects, and seamless foreground-background...
</description></item><item><title>Download Aiarty Image Enhancer 3.5</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 17:29:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aiarty-image-enhancer-12181.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aiarty-image-enhancer-12181.html
</guid><description>
Aiarty Image Enhancer is an AI-powered image enhancement software to de-noise, de-blur, enhance images and create more image details. It uses advanced deep learning technologies to enhance and upscale images while creating realistic details. Whether you want to enlarge low-resolution images by 200%, 400% or 800% for printing, deliver 2K/4K/8K images while preserving realistic details, correcting low-quality photos , remove blur and noise or restore compressed JPEGs, Aiarty Image Enhancer...
</description></item><item><title>Download Angry IP Scanner 3.9.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 17:29:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-angry-ip-scanner-2138.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-angry-ip-scanner-2138.html
</guid><description>
Angry IP Scanner can scan IP addresses in any range as well as any port of them. It is multi-platform and lightweight. Does not require any installation, it can be copied and used freely anywhere. Angry IP Scanner simply pings each IP address to check if it's alive or not, then optionally it is resolving the server name of it, determines the MAC address, scans ports, etc., the Amount of gathered data about each host can be extended by plugin.
Angry IP Scanner - Scan IP address
Scan...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare Repairit 6.5.18.9</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 17:28:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-recoverit-video-repair-3889.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-recoverit-video-repair-3889.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare Recoverit Video Repair is a reliable application that helps you fix the broken video, Wondershare Recoverit Video Repair supports file formats MP4, MOV, M4V, M2TS, MKV, MTS, 3GP, AVI and FLV is corrupt and broken. Great service we provide. It fixes the video that there is corruption in the process of shooting, when done, file transfer, while editing, convert.
Wondershare Recoverit Video Repair - video repair broken
Features of Wondershare Recoverit Video Repair
	Repair...
</description></item><item><title>Download ExtraDisks Home 25.11.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 17:28:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-extradisks-home-7758.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-extradisks-home-7758.html
</guid><description>
ExtraDisks is a set of tools for creating virtual disks on your computer physical drives that do not change and are not divided into additional partitions. The program contains tools for creating encrypted disks, file-based virtual disks and directory-based virtual disks. The current version includes the following tools: Encrypted Disks, Virtual Disks, Folder Disks, Startup Manager, System Tweaker.
Features of ExtraDisks
ExtraDisks: Encrypted Disk
This tool is used to create encrypted...
</description></item><item><title>Download Gilisoft Total Repair 11.1.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 17:27:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-total-repair-12836.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-total-repair-12836.html
</guid><description>
Total Repair Toolkit is an all-in-one system maintenance tool that integrates smart diagnosis, in-depth repair, and performance optimization. It has a one-click smart repair engine that can automatically resolve over 500 common problems such as system lag, game crashes, and file corruption. Meanwhile, it provides a professional manual repair module to meet advanced requirements.
Gilisoft Total Repair Features
	Application error repair based on a large DLL library
	In-depth diagnosis...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cutting Optimization Pro 5.18.16.16</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 17:27:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cutting-optimization-pro-6573.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cutting-optimization-pro-6573.html
</guid><description>
Cutting Optimization Pro is a cutting software used to obtain the optimal cut layout for one-dimensional (1D) and two-dimensional (2D) pieces. The software also allows you to define and process complex products, such as desks, tables, cabinets, cabinets, bookshelves... Cutting Optimization Pro can be used to cut rectangular panels made of glass, wood, metal, plastic or any other material used in industrial applications.
Features of Cutting Optimization Pro
	Optimize 1D and 2D in the...
</description></item><item><title>Download EFI Boot Editor 1.5.4</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 17:26:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-efi-boot-editor-7475.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-efi-boot-editor-7475.html
</guid><description>
EFI Boot Editor is a program that provides you with a graphical interface to check your current boot settings and make modifications to the EFI Boot Manager. With Windows Boot Manager you can check Description, path, category, general settings like timeout and whether properties are active or hidden. Optionally, the application can provide the same information in other formats, namel HEX, BASE64, UTF-8 or UTF-16.
Features of EFI Boot Editor
	Edit startup items.
	Add, remove, and...
</description></item><item><title>Download MyLanViewer Enterprise 6.6.5 / Business</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 17:26:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mylanviewer-enterprise-1274.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mylanviewer-enterprise-1274.html
</guid><description>
MyLanViewer is a program for scanning IP address, Netbios and LAN / Network powerful for Windows tool whois and traceroute, remote shutdown and process management Wake On LAN (WOL), scan and monitor wireless networks. This app will help you find all IP addresses, MAC addresses and shared folders of computers on the network wired or wireless (Wi-Fi).
MyLanViewer Enterprise - Scan IP address LAN/Network
The program scans network and displays the computer network in your window, friends...
</description></item><item><title>Download KeyNote NF 2.1.3.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 17:23:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-keynote-nf-11953.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-keynote-nf-11953.html
</guid><description>
KeyNote NF is a tabbed notebook with a RichText editor, multi-level note taking, and powerful encryption. KeyNote NF was written to overcome significant limitations in other popular information managers, both freeware and shareware. KeyNote is the only information manager that offers a combination of simple notes and tree notes, a rich text editor, the ability to freely combine multiple notes of different types in one file unique and securely encrypted.
Main features:
Unicode...
</description></item><item><title>Download VovSoft AI Requester 4.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 17:22:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-ai-requester-8997.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-ai-requester-8997.html
</guid><description>
Vovsoft AI Requester is a program that can connect to OpenAI API easily. The software provides users with a reliable and easy-to-use interface that seamlessly integrates with the latest AI technologies, including GPT-3.5 and GPT-4.
Just like ChatGPT, you can connect to the OpenAI platform and start chatting with powerful AI bots capable of giving intelligent responses to a variety of queries and questions. The software is designed to be user-friendly and intuitive, allowing even...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sandboxie 5.71.6</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 17:22:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sandboxie-818.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sandboxie-818.html
</guid><description>
Sandboxie software to browse the Web securely while still keeping all the functionality your browser for content works against harmful agents such as sanbox up your computer. You may not know, when you browse the Web, the change will occur with the system of your computer. When you use Sandboxie, the software will protect the web browser of their own.
Sandboxie - web protection, safe browsing
The main features of Sandboxie
Stay safe on the Internet with Sandboxie
	Run the program in...
</description></item><item><title>Download Coolutils Total Excel Converter 7.1.0.104</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 17:21:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-total-excel-converter-849.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-total-excel-converter-849.html
</guid><description>
Coolutils Total Excel Converter is software that converts Excel documents to other formats like ODS, XML, SQL, WK2, WKS WAB, DBF, TEX and DIF for you to use. In addition, the software also supports converting Excel files into file DOC, DOCX, PDF, HTML, Access, TXT, ODT, ODS, XML, SQL, CSV, Lotus, DBF, TEX, DIFF, SYLK and LaTeX.
Coolutils Total Excel Converter - batch convert Excel
Total Excel Converter has a perfect layout and tight. When the conversion is finished you will get an...
</description></item><item><title>Download Xreveal Pro 2.8.7</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 17:21:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xreveal-pro-14266.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xreveal-pro-14266.html
</guid><description>
Xreveal Pro is a Windows-based application similar to AnyDVD that automatically removes restrictions on DVD and Blu-ray discs. Xreveal works in the background to automatically and transparently allow access to read the contents of a DVD or Blu-ray movie disc as soon as it is inserted into the drive. The DVD/Blu-ray disc will be usable on the Windows operating system and all the programs on your computer, such as DVD/Blu-ray backup software like CloneDVD, CloneBD and others, which then...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sandboxie Plus 1.16.6</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 17:21:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sandboxie-plus-4962.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sandboxie-plus-4962.html
</guid><description>
Sandboxie Plus is an application version of the open source project on Github, equipped with software to protect your information while browsing the web or running valuable software. doubt. Web browsing, downloading or running software can affect system security. To prevent this from happening, a high user experience and strong layers of protection are needed to prevent malware from spreading to the system. For example, by opening an unknown application, malware in flash memory can...
</description></item><item><title>Download MiniTool Power Data Recovery Business Technician 12.7 Boot ISO</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 17:20:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minitool-power-data-recovery-business-technician-5660.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minitool-power-data-recovery-business-technician-5660.html
</guid><description>
MiniTool Power Data Recovery is a file recovery software and read-only data recovery software. Power data recovery software can help you recover all your data regardless of whether it was lost due to accidental deletion, formatting, repartition, system crash, or virus attack. Power Data Recovery can regionally scan your device by region to restore what's left on your device. Power Data Recovery provides a deep scan module that can scan and analyze raw data formats including Microsoft...
</description></item><item><title>Download Rambox 2.5.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 17:19:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rambox-1139.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rambox-1139.html
</guid><description>
Rambox is the app to email and messaging, open source, cross-platform and combine multiple web applications into a single interface. Rambox allows users to use a number of web services most commonly used to support the messaging feature and email editor, and displays the notification when the service has new messages through the main window simple and easy to use.
Instead of using several apps or have to use the web browser, you can access and manage all of the online services of from a...
</description></item><item><title>Download FolderSizes Enterprise 9.8.584</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 17:19:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-foldersizes-enterprise-1566.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-foldersizes-enterprise-1566.html
</guid><description>
FolderSizes Enterprise is software analysis to quickly and accurately space drives to monitor and manage disk space. FolderSizes Enterprise can quickly isolate the files large, old, temporary, and duplicate or even showing the distribution of files by type, attributes, or owner. All with multiple export formats, command line support, context shell menu integration, and much more.
FolderSizes goes beyond the capabilities of competing solutions by combining several tools into one: Disk...
</description></item><item><title>Download HTTP Downloader 1.0.6.8</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 17:18:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-http-downloader-1821.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-http-downloader-1821.html
</guid><description>
HTTP Downloader is a download manager for HTTP protocol(S). Maximize throughput download at your using the port complete input / output high-performance (I / o completion ports). HTTP Downloader can open thousands of connections at the same time and consumes very little system resources. You can Start, pause, stop, and queue up to 100 downloads at the same time and every download can be divided into 100 parts.
HTTP Downloader - Support downloading protocol HTTP
Other features include...
</description></item><item><title>Download Fast File Encryptor 25.11.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 17:17:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fast-file-encryptor-2606.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fast-file-encryptor-2606.html
</guid><description>
Fast File Encryptor is the encoder files fast designed for fast processing of the file very big. It can encrypt or decrypt files, contents of folders and contains a lot of additional tools. In addition, there is a tool responsible to completely remove files from the hard drive, you need it if you don't want to leave traces 100 percent in the system. You need to specify the password or key, then select the encryption method, remember remember everything, otherwise it will not work, then...
</description></item><item><title>Download BriskBard 4.7.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 17:17:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-briskbard-2913.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-briskbard-2913.html
</guid><description>
BriskBard software is powerful and efficient designed for MS Windows, letting you easily surf the web, chat with friends, manage personal information and contacts, watch videos online account management, e-mail, read latest news, listen to music, perform file transfers, and more. Packed program this feature will help you save precious time and improve your productivity.
BriskBard is web browser two engine integrated 10 different Internet applications into one, including email, news group,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Jailer 16.11</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 17:16:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jailer-3196.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jailer-3196.html
</guid><description>
Jailer is a tool to reset the database, schema and browse data. It the sets of continuous, intact reference from the database relations. It removes outdated data without violating integrity. Theory is that force majeure DBMS (using JDBC), platform-independent and tạobộ data DbUnit , XML has hierarchical structure and SQL-DML is arranged in the link structure.
Jailer - Installed back to the database
Database Jailer is growing both in scale and complexity to meet the growing needs of...
</description></item></channel></rss>