<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 11:57:06 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 11:57:06 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Blender 4.5.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:53:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blender-3017.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blender-3017.html
</guid><description>
Blender has a tool that new and very powerful, whose name is Ciking provides the ability to display extremely impressive and extremely realistic.
Features of Blender
	- Feature button support complete
	- The ball exactly on the physical side, SSS and translucency
	- Support languages open for coding the ball unique
Blender - The software-rendered optical
Tool output integration provides:
	- The GPU and CPU
	- Preview options view real-time
	- Support light HDR
	- The license...
</description></item><item><title>Download balenaEtcher 2.1.4</title><pubDate> Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:53:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-etcher-1748.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-etcher-1748.html
</guid><description>
Etcher help easy and safe to flash the operating system image to the SD card and USB drive, using a 3-step process simple. Just select the image file to the operating system you want to use (.iso, zip, .bin, etc.), specify the drive you want to flash and start the process. Etcher automatically check for SD card or hard drive to ensure that it is not corrupted, verify image file to ensure that it has the ability to launch and also ensure that you don't accidentally wipe the hard drive of...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaInfo 25.07</title><pubDate> Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:52:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediainfo-1456.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediainfo-1456.html
</guid><description>
MediaInfo is a software that provides access to view the information of media files, such as technical information and tags of the video file and bad sound. Software displays detailed information including: format, profile, commercial name of the format, duration, bit rate overall, writing application and library, title, author, director, album, track number, updates.
MediaInfo - View file info media
The features and functions of MediaInfo
	Container: format, profile, commercial name...
</description></item><item><title>Download Stellar Repair for Photo 8.7.0.8 (All Editions)</title><pubDate> Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:50:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stellar-repair-for-photo-7897.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stellar-repair-for-photo-7897.html
</guid><description>
Stellar Repair for Photo is the best software to repair damaged .JPG or .JPEG format photos. Stellar Repair for Photo will fix your completely unreadable JPEG files even in situations where the header is corrupted, the JPEG data is corrupted, the JPEG file structure is invalid, the JPEG marker is unknown or invalid ratio, missing SOS marker, etc.
Stellar Repair for Photo software is easy to use with a simple and intuitive GUI. You will find a progress bar showing the exact status of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download TeamViewer 15.68.5 + Portable</title><pubDate> Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:49:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-teamviewer-528.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-teamviewer-528.html
</guid><description>
TeamViewer is software that functions to connect and control the remote computer, the ability to connect with any system anywhere from all over the place. This is a support tool users is very convenient. TeamViewer to help users control remote computer becomes much more simple, help you interact and collaborate with others in the exchange and share of information, instruction manual, application software or fix the computer.
TeamViewer as a revolution of computer science. when you have...
</description></item><item><title>Download EmEditor Pro 25.2.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:48:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-emeditor-pro-69.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-emeditor-pro-69.html
</guid><description>
EmEditor Pro - the professional version of editor text powerful for programmers, web developers and ordinary users with illumination of syntax and Unicode support. The features of the editor such as search and replace in files using regular expressions, automatic code detect, bookmark link and address email, block selection mode, configure the button bar, menu, font and elements color. With each language you can set separate configuration.
EmEditor Pro - text Editor professional
The...
</description></item><item><title>Download TeamViewer QuickSupport 15.68.5</title><pubDate> Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:48:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-teamviewer-quicksupport-1933.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-teamviewer-quicksupport-1933.html
</guid><description>
A different version of TeamViewer is TeamViewer QuickSupport is a solution easy to use allows you to share your desktop with a users TeamViewer other to receive technical support or other support. All what you need to do is run the TeamViewer QuickSupport and provides for the remote user ID and your password to grant access to the computer to your desk. Only people you trust can connect to your computer and access password will automatically change after each session.
The software also...
</description></item><item><title>Download Red Gate SmartAssembly Professional 8.3.6.6474</title><pubDate> Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:47:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-red-gate-smartassembly-1593.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-red-gate-smartassembly-1593.html
</guid><description>
Red Gate SmartAssembly is a tool that helps protect your application against reverse engineering or modifications prevent side Tuesday access to source code. This comprehensive solution protects the data card of you and more likely to report errors. This program makes files difficult can disassemble and injection code does not use, to help engineer can reverse and understand the core structure of the code. With your smartphone, you will have many features to tamper with the code as the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Pale Moon 33.8.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:47:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pale-moon-1883.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pale-moon-1883.html
</guid><description>
Pale Moon is a copy of Firefox has been optimized for the Windows operating System with the processor performance, high current. It looks identical to Firefox browser standard, and supports the extensions, themes and identities of Firefox. All extensions, bookmarks and settings of your existing be entered during the installation process, so except for the logo, you won't notice any difference on function.
Pale Moon - secure web browser
However, what you may notice is the difference in...
</description></item><item><title>Download DesktopSnowOK 6.66</title><pubDate> Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:46:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopsnowok-1950.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopsnowok-1950.html
</guid><description>
DesktopSnowOK is an application to create snow fall effect interesting, DesktopSnowOK allows you to animate your desktop with the flakes of snow virtual. You can choose from many types of scales, configure the number of flakes (5-64) and the speed of them. The interface of DesktopSnowOK is quite simple but allows you to make more customization. At any time you can also choose to activate or deactivate DesktopSnowOK by the Activate/ Deactivate, click on Start with Windows to launch the app...
</description></item><item><title>Download Samurai Sharpen Video 1.2.14</title><pubDate> Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:46:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-samurai-sharpen-video-for-after-effects-and-premiere-pro-12634.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-samurai-sharpen-video-for-after-effects-and-premiere-pro-12634.html
</guid><description>
Samurai Sharpen Video is a specialized video sharpening plugin developed by Digital Anarchy, designed to enhance the clarity and detail of video footage without creating unwanted artifacts.
Video footage is often a bit soft, and making improvements to sharpen certain details can make a big difference. Samurai Sharpen lets you do this quickly with tools designed to make it easy for you to isolate specific areas of your footage and sharpen only those areas. This is advanced sharpening...
</description></item><item><title>Download Private Windows Script (PrivWindoze) 5.6.4</title><pubDate> Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:45:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-private-windows-script-12878.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-private-windows-script-12878.html
</guid><description>
Are you concerned about your personal information sent to others? Or do you feel that your Windows settings have many programs that you never use? Private Windows Script (or Privwindoze) provides a comprehensive anti -remote monitoring set designed to enhance your privacy when using Windows operating system.
The main features
	End the positive process. All unnecessary processes are turned off while the scanning program. A small white list is maintained.
	Clean up the positive runonce....
</description></item><item><title>Download IK Multimedia Tonex Max 1.9.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:44:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ik-multimedia-tonex-max-7877.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ik-multimedia-tonex-max-7877.html
</guid><description>
TONEX software uses groundbreaking AI Machine Modeling technology to let you model the sound of any amp, cabinet, or combo and turn it into a plug-in, all with precision sounds are almost indistinguishable from reality. You can instantly play up to the more than 1,000 already available Melody Models along with browsing, performing, and downloading more and more Melody Models available on TONEX in ToneNET.
Features of IK Multimedia Tonex Max
	Modeled tone generator, player,...
</description></item><item><title>Download DiskMax 7.26</title><pubDate> Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:43:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-diskmax-5940.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-diskmax-5940.html
</guid><description>
Using DiskMax to periodically make a robust drive cleaner and optimize performance to keep your PC healthy. After using DiskMax, you will notice that your system will work better, the apps will start faster, the files will open faster and the games will run better. Just run DiskMax over time to keep your system steady.
Even if you are an advanced user, DiskMax will be useful to you because it automate all the tasks needed to keep your system clean and quickly, helping you enjoy the...
</description></item><item><title>Download The Dude 7.19.4</title><pubDate> Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:39:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-the-dude-3238.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-the-dude-3238.html
</guid><description>
The Dude is a new application by MikroTik which can dramatically improve the way you manage your network environment. It will automatically scan all devices in the subnet is specified, draw and layout a map of your networks, monitor services of your devices and alert you in case some service has problems.is a new application by MikroTik which can dramatically improve the way you manage your network environment. It will automatically scan all devices in the subnet is specified, draw and...
</description></item><item><title>Download High-Logic MainType Professional 13.0.0.1365</title><pubDate> Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:30:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-high-logic-maintype-professional-3165.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-high-logic-maintype-professional-3165.html
</guid><description>
High-Logic MainType Professional is the font manager and font viewer powerful but easy to use for Windows, eliminates the frustration out of managing your fonts. It is integrated with lots of intuitive features to help you easily find, preview, organize, install, and print fonts his. MainType help simple to find, preview, organize, install and print your fonts. MainType supports all format popular fonts: TrueType, OpenType, TrueType Collection, and Postcript Type 1. Unlike the preview...
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 6.7.9</title><pubDate> Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:30:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-11-7760.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-11-7760.html
</guid><description>
TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 is a program that allows users to discover hidden settings in Windows 11. This application is specially designed for Windows 11, groups many registry settings and distribute them from the easy and secure user interface. With TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 you can move the Windows taskbar to the top and resize the taskbar by editing the registry value. With any application that modifies the registry, we recommend that you have a backup copy...
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 6.7.9</title><pubDate> Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:30:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-10-7759.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-10-7759.html
</guid><description>
TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 is a utility that allows users to discover hidden settings in Windows 10. This application is specially designed for Windows 10, groups many registry settings and provide them from an easy and secure user interface. With TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 you can move the Windows taskbar to the top and resize the taskbar by editing the registry value. With any application that modifies the registry, we recommend that you have a backup copy to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Picture Window Pro 8.0.520</title><pubDate> Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:29:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-picture-window-pro-7452.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-picture-window-pro-7452.html
</guid><description>
Picture Window Pro is a powerful image editing tool designed for serious photographers with strict creative and quality standards. Its comprehensive set of photo editing and editing tools let you control and shape every aspect of your images.
Picture Window Pro 8 is a complete rewrite of Picture Window Pro 7. It features non-destructive image editing through a novel interface based on an image tree. It also fully supports large, high-resolution displays and can be used in dual monitor...
</description></item><item><title>Download EMDB 5.38</title><pubDate> Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:29:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-emdb-64.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-emdb-64.html
</guid><description>
EMDB (Eric's Movie Database) allows you to sort and catalog collection DVD of you.All you have to do is enter the title (or part of it) and the program will enter the detail information and movie cover image from a selection database online.You can then add personal ratings, customize the details, replace cover photo and also set the path local file (if you have a digital copy on your disk).
EMDB - sort and catalog collection DVD of you
Other features include an option to track movies...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinTools System Font Size Changer 2.2.1.21</title><pubDate> Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:28:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wintools-system-font-size-changer-6143.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wintools-system-font-size-changer-6143.html
</guid><description>
WinTools System Font Size Changer allows you to set the system font in Windows 10. It allows you to set the system font used by Windows 10 easily and make the text more easily read. It can modify the system font without having to restart the computer. It supports the conversion between the system fonts with the configuration and the hot key.
This software is part of the software family that changes the system font. The terms of use and all other information related to the software...
</description></item><item><title>Download iZotope Cascadia 1.1.0.355</title><pubDate> Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:27:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-izotope-cascadia-12569.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-izotope-cascadia-12569.html
</guid><description>
Explore smart latency without distractions. Reinforce your rhythm and create deep echoes, tight reverbs, and creative textures – all while keeping instruments and vocals focused in the mix with unmasking adaptable, easy.
Smart delay for clean mixes
	With beat-synchronized or time-based delay, ping pong delay mode and vice versa, classic pitch offset, width control and adjustable display. Say goodbye to long plugin chains and tedious routing. Find your stream quickly with Cascadia's...
</description></item><item><title>Download FX Science Tools MultiDocs 25.07.29</title><pubDate> Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:27:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fx-science-tools-3744.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fx-science-tools-3744.html
</guid><description>
FX Science Tools provided to teachers of chemistry and physics the effective means to create equations and chemical structures. Just type and create. FX Chem FX Chem makes writing chemical equations become simple. You just type and FX Chem know enough about chemistry to put all the components of the equation at the right point. FX Chem can even create the chemical equations for nuclear - a very difficult thing in the Word. FX ChemSturation FX ChemSturation made the organic structure, what...
</description></item><item><title>Download ECam Pro 5.0.409</title><pubDate> Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:26:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ecam-1615.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ecam-1615.html
</guid><description>
ECam is a reliable tool that allows you to create the design and simulation process, cut by lathe computer programming. The software allows you to create the cutting, drilling, face, chisel, or sanding the workpiece. You cansetup each step of the desired process in a graphical environment, where you can view and edit the 3D elements on the ECam.
ECam - design and simulation of the cutting process 3D
The features and functions of ECam
3D modeling
	Understanding 3D is effective...
</description></item><item><title>Download Social Media Downloader 7.6.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:26:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-socialmediaapps-facebook-video-downloader-3742.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-socialmediaapps-facebook-video-downloader-3742.html
</guid><description>
SocialVideo Downloader (formerly SocialMediaApps Facebook Video Downloader) is a Windows application to download and convert your favorite videos from Facebook and hundreds of other video sharing sites. It increases your loading speed by up to 500%, or even more! The application has a simple and intuitive user interface, its main functions and features are quite obvious to anyone. , regardless of prior experience with similar purpose tools.
&amp;nbsp;
SocialVideo Downloader
The main...
</description></item></channel></rss>