<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 15:45:50 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 15:45:50 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Bandicam 8.3.0.2533</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Dec 2025 18:25:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bandicam-243.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bandicam-243.html
</guid><description>
Bandicam is the software screen recording powerful, helps users to record all activities happening on the computer such as video games, presentations,..
Software Bandicam uses graphics technology DirectX / OpenGL will help you carry out a video record with high compression ratio, while keeping the video quality closer to the original work and provide superior performance compared with other programs providing the same functionality.
Bandicam can create video with quality high but...
</description></item><item><title>Download ACDSee Photo Studio Professional 2026 v19.0.1.3450</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Dec 2025 18:24:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-acdsee-photo-studio-professional-5542.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-acdsee-photo-studio-professional-5542.html
</guid><description>
ACDSee Photo Studio Professional is a complete photo editor and photo manager. It was developed for professional and advanced amateur photographers who need full control over their workflow .ACDSee Photo Studio Professional 2020 offers state-of-the-art RAW processing for non-destructive photo editing RAW image conversion and conversion.
With the Manage, View, Develop, Edit and Online modes, it is the only solution that allows photographers to perform all the essential tasks of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download AOMEI Partition Assistant Professional 10.10.0 + Technician + Unlimited + Server</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Dec 2025 18:24:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aomei-partition-assistant-281.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aomei-partition-assistant-281.html
</guid><description>
AOMEI Partition Assistant is partition software hard disk all in one easy to use, offers many features partition manager free. AOMEI Partition Assistant to ensure the full features to create, resize, move, copy, delete, delete, align, format, merge, split partitions.
AOMEI Partition Assistant
AOMEI Partition Manager enables you to expand the available space on hard disk quickly for improve the capacity for the root partition. The instructions move smart can easily support you move the...
</description></item><item><title>Download ACDSee Photo Studio Ultimate 2026 v19.0.1.4391</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Dec 2025 18:23:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-acdsee-photo-studio-ultimate-1244.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-acdsee-photo-studio-ultimate-1244.html
</guid><description>
ACDSee Photo Studio Ultimate 2019 is the perfect combination between support layers, supports image processing is GPU accelerated, supports transparency with all the function adjust the picture from edit mode. ACDSee is a program function is designed for both professional photographers and amateurs. ACDSee lets you work with digital photos, RAW images, and supports more than 100 image file formats. The program also provides batch processing quickly a large number of files with visual...
</description></item><item><title>Download ACDSee Photo Studio Home 2026 v29.0.1.3351</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Dec 2025 18:22:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-acdsee-photo-studio-home-3444.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-acdsee-photo-studio-home-3444.html
</guid><description>
ACDSee Photo Studio Home 2020 - The management of digital assets the best on the market
Is an amateur,, reality, photo collection of you continue to expand and you need to continue his work. With tools that help manage digital assets, productivity, and edit and distribute photos, ACDSee Photo Studio Home 2020 packing a punch worth. Existing feature recognition and face recognition, many basket pictures to collect assets on your hard drive, manage your keywords, improve, convert files in...
</description></item><item><title>Download Fast Video Cutter Joiner 6.9.5</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Dec 2025 18:22:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fast-video-cutter-joiner-7542.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fast-video-cutter-joiner-7542.html
</guid><description>
Fast Video Cutter Joiner is a fast video cutter and joiner with an easy to use interface. It allows users to trim parts of a video quickly while maintaining the quality of the original video. It supports various formats like AVI, MPEG, MP4, WMV, 3GP, FLV...
This tool helps you to cut video files into small parts, to keep only the parts you need and remove unwanted parts like trailers and advertisements in a movie. The clips you cut can then be used for other video productions or for a...
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 7.6.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Dec 2025 18:21:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-11-7760.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-11-7760.html
</guid><description>
TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 is a program that allows users to discover hidden settings in Windows 11. This application is specially designed for Windows 11, groups many registry settings and distribute them from the easy and secure user interface. With TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 you can move the Windows taskbar to the top and resize the taskbar by editing the registry value. With any application that modifies the registry, we recommend that you have a backup copy...
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 7.6.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Dec 2025 18:21:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-10-7759.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-10-7759.html
</guid><description>
TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 is a utility that allows users to discover hidden settings in Windows 10. This application is specially designed for Windows 10, groups many registry settings and provide them from an easy and secure user interface. With TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 you can move the Windows taskbar to the top and resize the taskbar by editing the registry value. With any application that modifies the registry, we recommend that you have a backup copy to...
</description></item><item><title>Download XenoDream Jux 4.803</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Dec 2025 18:21:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xenodream-jux-3953.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xenodream-jux-3953.html
</guid><description>
XenoDream Jux is a tool fractal for the 2D Julia and Mandelbrot. It includes a variety of recipes. It has color effects and beautiful lighting. It is very easy to use. No recipe editor or script. There are many possible ways to color fractals Mandelbrot / Julia. XenoDream Jux has the integration method is selected because of the simplicity, flexibility and aesthetics of them. You can use color alone, or modify it with lighting effects market height. XenoDream Jux can add the light effect...
</description></item><item><title>Download Media Player Classic Black Edition 1.8.9</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Dec 2025 15:35:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-media-player-classic-black-edition-3351.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-media-player-classic-black-edition-3351.html
</guid><description>
Media Player Classic Black Edition is abbreviated as MPC-BE is a free program that can interface black support users to watch movies, listen to music on the computer with the new interface. Media Player Classic - BE is based on the project "Media Player Classic" original (Gabest) and the project "Media Player Classic Home Cinema" (Casimir666), contains additional features and bug fixes.
Both programs are quite similar, because they are based on Media Player Classic original. In fact, MPC...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare Repairit 6.6.1.7</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Dec 2025 15:31:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-recoverit-video-repair-3889.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-recoverit-video-repair-3889.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare Recoverit Video Repair is a reliable application that helps you fix the broken video, Wondershare Recoverit Video Repair supports file formats MP4, MOV, M4V, M2TS, MKV, MTS, 3GP, AVI and FLV is corrupt and broken. Great service we provide. It fixes the video that there is corruption in the process of shooting, when done, file transfer, while editing, convert.
Wondershare Recoverit Video Repair - video repair broken
Features of Wondershare Recoverit Video Repair
	Repair...
</description></item><item><title>Download Zortam Mp3 Media Studio Pro 33.65</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Dec 2025 15:31:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zortam-mp3-media-studio-pro-135.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zortam-mp3-media-studio-pro-135.html
</guid><description>
Zortam Mp3 Media Studio Pro brings you rich processing tools music includes extract and convert music from CD to Mp3 format, edit, music cards, music download....You can also create discs CD high-quality music, with Zortam Mp3 Media Studio search music files duplicated to remove them from the system, rename music files, switch back and forth between formats.
Zortam Mp3 Media Studio Pro is rated as perfect software in the processing of the MP3 files on the computer. First of all, you can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Free YouTube Download 4.4.48.1225 Premium</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Dec 2025 15:30:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-download-1177.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-download-1177.html
</guid><description>
Free YouTube Download Premium is the most popular application to download videos from YouTube. The program was released in 2006 and regularly updated since then. Use the program to download and convert YouTube videos to view offline anytime.
Free YouTube Download - added Support to download youtube
Download more videos! Save whole playlists and YouTube channels, videos from a playlist individually (history, video be favorite, favourites, Watch later), videos from many different...
</description></item><item><title>Download FastStone Photo Resizer 4.5 Corporate</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Dec 2025 15:30:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-faststone-photo-resizer-364.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-faststone-photo-resizer-364.html
</guid><description>
FastStone Photo Resizer is an image converter batch, such as rename, resize, crop, rotate, change color depth. FastStone Photo Resizer supports drag and drop will help you to quickly complete his work. FastStone Photo Resizer output files in the most popular formats, including TIFF, GIF, JPEG and BMP. Besides the skills, batch conversion, the application also can rename bulk images.
This program demonstrated speedy performance in our testing and we appreciate that its main window can be...
</description></item><item><title>Download Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium 4.4.48.1225</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Dec 2025 15:29:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-to-mp3-converter-premium-844.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-to-mp3-converter-premium-844.html
</guid><description>
Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium version is a software used to convert YouTube to MP3, extract audio from playlists YouTube, show listings, charts, video responses, channels, favorites of the user. With Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium, you can download and convert playlists, channels, stream original tv series and get them into iTunes at the same time.
Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium - convert YouTube to MP3
Features Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium from the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Draftable Desktop 25.12.100</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Dec 2025 15:29:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-draftable-desktop-3749.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-draftable-desktop-3749.html
</guid><description>
Draftable Desktop is comparison tool documents the fastest. Compare over 300 pages in a few seconds. Draftable Desktop 2.0 is now available - faster and stronger than ever! See all the changes in your documents, locally and online. Take your work to the next level. Compare secret and private do not use the internet and your documents never leave your computer. Specifically, Draftable Desktop compatible with .xls, .xlsx, .xlsxm. With Office 2013, 2016 or 365, you can compare text in...
</description></item><item><title>Download DAZ Studio Professional 4.24.0.4</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Dec 2025 15:28:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-daz-studio-professional-4946.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-daz-studio-professional-4946.html
</guid><description>
DAZ Studio Professional is a professional application to create 3D models and customize them with many different accessories. This app allows you to create scenes by using the model are included in the package. With this app, you can download drum patterns as well as customize it by changing the location, direction as well as the size of each component. DAZ Studio Professional provides the tools to help you can create the presets for any element by arranging the location as well as save it...
</description></item><item><title>Download Aidfile Recovery Software Professional 3.7.9.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Dec 2025 15:28:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aidfile-recovery-software-professional-4316.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aidfile-recovery-software-professional-4316.html
</guid><description>
Aidfile Recovery Software Professional is a software small but powerful will assist you to recover files lost, deleted or damaged. It is ideal to restore data such as videos, files, office, images, folders and many other things. Professional tool this will help you to perform full scan and in-depth hard drive and partition, USB drive, memory card or removable media , to fully restore your data. This software can restore the data file from the file system partition FAT32, NTFS and ExFAT,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Coolmuster iPhone Data Recovery 6.0.48</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Dec 2025 15:27:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-iphone-data-recovery-6599.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-iphone-data-recovery-6599.html
</guid><description>
Coolmuster iPhone Data Recovery is a useful tool designed to help users retrieve all lost data in the iPhone, iPad, or iPod quickly and efficiently. This professional software provides users with a safe way to find lost or deleted data on the Windows system. It can be used in any situation, both online and offline.
Features of Coolmuster iPhone Data Recovery
	Quickly restore the missing or deleted files from the iOS device and the iTunes backup.
	The processing of your iPhone data in...
</description></item><item><title>Download Helium Music Manager Premium 17.4.551</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Dec 2025 15:27:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-helium-music-manager-premium-164.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-helium-music-manager-premium-164.html
</guid><description>
Helium Music Manager is a music manager that can rip, tag, play, browse, search, rename, burn and synchronize your music with the mobile. You can control your music collection with Helium Music Manager. Stop using time looking for the file on your computer or looking through CDS, vinyl records and tapes - instead, simply enjoy and explore your music! Helium Music Manager can replace the ripper, the player, tag editor and related software to audio your other.
Helium Music Manager...
</description></item><item><title>Download Publicspace Photo Date Changer 1.20</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Dec 2025 15:26:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-publicspace-photo-date-changer-5151.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-publicspace-photo-date-changer-5151.html
</guid><description>
Publicspace Photo Date Changer is an easy to use utility allows you to troubleshoot with the date of shooting JPEG (called EXIF timestamp). Publicspace Photo Date Changer ensure arranged in order of time accuracy in the application of the Tuesday (app management, photo slideshow, photo website online, etc., and once captured, there is no easy way to change the date is embed this. forget to change the time zone when traveling or simply have the camera clock is set...
</description></item><item><title>Download Coolmuster iPhone WhatsApp Recovery 2.0.4</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Dec 2025 15:26:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-iphone-whatsapp-recovery-12378.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-iphone-whatsapp-recovery-12378.html
</guid><description>
Coolmuster iPhone WhatsApp Recovery provides effective recovery of WhatsApp messages and attachments from iPhone and iPad devices, ensuring you never lose important chats. View and access WhatsApp chat history and attachments conveniently on your PC, giving you complete control over your WhatsApp data.
Recover WhatsApp data in accessible formats for seamless management and use. Coolmuster iPhone WhatsApp Recovery ensures high retrieval speed and wide compatibility with many devices for...
</description></item><item><title>Download VovSoft Bulk QR Code Generator 2.4</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Dec 2025 15:25:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-bulk-qr-code-generator-7909.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-bulk-qr-code-generator-7909.html
</guid><description>
QR Code are commonly used to contain data for locators, identifiers, or trackers that point to a web page. QR Code stores data efficiently by supporting different encoding modes such as numeric, alphanumeric, byte, binary. Generating thousands of QR Code with different data individually can be time consuming. But with VovSoft Bulk QR Code Generator, you can generate QR Code containing different plain texts at the same time by generating QR Code in bulk.
Although there are various online...
</description></item><item><title>Download Coolmuster iCloud Backup Recovery 2.0.4</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Dec 2025 15:25:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-icloud-backup-recovery-10586.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-icloud-backup-recovery-10586.html
</guid><description>
Want to select files from your iCloud backup? Now, with the help of this iCloud Backup Restore tool, you can do it directly. With this iCloud backup restore program, you can save iCloud backup files to your computer in readable formats. So you can view and access them easily.
Coolmuster iCloud Backup Recovery can log in directly to iCloud there and preview your backup contacts. So, you have regained your contacts from your iCloud backup. By the way, this tool also supports other files....
</description></item><item><title>Download DesktopDigitalClock 6.19</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Dec 2025 15:24:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopdigitalclock-4114.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopdigitalclock-4114.html
</guid><description>
DesktopDigitalClock is a program that desktop clock digital simply and beautifully with the theme and different custom for all MS-OS was inspired from the lock screen! Be made according to numerous requests of users, with the idea of the clock lock screen appearance in Windows 10 / 8.1 after login, display the time and date when the log in the left corner, to the analog clock to appear on desktop Windows.
DesktopDigitalClock - the clock on the computer
The basic function: high...
</description></item></channel></rss>