<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 15:52:50 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 15:52:50 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Display Driver Uninstaller (DDU) 18.1.4.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 15 Feb 2026 14:57:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-display-driver-uninstaller-1999.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-display-driver-uninstaller-1999.html
</guid><description>
Display Driver Uninstaller (DDU) help to easily completely remove the packages and drivers graphics cards AMD, NVIDIA and Intel from your system without leaving any rest whatsoever. Display Driver Uninstaller will automatically detect your current GPU and allows you to delete drivers, registry and files related only by the click of a button. It will also prevent Windows automatically re-install drivers when you reboot your computer, leaving you a drivers graphics common until you install...
</description></item><item><title>Download K-Lite Codec Pack Update 19.4.9</title><pubDate> Sun, 15 Feb 2026 14:56:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-update-5145.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-update-5145.html
</guid><description>
K-Lite Codec Pack Update is the update of the set of codecs and related tools. Codec stands for Compressor-decompressor. Codec is necessary to encode and decode (play) audio and video. K-Lite Codec Pack Update is designed as a user-friendly solution with users to play all movie files your. With Codec Pack K-Lite, you can play 99% of all the movies found on your computer. A number of packages codec is not friendly with computers, as they tend to slow down Windows, break down multimedia...
</description></item><item><title>Download Alfa eBooks Manager Pro / Web 9.4.20.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 15 Feb 2026 14:55:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-alfa-ebooks-manager-web-981.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-alfa-ebooks-manager-web-981.html
</guid><description>
Alfa eBooks Manager Web is a program that enables to arrange the electronic books and paper of you in a single electronic library. eBooks Manager Website will host the electronic books and print in an electronic library. Group, filter and sort books by multiple parameters. Find any book in just a second by title, author or ISBN.
Alfa eBooks Manager Web - ebook library
Alfa eBooks Manager Web provides comprehensive set of fields, including the author, category, publisher, series, ISBN,...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube Downloader 3.9.18 (1402)</title><pubDate> Sun, 15 Feb 2026 14:54:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube Downloader  is a dedicated software that helps users  downloading youtube videos  Favorites on PC for offline viewing. With MediaHuman YouTube  Downloader  you can download videos from youtube website to your computer with  fast speed , with special software development technology that automatically receives videos from Websites, in addition to the ability to download videos from software websites, can convert downloaded video formats to various formats for the purpose...
</description></item><item><title>Download iZotope RX 11 Audio Editor Advanced 11.4.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 15 Feb 2026 14:53:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-izotope-rx-audio-editor-advanced-8619.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-izotope-rx-audio-editor-advanced-8619.html
</guid><description>
iZotope RX10 Audio Editor Advanced is professional audio editing software designed for sound restoration, post-production and sound design. It provides users with advanced tools and technologies to clean, repair and enhance recordings. The software's combination of advanced tools and technologies makes it a valuable tool for professional sound engineers and post-production professionals.
Features of iZotope RX10 Audio Editor Advanced
	Audio Restoration: The ability to repair and...
</description></item><item><title>Download NTFS Permissions Reporter Enterprise 5.2.653</title><pubDate> Sun, 15 Feb 2026 14:52:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ntfs-permissions-reporter-enterprise-6370.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ntfs-permissions-reporter-enterprise-6370.html
</guid><description>
System administrators are constantly required to check user rights for specific files and folders. This is often a time-consuming work, with multiple NTFS classes and repetitive adjustments over time creating a security maze. NTFS Permissions Reporter Enterprise allows you to confirm the security status of the entire file system quickly and efficiently. All have multiple export formats, command line support, integration scheduling, advanced filtration, and more.
Features of NTFS...
</description></item><item><title>Download DBF Recovery 4.66</title><pubDate> Sun, 15 Feb 2026 14:52:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbf-recovery-7931.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbf-recovery-7931.html
</guid><description>
DBF Recovery is software that gives users the ability to restore a damaged database back to its original condition without the expertise required to complete that task. It fixes headers and data structures in an automated process that doesn't involve user interaction. With DBF Recovery, you will truly have a lean, honest DBF repair machine without any functionality.
Features of DBF Recovery
	Quick and simple to use DBF file repair software.
	Repair almost any DBF...
</description></item><item><title>Download MSI Afterburner 4.6.7.16935 Beta 2</title><pubDate> Sun, 15 Feb 2026 14:50:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-msi-afterburner-1075.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-msi-afterburner-1075.html
</guid><description>
MSI Afterburner is overclocking software to speed up computer graphics card to increase gaming performance, support for spin off video card downloads. MSI Afterburner is a utility graphics card that supports users to track the status of the GPU and use the GPU with the maximum performance. Core application MSI Afterburner is based on RivaTuner - software overclocking graphics card top. The program is designed to enhance the performance of the GPU and support multiple graphics cards MSI...
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 7.9.9</title><pubDate> Sun, 15 Feb 2026 14:49:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-11-7760.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-11-7760.html
</guid><description>
TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 is a program that allows users to discover hidden settings in Windows 11. This application is specially designed for Windows 11, groups many registry settings and distribute them from the easy and secure user interface. With TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 you can move the Windows taskbar to the top and resize the taskbar by editing the registry value. With any application that modifies the registry, we recommend that you have a backup copy...
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 7.9.9</title><pubDate> Sun, 15 Feb 2026 14:49:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-10-7759.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-10-7759.html
</guid><description>
TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 is a utility that allows users to discover hidden settings in Windows 10. This application is specially designed for Windows 10, groups many registry settings and provide them from an easy and secure user interface. With TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 you can move the Windows taskbar to the top and resize the taskbar by editing the registry value. With any application that modifies the registry, we recommend that you have a backup copy to...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter 3.9.18 (1402)</title><pubDate> Sun, 15 Feb 2026 14:48:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-to-mp3-converter-1744.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-to-mp3-converter-1744.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter is the software support download youtube video and convert video to mp3 format fast and most simple. MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter allows you download and convert videos from YouTube and other websites to MP3 format by pasting the YouTube URL into the application. When you paste the URL, the program will display thumbnails for videos and you have the option to customize the title information, artist and album before you begin the process of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Vivaldi Browser 7.8.3925.66</title><pubDate> Sun, 15 Feb 2026 14:46:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vivaldi-159.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vivaldi-159.html
</guid><description>
Vivaldi is a browser designed for users who have power and offer the option to customize high. You can choose the location of the tabs and the address bar, put the hotkeys for the common tasks and many other features. Also, Vivaldi also provides a number of improvements such as Tab Stacks to group multiple open tabs into a tab, leads to interface less cluttered. Can notes and added a screenshot of a web page while browsing, storing an attachment, and add the URL to easily sort and locate...
</description></item><item><title>Download Coder Technologies Coder 2.29.6</title><pubDate> Sun, 15 Feb 2026 14:46:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coder-oss-enterprise-8726.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coder-oss-enterprise-8726.html
</guid><description>
Coder OSS Enterprise is a development platform that provides a complete cloud-based solution for software development, testing and deployment. It is designed to simplify the software development process by providing developers with a collaborative and streamlined environment.
Coder offloads development from local workstations to your on-premises infrastructure and public cloud. Boost developer productivity with powerful server resources and instant integration. Keep the code and data...
</description></item><item><title>Download NTFS Undelete 4.0.26.213</title><pubDate> Sun, 15 Feb 2026 14:45:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ntfs-undelete-1408.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ntfs-undelete-1408.html
</guid><description>
NTFS Undelete is application that allows you to recover files deleted from computer in just few clicks. Program recover files deleted from your hard drive even when you've cleared the trash. NTFS Undelete can restore all file types from devices that use the file system NTFS or FAT. You will be able to recover files accidentally deleted even if you deleted them or quick format your device. The program works with all types of removable media, that means you won't encounter any problems when...
</description></item><item><title>Download Macrorit Partition Expert WinPE 8.9.0 Technician Edition</title><pubDate> Sun, 15 Feb 2026 14:44:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-macrorit-partition-expert-winpe-12485.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-macrorit-partition-expert-winpe-12485.html
</guid><description>
Macrorit Partition Expert, especially the WinPE version, is a powerful disk management tool designed for Windows users. As the latest "Partition Magic" alternative software, "Macrorit Partition Expert" provides powerful features that allow users to extend system partition, resize, move partition, create, format, erase partitions easily; Besides, it also possesses unique data protection technology and the best data migration algorithm to ensure 100% data safety and the fastest data...
</description></item><item><title>Download FileRestorePlus 4.0.26.213</title><pubDate> Sun, 15 Feb 2026 14:43:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-filerestoreplus-1404.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-filerestoreplus-1404.html
</guid><description>
FileRestorePlus is a quick and effective way to retrieve files deleted from recycle bin, in a DOS window, from Windows Explorer... FileRestorePlus with a simple interface and a neat, compact, fast, useful, practical and powerful. The program will quickly scan a drive selected and give you a list of the files can be recovered, along with the status for each file.
FileRestorePlus - recover files deleted
FileRestorePlus automatically sorts the files based on file type and folder, making...
</description></item><item><title>Download Scientific Toolworks Understand 7.2 Build 1245</title><pubDate> Sun, 15 Feb 2026 14:42:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-scientific-toolworks-understand-1532.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-scientific-toolworks-understand-1532.html
</guid><description>
Scientific Toolworks Understand is a tool of static analysis to management, measurement and analysis, ability to program. This tool can measure multiple metrics and give you the clear chart about the indicator code different. For example: number of layers, number of project files, number of methods, number of lines, blank lines, comments, dead code, rate, comment on code, complexity in the cycle and the level of trouble of the code, the level of dependence of code together, the rate of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wagnardsoft Tools (WTools) 1.0.7.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 15 Feb 2026 13:41:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wagnardsoft-tools-8092.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wagnardsoft-tools-8092.html
</guid><description>
Wagnardsoft Tools (or WTools) is a lightweight utility that contains many tools to clean your system from temporary and error files Other times take up space and can be dangerous for your PC. It is developed by the author of the program Display Driver Uninstaller has been trusted and used by many people.&amp;lt; /p&amp;gt;
Wagnardsoft Tools gives you the essentials to clean up targeted areas of your machine and thus free up space. It's important to note that don't delete important registry keys...
</description></item><item><title>Download VovSoft Text Decoder And Encoder 2.4</title><pubDate> Sun, 15 Feb 2026 13:41:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-text-decoder-3175.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-text-decoder-3175.html
</guid><description>
VOVSOFT Text Decoder is a program dedicated to the encryption and decryption of content for communication, networking, and storage. This application is very simple to use text encryption and decryption utility supports the sở64, binary, encode URL, encode HTML and coding simple.
VOVSOFT Text Decoder - decode text
VOVSOFT Text Decoder is displayed from a user interface simple for the borrower to operate efficiently without the unnecessary steps. No install how comes and it only...
</description></item><item><title>Download Intel Graphics Driver for Windows 10 / 11 32.0.101.8509</title><pubDate> Sun, 15 Feb 2026 01:02:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intel-graphics-driver-for-windows-10-5954.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intel-graphics-driver-for-windows-10-5954.html
</guid><description>
Intel Graphics Driver for Windows 10 supports Intel ' s latest 8th-generation Core processor, introducing the Intel ® UHD graphics, with the ability to immerve in the top 4K UHD entertainment from your laptop for a maximum of 10 hours. Along with some security fixes, this driver also optimised the system's inactivity to reduce power consumption.
Look at the complete new interface of gameplay.intel.com, where you will find the proposed game settings for many of your favorite PC games....
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare PDFelement Pro 12.1.12.4034</title><pubDate> Sun, 15 Feb 2026 01:01:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-pdfelement-pro-105.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-pdfelement-pro-105.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare PDFelement Pro support users to convert PDF to office documents for easier use, modify in every situation. Is one of the software conversion material is rated best today, integrated with many features. We recommend that you should use experience software many useful features this.
Wondershare PDFelement Pro - conversion Fie PDF more features, multi-language
Wondershare PDFelement Pro what?
Convert PDF into Word, Excel, PowerPoint...
• Convert PDF and protected PDF into...
</description></item><item><title>Download ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro 15.26.0214</title><pubDate> Sun, 15 Feb 2026 01:00:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-videotube-downloader-pro-1276.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-videotube-downloader-pro-1276.html
</guid><description>
ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro is the professional version support download videos and playlists from YouTube, videos from Dailymotion, BBC iPlayer, ITV Player, ABC,  FOX,CBS.com Vimeo, Prosieben, Metacafe, Blip.tv CBC.ca many more video sites. After the video is downloaded, you can convert them to the formats compatible with iPad, iPhone, iPod, MPEG-4, H. 264, MP3, AC3.
ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro - Download videos on Youtube
This is one of the software download the most...
</description></item><item><title>Download Photo Mechanic All-in-One 2026.2 build 9034</title><pubDate> Sun, 15 Feb 2026 00:59:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photo-mechanic-all-in-one-12282.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photo-mechanic-all-in-one-12282.html
</guid><description>
Photo Mechanic All-in-One is an image management software, photo collection and categorization of all photos on your computer, it allows you to Import, Edit and Export quickly, helping you reduce your work. work in the workflow. Powerful batch processing, full support for image variables, IPTC and Exif metadata, make it the perfect tool for any digital photographer.
Photo Mechanic All-in-One Features
	Photo Mechanic takes this step further by automating other tasks at the same time,...
</description></item><item><title>Download OkMap Desktop 19.4.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 15 Feb 2026 00:59:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-okmap-desktop-581.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-okmap-desktop-581.html
</guid><description>
OkMap Desktop is interactive software working on the computer with web maps or digital maps bought or scanned. OkMap can also import a data vector from the most common formats and data DEM related to information height.
Through the map you can organize your path by creating waypoints , routesand tracks on the screen your computer, and upload this data to your GPS . OkMap set data high speedautomatic and estimated moving time . Furthermore OkMap provides you also have autorouting and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Libre Hardware Monitor 0.9.6</title><pubDate> Sun, 15 Feb 2026 00:58:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-libre-hardware-monitor-7447.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-libre-hardware-monitor-7447.html
</guid><description>
Libre Hardware Monitor, a fork of Open Hardware Monitor, is free software that can monitor your temperature, fan speed, voltage, load, and clock speed sensors. your computer. With the help of LibreHardwareMonitor you can read information from devices like:
	Motherboard
	Intel and AMD processors
	NVIDIA and AMD Graphics Card
	HDD, SSD, and NVMe
	Network cards.
</description></item></channel></rss>