<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 17:36:10 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 17:36:10 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Inno Setup Compiler 6.6.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 20:22:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-inno-setup-compiler-2655.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-inno-setup-compiler-2655.html
</guid><description>
Inno Setup Compiler is a system installed based on free software created by Delphi by Jordan Russell. The first version was released in 1997. QuickStart of Inno Setup include main Inno Setup and also includes an option to install the script editor Inno Script Studio. The script editor is not official and is not mandatory for general use, but help Inno Setup easier to use.
Inno Setup Compiler - software create file setup.exe
The features of Inno Setup Compiler
	Support for every...
</description></item><item><title>Download PicPick Pro 7.4.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 20:20:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-picpick-pro-2003.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-picpick-pro-2003.html
</guid><description>
PicPick Pro is a premium version paid free of PicPick. PicPick Pro is a screen capturing tool included editing has taken with many built-in tools available as measurement tool on the screen, including a color picker, color palette, protractor pixel, protractor, cross and many more. The program allows you to capture the entire desktop, active window, selected area or window control just by the click of a button or via keyboard shortcut.
PicPick Pro - Take a screenshot
PicPick Pro has an...
</description></item><item><title>Download PicPick 7.4.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 20:19:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-picpick-1323.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-picpick-1323.html
</guid><description>
PicPick is an application that captures the screen including the editing the photo has been taken with many built-in tools available as measurement tool on the screen, including a color picker, color palette, protractor pixel, protractor, cross and many more. The program allows you to capture the entire desktop, active window, selected area or window control just by the click of a button or via keyboard shortcut.
PicPick - Take a screenshot
Can load the captured image into the image...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tiny11 25H2 Build 26200.7171 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 20:19:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tiny11-8649.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tiny11-8649.html
</guid><description>
Tiny11 is a compact Windows operating system based on Windows 11 Pro 22H2, Tiny11 has everything you need for a comfortable, hassle-free computing experience. cumbersome and messy like a standard Windows installation. The operating system requires only 8GB of disk space and 2GB of RAM, and requires no TPM (Trusted Platform Module) and Secure Boot support.
The main goal of Tiny11 is to extend the reach of systems that can access Windows 11. The custom edition can run on any system...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare Filmora 15.0.11.16306</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 20:18:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-filmora-2025-31.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-filmora-2025-31.html
</guid><description>
In early November 2020 Wondershare came up with a new version called Wondershare Filmora 13 with two new ways to edit: Action Cam Tool (Lens distortion correction, Clean up your audio, Control speed new) and Instant Cutter (Cut or merge clips quickly, Export instantly).
Wondershare Filmora 13  allows you to add your favorite tracks to your videos, creating a more stylish, romantic film reel, with a rich music library besides Users can manually add their favorite songs to the editing...
</description></item><item><title>Download Boris FX Sapphire Plug-ins for OFX 2026.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 20:17:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-genarts-sapphire-839.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-genarts-sapphire-839.html
</guid><description>
GenArts Sapphire is the latest upgrade for the plugin VFX. The application includes LensFlare and Flare Designer been refurbished and completely revamped effects , digital art, new and is optimized for performance, CPU and GPU maximum. The current GenArts Sapphire is supported for Adobe, Avid, them Autodesk Flame and OFX as Resolve, Fusion, NUKE, Baselight (only version 4.3 and 4.4), VEGAS Pro and Harmony.
GenArts Sapphire - edit, add visual effects
The main features of GenArts...
</description></item><item><title>Download EaseUS Partition Master Technican Edition 19.23.0 Build 202510091552</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 20:16:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-partition-master-350.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-partition-master-350.html
</guid><description>
EaseUS Partition Master is software partition management all-in-one be used to redistribute capacity hard drive with high performance and keep all PC, laptop and server running perfect performance. Engineering software master partition deals with all the task partition in an effective way without loss of data. Just a few clicks to re-partition your hard drive, SSD, USB, flash drive, memory card, SD card, memory card and many other storage devices in Windows 10, 8.1, 8, 7, Vista, XP and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Boris FX Sapphire Plug-ins for After Effects 2026.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 20:16:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-boris-fx-sapphire-plug-ins-for-adobe-5314.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-boris-fx-sapphire-plug-ins-for-adobe-5314.html
</guid><description>
Boris FX, Sapphire Plug-ins for Adobe is a collection of very useful gadgets with additional powerful, as well as the effects to create the effect of the attractive images in the movies and video files. The film today is not complete without photo effects and include a number of photo effects to increase the beauty for their film. To add effect, clip to your movie, you can use a number of different applications and BorisFX Genarts Sapphire is one of them.
Boris FX, Sapphire Plug-ins for...
</description></item><item><title>Download TreeSize Free 4.8.1.609</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 20:16:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-treesize-free-10656.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-treesize-free-10656.html
</guid><description>
TreeSize Free is a free disk space manager for Windows, it will show you the size of folders including its subfolders in a similar fashion like Explorer. Large folders can be identified at a glance thanks to the gradient bar displayed in the background. All scan results can be detailed at the file level and filters, e.g. for files of a certain type, can be applied.
Features of TreeSize Free
	Search space: clean up hard drive space
	Break down hard drive space usage to file level:...
</description></item><item><title>Download EASEUS Partition Master Server Edition 19.23.0 Build 202510091552</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 20:15:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-partition-master-server-edition-3457.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-partition-master-server-edition-3457.html
</guid><description>
EASEUS Partition Master Server Edition is a powerful program that allows you to solution delete, create, merge, resize / move, split the partition to use better the full capacity of the hard drive. EasUS Partition Master Server Edition is the partition manager packed full of features and includes three main functions: The recovery guide partition manager partition and wizard restore partition.
These tools will enhance the management of your hard drive and will help you to use disk space...
</description></item><item><title>Download AndroidDrive 2.4.13</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 20:15:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-androiddrive-10400.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-androiddrive-10400.html
</guid><description>
AndroidDrive is a program that allows mounting Android smartphones/tablets as drives on Windows. When AndroidDrive is running and you connect an Android device, AndroidDrive automatically mounts the drive containing that device's internal storage (files, folders).
Once you have started AndroidDrive, the connected Android smartphone/tablet will be recognized as a new drive in Windows Explorer. This way, any files, photos, or other media can be moved back and forth between your Windows...
</description></item><item><title>Download EASEUS Partition Master WinPE Edition 19.23.0 Build 202510091552</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 20:15:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-partition-master-winpe-edition-3460.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-partition-master-winpe-edition-3460.html
</guid><description>
EASEUS Partition Master WinPE Edition is a version plugins help you to create a disk partition on WinPE for you to easily recover hard drive partition computer if not may broken or error. Boot disk EasUS Partition Master WinPE, format software mobile, you can:
	Works well in Windows, such as extend system partition or settling low disk space and managing disk space, recovery partition deleted , rebuild MBR, restore partition GPT, etc.
	You are allowed to resize the primary drive to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Boris FX Sapphire Plug-ins for Photoshop 2026.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 20:14:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-boris-fx-sapphire-plug-ins-for-photoshop-7185.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-boris-fx-sapphire-plug-ins-for-photoshop-7185.html
</guid><description>
Sapphire 2022 adds new host support for Adobe Photoshop. Featuring 270+ resolution independent and non-destructive effects built into a one-of-a-kind nodal based effects compositor. Photoshop artists will delight at 3000+ easily searchable presets organized by name, type, or intended use. Sapphire Photoshop has the same extensive parameter set as Sapphire plugins, giving artists complete control over every aspect of an effect.
Anything created with Sapphire Photoshop can be shared with...
</description></item><item><title>Download EASEUS Partition Master Unlimited Edition 19.23.0 Build 202510091552</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 20:14:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-partition-master-unlimited-edition-3458.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-partition-master-unlimited-edition-3458.html
</guid><description>
EASEUS Partition Master Unlimited Edition is a partition solution all-in-one and tool kit, disk management PC &amp;amp; Server reliable, especially for large enterprise users. It allows unlimited usage within your company. Just a few clicks to re-partition your hard drive, SSD, USB, flash drive, memory card, SD card, memory card and many other storage devices in Windows 10, 8.1, 8, 7, Vista, XP and Windows Server 2016, 2012, 2008, 2003. EASEUS Partition Master Unlimited Edition extend...
</description></item><item><title>Download Freemake Video Converter Gold 5.0.0.22</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 20:13:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-freemake-video-converter-gold-167.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-freemake-video-converter-gold-167.html
</guid><description>
Freemake Video Converter Gold is a software to help convert tail high quality videos with many different formats on many devices. Freemake Video Converter - convert video to AVI, MP4, WMV, MKV, 3GP, DVD, MP3, iPad, iPhone, PSP, Android phone. Video to MP3 just with one click! Rip and burn DVD. Convert YouTube to MP4, AVI, etc. with Freemake! Results guaranteed. Freemake Video Converter has fast conversion speed, guarantee the output quality,support create HTML5 videos have the embed code...
</description></item><item><title>Download Boris FX Sapphire Plug-ins for Avid 2026.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 20:13:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-boris-fx-sapphire-plug-ins-for-avid-12269.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-boris-fx-sapphire-plug-ins-for-avid-12269.html
</guid><description>
Sapphire Plug-ins is an image processing and compositing effects package for use with Avid AVX products including Media Composer, Symphony, Xpress Pro, Newscutter and DS. It includes more than 250 AVX 2 plug-ins, each with multiple parameters that can be adjusted and animated to create unlimited results.
Key features include 270+ effects and 3000+ presets, powerful Transition and Effect Builder, integrated tracking and overlay with Academy Award-winning Mocha. Sapphire's superior image...
</description></item><item><title>Download EASEUS Partition Master Professional Edition 19.23.0 Build 202510091552</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 20:12:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-partition-master-professional-edition-3459.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-partition-master-professional-edition-3459.html
</guid><description>
EASEUS Partition Master Professional Edition is a utility software powerful and full will help you to better manage hard drives and partitions by yourself. This application includes three main functions, such as Program instructions for copying disk and partition, manager partition and wizard restore partition. Moreover, the program allows you to create CD or DVD that can boot, to help you recover the system in case of no boot.
EASEUS Partition Master Professional Edition is the most...
</description></item><item><title>Download Scientific Toolworks Understand 7.2 Build 1240</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 20:11:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-scientific-toolworks-understand-1532.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-scientific-toolworks-understand-1532.html
</guid><description>
Scientific Toolworks Understand is a tool of static analysis to management, measurement and analysis, ability to program. This tool can measure multiple metrics and give you the clear chart about the indicator code different. For example: number of layers, number of project files, number of methods, number of lines, blank lines, comments, dead code, rate, comment on code, complexity in the cycle and the level of trouble of the code, the level of dependence of code together, the rate of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Calibre 8.15.0 + Portable</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 19:11:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-calibre-1669.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-calibre-1669.html
</guid><description>
Calibre  is an eBook library management application that allows you to manage your eBook collection, convert eBooks between different formats, Sync with popular e-reading devices and read your e-books with included viewer. You can sort books by author, title, date and other details, download meta information and book covers, add personalized tags and comments, and view your images in the cover display.
Collection of essential tools for adding metadata editing books or managing your...
</description></item><item><title>Download Minimal Firewall 2.6.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 17:37:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minimal-firewall-13877.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minimal-firewall-13877.html
</guid><description>
Minimal Firewall works in conjunction with Windows Firewall to block all unknown connections by default, prompting you to create application-based rules to mitigate malware, telemetry, and data leaks. Completely eliminate applications that call home without your knowledge. Minimal Firewall provides a more secure and integrated approach by interacting directly with the native Windows Firewall, eliminating the need for risky system modifications.
Core Features
	Lockdown Mode: The core...
</description></item><item><title>Download Unicodia 3.0.3</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 17:37:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-unicodia-8521.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-unicodia-8521.html
</guid><description>
Unicodia is free, open source software that can be used as an alternative character map for your Windows machine. The interface contains everything you need, allowing you to easily cycle through all the available ASCII symbols and copy them to the clipboard. Uncicodia is a great alternative to your standard Unicode characters and is filled with symbols/characters that make it useful for a number of different uses.
Features of Unicodia
	In Windows 10/11 — all characters of Unicode 15...
</description></item><item><title>Download Flyby11 2.1.790</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 17:36:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-flyby11-12467.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-flyby11-12467.html
</guid><description>
Flyby11 is a simple patcher that removes annoying restrictions that prevent you from installing Windows 11 (24H2) on unsupported hardware. Do you have an old PC? No TPM, Secure Boot or your processor is not supported? Flyby11 allows you to install Windows 11 24H2. There are no complicated steps. Just run the tool and you'll be running Windows 11 on your outdated machine in no time.
Technical overview
Flyby11 takes advantage of a feature of the Windows 11 setup process that uses the...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDF-XChange Editor Plus 10.7.6.404</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 17:34:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-xchange-editor-plus-645.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-xchange-editor-plus-645.html
</guid><description>
PDF-XChange Editor Plus is the editor, PDF viewer, compact, fast with many features, add-ons, professional. When using the PDF-XChange Editor Plus, easy for users to create, view, edit, annotate, OCR and digital signing PDF files, plus much more.
PDF-XChange Editor is a PDF editing full-featured. With the help of it, you can edit, fix, add, or delete text easily. Graphics can also be moved, resized or removed.
Features PDF-XChange Editor Plus
Edit documents
	Use a variety of editing...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinRAR 7.20 Beta 2 / 7.13 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 17:33:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winrar-127.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winrar-127.html
</guid><description>
WinRAR is a compression utility data advanced supports multiple formats including RAR, ZIP, CAB, ARJ, LZH, ACE, TAR, GZip, UUE, ISO, BZIP2, Z and 7-Zip. It allows you to create, organize and manage archives in a comfortable way and quickly. WinRAR naturally are is a leading software currently in the compression and decompression of data. With the enhanced algorithm is applied, the software allows users to compress bulk files in different formats into synthetic 1 single file to facilitate...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wise Duplicate Finder Pro 2.1.9.71</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 17:33:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wise-duplicate-finder-pro-544.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wise-duplicate-finder-pro-544.html
</guid><description>
Wise Duplicate Finder Pro is a software supports to find and delete file duplicates based on file name, size and content of file a most accurate way. Besides, Wise Duplicate Finder Pro trigger help the user to find and delete the file, empty, backup and data recovery ensure you can recover data deleted at any time.
In addition, you can use more Wise Disk Cleaner to completely remove junk files from his system.
Features Wise Duplicate Finder Pro
	Provide filter, search for files...
</description></item></channel></rss>