<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 19:52:19 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 19:52:19 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download LDPlayer 9.1.67.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 11 Oct 2025 15:22:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ldplayer-2331.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ldplayer-2331.html
</guid><description>
LDPlayer is software that emulates Android, allowing users to play games, run apps on a Windows computer. LDPlayer support play heavy games, run chat applications, photo editing, video and many other Android apps, LDPlayer compatible with Android 5.1 and above, supports multitasking for experience not inferior when used on Mobile.
Installation is a simple process and quickly without the need for special attention from your side, there's more. installed, you can't touch them. This...
</description></item><item><title>Download MuseScore 4.6.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 11 Oct 2025 15:21:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musescore-2857.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musescore-2857.html
</guid><description>
MuseScore is the tool score for Windows, macOS and Linux, can compare with Finale and Sibelius, support multiple file formats and input methods. It is released as free software and open source under The GNU general public License.
MuseScore - The application composer
Features of MuseScore
	Design WYSIWYG, notes are entered on a "virtual notice"
	TrueType fonts for printing and display allows split ratio high quality for all sizes
	Enter notes easily and quickly
	Many editing...
</description></item><item><title>Download Hypersnap 9.6.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 11 Oct 2025 15:03:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hypersnap-764.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hypersnap-764.html
</guid><description>
Hypersnap is a software screen capture from Windows screen and capture text (TextSnap) from places can't copy normal text. HyperSnap combines the power of screen capture app class with utility image editing advanced is packaged in a easy to use tool! It's perfect for capturing images that you want to put into the help system, online tutorials, manuals, training guides, presentations, marketing materials, website, email, and more. Use HyperSnap to quickly share a picture perfect...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube Downloader 3.9.17 (1010)</title><pubDate> Sat, 11 Oct 2025 15:03:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube Downloader  is a dedicated software that helps users  downloading youtube videos  Favorites on PC for offline viewing. With MediaHuman YouTube  Downloader  you can download videos from youtube website to your computer with  fast speed , with special software development technology that automatically receives videos from Websites, in addition to the ability to download videos from software websites, can convert downloaded video formats to various formats for the purpose...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Camera Raw 17.5.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 11 Oct 2025 15:02:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-camera-raw-02en-785.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-camera-raw-02en-785.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Camera Raw is Plugin edit photo on photoshop with the ability to handle the raw photos after the shoot to create beautiful photos and quality than the input image initially, this program helps support the photographers in editing and photography, make the photo beautiful.
Adobe Camera Raw - edit Raw images Photoshop
Adobe Camera Raw is a plugin which is integrated accompanied by a number of software photo editing such as Photoshop, Photoshop Elements, After Effects and...
</description></item><item><title>Download R-Wipe &amp;amp; Clean 20.0 Build 2530</title><pubDate> Sat, 11 Oct 2025 15:02:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-wipe-clean-891.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-wipe-clean-891.html
</guid><description>
R-Wipe &amp;amp; Clean is software to delete junk files, unnecessary files from your computer to release the storage space and speed up your computer. In addition, R-Wipe &amp;amp; Clean also unleash the capacity of your drive and delete information invasion of privacy on different operations online and offline including your internet history and cookies, the list of downloaded files and documents were open, buffer different data, temporary files and many other items, created by the operating...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Dimension 4.1.5 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Sat, 11 Oct 2025 15:01:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-dimension-cc-254.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-dimension-cc-254.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Dimension CC 2019 is software for designing 2D and 3D to easily create 3D images are of high quality, made to combine the resources intuitive 2D and 3D in one product the actual environment. Purpose introduction of Adobe Dimension is to provide to developers the tools necessary to integrate assets in 2D and 3D without having to study the application complex and specialized. In other words, the program allows you to quickly and simple and creative image other combined 2D and 3D...
</description></item><item><title>Download PIDKey Lite 1.64.4 b50</title><pubDate> Sat, 11 Oct 2025 15:01:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pidkey-lite-2693.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pidkey-lite-2693.html
</guid><description>
PIDKey Lite is a program intended to show the renovation and preservation in the database of the product information to check "validity" of the key Microsoft from the famous program we or is Ratiborus and VAMT. Program PIDKey LiteIt is the successor of the PIDKey. and I got out of it the idea the best program (allows you To add new keyboard with two methods additional mode key).
The program has a number of configuration integration, but you can also create custom profiles by themselves....
</description></item><item><title>Download XYplorer 28.00.0300 Beta</title><pubDate> Sat, 11 Oct 2025 15:00:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-533.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-533.html
</guid><description>
XYplorer - File Manager for Windows is software that supports users to manage files on the Window quickly and to arrange the folder tidy. XYplorer features tabbed browsing, search, files, powerful, preview, flexible, highly customizable interface, dual frame options and a variety of unique ways to automate effective tasks often repeat. It's fast, lightweight, and portable.
Features XYplorer
	XYplorer is a file manager mobile. It does not require any settings, store all configuration...
</description></item><item><title>Download Power-user Premium 1.7.56.189</title><pubDate> Sat, 11 Oct 2025 14:59:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-power-user-premium-3149.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-power-user-premium-3149.html
</guid><description>
Power-user is a plugin for software, Microsoft Excel, PowerPoint and Word help you to provide more visual content so you can create the spreadsheet attractive. It contains templates, icons, tables, drawings and charts, modern, professional, allows you to build professional looking documents. You can add custom content to your project just by a click of the mouse and surprise clients and colleagues with your skills on Excel, PowerPoint and Word.
Power-user Premium - Plugin Excel,...
</description></item><item><title>Download ProfiCAD 13.2.4</title><pubDate> Sat, 11 Oct 2025 14:59:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-proficad-1546.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-proficad-1546.html
</guid><description>
ProfiCAD is a software Program to draw diagram and circuit diagram of the electrical circuit and electronics with many features to support users. ProfiCAD will search the control circuit is different then help, you can design a variety of diagram techniques, such as diagrams, pneumatic and hydraulic. One of the obvious features of this product is the simplicity of it. Simple in the tool bar and the icons represent the parts. Simply arrange the menu, just put the items on the screen and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Monkeys Audio 11.60</title><pubDate> Sat, 11 Oct 2025 14:58:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-monkeys-audio-949.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-monkeys-audio-949.html
</guid><description>
Monkey\'s Audio is software that compresses digital music without loss of quality. Supports high quality WAV files and CD ripping. Monkeys Audio will compress .wav tracks into .ape files to reduce their size without loss of sound quality, decompress .ape, convert files, check file integrity and manage tags.
Unlike traditional methods like MP3 and OGG, which permanently remove quality to save space, Monkey\'s Audio only creates perfect copies with the same sound quality as the originals....
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe DNG Converter 17.5.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 11 Oct 2025 14:58:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-dng-converter-2452.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-dng-converter-2452.html
</guid><description>
Adobe DNG Converter, a free utility that converts files from more than 350 cameras to DNG, enables you to easily convert the files raw exclusively for camera file raw DNG more universal. A program strong enough which allows you to convert the source files RAW to DNG format popular and more convenient with a few clicks of the mouse.
DNG allows photographers to archive files, raw images of them in a single format for easy cataloging and access in the future. With specification formats are...
</description></item><item><title>Download Power-user for PowerPoint and Excel 1.7.56.189</title><pubDate> Sat, 11 Oct 2025 14:57:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-power-user-for-powerpoint-and-excel-522.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-power-user-for-powerpoint-and-excel-522.html
</guid><description>
Power-user for PowerPoint and Excel is a utility providing you with a library of templates, icons, charts, maps and diagrams for spreadsheet and presentation. With Power-user for PowerPoint and Excel, you will attract the attention of your audience with stunning graphics will certainly impress.
Power-user comes with a collection of 2,000 icons to illustrate your slides. The icons are vector shapes so you can resize them without distortion and color back as you with. With Power-user, you...
</description></item><item><title>Download EASEUS Partition Master Unlimited Edition 19.15.0 Build 202510091552</title><pubDate> Sat, 11 Oct 2025 14:57:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-partition-master-unlimited-edition-3458.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-partition-master-unlimited-edition-3458.html
</guid><description>
EASEUS Partition Master Unlimited Edition is a partition solution all-in-one and tool kit, disk management PC &amp;amp; Server reliable, especially for large enterprise users. It allows unlimited usage within your company. Just a few clicks to re-partition your hard drive, SSD, USB, flash drive, memory card, SD card, memory card and many other storage devices in Windows 10, 8.1, 8, 7, Vista, XP and Windows Server 2016, 2012, 2008, 2003. EASEUS Partition Master Unlimited Edition extend...
</description></item><item><title>Download OEM Recovery Partition Creator 6.1.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 11 Oct 2025 14:57:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oem-recovery-partition-creator-6883.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oem-recovery-partition-creator-6883.html
</guid><description>
OEM Recovery Partition Creator for advanced users can clone your partition and bootable rescue media to restore your computer to its original state . The idea behind the app is to be able to create a factory reset just like a factory reset with Dell, HP and others. However, if you are not an advanced user, and possibly even if you are at it, you may not know where to start or how to use the program. The document is very large and can easily be replaced with a graphical user...
</description></item><item><title>Download Atlantis Word Processor 5.0.0.5</title><pubDate> Sat, 11 Oct 2025 14:56:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-atlantis-word-processor-585.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-atlantis-word-processor-585.html
</guid><description>
Atlantis Word Processor is a word processor app with features format, standard text, autocorrect, and spell check.  Atlantis is a word processor in accordance with most of the tasks handled daily text. The interface is very easy to use and offers the toolbars, hotkeys and sound effects thanh can customize (can turn off). It includes a clip library for quick access to the text or images used regular preview, font format and many other features aimed at improving the process of your...
</description></item><item><title>Download GoodSync Enterprise 12.9.9.10</title><pubDate> Sat, 11 Oct 2025 14:56:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-goodsync-enterprise-163.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-goodsync-enterprise-163.html
</guid><description>
GoodSync Enterprise is a software that saves files and files easily and is reliable. It automatically analyts, synchronize and backup your email, family photos, contacts, MP3, financial documentation and other important files-between desktop computers, laptops, servers, external drives and Windows Mobile devices as well as remotely via FTP , SFTP, WebDAV and more. The GoodSync synchronized software combines bulletproof reliability with an extremely easy interface to compare, synchronize...
</description></item><item><title>Download Automatic Email Processor 3.8.15</title><pubDate> Sat, 11 Oct 2025 14:55:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-automatic-email-processor-702.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-automatic-email-processor-702.html
</guid><description>
Automatic Email Processor is a software for managing Email in Outlook efficiency by automatically working with predefined settings. The user interface is divided into two main parts, which is the area allows you to view a list of profiles that you have created and their status and the filters located in the lower part of the interface.
Automatic Email Processor is a comprehensive solution in the archive and print emails and attachments on Outlook fully-automatic. Therefore, you can create...
</description></item><item><title>Download Viber for PC 26.3.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 11 Oct 2025 14:55:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-viber-2406.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-viber-2406.html
</guid><description>
Viber is a software of instant messaging, based on VoIP protocols, multi-platform due to the Viber Media development for smart phones used to send sms and make calls over the internet. Along with text messaging, users can exchange images, video and audio.
Viber - software news message, chat online
This is a program that is quite popular is mainly designed for mobile phones, but now we are talking about the version for Windows, so immediately. It will allow you to send messages to other...
</description></item><item><title>Download Folder Marker Pro 4.5.1 / 4.9.1 Free</title><pubDate> Sat, 11 Oct 2025 14:54:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-folder-marker-pro-4084.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-folder-marker-pro-4084.html
</guid><description>
Folder Marker Pro version is the most functional help you supports all functions of folder marker home and free plus allows the user to customize Network folders and contains additional icons for office work. This adds organization to the office routine and improves our productivity because we can quickly find the document we need. Now you can achieve the same organizational level with the electronic document of you. For example, you can use the red icon to mark the folder with the project...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter 3.9.17 (1010)</title><pubDate> Sat, 11 Oct 2025 14:53:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-to-mp3-converter-1744.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-to-mp3-converter-1744.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter is the software support download youtube video and convert video to mp3 format fast and most simple. MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter allows you download and convert videos from YouTube and other websites to MP3 format by pasting the YouTube URL into the application. When you paste the URL, the program will display thumbnails for videos and you have the option to customize the title information, artist and album before you begin the process of...
</description></item><item><title>Download EMDB 5.39</title><pubDate> Sat, 11 Oct 2025 14:53:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-emdb-64.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-emdb-64.html
</guid><description>
EMDB (Eric's Movie Database) allows you to sort and catalog collection DVD of you.All you have to do is enter the title (or part of it) and the program will enter the detail information and movie cover image from a selection database online.You can then add personal ratings, customize the details, replace cover photo and also set the path local file (if you have a digital copy on your disk).
EMDB - sort and catalog collection DVD of you
Other features include an option to track movies...
</description></item><item><title>Download WonderPen 3.0.2.8116</title><pubDate> Sat, 11 Oct 2025 14:52:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tominlab-wonderpen-7753.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tominlab-wonderpen-7753.html
</guid><description>
WonderPen is a writing app for both professional and amateur writers. WonderPen uses a tree directory to organize documents, supports unlimited levels, and can easily manage both short articles and long works. Documents can be exported to various formats such as images, PDF, Word, Epub and web pages. Multiple chapters can be exported as a book in batches.
WonderPen has a built-in full automatic backup function. By default, it will perform a full database backup every 15 minutes. It also...
</description></item><item><title>Download Easy Gamer Utility Pro 1.3.84</title><pubDate> Sat, 11 Oct 2025 14:52:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easy-gamer-utility-pro-12381.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easy-gamer-utility-pro-12381.html
</guid><description>
Easy Gamer Utility Pro is an easy-to-use program for Windows that can do a lot on your PC to help fix gaming problems, performance problems, and general optimization! The best tool to improve your Windows gaming experience! Is your game laggy and slow? If so, you can use the built-in game accelerator in Easy Gamer Utility, which boosts system performance, makes games run smoother, and increases FPS.
Additionally, this handy utility deletes and cleans unwanted and unnecessary temporary...
</description></item></channel></rss>