<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 05:29:56 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 05:29:56 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download DriversCloud 12.0.30.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 04 Oct 2025 23:32:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-driverscloud-6228.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-driverscloud-6228.html
</guid><description>
DriversCloud is a complex tool that helps you retrieve full data on your system configuration, both hardware and software, while simultaneously implementing additional maintenance tasks such as installing and updating drivers, tracking hard real-time or BSOD analysis. The incident. This tool does not only accurately detect your complete system configuration but also allows you to export this important data to PDF documents to allow you to easily share them online.
Not only did the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wintoys 2.4.6.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 04 Oct 2025 23:31:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wintoys-11863.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wintoys-11863.html
</guid><description>
Are you looking for a utility that makes Windows your own and keeps it up to date, clean, functional and efficient while having all the essentials in one convenient location. Use Wintoys, it helps you organize and easily navigate through available edits etc.
Experience Windows your way and keep it fresh every day. Set up, debug, optimize, repair and tweak your operating system in a simple, time-saving yet secure approach. Keep it clean, healthy and efficient while having everything you...
</description></item><item><title>Download NWinfo 1.4.4</title><pubDate> Sat, 04 Oct 2025 23:30:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nwinfo-12590.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nwinfo-12590.html
</guid><description>
NWinfo is a Win32 program that allows you to obtain system and hardware information. It displays essential information about CPU, memory, disk, network, and even system operating details. Because it's portable, you can carry NWinfo on a USB stick and use it on any Windows machine, making it a useful tool for both tech enthusiasts and troubleshooters.
Features of NWinfo
	Get detailed information about SMBIOS, CPUID, S.M.A.R.T., PCI, EDID, etc.
	Supports export in JSON, YAML and LUA...
</description></item><item><title>Download MemoryCleaner 1.8.9</title><pubDate> Sat, 04 Oct 2025 23:30:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-memorycleaner-12469.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-memorycleaner-12469.html
</guid><description>
MemoryCleaner is a tool to free up memory on your computer. This is a free app with a simple user interface that makes it easy for users of all skill levels to use. MemoryCleaner uses many functions built into Windows to free up memory without affecting your system. You can also access Memory Cleaner's functions right from the system tray without having to open the program. The cleaning processes are silent and the only time you see a warning is to briefly display the amount of RAM...
</description></item><item><title>Download Radmin VPN 2.0.4899.9</title><pubDate> Sat, 04 Oct 2025 23:29:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-radmin-vpn-9996.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-radmin-vpn-9996.html
</guid><description>
Radmin VPN is a simple and effective software that allows you to create or join virtual private networks. As you can imagine, it is useful in cases where you want to create a secure connection through a VPN tunnel between one or more computers over the Internet (gaming cases are probably one of the best examples).
Thanks to the integration with Radmin Remote Control and once installed you can send text or voice messages, end shutdown signals, transfer files as well as remotely control...
</description></item><item><title>Download AppReadWriteCounter 1.43</title><pubDate> Sat, 04 Oct 2025 17:06:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-appreadwritecounter-2896.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-appreadwritecounter-2896.html
</guid><description>
AppReadWriteCorer is a tool for Windows, counts and displays the operations read / write files current of all running apps on your system. It displays the number of bytes read / write number of read / write speed read / write is calculated current and the app details (product name, product version, etc.) make read / write operations to the file. AppReadWriteCorer is designed to help you monitor the action that displays the timer for the activity read and write, along with other parameters,...
</description></item><item><title>Download DSynchronize 2.48.182</title><pubDate> Sat, 04 Oct 2025 17:05:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dsynchronize-88.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dsynchronize-88.html
</guid><description>
DSynchronize is a tool to synchronize files allows you to synchronize one or more folders on your local computer, removable drives or on the network. It supports file filters based on extension, two-way sync, and can run according to regular schedule to synchronize your folders automatically, with an option to run as a Windows service.
DSynchronize - synchronization tool file independent
Other features include support for priority idle, create directories, manipulate the command line...
</description></item><item><title>Download AmoyShare AnyMusic 10.9.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 04 Oct 2025 17:03:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-amoyshare-anymusic-14132.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-amoyshare-anymusic-14132.html
</guid><description>
AmoyShare AnyMusic is a multi-purpose music downloader and player. The app allows users to search, explore and download unlimited high-quality music (MP3, M4A, WebM, etc.) from over 1,000 online music streaming sites, including SoundCloud, Bandcamp, TikTok, etc. Users can download entire playlists, batch download multiple songs, and enjoy music offline with the built-in music player. The software supports music video downloading and provides fast download speed with multi-threading...
</description></item><item><title>Download MobaXterm Professional 25.3 / Personal / Educational</title><pubDate> Sat, 04 Oct 2025 17:02:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mobaxterm-professional-2026.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mobaxterm-professional-2026.html
</guid><description>
MobaXterm Professional is an SSH Client application server administration remotely via SSH for the client quite well and are more convenient. MobaXterm Professional offers a multitude of functions suitable for programmers, webmasters, IT administrators and pretty much the user need to handle the job from far more simple way. MobaXterm provides all the tools network key remote (SSH, X11, RDP, VNC, FTP, MOSH, ...) and Unix commands (bash, ls, cat, sed, grep, awk, rsync, ...) , in a file exe...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mozilla Firefox 143.0.4</title><pubDate> Sat, 04 Oct 2025 17:02:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-firefox-quantum-501.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-firefox-quantum-501.html
</guid><description>
Firefox Quantum is a web browser independently provide the tabbed browsing combined with numerous handy features like pop-up blocker, Bookmarks, direct (integrated RSS), password manager, and more. Functionality can be extended with dozens of plugins available for free (extensions).
Firefox Quantum are interface completely new, beautiful, neat, minimalistic and delicate, eats less RAM to 30% compared with the old version and solve the condition consuming capacity
Firefox can import all...
</description></item><item><title>Download lessmsi 2.10.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 04 Oct 2025 17:01:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lessmsi-12392.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lessmsi-12392.html
</guid><description>
Lessmsi (Less MSIerables) is a free and portable application that allows users to view and extract the contents of MSI files.
How does it work? Files with the .msi extension are not as widely used as their .exe cousins, but both contain programs for Windows. The main difference between them is that the latter does not always come with an installer, while it comes standard with the former. However, there will be cases where you just need to view or want to extract specific content from...
</description></item><item><title>Download GoodSync Enterprise 12.9.9.7</title><pubDate> Sat, 04 Oct 2025 17:01:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-goodsync-enterprise-163.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-goodsync-enterprise-163.html
</guid><description>
GoodSync Enterprise is a software that saves files and files easily and is reliable. It automatically analyts, synchronize and backup your email, family photos, contacts, MP3, financial documentation and other important files-between desktop computers, laptops, servers, external drives and Windows Mobile devices as well as remotely via FTP , SFTP, WebDAV and more. The GoodSync synchronized software combines bulletproof reliability with an extremely easy interface to compare, synchronize...
</description></item><item><title>Download ParkControl Pro 5.5.1.8</title><pubDate> Sat, 04 Oct 2025 17:00:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bitsum-parkcontrol-pro-6765.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bitsum-parkcontrol-pro-6765.html
</guid><description>
ParkControl Pro is free software to display and adjust CPU core settings in real time. It also has a bunch of free power automation features. Core Parking automatically disables CPU cores to save power when idle. Disabled cores are re-enabled as CPU load once again increases. This technology is very similar to frequency scaling, in that it seeks to throttle the CPU when idle.
These tweaks are completely safe for any properly configured PC. The only way they seem to be able to cause some...
</description></item><item><title>Download RocketCake Professional 6.4.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 04 Oct 2025 16:59:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rocketcake-professional-2632.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rocketcake-professional-2632.html
</guid><description>
RocketCake Professional is a WYSIWYG HTML editor that allows you to create a website based on the responsive template without coding. Simply choose your template and customize it or create a new design from scratch.In addition to text content you can add images, galleries, slideshows, YouTube videos, Flash, buttons, audio / video HTML5, table and many page elements enhance the other.
RocketCake Professional - design application Website
Allows you to create a website as quickly as...
</description></item><item><title>Download DShutdown 1.78.130</title><pubDate> Sat, 04 Oct 2025 16:59:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dshutdown-329.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dshutdown-329.html
</guid><description>
DShutdown is a stand-alone program can be used to perform the shutdown operations on one or more network machines, including reboot, shutdown, logout, and more. The program works as a package server / client and requires running RDShutdown.exe include on the remote machine.
If you have administrator login valid for the machine (s), you can also use the mode do not need server, do not require any app remote, how to run. Assistance program off schedule, Wake-on-LAN, monitor does not work...
</description></item><item><title>Download KeyScrambler Premium 3.18.0.7 + Professional</title><pubDate> Sat, 04 Oct 2025 16:57:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-keyscrambler-premium-professional-143.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-keyscrambler-premium-professional-143.html
</guid><description>
KeyScrambler Premium / Professional allows users to search for and remove the malicious program, the spy program on the computer system. This program support users to handle a number of spy programs send user information to the server by way thoroughly remove them from the system.
KeyScrambler Premium Key key encryption real-time encryption key, every key you type deep in the Windows. It protects the personal information of you against all malware keylog already know and not know on...
</description></item><item><title>Download WYSIWYG Web Builder 20.3.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 04 Oct 2025 16:57:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wysiwyg-web-builder-177.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wysiwyg-web-builder-177.html
</guid><description>
WYSIWYG Web Builder : The construction of the website from scratch using HTML code isn't a pleasant process, even when you know what you are doing. The website can be built using WYSIWYG Web Builder with using the element similar to the package published on the desktop: text and images placed in frames and tables on the page, so very little surprised when most of the efforts to make the web become a experience user-friendly than. the controls do you use to build your pages.
WYSIWYG Web...
</description></item><item><title>Download ProtonVPN 4.3.4</title><pubDate> Sat, 04 Oct 2025 16:50:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-protonvpn-10433.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-protonvpn-10433.html
</guid><description>
ProtonVPN app for Windows is the best way to stay safe and private while surfing the internet. It is open source, easy to use, and packed with useful security features. ProtonVPN will secure your connection by routing your traffic through multiple servers to protect you against advanced network-based attacks.
It helps keep your IP address safe if something goes wrong with your VPN connection. If your VPN connection fails, the kill switch feature will prevent your device from connecting...
</description></item><item><title>Download FreeFileSync 14.5</title><pubDate> Sat, 04 Oct 2025 16:50:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-freefilesync-2447.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-freefilesync-2447.html
</guid><description>
FreeFileSync is a program open source and free to be used to sync files. It's available on Windows, Linux and OS X. The project is supported by donations. Donors get a few extra features like the automatic updates, synchronize, parallel, mobile version and install silent.
FreeFileSync - sync data
Features of FreeFileSync
	Detect moved and renamed files and folders
	Copy the file locked (Volume Shadow Copy Service)
	Detect conflicts and propagate delete
	Compare binary
	Full support...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adlice Protect (formerly RogueKiller) 16.4.1.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 04 Oct 2025 16:48:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rogueKiller-171.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rogueKiller-171.html
</guid><description>
RogueKiller is a tool anti-malware independent can assist advanced users with the removal of a number of difficulties in the removal of malware, in security software rogue special.
The program can terminate processes, malware has to know to you can delete them manually or use the tool clear of the Tuesday to complete the work. RogueKiller can also restore HOSTS file as well as your DNS settings and Proxy, which is often modified by rogue applications.
RogueKiller
When you run...
</description></item><item><title>Download Argente Registry Cleaner 4.0.3.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 04 Oct 2025 16:48:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-argente-registry-cleaner-13814.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-argente-registry-cleaner-13814.html
</guid><description>
Argente Registry Cleaner is a free Windows utility designed to scan, clean and repair invalid or obsolete entries in the Windows Registry, helping to improve system stability and performance. This utility quickly analyzes the entire Registry for errors such as invalid entries left by uninstalled programs, missing keys, broken references, and other junk that can cause system crashes.
Key Features:
	Fast and Thorough Scan: Provides multiple scan modes including Safe (fastest), Normal...
</description></item><item><title>Download Disk Pulse Ultimate 17.3.18 + Enterprise + Pro</title><pubDate> Sat, 04 Oct 2025 16:47:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-disk-pulse-ultimate-1465.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-disk-pulse-ultimate-1465.html
</guid><description>
Disk Pulse Ultimate is a monitoring solution change disk real-time allows one to monitor one or more disks or directories, save reports and statistics monitoring disk changes, the change is detected to the SQL database focus, execute custom commands and send E-Mail notifications when unauthorized changes are detected in the file system important.
Disk Pulse Ultimate - Monitor disc change
DiskPulse provides the ability for users to start / stop the monitoring operation disc change,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Argente Malware Cleaner 3.0.3.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 04 Oct 2025 16:47:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-argente-malware-cleaner-13494.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-argente-malware-cleaner-13494.html
</guid><description>
Argente Malware Cleaner is a lightweight utility designed to detect and remove a wide range of malware, including spyware, adware, Trojans and other threats that can compromise your privacy and data. It works as a complementary tool alongside your main antivirus software, helping to detect malware that may slip through the cracks.
Key features of Argente Malware Cleaner include:
	Easy-to-use, clean, and user-friendly interface that suits both casual and advanced users.
	Deep scanning...
</description></item><item><title>Download Argente System Repair 1.0.2.9</title><pubDate> Sat, 04 Oct 2025 16:46:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-argente-system-repair-13813.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-argente-system-repair-13813.html
</guid><description>
Argente System Repair is a lightweight utility designed to diagnose and fix common Windows system problems. It scans your system to identify errors in operating system components, file systems, installation files, and other system components, and then applies targeted fixes to resolve these problems. The tool provides different scan modes, including simple scan, recommended scan, and custom scan, allowing users to customize the repair process according to their needs.
System Repair...
</description></item><item><title>Download RocketCake 6.4.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 04 Oct 2025 16:46:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rocketcake-1697.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rocketcake-1697.html
</guid><description>
RocketCake is WYSIWYG HTML editor allows you to create a website based on the responsive template without coding. Simply choose your template and customize it or create a new design from scratch.In addition to text content you can add images, galleries, slideshows, YouTube videos, Flash, buttons, audio / video HTML5, table and many page elements enhance the other.
RocketCake - WYSIWYG HTML editor
RocketCake does not require any knowledge of HTML or CSS, you only need to drag the page...
</description></item></channel></rss>