<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 13:43:42 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 13:43:42 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download OP Auto Clicker 4.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 14 Oct 2025 16:19:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-op-auto-clicker-4289.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-op-auto-clicker-4289.html
</guid><description>
OP Auto Clicker software auto mouse click advanced mode click at the mouse cursor, dynamic, or at a location to be determined in advance. The shortcut works on the system background should be very convenient to use. OP Auto Clicker is especially useful when you play games or work with the utility requires to click the mouse many times, quickly and repeated. It helps you get rid of the missions repetitive, boring by the creation of a list queue the click position on the screen.
OP Auto...
</description></item><item><title>Download CPU-Z 2.17</title><pubDate> Tue, 14 Oct 2025 16:17:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cpu-z-2240.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cpu-z-2240.html
</guid><description>
A wonderful development has been updated, in a simple way, can display technical information about the computer, your personal nature it will operate in Windows operating systems from version 98 to latest version 7. After starting, you can see the specifications of different sets of processing center, you can find out full data on the video card and motherboard, I forgot to add about RAM, download CPU-Z from our project in full news.
CPU-Z - Check CPU hardware
After installing, launch...
</description></item><item><title>Download EverNote 10.158.1.45283</title><pubDate> Tue, 14 Oct 2025 16:16:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-evernote-3261.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-evernote-3261.html
</guid><description>
EverNote is the all in one tool allows you to track notes, todo items, memos, outlines, excerpts, websites, ideas and other things and automatically synchronize them between multiple computers and mobile devices (iPhone, Android, etc.). You can choose to sort their notes into categories, password protect them, export them to XML and more. EverNote supports a number of pattern notes allow you to add to-do list, spreadsheet like Excel to calculate costs (automatic sum), notes, phone, contact...
</description></item><item><title>Download Turbo Studio 25.10.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 14 Oct 2025 16:15:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-turbo-studio-1797.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-turbo-studio-1797.html
</guid><description>
Turbo Studio (formerly known as Spoon Studio) - with this application you can combine the files needed to make the application run into a ready-to-use package without deployment. This application allows you to create a container program and run it virtually in a virtual environment without installing and making changes in the registry and system. Since driver and system updates are constantly being developed to reduce the likelihood of errors, applications may need to be rooted to your...
</description></item><item><title>Download MyLanViewer Enterprise 6.6.1 / Business</title><pubDate> Tue, 14 Oct 2025 16:14:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mylanviewer-enterprise-1274.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mylanviewer-enterprise-1274.html
</guid><description>
MyLanViewer is a program for scanning IP address, Netbios and LAN / Network powerful for Windows tool whois and traceroute, remote shutdown and process management Wake On LAN (WOL), scan and monitor wireless networks. This app will help you find all IP addresses, MAC addresses and shared folders of computers on the network wired or wireless (Wi-Fi).
MyLanViewer Enterprise - Scan IP address LAN/Network
The program scans network and displays the computer network in your window, friends...
</description></item><item><title>Download Photo Supreme 2025.3.3.8115</title><pubDate> Tue, 14 Oct 2025 16:13:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photo-supreme-430.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photo-supreme-430.html
</guid><description>
Photo Supreme is a software product management professional pictures of idimager. With Photo Supreme you can arrange, manage back stock photo archive of yourself and share them with you here and relatives easily via Email or Facebook. Photo Supreme provides users method to sort images effective, logical, as well as edit and share your photos with friends and relatives in the family. Especially the Photo Supreme allows to work with multiple image formats and support mounting support,...
</description></item><item><title>Download DU Meter 9.01</title><pubDate> Tue, 14 Oct 2025 16:13:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-du-meter-91.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-du-meter-91.html
</guid><description>
DU Meter provides users the ability to check the internet connection at any time. The software allows users to check download and upload speeds practice at different times. DU Meter also provides features press the clock to measure the exact download time of the communication line and report back. DU Meter really useful and necessary for parents to control their children use the internet or the manager supervision of his employees during office hours
DU Meter - Check the internet...
</description></item><item><title>Download Coolutils Total PDF Converter 6.5.0.356/149</title><pubDate> Tue, 14 Oct 2025 16:12:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-total-pdf-converter-830.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-total-pdf-converter-830.html
</guid><description>
Coolutils Total PDF Converter is software to convert PDF convert PDF files to HTML, DOC (Word), text, Excel, PostScript, CSV or image files. The advantage of Coolutils Total PDF Converter is the fast, easy-to-handle, accurate, does not require Adobe Acrobat, supports many target format and have the option of batch (can convert hundreds of PDF files as well as the single file). Added to this, registered users get command line support to manage the utility with maximum...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ableton Live Suite 12.2.6</title><pubDate> Tue, 14 Oct 2025 16:12:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ableton-live-suite-663.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ableton-live-suite-663.html
</guid><description>
Ableton Live Suite is professional software to create, edit, music with effects, instruments, audio and all creative. Ableton Live Suite is the software fast, flexible and flexibility to create and perform music. Move freely between the musical elements and play with ideas, that don't stop the music and do not break the flow of your sound.
Features, Ableton Live Suite
	Meet Wavetable, Echo, Drum Buss and Pedal: the new equipment means new sounds, colorful can with the instruments and...
</description></item><item><title>Download MusConv 4.10.426 Lifetime</title><pubDate> Tue, 14 Oct 2025 16:10:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html
</guid><description>
MusConv transfers playlists, albums, followed artists and liked songs across a variety of services – Spotify, Apple Music, Amazon Music, YouTube, YouTube Music, iTunes, Deezer, Tidal, SoundCloud, Pandora and more 125 music services!
Features of MusConv Ultimate
	Transfer playlists, albums, followed artists and liked tracks between over 125 music servicesManage playlists (Delete, Merge, Split, Copy...)
	More than 125 music services supported
	Access DAILY updated music charts on...
</description></item><item><title>Download CoolUtils Total Image Converter 8.2.0.283</title><pubDate> Tue, 14 Oct 2025 16:05:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-total-image-converter-848.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-total-image-converter-848.html
</guid><description>
CoolUtils Total Image Converter is software to convert images to other formats, and can edit, cut, resize and rotate them. With Total Image Converter you easy convert TIFFs into JPEGS, make photos suitable for the web or recover old photos in the supported format.
&amp;nbsp;CoolUtils Total Image Converter - convert images to other formats
Features CoolUtils Total Image Converter
	Total Image Converter supports almost all image formats
	Support convert eagle picture series.
	Total Image...
</description></item><item><title>Download Coolutils Total Excel Converter 7.1.0.102</title><pubDate> Tue, 14 Oct 2025 16:04:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-total-excel-converter-849.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-total-excel-converter-849.html
</guid><description>
Coolutils Total Excel Converter is software that converts Excel documents to other formats like ODS, XML, SQL, WK2, WKS WAB, DBF, TEX and DIF for you to use. In addition, the software also supports converting Excel files into file DOC, DOCX, PDF, HTML, Access, TXT, ODT, ODS, XML, SQL, CSV, Lotus, DBF, TEX, DIFF, SYLK and LaTeX.
Coolutils Total Excel Converter - batch convert Excel
Total Excel Converter has a perfect layout and tight. When the conversion is finished you will get an...
</description></item><item><title>Download VMware InstallBuilder Enterprise 25.10</title><pubDate> Tue, 14 Oct 2025 16:04:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vmware-installbuilder-enterprise-6055.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vmware-installbuilder-enterprise-6055.html
</guid><description>
VMware InstallBuilder Enterprise  is a development tool for building cross-platform installers for desktop and server software. With InstallBuilder, you can quickly create professional, dynamic installers for Linux, Windows, Mac OS X, Solaris, and other platforms from a project file and build environment. In addition to the installer, InstallBuilder will create RPM and Debian packages and rich CD / DVD. The automatic update function makes it easy to deliver updates directly to users...
</description></item><item><title>Download CoolUtils PDF Splitter Pro 5.2.0.103/37</title><pubDate> Tue, 14 Oct 2025 16:03:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-pdf-splitter-1628.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-pdf-splitter-1628.html
</guid><description>
CoolUtils PDF Splitter is intelligent software to split the PDF file extra large according to the bill number or a keyword. A handy software that can help you solve the problem of split different pages inside one PDF file multiple pages. PDF Splitter is very easy to use and has neat interface. All what you need to do is install it and make a few clicks.
Besides, PDF Splitter also lets you combine the page was divided. So if you have a data multi-page PDF and need to re-arrange the pages,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Chaos V-Ray 7.1.1 Build 7.10.01 for Blender 4.2 - 4.5</title><pubDate> Tue, 14 Oct 2025 16:02:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chaos-v-ray-for-blender-13913.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chaos-v-ray-for-blender-13913.html
</guid><description>
Chaos V-Ray for Blender is a professional, photorealistic rendering engine, now fully integrated into Blender, one of the most popular open source 3D creation tools. This tool brings Chaos' Emmy and Academy Award-winning rendering technology directly to Blender users, allowing for easy and efficient creation of high-quality images and animations.
Key Features:
	Realistic Rendering: Use Chaos' Global Illumination technology to create realistic lighting, reflections, shadows, and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wing FTP Server Corporate 8.0.5</title><pubDate> Tue, 14 Oct 2025 16:01:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wing-ftp-server-corporate-2752.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wing-ftp-server-corporate-2752.html
</guid><description>
Wing FTP Server Corporate is a highly functional, easy and safe can be used in the operating system Windows, Linux, Mac and Solaris are used. The software supports a number of file transfer protocol such as FTP, HTTP, FTPS, HTTPS and SFTP. Wing FTP Server provides web-based interface to manage the server at any time. You can also get performance server and the online and even send email notifications about various events happening on the server.
Management server multi-function
Wing FTP...
</description></item><item><title>Download Flyoobe 1.31.531</title><pubDate> Tue, 14 Oct 2025 16:00:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oobelux-13956.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oobelux-13956.html
</guid><description>
Flyoobe was born out of the frustration many users felt with the Windows 11 setup experience. Whether it was the mandatory online account, the endless "Next, next, next..." screens, or the incomplete configuration options when you finally reached the desktop, the current setup lacked focus on what users really wanted.
Why choose Flyoobe?
	Simplifies the Windows 11 setup process right out of the box.
	Allows easy local account creation without need to hunt for hidden options.
	Includes...
</description></item><item><title>Download ThunderSoft GIF to Video Converter 5.6.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 14 Oct 2025 15:54:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thundersoft-gif-to-video-converter-2398.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thundersoft-gif-to-video-converter-2398.html
</guid><description>
ThunderSoft GIF to Video Converter is an interesting program that allows you to create video files in full size with the different formats with the desired quality from the images of type GIF (animated images). In addition to the plus points of plastic, you can note the ability to preview each frame have crop mode video, now you can create a small video clips with just a few mouse clicks.
ThunderSoft GIF to Video Converter - Create videos from GIF images
Among additional features is to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Abelssoft EasyBackup 2026 v16.01.66373</title><pubDate> Tue, 14 Oct 2025 15:52:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-abelssoft-easybackup-173.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-abelssoft-easybackup-173.html
</guid><description>
Abelssoft Backup is a great software that allows you to backup your important data to a safe location in case of corruption or damaged due to random or some form of data loss other surprises. Backup interface is modern, minimalist. It has a simple instructions guide you through the process of your backup in a few simple steps.
Abelssoft Backup
You can add multiple tasks into the manager and you can perform any task any of them by a single click. Utilities software mode support...
</description></item><item><title>Download Scientific Toolworks Understand 7.2 Build 1236</title><pubDate> Tue, 14 Oct 2025 15:52:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-scientific-toolworks-understand-1532.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-scientific-toolworks-understand-1532.html
</guid><description>
Scientific Toolworks Understand is a tool of static analysis to management, measurement and analysis, ability to program. This tool can measure multiple metrics and give you the clear chart about the indicator code different. For example: number of layers, number of project files, number of methods, number of lines, blank lines, comments, dead code, rate, comment on code, complexity in the cycle and the level of trouble of the code, the level of dependence of code together, the rate of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Steelray Project Analyzer 7.21</title><pubDate> Tue, 14 Oct 2025 15:50:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-steelray-project-analyzer-607.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-steelray-project-analyzer-607.html
</guid><description>
Steelray Project Analyzer is software reviews schedules and resources for multiple projects and create reports to improve quality and performance. Steelray Project Analyzer is software that eases the creation, maintenance and provide schedule quality. With The analysis, you can evaluate the progress of your project in terms of quality and performance in minutes and produce results easy to understand. The schedule can be analyzed against the best practices of project management best...
</description></item><item><title>Download Omidsoft Red Burner 18.30</title><pubDate> Tue, 14 Oct 2025 15:50:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-red-burner-10119.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-red-burner-10119.html
</guid><description>
Red Burner is a lightweight burning software based on Blue Burner with full functionality to work with ISO/CUE images and drives. Start the move to a lightweight, yet powerful, and time-saving standalone optical disc burner with the simplest user interface and fastest possible burning algorithm.
Features of Red Burner
	Fastest possible CD/DVD/BD burning algorithm
	Standard, dual-layer and high-capacity media recording
	Browse ISO/CUE images via internal image browser
	Writable M-Disc,...
</description></item><item><title>Download SSD Booster .NET 18.30</title><pubDate> Tue, 14 Oct 2025 15:49:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ssd-booster-net-7375.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ssd-booster-net-7375.html
</guid><description>
SSD Booster .NET is our perfect tool to optimize and adjust Windows for the SSD drive to increase performance and maintain the highest performance for your SSD. In addition, the app comes with the system information tab for information about the hardware and operating system of your machine. To check your specifications, move to the Introduction and find the System Information button.
Features of SSD Booster .NET
	The perfect tool to optimize and adjust Windows for the SSD drive to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Edge Remover 18.30</title><pubDate> Tue, 14 Oct 2025 15:48:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-edge-remover-7689.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-edge-remover-7689.html
</guid><description>
Edge Remover is our mini user interfaceless tool to permanently remove Microsoft Edge from your system. Easily remove Microsoft Edge browser from your system, with just one click, with this simple, no UI app.
Features of Edge Remover
	Remove MSEdge and its components
	Prevent reinstalling MSEdge on your system
Requirements:
Operating System: Microsoft Windows 7 or later
Framework: Microsoft .NET Framework 4.0
</description></item><item><title>Download SysTools Outlook Recovery 9.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 14 Oct 2025 15:48:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-systools-outlook-recovery-411.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-systools-outlook-recovery-411.html
</guid><description>
SysTools Outlook Recovery is software that repairs damaged Outlook files and recovers Outlook files in PST, EML, MSG, HTML and Office 365. The SysTools Outlook Recovery utility is an effective solution. The results have been excellent in recovering PST inaccessible data items and recovering Outlook folders like: emails, calendar contacts, tasks.
Using Outlook PST Recovery tool, users can repair Outlook PST files and quickly recover damaged Outlook files. This PST Fix tool can easily...
</description></item></channel></rss>