<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 12:39:28 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 12:39:28 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Opera One 127.0.5778.76</title><pubDate> Thu, 19 Feb 2026 00:45:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-972.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-972.html
</guid><description>
Opera is a fast, safe, configurable and compliant intranet web browser, which includes both the reader and the application. The Opera browser supports web browsing, listening to music, watching high speed movies, you can open many tabs on the Opera without affecting your browsing speed. Opera now supports almost all devices and operating systems such as windows, IOS, Android, linux, MacOS ...
Opera is a beautiful interface and many interesting features, operating on both PCs and mobile,...
</description></item><item><title>Download UltraSearch Professional 4.9.0.1201</title><pubDate> Thu, 19 Feb 2026 00:44:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ultrasearch-professional-10252.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ultrasearch-professional-10252.html
</guid><description>
UltraSearch Professional is the professional version that helps you find your files and documents on all connected hard drives and network drives. Search by file type, document content, or file properties. Take back your valuable time and let UltraSearch do the searching for you.
UltraSearch Professional does not maintain an index stored on your hard disk. It achieves speed by working directly on the Master File Table (MFT) of NTFS partitions. So it even identifies NTFS hardlinks. That...
</description></item><item><title>Download Batch Image Combiner PRO 1.3.2.4</title><pubDate> Thu, 19 Feb 2026 00:43:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-batch-image-combiner-pro-11123.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-batch-image-combiner-pro-11123.html
</guid><description>
Are you looking for a quick and effective way to combine multiple images vertically and horizontally? Look no further than this utility: Batch Image Combiner PRO is an easy-to-use Windows application that allows you to quickly join two or more images into one both vertically and horizontally in just 1-2 seconds.
With the help of Batch Image Combiner, a powerful program that allows users to combine images into one image, this task can be done quickly and automatically. No more tedious...
</description></item><item><title>Download AI Video to SRT 1.1.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 19 Feb 2026 00:43:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ai-video-to-srt-14564.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ai-video-to-srt-14564.html
</guid><description>
VideoToSRT uses advanced on-premise artificial intelligence (AI) to convert video and audio files into SRT, VTT, and TXT formats. No cloud upload required, no registration needed, and absolute privacy guaranteed for your content.
Features of AI Video to SRT
	Offline speech-to-text conversion using AI technology.
	Batch processing queue for multiple files in sequence.
	NVIDIA GPU acceleration for ultra-fast speeds.
	Supports input formats MP4, MOV, MKV, MP3, WAV, and M4A.
	Export to...
</description></item><item><title>Download dBpoweramp Image Converter Premier 2026-02-16</title><pubDate> Thu, 19 Feb 2026 00:42:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbpoweramp-image-converter-7007.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbpoweramp-image-converter-7007.html
</guid><description>
dBpoweramp Image Converter is a simple visual transformation application that aims to make the transition as simple as possible. dBpoweramp Image Converter will switch between all popular formats, Bitmap, PNG, JPEG, TIFF and many other formats. It also has the ability to make mass transformation for multiple files and folders with only one click and filter on the png or other types of files.
dBpoweramp Image Converter is capable of switching high speed by using simultaneously all CPU...
</description></item><item><title>Download Bitvise SSH Client 9.59</title><pubDate> Thu, 19 Feb 2026 00:41:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bitvise-ssh-client-2845.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bitvise-ssh-client-2845.html
</guid><description>
Bitvise SSH Client is a SSH terminal, tunneling and file transfer application SFTP for free with the command line interface and graphics. It supports all versions desktop and server of Windows! Bitvise SSH Client for free use! Bitvise SSH Client is an application multipurpose, fast and powerful in the transmission of the advanced file helps users control and manage the terminal remotely in a flexible manner. Bitvise SSH Client intensive support for establishing the secure connection...
</description></item><item><title>Download Freemake Video Converter Gold 5.0.0.36</title><pubDate> Thu, 19 Feb 2026 00:39:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-freemake-video-converter-gold-167.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-freemake-video-converter-gold-167.html
</guid><description>
Freemake Video Converter Gold is a software to help convert tail high quality videos with many different formats on many devices. Freemake Video Converter - convert video to AVI, MP4, WMV, MKV, 3GP, DVD, MP3, iPad, iPhone, PSP, Android phone. Video to MP3 just with one click! Rip and burn DVD. Convert YouTube to MP4, AVI, etc. with Freemake! Results guaranteed. Freemake Video Converter has fast conversion speed, guarantee the output quality,support create HTML5 videos have the embed code...
</description></item><item><title>Download TreeSize Professional 9.7.1.2201</title><pubDate> Thu, 19 Feb 2026 00:39:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-treesize-professional-390.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-treesize-professional-390.html
</guid><description>
TreeSize Pro is a software to manage hard disk space powerfully and flexibly for Windows 2003/2008 / XP / Vista / 7/8/10. TreeSize will find out which directory the largest on your drives and recover megabytes on disk. TreeSize Professional shows you the size, allocated and wasted space, number of files, 3D charts, last accessed date, file owner and permissions, the speed NTFS compression and much more information for several folders or drives you choose. It also lets you search drives,...
</description></item><item><title>Download FormulaDesk FormulaSpy 1.39</title><pubDate> Thu, 19 Feb 2026 00:38:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-formuladesk-formulaspy-12266.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-formuladesk-formulaspy-12266.html
</guid><description>
FormulaDesk FormulaSpy is an Excel add-on that makes Excel formulas easy to understand, easy to test, easy to troubleshoot, and easy to repair. It provides a horizontal view that shows the results of each part of the formula to see how the results are calculated. You can also expand and collapse formula sections by clicking the green results bar. Additionally, you can use FormulaSpy to discover the cells the formula uses, access those cells and view their formulas, then dig deeper into...
</description></item><item><title>Download xplorer2 Professional / Ultimate 6.3.0.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 19 Feb 2026 00:37:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xplorer2-ultimate-1024.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xplorer2-ultimate-1024.html
</guid><description>
Xplorer2 Ultimate is software, file manager replaces Windows explorer traditional with more advanced functions and flexibility. Xplorer2 Ultimate give the user the extension name space, such as FTP, zipprinters, webprinters, v. v. the model browser, find the ratio of good up large folders with thousands of files. Software, quick read, providing image filters and a variety of selection mechanism that allows you to manage your files effectively.
Xplorer2 Ultimate - file Management,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Elasticsearch Enterprise 9.3.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 19 Feb 2026 00:34:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-elasticsearch-enterprise-12537.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-elasticsearch-enterprise-12537.html
</guid><description>
Elasticsearch Enterprise is a suite of products and services designed to enhance the search capabilities of applications and websites, primarily through the use of Elastic Enterprise Search and Elastic Cloud Enterprise (ECE). These tools provide advanced features to manage and optimize search functionality across different platforms.
Features
	Elastic Search AI Platform: Get relevant results at unprecedented speed with open and flexible enterprise solutions. Accelerate business...
</description></item><item><title>Download Helium Music Manager Premium 18.0.687</title><pubDate> Thu, 19 Feb 2026 00:33:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-helium-music-manager-premium-164.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-helium-music-manager-premium-164.html
</guid><description>
Helium Music Manager is a music manager that can rip, tag, play, browse, search, rename, burn and synchronize your music with the mobile. You can control your music collection with Helium Music Manager. Stop using time looking for the file on your computer or looking through CDS, vinyl records and tapes - instead, simply enjoy and explore your music! Helium Music Manager can replace the ripper, the player, tag editor and related software to audio your other.
Helium Music Manager...
</description></item><item><title>Download Imagine 2.5.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 19 Feb 2026 00:31:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-imagine-7369.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-imagine-7369.html
</guid><description>
Imagine is an application that allows you to view images and animations in a variety of formats, including JPG, BMP, PNG and GIF. With Imagine you can view file properties and EXIF ​​information, copy, move, delete and rename images. Additionally, you can also flip, resize and rotate them, swap colors, set transparency levels, import, export, and edit palettes, and change color depth.
Features of Imagine
	View and save image/animation files at lightning speed
	Multiple...
</description></item><item><title>Download VovSoft Image Combiner 2.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 19 Feb 2026 00:30:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-image-combiner-7477.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-image-combiner-7477.html
</guid><description>
VovSoft Image Combiner is a simple software tool that allows you to combine unlimited images into a single image, even if the source image is in different formats . You can combine multiple photos into one with the size and quality of the original with this easy-to-use software.
You can add images individually, drag and drop or select a folder containing them and let the application extract all compatible images. All images are displayed in a list, along with their width and height. It...
</description></item><item><title>Download Intel Wireless Bluetooth Driver (Windows 10/11) 24.20.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 19 Feb 2026 00:29:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intel-wireless-bluetooth-driver-5952.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intel-wireless-bluetooth-driver-5952.html
</guid><description>
Intel Wireless Bluetooth Driver is recommended for users, including family users and business customers with Intel Wireless Bluetooth technology.
Note: When you update the wireless application suite software package, it may not update the wireless controller controller if it includes the same driver as the previous release.
The internal products include:
	Intel ® Dual Band Wireless-AC 3165
	Intel ® Dual Band Wireless-AC 3168
	Intel ® Dual Band Wireless-AC 7265
	Intel ® Dual Band...
</description></item><item><title>Download WoodWorks 1.8.7.2298</title><pubDate> Thu, 19 Feb 2026 00:28:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-woodworks-12511.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-woodworks-12511.html
</guid><description>
With WoodWorks, you can optimize cuts in wood, glass, steel, paper, cardboard, plastic or other sheet materials quickly. Very simple operation (also via MS-Excel™ and LibreOffice Calc), taking into account every grain, using leftover pieces, determining the main cutting direction (vertical or horizontal, creating strips), gluing edges, intersecting XML interface (In/Out), print plans/cut labels (with components/work/edges) are just some of the features supported by...
</description></item><item><title>Download NanaZip 6.0.1630.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 18 Feb 2026 17:45:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nanazip-8074.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nanazip-8074.html
</guid><description>
NanaZip is an open source file archiver for the modern Windows experience, forked from the source code of the popular open source file archiver 7-Zip. NanaZip is considered an interesting alternative to WinRAR and WinZip. According to tests, NanaZip provides about 10% better compression ratio than WinRAR and WinZip.
Supported formats:
	Packing/unpacking: 7Z, ZIP, XZ, BZIP2, GZIP, TAR and WIM.
	Extract: RAR, AR, ARJ, CAB, CHM, CPIO, CramFS, DMG, EXT, FAT, GPT, HFS, IHEX, ISO, LZH,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Internet Download Manager (IDM) 6.42 Build 60</title><pubDate> Wed, 18 Feb 2026 17:43:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-inetnet-download-manager-161.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-inetnet-download-manager-161.html
</guid><description>
Internet Download Manager is the download acceleration software, the best download support now, it can help you speed up the download up to five times, continue and schedule downloads. The latest version of IDM adds the compatibility of Windows 10 and Windows 11, it has supported all current popular browsers such as Internet Explorer, Mozilla Firefox, Opera, Google Chrome, ..
Download IDM with the latest version on taiwebs.com making it easy to download and manage your downloaded files...
</description></item><item><title>Download JRiver Media Center 35.0.47</title><pubDate> Wed, 18 Feb 2026 17:42:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jriver-media-center-110.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jriver-media-center-110.html
</guid><description>
JRiver Media Center can help you strictly manage all your files media and enjoy them in a completely new way. Launching the application for the first time, users will be immediately impressed with the intuitive and eye-catching interface with many interesting features to explore. Most people who have used JRiver Media Center evaluate that the software interface design is youthful and modern.
The software for arranging cover art of music files is also extremely neat, especially Insert...
</description></item><item><title>Download IDM Retail 6.42 Build 60</title><pubDate> Wed, 18 Feb 2026 17:41:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-internet-download-manager-retail-3609.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-internet-download-manager-retail-3609.html
</guid><description>
IDM - Internet Download Manager Retail is a reliable utility and high efficiency will help you to increase your download speed and manage download at better. The program allows you to easily schedule, pause and resume downloads with a single click. Moreover, the application provides error resilience robust and can restart the download at the interrupted or broken. You can restore the download is interrupted due to network problems, lost connections, unexpected power outages, computer...
</description></item><item><title>Download Rufus 4.13 + Portable</title><pubDate> Wed, 18 Feb 2026 17:40:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rufus-2442.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rufus-2442.html
</guid><description>
Rufus support create a USB install Windows operating system like installing from a Windows installation disc often. Rufus offers to users the features from simple to lift the cap fit the needs as well as the ability of many objects. Rufus also has useful functions such as automatic identification, USB, display information about the connected USB.
A new version of a small program has been released that allows you to create and format the USB flash drive that can boot, it also can operate...
</description></item><item><title>Download Agisoft Metashape Professional 2.3.1 Build 22102</title><pubDate> Wed, 18 Feb 2026 17:39:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-agisoft-metashape-professional-1731.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-agisoft-metashape-professional-1731.html
</guid><description>
Agisoft Metashape (formerly PhotoScan) is a software product independently perform image processing and digital data creation, 3D space used in GIS applications, material cultural heritage and the production visual effects as well as the indirect measurement of the different subjects scale. Technical digital photography is deployed wisely is applied with the method of computer vision led to the system processor, smart auto, on the one hand, can be managed by a new person in the field of...
</description></item><item><title>Download K-Lite Codec Pack Update 19.5.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 18 Feb 2026 17:38:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-update-5145.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-update-5145.html
</guid><description>
K-Lite Codec Pack Update is the update of the set of codecs and related tools. Codec stands for Compressor-decompressor. Codec is necessary to encode and decode (play) audio and video. K-Lite Codec Pack Update is designed as a user-friendly solution with users to play all movie files your. With Codec Pack K-Lite, you can play 99% of all the movies found on your computer. A number of packages codec is not friendly with computers, as they tend to slow down Windows, break down multimedia...
</description></item><item><title>Download Picture Window Pro 8.0.551</title><pubDate> Wed, 18 Feb 2026 17:37:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-picture-window-pro-7452.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-picture-window-pro-7452.html
</guid><description>
Picture Window Pro is a powerful image editing tool designed for serious photographers with strict creative and quality standards. Its comprehensive set of photo editing and editing tools let you control and shape every aspect of your images.
Picture Window Pro 8 is a complete rewrite of Picture Window Pro 7. It features non-destructive image editing through a novel interface based on an image tree. It also fully supports large, high-resolution displays and can be used in dual monitor...
</description></item><item><title>Download TreeSize Free 4.8.1.610</title><pubDate> Wed, 18 Feb 2026 17:36:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-treesize-free-10656.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-treesize-free-10656.html
</guid><description>
TreeSize Free is a free disk space manager for Windows, it will show you the size of folders including its subfolders in a similar fashion like Explorer. Large folders can be identified at a glance thanks to the gradient bar displayed in the background. All scan results can be detailed at the file level and filters, e.g. for files of a certain type, can be applied.
Features of TreeSize Free
	Search space: clean up hard drive space
	Break down hard drive space usage to file level:...
</description></item></channel></rss>