<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 15:40:00 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 15:40:00 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Internet Download Manager (IDM) 6.42 Build 52</title><pubDate> Fri, 24 Oct 2025 16:49:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-inetnet-download-manager-161.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-inetnet-download-manager-161.html
</guid><description>
Internet Download Manager is the download acceleration software, the best download support now, it can help you speed up the download up to five times, continue and schedule downloads. The latest version of IDM adds the compatibility of Windows 10 and Windows 11, it has supported all current popular browsers such as Internet Explorer, Mozilla Firefox, Opera, Google Chrome, ..
Download IDM with the latest version on taiwebs.com making it easy to download and manage your downloaded files...
</description></item><item><title>Download 4K Video Downloader Plus 25.3.4</title><pubDate> Fri, 24 Oct 2025 16:48:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-video-downloader-617.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-video-downloader-617.html
</guid><description>
4K Video Downloader Plus is software support downloads video, audio and subtitles from YouTube with high quality up to 4K. Download process video is very simple: just copy the video link from your browser and click Paste Url. Done! If you want that video on your iPad, iPhone or other device, we have protected you.
The feature on 4K Video Downloader Plus
	Download entire playlists and channels from YouTube and save them in MP4, MKV, M4A, MP3, FLV, 3G, create a file .m3u for...
</description></item><item><title>Download IDM Retail 6.42 Build 52</title><pubDate> Fri, 24 Oct 2025 16:48:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-internet-download-manager-retail-3609.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-internet-download-manager-retail-3609.html
</guid><description>
IDM - Internet Download Manager Retail is a reliable utility and high efficiency will help you to increase your download speed and manage download at better. The program allows you to easily schedule, pause and resume downloads with a single click. Moreover, the application provides error resilience robust and can restart the download at the interrupted or broken. You can restore the download is interrupted due to network problems, lost connections, unexpected power outages, computer...
</description></item><item><title>Download Irix HDR Pro 2.3.52</title><pubDate> Fri, 24 Oct 2025 16:47:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-irix-hdr-pro-10653.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-irix-hdr-pro-10653.html
</guid><description>
Irix HDR Pro is an AI-powered photo editing application for Windows, it is available on Microsoft Store. This program has tons of professional HDR photo editing features including Sky Replacement, Face Sculpting &amp;amp; body, over 200 presets &amp;amp; AI powered tool' and is a Photo Editor in the category of photo &amp;amp; Graphics. It delivers true-to-life HDR photo editing, providing one-click edits for a full-scale professional editing toolkit.
Features of Irix HDR Pro
	Sky Replacement...
</description></item><item><title>Download 4K YouTube to MP3 25.3.4</title><pubDate> Fri, 24 Oct 2025 16:46:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-youtube-to-mp3-622.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-youtube-to-mp3-622.html
</guid><description>
4K YouTube to MP3 is a software to convert video youtube to mp3 quickly and easily by the manipulation drag-and-drop simple. With 4K YouTube to MP3 you just drag and drop the link to the favorite songs of you and get the MP3 files to your computer, as easy as that. Transfer songs directly to iPod, iPhone and iPad everywhere you go. No install annoying and complex to solve, just a clean interface, user friendly and functional.
When using 4K YouTube to MP3, users will get the playlists,...
</description></item><item><title>Download ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro 15.25.1023</title><pubDate> Fri, 24 Oct 2025 16:46:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-videotube-downloader-pro-1276.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-videotube-downloader-pro-1276.html
</guid><description>
ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro is the professional version support download videos and playlists from YouTube, videos from Dailymotion, BBC iPlayer, ITV Player, ABC,  FOX,CBS.com Vimeo, Prosieben, Metacafe, Blip.tv CBC.ca many more video sites. After the video is downloaded, you can convert them to the formats compatible with iPad, iPhone, iPod, MPEG-4, H. 264, MP3, AC3.
ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro - Download videos on Youtube
This is one of the software download the most...
</description></item><item><title>Download Secret Video Downloader 1.0.5</title><pubDate> Fri, 24 Oct 2025 16:45:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secret-video-downloader-13775.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secret-video-downloader-13775.html
</guid><description>
Secret Video Downloader is a free application designed to facilitate easy video downloading from various websites. It leverages the yt-dlp command line program to efficiently grab video content, allowing users to save videos in the highest quality available without complicated installation or configuration. The tool has a minimalist interface focused on simplicity: the user pastes the video URL into the built-in browser, clicks the Download button, and the video is added to the download...
</description></item><item><title>Download Kalmuri 4.1.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 24 Oct 2025 16:45:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kalmuri-12521.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kalmuri-12521.html
</guid><description>
Kalmuri provides one of the simplest means of recording screen activity, working as both a snapshot utility and a screen recorder. It requires no installation and is ready to go at any time, waiting for your action quietly in the tray area, thus not disturbing your work.
Features of Kalmuri
	Supports video recording (specify entire screen and area)
	Entire screen, active program, window control, application area
	Supports PNG, JPG, BMP, GIF, MP4 file formats
	Supports saving documents...
</description></item><item><title>Download By Click Downloader 2.4.27</title><pubDate> Fri, 24 Oct 2025 16:44:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-by-click-premium-193.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-by-click-premium-193.html
</guid><description>
YouTube By Click Premium is a high quality powerful video downloader including YouTube downloader, YouTube Converter, YouTube Chrome Downloader, Facebook Video Downloader, Downloader Vimeo, Dailymotion Downloader and supports many other video sites.
YouTube By Click
YouTube By Click Features
	YouTube by Click can download and convert files to MP3, MP4, FLV, AVI, WMV, 3GP, WAV and WEBM formats.
	Download all supported qualities, including HD.
	YouTube By Click downloads entire YouTube...
</description></item><item><title>Download Irix HDR Classic Pro 2.3.52</title><pubDate> Fri, 24 Oct 2025 16:44:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-irix-hdr-classic-pro-10652.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-irix-hdr-classic-pro-10652.html
</guid><description>
Irix HDR Classic Pro is an AI-powered photo editor that delivers true-to-life HDR photo editing, providing one-click edits to the editing toolkit professional at full scale with a highly cognitive user interface (UI).
Main features:
	Sky replacement (SkyXpress): replaces the sky and imports weather. Import custom skies and merge, blend, and integrate with your images for a natural look with AI Edge Detect.
	Presets &amp;amp; Filters: 200+ social media optimized presets with just one tap...
</description></item><item><title>Download Unicodia 3.0.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 24 Oct 2025 16:43:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-unicodia-8521.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-unicodia-8521.html
</guid><description>
Unicodia is free, open source software that can be used as an alternative character map for your Windows machine. The interface contains everything you need, allowing you to easily cycle through all the available ASCII symbols and copy them to the clipboard. Uncicodia is a great alternative to your standard Unicode characters and is filled with symbols/characters that make it useful for a number of different uses.
Features of Unicodia
	In Windows 10/11 — all characters of Unicode 15...
</description></item><item><title>Download AnyTrans for iOS 8.9.13.20251023</title><pubDate> Fri, 24 Oct 2025 16:43:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anytrans-for-ios-755.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anytrans-for-ios-755.html
</guid><description>
AnyTrans for iOS is content manager essential fully managed iPhone, Android and content of your cloud. Including all mobile devices, all cloud drives from your iPhone, iPad, iPod touch to phones and tablets. From local disk to cloud storage. AnyTrans has protected them all, providing you convenient management for all data and your files, regardless of whether they are stored where.
AnyTrans is the one stop solution to meet all the management needs of your data. For the first time, you can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Secret Disk Pro 2025 v314</title><pubDate> Fri, 24 Oct 2025 16:42:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secret-disk-pro-933.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secret-disk-pro-933.html
</guid><description>
Secret Disk Pro 4 is a software to create a virtual disk can be hidden and password protected to keep your data private and safe. You can store any file and folder on the disk. Disc secret works like a hard disk typically, and is compatible with any any other program that you have installed. You can have more than one disk secret, and you can also choose disk letter.
Secret Disk Pro 4 - Create and secure drive
Secret Disk does not encrypt any files, it just limits access to your files...
</description></item><item><title>Download Gilisoft DRM Protection 9.1.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 24 Oct 2025 16:41:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-video-drm-protection-5260.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-video-drm-protection-5260.html
</guid><description>
Gilisoft Video DRM Protection is software that helps you can protect your videos and the E-Learning content to another by secure, encrypted the files, your content and distribute them to the target audience authorized of you. Very easy to make video / sound / pictures of you can't see are for anyone except those you allow. Gilisoft Video DRM Protection can encrypt and pack video &amp;amp; codec &amp;amp; player into exe.
Gilisoft Video DRM Protection can easily encode almost any kind of Video...
</description></item><item><title>Download FurMark 2.10.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 24 Oct 2025 16:40:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-furmark-1718.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-furmark-1718.html
</guid><description>
FurMark is free software to help check the operation of the computer graphics card at the same time can emulator the situation, unplanned incidents of the CPU, the video card to you have how to handle best. FurMark allows you to set resolutions that card check will pass directly, you can perform both in full-screen mode and window, there are many parameters smoothing, in general, have enough parameters, you just need to artfully place them and you can immediately proceed to check out. If...
</description></item><item><title>Download ThinkAutomation Studio Professional 5.1.1094.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 24 Oct 2025 16:39:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thinkautomation-studio-professional-9635.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thinkautomation-studio-professional-9635.html
</guid><description>
ThinkAutomation Studio Professional is software that automates on-premises and cloud-based business processes to cut costs and save time. Automate incoming communication channels, monitor databases, react to incoming webhooks, web forms and chat bots. Handles documents, attachments, local files, and other message sources.
Parse and extract data from incoming messages and take actions in business processes, such as outbound communications, updating on-premises and cloud databases,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Zoner Photo Studio X 19.2509.2.661</title><pubDate> Fri, 24 Oct 2025 16:39:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zoner-photo-studio-x-95.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zoner-photo-studio-x-95.html
</guid><description>
Zoner Photo Studio X Pro helps you to control your photos. Zoner Photo Studio is a complete toolbox for managing and processing digital photos. Get photos from your camera, organize your archive, and edit and share your photos - never been easier! Zoner Photo Studio is useful for beginners, advanced users and photographers with experience, who can choose one of four different variations. Zoner Photo Studio is made for every user of digital cameras, scanners, and mobile devices. It contains...
</description></item><item><title>Download OEM Recovery Partition Creator 6.1.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 24 Oct 2025 16:37:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oem-recovery-partition-creator-6883.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oem-recovery-partition-creator-6883.html
</guid><description>
OEM Recovery Partition Creator for advanced users can clone your partition and bootable rescue media to restore your computer to its original state . The idea behind the app is to be able to create a factory reset just like a factory reset with Dell, HP and others. However, if you are not an advanced user, and possibly even if you are at it, you may not know where to start or how to use the program. The document is very large and can easily be replaced with a graphical user...
</description></item><item><title>Download O&amp;amp;O Defrag Pro 30.0.1073</title><pubDate> Fri, 24 Oct 2025 16:36:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-o-o-defrag-pro-149.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-o-o-defrag-pro-149.html
</guid><description>
O&amp;amp;O Defrag Pro is the professional software has the ability to defragment the hard disk and can work with the file system different from FAT / 32 to NTFS / 5, and support for the different arrays Volume / Stripe Sets. You can also set the schedule which O &amp;amp; O Defrag will be booted and perform a number of manipulation certain. Regular defragmentation of the disk partition optimized performance of your computer. The user interface is very easy to use. It has a ribbon bar displays all...
</description></item><item><title>Download O&amp;amp;O Defrag Server 30.0.1073</title><pubDate> Fri, 24 Oct 2025 16:36:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-defrag-server-2521.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-defrag-server-2521.html
</guid><description>
O&amp;amp;O Defrag Server professional software has the ability to defragment the hard disk and can work with the file system different from FAT / 32 to NTFS / 5, and support for the different arrays Volume / Stripe Sets. You can also set the schedule which O &amp;amp; O Defrag will be booted and perform a number of manipulation certain. Regular defragmentation of the disk partition optimized performance of your computer. The user interface is very easy to use. It has a ribbon bar displays all the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft PowerToys for Windows 10/11 0.95.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 24 Oct 2025 16:36:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-powertoys-for-windows-6014.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-powertoys-for-windows-6014.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft PowerToys is a user-proficiency set to adjust and streamline their Windows experience for higher productivity. Inspired by Windows 95's PowerToys project, this reboot provides users with proficiency in ways to exploit the more efficient Windows 10 and customisable processes it provides for each work process.
Utility of Microsoft PowerToys
	FancyZones is a window manager that allows you to easily create complex windows layout and quickly locate windows in those layout.
	Image...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDFsam -PDF Split and Merge 5.4.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 24 Oct 2025 16:29:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-split-and-merge-2337.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-split-and-merge-2337.html
</guid><description>
PDF Split and Merge is free software that makes it easy to split PDF files into smaller files or merge them all into one complete PDF file. PDF Split and Merge is considered to be one of the best PDF file merging software available today, the special thing about this PDF file merge software is that it is completely free, this is one of the reasons that make up the attraction of this software.
PDF Split and Merge - Split and merge PDF 
This is a great alternative to the famous ARTS PDF...
</description></item><item><title>Download ToneBoosters Plugin Bundle 2.1.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 24 Oct 2025 16:27:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-toneboosters-plugin-bundle-3675.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-toneboosters-plugin-bundle-3675.html
</guid><description>
ToneBoosters Plugin Bundle is a package tool sound is to combine the digital signal processing advanced and deployed multi-platform is optimized with the easy to use interface to optimize workflow of you. We combine the digital signal processing advanced and highly optimized deployment platform interface with simple-to-use to optimize your work.
ToneBoosters Plugin Bundle - audio tools
ToneBoosters Plugin Bundle includes:
	Barricade: True-peak mastering limiter.
	BitJuggler: The...
</description></item><item><title>Download Plasticity CAD 2025.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 24 Oct 2025 13:42:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-plasticity-cad-for-artists-11178.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-plasticity-cad-for-artists-11178.html
</guid><description>
With a workflow optimized for creativity, amazing fillets and the most advanced modeling tools, Plasticity is the perfect choice for those who need the best. Plasticity CAD for artists is the ultimate tool for creative professionals in video games, product design and more. It provides all the power of NURBS modeling combined with the best workflow improvements from polygon modeling software. This unique combination gives you the flexibility and creativity you need to turn your ideas into...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ahoge for Maya 0.9.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 24 Oct 2025 13:35:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ahoge-for-maya-14250.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ahoge-for-maya-14250.html
</guid><description>
Ahoge for Maya is a plugin designed to simplify the creation of hair, including both stylized and complex styles commonly found in anime, manga, and games. It supports Autodesk Maya versions 2023 to 2026 on Windows and works with the Arnold renderer. The plugin allows for converting polygons to hair, editing NURBS surfaces for hair, creating hair surface effects, and detailing various hair elements such as tufts and eyelashes. The plugin also has tools for hair mesh shaping and supports...
</description></item></channel></rss>