<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 20:03:00 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 20:03:00 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download FolderSync Pro 4.8.0 build 2020100186</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 22:59:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-foldersync-pro-8221.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-foldersync-pro-8221.html
</guid><description>
FolderSync Pro allows users to synchronize files and folders between their mobile devices and various cloud storage services, such as Dropbox, Google Drive and OneDrive. Back up music, pictures, and other important files from your phone to your cloud storage, or vice versa. It has never been easier. Automation support with Tasker and similar programs allows granular control over your synchronization process.
FolderSync contains a full file manager, allowing you to manage your files...
</description></item><item><title>Download ProShot 8.32.1.3 build 536</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 22:59:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-proshot-8195.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-proshot-8195.html
</guid><description>
ProShot is a camera app for Android devices that offers advanced manual controls for photography enthusiasts. It allows users to manually adjust settings such as shutter speed, ISO, white balance, and focus. It also offers a level of integration, a powerful time-lapse mode, and many other features for advanced photography. It's designed for advanced users who want more control over their photos than the default camera app offers.
Camera features of ProShot
	Auto, Program, Manual and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Circuit Route Planner 3.58.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 22:59:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-circuit-route-planner-11536.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-circuit-route-planner-11536.html
</guid><description>
Easy-to-use multi-stop route planning and delivery app downloaded by over 10 million drivers! Deliver more packages and complete your routes faster. Save time, money and gas with Circuit Route Planner. Adding a stop to a route takes just a few seconds. One click optimizes all your deliveries and automatically maps out the fastest routes. Avoid traffic congestion, find packages faster and deliver more efficiently.
Circuit Route Planner Features
	Easily find and add stops with your...
</description></item><item><title>Download ezPDF Reader PDF Annotate Form 2.7.1.12</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 22:58:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ezpdf-reader-pdf-annotate-form-9766.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ezpdf-reader-pdf-annotate-form-9766.html
</guid><description>
ezPDF Reader is the best-selling, best-rated, and most-reviewed PDF viewer, annotator, form filler, and paperless solution and frame-animated multimedia PDF viewer. Share your sensitive documents such as contracts, invoices and literary works with ezPDF DRM Service.
Features of ezPDF Reader PDF Annotation Form
Viewing PDF
	Support changing reading direction, page layout settings
	Support Text Search, Scrolling Direction, Table of Contents, Hyperlinks, Lists (Annotations,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Map My Run GPS Running Tracker 25.10.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 22:58:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-map-my-run-by-under-armour-8145.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-map-my-run-by-under-armour-8145.html
</guid><description>
Map My Run by Under Armor is a mobile app that allows users to track their running, walking, and other outdoor activities using GPS. The app is available to download from the Google Play Store and Apple App Store. It was developed by Under Armour, a company specializing in sports apparel and equipment. In addition to tracking workouts, the app also provides users with tools to analyze performance and set goals.
Features of Map My Run by Under Armor APK
	GPS tracking: The app uses GPS...
</description></item><item><title>Download Network Monitor Mini Pro 1.0.281</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 22:57:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-network-monitor-mini-pro-10154.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-network-monitor-mini-pro-10154.html
</guid><description>
Android doesn't show network connection statistics on the screen. You don't know the current internet bandwidth used for uploading and downloading. Network Monitor Mini Pro is a mini network monitor for your phone. It tracks the upload and download speed per second. It will always be in the corner of your phone screen. You can place the indicator in any corner of the screen, customize the color and transparency of the indicator. This way, you can enjoy surfing the internet, just like...
</description></item><item><title>Download Genius Scan Enterprise 7.33.0 build 7028</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 22:56:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-genius-scan-enterprise-8561.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-genius-scan-enterprise-8561.html
</guid><description>
Genius Scan Enterprise: Quickly scan your paper documents on the go and export them as multi-page PDF files. Place any document in front of your device's camera: our scanner app automatically recognizes the paper on the background, crops it and cleans the result. You get sharp, easy-to-read scans. Batch scanning allows you to scan dozens of pages in just a few seconds. Powerful tools help you organize, share or archive your documents.
Features of Genius Scan Enterprise for...
</description></item><item><title>Download Reminder Pro 4.0.9</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 22:56:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-reminder-pro-8695.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-reminder-pro-8695.html
</guid><description>
Are you looking for a simple pop-up reminder app? Do you want to create reminders for one-time and recurring tasks? Get reminders and increase your productivity. Never forget an important task again! Finally, a simple and easy way to set reminders or deadline notifications. This hourly reminder app gets straight to the point. Set notifications to remind you of all your tasks, chores, and to-do list items, then sit back and clear your head.
No unnecessary or complicated features....
</description></item><item><title>Download Meteoblue weather &amp;amp; maps vCirrus Uncinus 2.12.01</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 22:56:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-meteoblue-weather-maps-vcirrus-uncinus-10132.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-meteoblue-weather-maps-vcirrus-uncinus-10132.html
</guid><description>
Meteoblue displays highly accurate weather forecasts combined with a beautiful, simple and easy-to-use design. The weather forecast for any place on Earth can be requested easily and comfortably.
Features of Meteoblue vCirrus Uncinus Weather &amp;amp; Maps
	Weather forecast for any point on land or sea.
	Location search with over 6 million locations: search for a location name, postal code or coordinates, or let the app find your current location using the GPS module.
	3 different widgets...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sleep Monitor: Sleep Tracker 2.9.24</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 22:55:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sleep-monitor-sleep-tracker-11480.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sleep-monitor-sleep-tracker-11480.html
</guid><description>
Sleep Monitor helps you track and record detailed sleep cycles. Sleep Monitor also has a smart alarm clock to remind you to sleep early at night and wake you gently in the morning. In addition, Sleep Monitor also provides relaxing, soothing music to help you sleep better.
New feature: Write notes about sleep
	Take brief notes about your sleep. Write down anything you want so you will never forget them.
Record snoring or talking in your dreams
	The sleep tracker will record snoring...
</description></item><item><title>Download Reverso Translate and Learn 14.9.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 22:55:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-reverso-translate-and-learn-8356.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-reverso-translate-and-learn-8356.html
</guid><description>
Reverso is a comprehensive tool that helps you get high-quality translations and continuously improve your language skills. The best part about the Reverso app? It is available for free. Teachers or translators, students or business professionals, beginners or advanced learners use Reverso to enrich their vocabulary and read, write and speak more accurately and confidently.
Download the Reverso app and you'll have millions of words and expressions at your fingertips, with their...
</description></item><item><title>Download Today Weather: Radar &amp;amp; Widgets 2.4.0-12</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 22:54:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-today-weather-alerts-widgets-8915.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-today-weather-alerts-widgets-8915.html
</guid><description>
Weather Today is a beautiful and easy-to-use weather app that provides the world's most accurate local weather forecasts.
Features of Weather Today for Android
	Displays clear, easy-to-understand weather forecasts.
	Enjoy every moment you open the app with thousands of beautiful photos corresponding to the weather and day.
	Prepare for any situation with 24/7 weather forecasts and chance of rain.
	Protect your health with air quality, UV index and pollen count.
	Capture beautiful...
</description></item><item><title>Download Lifesum: AI Calorie Tracker 19.6.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 22:54:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-lifesum-healthy-eating-diet-8257.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-lifesum-healthy-eating-diet-8257.html
</guid><description>
Lifesum is a health and fitness app that helps users track their diet and exercise. The app allows users to set personalized health goals, such as losing weight or building muscle, and offers suggestions for healthy meals and snacks based on the goals there. Users can also track their water intake, log their workouts, and track their progress over time.
Some key features include:
	Personalized health goals: Users can set specific goals, such as losing weight or building muscle, and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Edge Gestures 1.15.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 22:54:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-edge-gestures-8158.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-edge-gestures-8158.html
</guid><description>
Edge Gestures is an Android app that lets you use gestures to perform various actions on your device. Now you can do something quickly with just a simple gesture on the edge of the screen. It supports tap, double-tap, press and hold, swipe from the edge, and drag and slide.
To use Edge Gestures, you need to install the app on your Android device and then enable the feature in the app's settings. Once you set up Edge Gestures, you can use gestures to navigate your device and perform...
</description></item><item><title>Download Multi Calculator 1.9.4 build 475</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 22:52:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-multi-calculator-9018.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-multi-calculator-9018.html
</guid><description>
A general-purpose calculator is a type of calculator that allows users to perform many types of calculations in a single application. It often includes features like basic arithmetic operations, scientific functions, unit conversions, currency conversions, etc.
Universal Calculator apps are typically available for smartphones and other mobile devices as well as for desktop computers. They can be useful for many users, including students, professionals, and anyone who needs to perform...
</description></item><item><title>Download Malloc Privacy &amp;amp; Security VPN 2025.11.101</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 22:52:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-malloc-privacy-security-vpn-8576.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-malloc-privacy-security-vpn-8576.html
</guid><description>
Malloc Privacy &amp;amp; Security VPN is a virtual private network (VPN) service to protect your privacy and security online. VPNs encrypt your Internet traffic and route it through a server in another location, making it more difficult for third-party websites and services to track your online activity and steal your personal information.
Malloc Privacy &amp;amp; Security VPN is a useful tool for anyone who wants to protect their privacy and security online, whether they are browsing the web,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Moviebase: Movies &amp;amp; TV Guide 5.5.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 22:51:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-moviebase-track-tv-shows-8175.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-moviebase-track-tv-shows-8175.html
</guid><description>
Are you looking for a useful movie finder and movie tracker app to help you find movie ratings, movie reviews, movie recommendations, movie trailers and more? Try Moviebase – Movie Manager. Moviebase is the most popular movie finder and movie tracker app where you can find movies, series, seasons, episodes. Movie reviews, movie trailers, movie descriptions and actors from the largest community database TMDB.
Explore the world of movies and series from Movie Tracker
	Explore a huge...
</description></item><item><title>Download Easy Notes - Note Taking Apps 1.3.29.1029</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 22:51:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-easy-notes-notebook-notepad-8388.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-easy-notes-notebook-notepad-8388.html
</guid><description>
Easy Notes - Great note taking app, Notepad, Notebook, Free Notes is a free easy to use note taking app for notes app. With this easy notebook and notepad app, take quick notes with colorful backgrounds and checklists to organize notes and tasks easily. Use this aesthetic note taker and note taker to add photos or audio to your notes. Easy Notes is a useful notebook and note-taking app for taking notes and organizing work.
Features of Easy Notes - Notebook, Notepad
	Free Notepad and...
</description></item><item><title>Download FBReader Premium 3.8.21</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 22:51:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-fbreader-premium-8512.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-fbreader-premium-8512.html
</guid><description>
FBReader Premium is an e-book reading application for mobile devices. It provides a convenient way to read e-books on your phone or tablet and offers several features to enhance your reading experience. FBReader supports synchronization of your library and/or reading locations with the FBReader book network (https://books.fbreader.org/), a cloud service based on Google Drive™. Sync is disabled by default; To enable and configure it, use the options dialog.
This reader also includes a...
</description></item><item><title>Download Six Pack Abs in 30 Days 3.13</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 22:51:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-abs-in-30-days-at-home-13250.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-abs-in-30-days-at-home-13250.html
</guid><description>
Do you dream of toned abs and six-pack abs but don't have time to go to the gym? Then this is your personal fitness trainer right in your pocket!
Why choose "Abs in 30 Days at Home"?
	Guaranteed workout plans developed by professional fitness trainers to ensure you see initial changes within a month!
	No gym or equipment required! Use only your body weight – train anytime, anywhere, saving time and money.
	Pre-designed 30-day workout plans, step-by-step intensity increases, voice...
</description></item><item><title>Download BetterSleep: Sleep tracker 25.20</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 22:50:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-bettersleep-sleep-tracker-8274.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-bettersleep-sleep-tracker-8274.html
</guid><description>
BetterSleep is a sleep tracking app that helps users track and improve their sleeping habits. The app uses the phone's sensors to track movement and sounds during sleep, then provides users with detailed sleep reports and analysis. It also includes features such as a sleep log, smart alarm, and white noise generation to help users fall asleep and wake up more refreshed. Additionally, BetterSleep allows users to set sleep goals, track their progress, and receive personalized...
</description></item><item><title>Download Listen Audiobook Player 5.3.5</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 22:50:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-listen-audiobook-player-8511.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-listen-audiobook-player-8511.html
</guid><description>
Listen Audiobook Player is a mobile app for playing audiobooks on your phone or tablet. It lets you play, pause, rewind, and fast-forward audiobooks with ease, while also providing a convenient way to track your listening progress.
Some key features of Listen Audiobook Player include:
	Library Management: Allows you to store and organize your audiobooks in a virtual library for easy access.
	Bookmark: Automatically saves your listening position so you can pick up where you left...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sleep as Android: Smart alarm 20251024 Final</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 22:50:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sleep-as-android-smart-alarm-8661.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sleep-as-android-smart-alarm-8661.html
</guid><description>
Sleep as Android is an alarm clock and sleep tracking app for Android devices. The app uses your phone's accelerometer to track your movements and detect when you're in deep sleep, light sleep, or awake. Based on this information, Sleep as Android gives you detailed sleep statistics, including total sleep time, efficiency, and sleep cycle graphs.
Sleep mode features like Android
	Gentle alarm clock: The app uses increasing volume and natural sounds to gently wake you at the optimal...
</description></item><item><title>Download Lose Weight at Home in 30 Days 3.14</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 22:49:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-lose-weight-in-30-days-8632.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-lose-weight-in-30-days-8632.html
</guid><description>
Lose Weight in 30 Days is a fitness app for Android and iOS Devices that Helps Users Lose Weight and Ach now. The App provides Users with a comprehensive and personalized weight-loss plan, Complete with workout routines and diet Recommendations.
The Workout Plan is based on Tabata. Tabata is a form of high-cintensity interval training (hiit)
	Workout Hard for 20 seconds
	Rest for 10 seconds
	Repeat
Features of Lose Weight in 30 Days for Android
	30-Day Workout Plans for Weight...
</description></item><item><title>Download My Dictionary - polyglot Pro 10.7</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 22:49:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-my-dictionary-polyglot-pro-8513.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-my-dictionary-polyglot-pro-8513.html
</guid><description>
My Dictionary - Polyglot is a mobile dictionary application that provides translations between many languages. It is designed for people who speak several languages ​​or are learning a new language.
A unique program for memorizing words will help you do it. The main success of learning a foreign language consists in the fastest addition of vocabulary: you should repeat words many times. For this purpose, people often use notepads, which is not always convenient.
Features of my...
</description></item></channel></rss>