<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 11:36:58 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 11:36:58 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Yandex Browser 25.8.0.1908</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 12:35:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yandex-browser-3242.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yandex-browser-3242.html
</guid><description>
Yandex Browser is a browser based free Chrome features a minimalist interface fast with the unique features such as hidden Mode. It take Chrome to a higher level begin with home search Tile of it and background of your choice, including animated backgrounds, make this interface become familiar with users of Windows 10. Yandex calls this a Tableau. Let's say, we have to search for it. I think the most suitable is a description or graphical representation. People like the looks in addition...
</description></item><item><title>Download Soda PDF Desktop Pro 14.0.510.23074</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 00:44:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-soda-pdf-home-808.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-soda-pdf-home-808.html
</guid><description>
Soda PDF Pro  is intuitive PDF software that helps you to easily process and create PDF files from more than 300 different formats. Soda PDF is built to help you power through any PDF task. Convert to a wide range of file types. Edit the content of your document. Create custom forms. Annotate your files. Send and track contracts for electronic signatures.
Soda PDF Pro: Create PDF file
Features of Soda PDF Pro
	Read your PDFs and digital publications in 3D with unique page-turning...
</description></item><item><title>Download HEU KMS Activator 63.2.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 00:44:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-heu-kms-activator-7529.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-heu-kms-activator-7529.html
</guid><description>
HEU KMS Activator is a quick Windows and Office activator with multiple methods like Digital License, KMS38, OEM and KMS. This tool takes advantage of building a KMS server inside your system, so it can easily activate both Windows and Office.
In addition, it also supports Windows backup and restore, Change MS Office Edition, Key setting manually in case you purchased the original Key and more.
Features of HEU KMS Activator
	Digital Trigger &amp;amp; KMS
	Office uninstallation...
</description></item><item><title>Download Any Video Downloader Pro 9.5.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 00:43:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-video-downloader-pro-3731.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-video-downloader-pro-3731.html
</guid><description>
Any Video Downloader Pro is software support you can download video HD 720p, 1080p, 2K, 4K and 8K from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion, Vimeo, Metacafe and thousands of video sharing sites, other. It is a tool to speed up multi-threading can speed up your download faster up to 5 times. This helpful program support download at the same time. Any Video Downloader Pro lets you download multiple videos at the same time. Moreover, it allows you to pause and resume downloads if you need more...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cyberduck 9.2.3.43590</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 00:43:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberduck-2637.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberduck-2637.html
</guid><description>
Cyberduck is a browser, file open-source and the client transferred to the hosting account FTP, SFTP, WebDAV, Cloud Files, Google Docs and Amazon S3. In addition to file transfers it offers features account management includes installing ACL, version group S3 configuration, Akamai and CloudFront, and more.
In addition, the Cyberduck also helps you can create bookmarks to quickly access favorite locations, edit files remotely using the editor you choose, import bookmarks from popular...
</description></item><item><title>Download Systweak PDF Editor 1.0.0.8038</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 00:42:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-systweak-pdf-editor-11484.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-systweak-pdf-editor-11484.html
</guid><description>
Systweak PDF Editor is a fast and simple solution to edit, convert, sign, protect, compress PDF files and make scanned PDF files searchable and can choose. With Systweak PDF Editor, quickly convert your PDF files into a variety of editable formats. Converting PDF files to and from any MS Office files, images, ebooks, web pages, and other formats just got easier.
For working and editing PDF files, Systweak PDF editor offers many features and tools. Using them, you can mark text for...
</description></item><item><title>Download Thorium Reader 3.2.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 00:42:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thorium-reader-11878.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thorium-reader-11878.html
</guid><description>
Thorium Reader is open source ebook reading software designed to deliver a seamless and feature-rich reading experience. It supports various e-book formats, including EPUB, PDF, and CBZ, allowing users to read their favorite books, magazines, and comics from a single app.
Thorium Reader is a user-friendly, versatile ebook reader software designed to meet the needs of bookworms and digital readers. With a customizable interface, extensive format compatibility, accessibility features, and...
</description></item><item><title>Download BackupAssist 14.0.5</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 00:41:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-backupassist-4533.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-backupassist-4533.html
</guid><description>
BackupAssist is a software application that allows you to create backup for all file types, as well as recover and restore the item, follow the process is running and creating reports. BackupAssist is built for small and medium business is developing your. Select backup software Windows help to keep safe your data. Software backup storage to your server from the ruin. Never lose data again. Use BackupAssist to perform backups onsite and offsite to protect your server.
BackupAssist -...
</description></item><item><title>Download Room Arranger 10.2.0.730</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 00:41:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-room-arranger-3779.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-room-arranger-3779.html
</guid><description>
Room Arranger is a 3D application lets you easily plan for the room, office or his apartment just a few mouse clicks. The application comes with a simple interface will significantly simplify your work. You can draw many kinds of objects and items to create furniture of your own. This app also includes a library of object rich.
Software Room Arranger enables you to view your project in 3D form. You can also upload the 3D scene interact on your blog or your website. The application uses...
</description></item><item><title>Download HE - Hardware Read and Write Utility 1.25.08.19</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 00:39:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-he-hardware-read-and-write-utility-4287.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-he-hardware-read-and-write-utility-4287.html
</guid><description>
HE - Hardware Read and Write Utility is a powerful utility intended for hardware engineer, engineer, BIOS developer, driver, engineer, QA engineers, performance test engineers, diagnostic, etc., this utility access almost all the computer hardware, including PCI (PCI Express), index / Data, PCI, memory, index memory / Data space I / O, Index I / O / Data, Super I / O, DIMM SPD, CPU The registers MSR, screen, SMART, physical area of the hard drive identification data, ATA, dump tables ACPI...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Video Downloader 11.27</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 00:39:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-video-downloader-9636.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-video-downloader-9636.html
</guid><description>
YT Video Downloader is software used to easily and quickly download any video or audio content from any website in HD quality using video downloader online. Save videos from almost any website supported by a video downloader on your local hard drive. Media search is a convenient way to do this.
Features of YT Video Downloader
	Download videos from hundreds of video sites.
	Really increase your download speed by up to 500% or even more!
	Download 8K, 5K, 4K Ultra HD, 2K Quad HD, 1080p...
</description></item><item><title>Download FX Math Tools MultiDocs 25.08.19</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 00:38:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fx-draw-tools-1909.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fx-draw-tools-1909.html
</guid><description>
FX Draw Tools to provide an environment to draw high productivity is exclusively designed for math teachers. Quickly create editable, high quality diagrams for the quiz, test, worksheets, web pages, presentations and demonstrations. FX Sketch, free extension of FX Draw Tools, allows you to sketch diagrams math and to them automatically converted into the drawing of professional quality can be edited by the power of FX Draw. Efofex also provides for the registration FX Draw three bonus...
</description></item><item><title>Download JWIZARD Cleaner 1.7.0.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 00:38:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jwizard-cleaner-12853.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jwizard-cleaner-12853.html
</guid><description>
Effective Windows cleaning software to remove unnecessary files from your PC. JWIZARD Cleaner for Windows quickly frees up disk space and keeps your system in an optimal state, ensuring your PC runs stably and efficiently. This application is designed to provide you with a comprehensive tool to analyze and optimize your PC by performing a comprehensive cleanup or a more detailed cleanup, targeting specific areas such as system, browser, mail, etc.
Features of JWIZARD Cleaner
	Clean...
</description></item><item><title>Download Waterfox 6.6.0 / 2022.11</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 00:37:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-waterfox-114.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-waterfox-114.html
</guid><description>
Waterfox is a 64-bit version of the foundation Firefox was built and the compiler Intel is optimized for speed and performance on Windows systems.Waterfox does not add any additional features or bling, in fact, it will automatically import all the gadgets and install is have of you, so you will feel like at home when you run it the first time.All the add-on your Firefox will work with Waterfox, however, only support the plug-in more 64-bit, is includes Adobe Flash, Oracle Java and...
</description></item><item><title>Download 4KSoftware 4K Downloader 5.17</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 00:37:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-downloader-3858.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-downloader-3858.html
</guid><description>
4K Downloader is a Windows application small but powerful to download and convert video in 4K and 8K Ultra HD from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion and thousands of other video-based websites. It speeds up your download by up to 5 times. Consider that most smart phones, TVS, computers, and tablets all support the high definition format, don't be surprised when many users want to enjoy quality content on their device. 4K Downloader is a lightweight software designed to help you grab videos...
</description></item><item><title>Download HTML Compiler 2025.16</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 00:37:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-html-compiler-2548.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-html-compiler-2548.html
</guid><description>
HTML Compiler is a program for Microsoft Windows (tm) allows you to put an entire HTML application (including HTML, CSS, JavaScript, images, etc.) into a Windows application independent can be executed like any other application window the application. HTML Compiler allows you to customize file real exam results by changing the icon of them and set some other options. For example, you can allow or not allow the ability to print the HTML pages, allow or disallow the text selection and many,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Clean Media Player 2025.8.19.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 00:35:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-clean-media-player-12416.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-clean-media-player-12416.html
</guid><description>
If you've ever been offended by profanity in a movie, chances are you'll want the censored version of the movie. However, until the director decides to release it, you still have the option of muting unwanted scenes or editing the subtitles manually, if you are able to do so. The application mutes and displays subtitles without offensive words and phrases. Customize the profanity filter to your preferences. Skip inappropriate scenes by selecting their start and end times.
Clean Media...
</description></item><item><title>Download Angry IP Scanner 3.9.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 00:35:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-angry-ip-scanner-2138.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-angry-ip-scanner-2138.html
</guid><description>
Angry IP Scanner can scan IP addresses in any range as well as any port of them. It is multi-platform and lightweight. Does not require any installation, it can be copied and used freely anywhere. Angry IP Scanner simply pings each IP address to check if it's alive or not, then optionally it is resolving the server name of it, determines the MAC address, scans ports, etc., the Amount of gathered data about each host can be extended by plugin.
Angry IP Scanner - Scan IP address
Scan...
</description></item><item><title>Download Internet Video Downloader 7.5</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 00:29:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hdapplications-hd-downloader-6041.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hdapplications-hd-downloader-6041.html
</guid><description>
Internet Video Downloader is a small tool designed to help you download video clips from YouTube, Dailymotion and many other similar sites with high quality that can easily run on smartphones, tablets or the latest Xbox devices. After the quick and simple installation process, you will be welcomed by a user-friendly interface without the ability to cause any problems for you.
Although you can set the app start to download immediately, but you can also create a download list that can be...
</description></item><item><title>Download Master Packager Pro 25.6.9358</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 00:29:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-master-packager-pro-7982.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-master-packager-pro-7982.html
</guid><description>
Master Packager Pro is an application packaging tool for creating and editing Microsoft Windows Installer (MSI) files and repackaging other installations to MSI format. Its job is to make application packaging easy, fast, accessible to everyone from freelancers, small companies, and application packaging businesses.
Features of Master Packager Pro
	Create MSI and MST files from scratch or modify the Vendor Microsoft Windows installer.
	Simple design made to be as user-friendly as...
</description></item><item><title>Download Robin YouTube Video Downloader Pro 6.16</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 00:28:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-video-downloader-pro-2828.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-video-downloader-pro-2828.html
</guid><description>
YouTube Video Downloader Pro is a Windows application professional to download and convert videos from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion and thousands of video sharing sites, other. It accelerates your download up to 5 times. YouTube Video Downloader Pro allows you to download multiple videos at the same time. It also allows you to pause, resume and cancel a download at any time.
YouTube Video Downloader Pro - Download online videos on social networks
Features of YouTube Video Downloader...
</description></item><item><title>Download App Builder 2025.23</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 00:28:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-app-builder-241.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-app-builder-241.html
</guid><description>
App Builder is a software application developer to help create and design apps, HTML5, web app, web app PWA on both platforms mobile and desktop. App Builder is professional software supports users to create the program HTML5 without writing code. It is very easy to use, suitable with all users who lack of professional knowledge in the field of programming and application design.
App Builder brings to 22 different themes that users can use to design for your app. You can choose 1 or a...
</description></item><item><title>Download TubeDownload Pro 6.29</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 00:27:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubedownload-pro-12035.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubedownload-pro-12035.html
</guid><description>
TubeDownload Pro is a professional Windows application for downloading your favorite videos from YouTube and hundreds of other video sites. TubeDownload Pro can increase download speed up to 500% or even more.
Features of TubeDownload Pro
	Download your favorite videos from YouTube and hundreds of other video sites.
	Increase download speed up to 500% or even more.
	Download 720p, 1080p, 2K, 4K and 8K HD videos from YouTube.
	Download entire playlists in just a few clicks.
	Download...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT-DL 11.5</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 00:27:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-dl-5876.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-dl-5876.html
</guid><description>
YT-DL is a small program to download videos from YouTube and other video sites. Our goal is to make the program as simple as its name.
The features of YT-DL
	Download the video from YouTube and other video sites
	Increase download speed up to 400%
	Download multiple videos at the same time
	Pause and continue to download at any time
	Preview video content while downloading
</description></item><item><title>Download FTPGetter Professional 5.97.0.291</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 00:27:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ftpgetter-professional-1550.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ftpgetter-professional-1550.html
</guid><description>
FTPGetter Professional is software that automates the uploading and downloading of files, allowing scheduling file transfer between your computer with the FTP server and SFTP remote. If you often access FTP / SFTP to sync files between local computer and remote PC, to update your website or upload images, webcam, FTPGetter will save you lots of time and effort.
FTPGetter Professional comes with emulator terminal integration, allowing you to connect and execute commands on remote server...
</description></item></channel></rss>