<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 14:19:08 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 14:19:08 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Visual Studio Code 1.109.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 16:27:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-visual-studio-code-3182.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-visual-studio-code-3182.html
</guid><description>
Visual Studio Code is the encryption tool of Microsoft has met most of the needs of the developer. Environment this encoding was introduced to compete with other products such as Sublime and Nodepad ++ . Microsoft, in its new product, has not been released in many years, has provided many features in a simple environment. In addition to the familiar with a dozen programming languages, the syntax and get to know coding language as soon as be encrypted and allows for syntax highlighting, it...
</description></item><item><title>Download Light Image Resizer 7.5.1.147</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 16:26:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-light-image-resizer-945.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-light-image-resizer-945.html
</guid><description>
Light Image Resizer or also known as VSO Image Resizer. This is a software support thumbnail resolution images or move images in your hard drive. Light Image Resizer helps people store photos and digital images on their PC and who want to resize, compress, convert, create copies, import or organize photos. Light Image Resizer is integrated into Windows Explorer, right-click on your pictures and start working on your photos.
Light Image Resizer - miniature high-resolution photos and sort...
</description></item><item><title>Download CyberLink PhotoDirector Ultra 2026 v17.1.1330.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 16:25:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-photodirector-ultra-129.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-photodirector-ultra-129.html
</guid><description>
Cyberlink PhotoDirector Ultra is known to be photo editing tools and videos with the effect is extremely rich, help you to change the style for the individual images or the videos of his favorite. This software integrated the 3D engine helps to speed up Video processing, which allows accessing the repository effect online and extract the Videos into the movies 3D Bru-ray, 3D AVCHD.
Cyberlink PhotoDirector Ultra to offer users a more professional tool to handle their images, remove...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sysinternals Suite 2026.2.4</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 16:25:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sysinternals-suite-1447.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sysinternals-suite-1447.html
</guid><description>
Sysinternals Suite is a software monitoring and control system helps to find and fix errors most impressive. The software includes more than seventy utilities aimed at overcoming the problem related to managing files and disks, network problems and security, as well as information about processes and systems. Because of this very rich, the analysis of each ministry will take a significant period of time and therefore, we decided to focus on the most popular.
Sysinternals Suite - Set of...
</description></item><item><title>Download RapidRAW 1.4.12</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 16:24:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rapidraw-13957.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rapidraw-13957.html
</guid><description>
RapidRAW is a modern, high-performance, open-source RAW photo editor, designed to deliver a fast and clean editing experience with a lightweight footprint (under 30MB). Built with performance and usability in mind, the software is aimed at photographers who want a simple, efficient, and fun workflow without compromising performance.
Key Features
	GPU-accelerated processing: Uses a custom WGSL shader to process all image adjustments on the GPU, allowing for smooth, responsive editing...
</description></item><item><title>Download O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Premium 22.4.1206</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 16:23:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-diskimage-server-4547.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-diskimage-server-4547.html
</guid><description>
O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Server is software that is specially designed for use in enterprise environments, the software allows users to backup all the files you want and keep them safe from any incident or disaster computer. O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Server comes with a variety of easy to use utility that allows users to backup entire partitions of the specific files from their PC, as well as recover the version previous data of them, all from a simple interface.
O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Server - data...
</description></item><item><title>Download UWPSpy 1.5</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 16:23:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-uwpspy-10357.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-uwpspy-10357.html
</guid><description>
UWPSpy is a testing tool for UWP and WinUI 3 applications. Seamlessly view and manipulate UI elements and their properties in real time.
It allows users to observe how changes affect the structure and functionality of their UWP app. This is beneficial for helping with user interface design tasks during application development. When you select specific properties, the associated elements will be highlighted and any changes will update in real time.
How to use:
	Run UWPSpy.exe and...
</description></item><item><title>Download VectorStyler 1.3.009</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 16:22:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vectorstyler-7917.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vectorstyler-7917.html
</guid><description>
VectorStyler provides a complete set of drawing, design and illustration tools needed for modern design. Create illustrations, logos, icons, drawings, typography, vector art for screen, print and web. With many new features, VectorStyler redefines and extends the tools available to illustrators and designers, improving the creation of complex illustrations and designs.
Shape effects can be used to adjust the shape of objects, create different distortions, or add detail to shapes. Shape...
</description></item><item><title>Download PlayerFab (Ultra HD Player) 7.0.5.5</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 16:22:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dvdfab-player-ultra-68.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dvdfab-player-ultra-68.html
</guid><description>
PlayerFab (DVDFab Player Ultra) is one of the best 4K UHD media players. The software plays DVD, Blu-ray, 4K Ultra HD Blu-ray and also supports online video. It supports native navigation menus, along with HDR10, and supports high-resolution audio output. PlayerFab supports watching videos of a variety of popular streaming platforms such as Amazon, Netflix, Tubi, Peacock, and more.
Video streaming in FHD 1080p video quality and high quality EAC3 audio quality is the prerequisite and...
</description></item><item><title>Download lessmsi 2.11.9</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 16:22:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lessmsi-12392.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lessmsi-12392.html
</guid><description>
Lessmsi (Less MSIerables) is a free and portable application that allows users to view and extract the contents of MSI files.
How does it work? Files with the .msi extension are not as widely used as their .exe cousins, but both contain programs for Windows. The main difference between them is that the latter does not always come with an installer, while it comes standard with the former. However, there will be cases where you just need to view or want to extract specific content from...
</description></item><item><title>Download Trillian 6.6 Build 11</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 16:21:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-trillian-2638.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-trillian-2638.html
</guid><description>
Trillian is the chat help you sign in to more the registered name of a certain service or you can log on at the same time many services in a working window. It integrates multiple services such as Yahoo! MSN, IRC, AIM and ICQ. In addition, you can manage Email accounts, Facebook and Twitter friends - all in just one application.
Login is easy; just click on the network or the appropriate website and log in as normal. Trillian requires access your data (accepted) and post to friends...
</description></item><item><title>Download Free YouTube Download 4.5.5.204 Premium</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 16:21:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-download-1177.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-download-1177.html
</guid><description>
Free YouTube Download Premium is the most popular application to download videos from YouTube. The program was released in 2006 and regularly updated since then. Use the program to download and convert YouTube videos to view offline anytime.
Free YouTube Download - added Support to download youtube
Download more videos! Save whole playlists and YouTube channels, videos from a playlist individually (history, video be favorite, favourites, Watch later), videos from many different...
</description></item><item><title>Download WindowManager 10.25</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 16:20:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desksoft-windowmanager-573.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desksoft-windowmanager-573.html
</guid><description>
WindowManager is a software by DeskSoft dedicated to providing software utilities for windows. DeskSoft WindowManager is the window manager window to ensure your windows are placed exactly where you want. Software will help you to help you improve your work flow by remembering and restoring the position and size of the program and your window. The processing window can completely customize and you can set the special rules for the windows favorite or used most often.
WindowManager send...
</description></item><item><title>Download EmEditor Pro 26.0.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 16:19:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-emeditor-pro-69.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-emeditor-pro-69.html
</guid><description>
EmEditor Pro - the professional version of editor text powerful for programmers, web developers and ordinary users with illumination of syntax and Unicode support. The features of the editor such as search and replace in files using regular expressions, automatic code detect, bookmark link and address email, block selection mode, configure the button bar, menu, font and elements color. With each language you can set separate configuration.
EmEditor Pro - text Editor professional
The...
</description></item><item><title>Download Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium 4.5.5.204</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 16:19:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-to-mp3-converter-premium-844.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-to-mp3-converter-premium-844.html
</guid><description>
Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium version is a software used to convert YouTube to MP3, extract audio from playlists YouTube, show listings, charts, video responses, channels, favorites of the user. With Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium, you can download and convert playlists, channels, stream original tv series and get them into iTunes at the same time.
Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium - convert YouTube to MP3
Features Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium from the...
</description></item><item><title>Download VCap Downloader Pro 0.1.44.6930</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 16:18:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vcap-downloader-pro-8474.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vcap-downloader-pro-8474.html
</guid><description>
VCap Downloader Pro (VCapDL) is a popular piece of software that allows you to record video and audio from websites on the internet. The interface of the software is similar to a normal browser, making it easy for users to get used to and work with this software. User just need to copy video url from favorite browser and convert it to VCap Downloader Pro. It will capture the video and make the quality available for download. You can also extract the audio track from any video and convert...
</description></item><item><title>Download Universal USB Installer 2.0.3.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 16:18:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-universal-usb-installer-3140.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-universal-usb-installer-3140.html
</guid><description>
Universal USB Installer is a software to create a USB Linux that will give you the ability to choose from a large selection of Linux distributions to create bootable USB Flash Drives. the software is intuitive and easy to use, allowing you to simply choose a distribution Live Linux, your flash drive and the ISO file and make USB drive bootable with just a single mouse click. When the task finishes, you will get USB Flash Drive ready to accommodate Linux distributions have chosen. This...
</description></item><item><title>Download Unicodia 3.0.9</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 16:17:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-unicodia-8521.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-unicodia-8521.html
</guid><description>
Unicodia is free, open source software that can be used as an alternative character map for your Windows machine. The interface contains everything you need, allowing you to easily cycle through all the available ASCII symbols and copy them to the clipboard. Uncicodia is a great alternative to your standard Unicode characters and is filled with symbols/characters that make it useful for a number of different uses.
Features of Unicodia
	In Windows 10/11 — all characters of Unicode 15...
</description></item><item><title>Download Trellix Stinger (McAfee Stinger) 13.0.0.601</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 16:17:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mcafee-stinger-202.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mcafee-stinger-202.html
</guid><description>
McAfee Stinger is a free utility that functions to scan, check and remove the hazards and obstacles as virus or malware for Windows, whether they are hiding deep into the system.
In addition, due to the ability to search for the correct folder, or the data at risk contains viruses to scan instead you have to remove a long time waiting for antivirus software to scan all system on your computer. Thus speed of work of the McAfee Stinger faster and somewhat more accurate.
Themselves McAfee...
</description></item><item><title>Download Xreveal 2.9.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 16:16:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xreveal-7252.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xreveal-7252.html
</guid><description>
Xreveal is an application similar to AnyDVD. This is an interactive research and purpose project. Xreveal does NOT contain any decryption key, it is based solely on the official public AACS specification. You need the decryption key or key database to make it work.
Features of Xreveal
	Remove Blu-ray AACS 1.0 protection
	Remove Blu-ray AACS 2.0 (UHD) protection
	Remove BD+ protection
	Remove BDAV Protection
	Remove DVD CSS protection
	Remove CPRM Protection
	Remove CPPM...
</description></item><item><title>Download Software Ideas Modeler Ultimate 15.25</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 16:16:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-software-ideas-modeler-ultimate-10388.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-software-ideas-modeler-ultimate-10388.html
</guid><description>
Software Ideas Modeler Ultimate is a feature-rich CASE tool that can help you design software using various modeling tools and schematic notations. It will help you create a UML model, ERD designer, diagram generator, wireframing tool or BPMN editor.
Features of Software Ideas Modeler Ultimate
	Tools for UML diagrams, class diagrams, block diagrams, data flow diagrams, and other tools help you design your software or its key parts accurately.
	Handle user requests...
</description></item><item><title>Download Red Rock Sound Plugins Bundle 2026.01.06</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 16:16:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-red-rock-sound-plugins-bundle-10260.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-red-rock-sound-plugins-bundle-10260.html
</guid><description>
Save time and avoid tedious manual workarounds with Red Rock Sound's rich plug-ins. This comprehensive package includes many audio plugins that can enhance the sound of your music, podcasts, and other audio projects. Red Rock Sound Plugins Bundle's user interface is designed to be intuitive and easy to use, even for those new to sound processing. All plugins feature clear and concise controls, making it simple to achieve the desired sound.
Audio plugins include:
	RRS AQ550 v3.0.0
	RRS...
</description></item><item><title>Download Vivaldi Browser 7.8.3925.62</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 16:15:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vivaldi-159.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vivaldi-159.html
</guid><description>
Vivaldi is a browser designed for users who have power and offer the option to customize high. You can choose the location of the tabs and the address bar, put the hotkeys for the common tasks and many other features. Also, Vivaldi also provides a number of improvements such as Tab Stacks to group multiple open tabs into a tab, leads to interface less cluttered. Can notes and added a screenshot of a web page while browsing, storing an attachment, and add the URL to easily sort and locate...
</description></item><item><title>Download Vivaldi for macOS 7.8.3925.62</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 16:15:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/mac/download-vivaldi-for-macos-3443.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/mac/download-vivaldi-for-macos-3443.html
</guid><description>
The Vivaldi for MacOS browser does not track users and offers more features than any other modern browser. Managed by Jon von Tetzchner (co-founder of Opera browser), Vivaldi for MacOS is driven by the real needs of today's users and ensures that they have the best tools to browse and get work done.
Vivaldi for MacOS - Modern web browser
Users can adjust Vivaldi to suit their browsing needs them without limiting customization options. Vivaldi takes the browser to the next level with a...
</description></item><item><title>Download DBF Viewer 2000 v8.97</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 16:14:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbf-viewer-2000-7869.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbf-viewer-2000-7869.html
</guid><description>
DBF Viewer 2000 is a fast, efficient solution for viewing and editing all types of DBF files. It can handle files from dBase, Visual dBase, Foxpro, Visual FoxPro and Clipper, just to name a few, with performance that easily rivals expensive professional database utilities. DBF Viewer 2000 is extremely fast, does any task, just one simple query and cleanup copy to export data at lightning speed.
With DBF Editor's simple, dynamically generated visual dialogs, you can easily view the...
</description></item></channel></rss>