<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 12:38:39 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 12:38:39 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download K-Lite Codec Pack Full 19.5.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:38:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-115.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-115.html
</guid><description>
K Lite Codec Pack Full brings pc users an optimal solution for watching movies, listening to music, support most popular format today by using collection codec rich. This software also allows you to refine the quality of videos and music to enjoy, create a list of music and video to comfortable enjoy.
Prompt to software, listen to music, watch movies, currently, part, user will prompt to programs like VLC or KMP ... With VLC, it was too familiar with users, not just watch videos, listen...
</description></item><item><title>Download CrystalDiskInfo Portable 9.8.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:38:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-crystaldiskinfo-portable-11173.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-crystaldiskinfo-portable-11173.html
</guid><description>
CrystalDiskInfo Portable (portable version) is utility software designed to monitor the health and performance of hard disk drives (HDD) and solid state drives (SSD). This tool is often used to check the status of drives in a computer to ensure they are operating normally and predict possible drive errors.
It provides detailed information about the drive, such as temperature, drive status, total operating hours, etc. Software to read S.M.A.R.T. (Self-Monitoring, Analysis and Reporting...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube Downloader 3.9.18 (1602)</title><pubDate> Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:37:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube Downloader  is a dedicated software that helps users  downloading youtube videos  Favorites on PC for offline viewing. With MediaHuman YouTube  Downloader  you can download videos from youtube website to your computer with  fast speed , with special software development technology that automatically receives videos from Websites, in addition to the ability to download videos from software websites, can convert downloaded video formats to various formats for the purpose...
</description></item><item><title>Download K-Lite Codec Pack Mega 19.5.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:36:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-mega-3202.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-mega-3202.html
</guid><description>
K-Lite Mega Codec Pack is a collection of components needed for audio playback and the video in the player DirectShow like Windows Media Player, Media Center, and Media Player Classic. This is the latest beta version, Pack Codec K-Lite latest stable. The Mega variant is the biggest of the four variants of the codec pack. It provides everything you need to play all audio and video files. In addition, it also contains some codecs ACM / VFW can be used by the application coding / video...
</description></item><item><title>Download Quick Access Popup 12.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:35:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quick-access-popup-984.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quick-access-popup-984.html
</guid><description>
Quick Access Popup  ( QAP ) is a software that provides quick access to files, files, windows applications and is  shortcut manager , mouse and keyboard.  Quick Access Popup  helps you quickly move between FILE, DOCUMENT, APPS in Windows Explorer or file dialog to quickly launch applications, documents or web pages at once 
To launch the pop-up menu, click the  QAP  icon in the Notifications area, press the Middle mouse button, or press Windows + W (these triggers can be changed under...
</description></item><item><title>Download Easy System Utility Pro 1.1.51</title><pubDate> Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:34:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easy-system-utility-pro-12380.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easy-system-utility-pro-12380.html
</guid><description>
Easy System Utility Pro is a powerful, all-in-one program designed for Windows 10 and 11 users. This versatile tool should be your primary choice to improve your computing experience ! This is the complete version with additional and enhanced features. It will help you easily determine your computer's hardware specifications with a system overview. You can view the operating system, CPU model, GPU, Memory, Motherboard, Network and even drivers.
It also supports launching programs,...
</description></item><item><title>Download K-Lite Codec Pack Update 19.5.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:34:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-update-5145.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-update-5145.html
</guid><description>
K-Lite Codec Pack Update is the update of the set of codecs and related tools. Codec stands for Compressor-decompressor. Codec is necessary to encode and decode (play) audio and video. K-Lite Codec Pack Update is designed as a user-friendly solution with users to play all movie files your. With Codec Pack K-Lite, you can play 99% of all the movies found on your computer. A number of packages codec is not friendly with computers, as they tend to slow down Windows, break down multimedia...
</description></item><item><title>Download ASCOMP Easy Slideshow Professional 2.101</title><pubDate> Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:33:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ascomp-easy-slideshow-professional-13811.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ascomp-easy-slideshow-professional-13811.html
</guid><description>
ASCOMP Easy Slideshow Professional is a user-friendly Windows software designed to quickly create stunning slideshow videos from your photos. Ideal for both beginners and professionals, the software offers an intuitive drag-and-drop interface for arranging images, setting display durations, and adding individual subtitles or captions for personalization.
Key features include:
	Over 200 built-in transition effects such as soft fades, dynamic zooms, and creative animations for changing...
</description></item><item><title>Download SEO Checker 11.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:32:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-seo-checker-2514.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-seo-checker-2514.html
</guid><description>
SEO Checker (A product of genuine VOVSoft) is a tool to analyze all type of web site or personal web page. The software works in many different ways, it can help you discover the content that you have specifically chosen to analyze from suitable site. As the authors write, the program, as this program allows you to plan for your SEO strategy by providing information about the function of it, you will get a set of keyword analysis and tracking the reverse link.
SEO Checker - Support SEO...
</description></item><item><title>Download Godot Game Engine 4.6.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:32:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-godot-engine-10493.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-godot-engine-10493.html
</guid><description>
Godot Engine is a feature-rich, cross-platform game engine for creating 2D and 3D games from a unified interface. It provides a comprehensive set of common tools so users can focus on game creation without having to reinvent the wheel. Games can be exported with a single click to several platforms, including major desktop platforms (Linux, macOS, Windows), mobile platforms (Android, iOS), as well as Web-based platform and dashboard.
Supported platforms:
Godot Engine, used to create...
</description></item><item><title>Download DBF Viewer 2000 v8.98</title><pubDate> Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:31:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbf-viewer-2000-7869.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbf-viewer-2000-7869.html
</guid><description>
DBF Viewer 2000 is a fast, efficient solution for viewing and editing all types of DBF files. It can handle files from dBase, Visual dBase, Foxpro, Visual FoxPro and Clipper, just to name a few, with performance that easily rivals expensive professional database utilities. DBF Viewer 2000 is extremely fast, does any task, just one simple query and cleanup copy to export data at lightning speed.
With DBF Editor's simple, dynamically generated visual dialogs, you can easily view the...
</description></item><item><title>Download 7-Zip Portable 26.00</title><pubDate> Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:30:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-7-zip-portable-11320.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-7-zip-portable-11320.html
</guid><description>
7-Zip Portable is a file archiving (compression) utility for Windows with many great features including: high compression ratio in the new 7z format with LZMA compression; Multiple formats supported including 7z, ZIP, GZIP, BZIP2 and TAR; decompression support for RAR, CAB, ISO, ARJ, LZH, CHM, Z, CPIO, RPM, DEB &amp;amp; NSIS.
Features of 7-Zip Portable
	High compression ratio in 7z format with LZMA and LZMA2 compression
	Supported formats:
	Packing/unpacking: 7z, XX, BZIP2, GZIP, TAR,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Markdown Monster 4.1.5.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:30:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-markdown-monster-2640.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-markdown-monster-2640.html
</guid><description>
Markdown Monster is the edit and view Markdown allows you to edit Markdown by syntax highlighting and fast text input. Live preview can collapse, synchronized allows you to see the output of when you enter. You can easily embed images, links, emoticons and code in text form or by using the support UI lightness of we to simplify many operations. You can also paste and drag images directly into the editor.
Markdown Monster is a solution comprehensive software designed to solve almost any...
</description></item><item><title>Download AppCompactor 3.14</title><pubDate> Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:29:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-appcompactor-4529.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-appcompactor-4529.html
</guid><description>
AppCompactor is a free software to help you switch the application into the mobile version with this lightweight application comes with a simple interface. With the help of this tool, you just extract the program files to any location on the hard drive and directly launch the executable file.
AppCompactor - Create version application Portable
AppCompactor is itself mobile application, no installation required
Because this application is portable, you don't need to install it on the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Zero Install 2.28.4</title><pubDate> Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:28:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zero-install-1632.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zero-install-1632.html
</guid><description>
Zero Install is a system, install the software distribution cross africa focus. Other features include full support for shared libraries (with the SAT for resolution dependent), share between users, and integration with the package manager original foundation. Zero Install supports both binary packages and source and works on Linux systems , OS X , Unix and Windows. It is completely open source.
Zero Install - System software installation
Zero Install also has a number of interesting...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ultimate Power Assistant 1.1.24</title><pubDate> Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:27:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ultimate-power-assistant-12372.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ultimate-power-assistant-12372.html
</guid><description>
Ultimate Power Assistant provides you with an efficient and easy way to manage your computer's power settings and tasks. With this tool, you can schedule and apply various power options in Windows.
Main features
	Shut down when download completes: Turn off your computer after your favorite game launcher or web browser completes the download. You no longer have to leave your PC running for hours wasting electricity!
	Change Power Plan when certain programs are detected: Launch a...
</description></item><item><title>Download dbForge Studio for PostgreSQL Professional 2025.3.93</title><pubDate> Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:25:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbforge-studio-for-postgresql-enterprise-11213.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbforge-studio-for-postgresql-enterprise-11213.html
</guid><description>
dbForge Studio for PostgreSQL Enterprise is a GUI client and popular tool for managing and developing PostgreSQL databases. This PostgreSQL IDE allows users to create, develop and execute queries, edit and adapt code according to their requirements in a convenient and user-friendly interface.
Main features:
SQL Development
	Save your time and improve code quality when creating and editing queries with the following features
	PostgreSQL code completion
	Code format
	SQL Check SQL...
</description></item><item><title>Download Easy Gamer Utility Pro 1.3.91</title><pubDate> Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:24:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easy-gamer-utility-pro-12381.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easy-gamer-utility-pro-12381.html
</guid><description>
Easy Gamer Utility Pro is an easy-to-use program for Windows that can do a lot on your PC to help fix gaming problems, performance problems, and general optimization! The best tool to improve your Windows gaming experience! Is your game laggy and slow? If so, you can use the built-in game accelerator in Easy Gamer Utility, which boosts system performance, makes games run smoother, and increases FPS.
Additionally, this handy utility deletes and cleans unwanted and unnecessary temporary...
</description></item><item><title>Download HopToDesk 1.45.8</title><pubDate> Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:23:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hoptodesk-11056.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hoptodesk-11056.html
</guid><description>
HopToDesk is a remote desktop application that allows users to access their remote computer or server from anywhere using a mobile device or browser their website. It provides a secure and convenient way to control and manage computers remotely, making it easier for individuals and teams to work remotely or access their files and applications on the go.
With HopToDesk, users can establish a secure connection to a remote computer or server and perform tasks as if they were sitting in...
</description></item><item><title>Download lessmsi 2.12.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:20:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lessmsi-12392.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lessmsi-12392.html
</guid><description>
Lessmsi (Less MSIerables) is a free and portable application that allows users to view and extract the contents of MSI files.
How does it work? Files with the .msi extension are not as widely used as their .exe cousins, but both contain programs for Windows. The main difference between them is that the latter does not always come with an installer, while it comes standard with the former. However, there will be cases where you just need to view or want to extract specific content from...
</description></item><item><title>Download QOwnNotes 26.2.5</title><pubDate> Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:19:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qownnotes-3178.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qownnotes-3178.html
</guid><description>
QOwnNotes is notes bookmark file simple text (GPL) open source application for GNU / Linux , Mac OS X and Windows of Patrizio Bekerle ( pbek on GitHub and IRC) (optional) activity along with the notes application of ownCloud or Nextcloud. QOwnNote store your notes as plain text files and can be synchronized with synchronization function file of ownCloud / Nextcloud. You can also use other apps like Syncthing or Dropbox . Just write out your thoughts as they appear, and edit them if...
</description></item><item><title>Download StaxRip 2.50.8</title><pubDate> Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:18:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-staxrip-2930.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-staxrip-2930.html
</guid><description>
StaxRip app is a comprehensive and powerful, allowing you to convert all video files DVB, DVD, or DV video into a variety of file formats. The program is open Source, meaning completely free to download and use. StaxRip can support many video formats such as x264, MPEG-4, DivX, XviD, MPEG-2 and many other formats. The format sounds different also be supported, including MP2 / MPA, AAC, WAV, Ogg Vorbis, MP3, AC3, DTS and other formats. Moreover, the program also supports a variety of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cresset Flare 11.0.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 17 Feb 2026 12:25:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cresset-flare-12312.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cresset-flare-12312.html
</guid><description>
Cresset Flare is a powerful molecular design software developed by Cresset, a leading provider of computational chemistry solutions. It is designed to assist researchers and scientists in discovering and optimizing new chemical compounds. Flare provides many tools and features to support medicinal chemistry, molecular design, and structure-based design. It allows users to visualize, edit and analyze chemical structures with ease. The software uses advanced algorithms and techniques to...
</description></item><item><title>Download 4K Video Downloader Plus 26.0.4</title><pubDate> Tue, 17 Feb 2026 02:54:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-video-downloader-617.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-video-downloader-617.html
</guid><description>
4K Video Downloader Plus is software support downloads video, audio and subtitles from YouTube with high quality up to 4K. Download process video is very simple: just copy the video link from your browser and click Paste Url. Done! If you want that video on your iPad, iPhone or other device, we have protected you.
The feature on 4K Video Downloader Plus
	Download entire playlists and channels from YouTube and save them in MP4, MKV, M4A, MP3, FLV, 3G, create a file .m3u for...
</description></item><item><title>Download Freemake Video Converter Gold 5.0.0.35</title><pubDate> Tue, 17 Feb 2026 02:53:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-freemake-video-converter-gold-167.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-freemake-video-converter-gold-167.html
</guid><description>
Freemake Video Converter Gold is a software to help convert tail high quality videos with many different formats on many devices. Freemake Video Converter - convert video to AVI, MP4, WMV, MKV, 3GP, DVD, MP3, iPad, iPhone, PSP, Android phone. Video to MP3 just with one click! Rip and burn DVD. Convert YouTube to MP4, AVI, etc. with Freemake! Results guaranteed. Freemake Video Converter has fast conversion speed, guarantee the output quality,support create HTML5 videos have the embed code...
</description></item></channel></rss>