<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 14:05:56 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 14:05:56 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Topaz Gigapixel Pro 1.1.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 14 Feb 2026 16:42:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-ai-gigapixel-1318.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-ai-gigapixel-1318.html
</guid><description>
Topaz ONE Gigapixel is the first app and only use the power of artificial intelligence to enhance your photos, add natural details, for great results. Use technology to learn deep, AIGigapixel ™ can zoom in and fill in the details that the products change in size other are not included. The traditional method this created blurred image, a non-realistic and do not have the detail present in the image have high resolution.
Topaz A.I. Gigapixel - enhance image quality
The content of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Fan Control v259</title><pubDate> Sat, 14 Feb 2026 16:41:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fancontrol-5749.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fancontrol-5749.html
</guid><description>
FanControl is a highly customizable fan control software for Windows. Stay in control of every aspect of your PC's GPU and CPU fan with the help of this highly customizable fan control app.
Features of FanControl
	Save, edit and load multiple configurations
	Multiple temperature sources (CPU, GPU, motherboard, hard drive, ".sensor" files)
	Custom fan curve
	Fine tune fan control response with steps,% start,% stop, response time and delay
	Mix different curves and sensors...
</description></item><item><title>Download .NET Checker 1.5</title><pubDate> Sat, 14 Feb 2026 16:41:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-net-checker-10355.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-net-checker-10355.html
</guid><description>
.NET Checker is a free utility that gives you an easy way to determine which version of Microsoft .NET and Visual C++ is currently installed on your device. You can also find out what version of .NET a particular application needs. .NET Checker makes the process of checking which versions you have and which ones you don't easy, and the fact that it's small and portable is a bonus. Results are compiled and displayed quickly, and usage is simple, making it great for users of all levels who...
</description></item><item><title>Download reaConverter Pro 8.0.197</title><pubDate> Sat, 14 Feb 2026 16:40:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html
</guid><description>
reaConverter Pro is software image processing feature with batch conversion and image editing periodically becomes simple. eaConverter also provide command line utilities allow you to process images automatically, thus helping you shorten the time for other work.
reaConverter Pro integrated powerful tool of Uber with many great features. It provides advanced solutions to process and adjust images. Management of the conversion process the base image with the latest version of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Urban VPN 5.0.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 14 Feb 2026 16:39:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-urban-vpn-7155.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-urban-vpn-7155.html
</guid><description>
Urban VPN is a subsidiary of Urban Cyber ​​Security and the creators of one of the world's most trusted and free virtual private networks. VPN Browser Extension Gives You Quick and Easy Activation &amp;amp; Unlimited bandwidth! Urban VPN helps you keep your device activities safe and private. Protect your device from harmful ads and protect your device from malware and other security holes when using public Wi-Fi connections. With Urban VPN, you can safely surf the web without fear of...
</description></item><item><title>Download PhraseExpress 17.0.135</title><pubDate> Sat, 14 Feb 2026 16:38:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-phraseexpress-41.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-phraseexpress-41.html
</guid><description>
PhraseExpress is a useful application that helps users save time when typing frequently used text or commands. This application allows users to create shortcuts to automatically insert text quickly and conveniently.
With PhraseExpress, users can create "templates" for common commands, regular emails, chat messages, or any text they have to retype frequently. Users only need to set up shortcuts for each template and when needed, just type that shortcut and the text will automatically...
</description></item><item><title>Download ExamDiff Pro Master Edition 16.0.1.23</title><pubDate> Sat, 14 Feb 2026 16:37:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-examdiff-pro-master-312.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-examdiff-pro-master-312.html
</guid><description>
ExamDiff Pro Master is a tool to compare files and folders intuitive and easy to use, intuitive and easy to use for Windows. ExamDiff Pro Master has unique features distinguishes ExamDiff Pro with the program compare other. ExamDiff Pro Master to help perform reviews of code and share other reports with your colleagues and compare local website with FTP server by plug-ins more integrated.
ExamDiff Pro Master can create a snapshot folder for comparison and storage in the future, compare...
</description></item><item><title>Download AllMapSoft Offline Map Maker 8.367</title><pubDate> Sat, 14 Feb 2026 16:36:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-offline-map-maker-656.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-offline-map-maker-656.html
</guid><description>
AllMapSoft Offline Map Maker is software create, organize, offline map from Google Maps, Yahoo maps, Bing maps and Openstreetmap. You can view offline maps downloaded with map viewer offline. And you can zoom out or zoom in the offline map or export map under the file format .BMP with file world xxx.bpw, and can output files xxx.map for OziExplorer. If you want to make a offline map of your city by yourself, it is very useful for you.
Features AllMapSoft Offline Map Maker
	You can...
</description></item><item><title>Download MeinPlatz 8.56</title><pubDate> Sat, 14 Feb 2026 16:36:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-meinplatz-1860.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-meinplatz-1860.html
</guid><description>
MeinPlatz is a free software provides an easy and fast way to scan the hard disk to find the disk space lost. After the search is complete, results can be exported to XLS, HTM, CSV and TXT. MeinPlatz "My-Place" also has a print function with preview feature integrated print and frame rate change, and is also a magnifying glass the small screen.
MeinPlatz - Scan disk
The new features of MeinPlatz
	General optimization and general improvements as well as update the file language in...
</description></item><item><title>Download DirPrintOK 7.52</title><pubDate> Sat, 14 Feb 2026 16:35:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dirprintok-2073.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dirprintok-2073.html
</guid><description>
DirPrintOK allows you to print and save the contents of the folder and / or entire folder structures. You can browse the directory with Explorer-like interface and arbitrary filter folder contents by file extensions or matching the wildcard. You can also right-click to exclude files or folders selected from the printed version.
&amp;nbsp;
Folder contents can be grouped by path, date, size or file extension and you can customize the data columns to be included in the printed book. Very easy...
</description></item><item><title>Download PC Internals Pro 2.102</title><pubDate> Sat, 14 Feb 2026 16:34:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pc-internals-pro-13002.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pc-internals-pro-13002.html
</guid><description>
PC Internals Pro is a new solution that allows Windows users to comprehensively analyze the system components and reliable monitoring of the hard drive. This software is aimed at individual users as well as IT experts and retail agents attach importance to transparency, early detection and data security. PC Internals provides detailed information about the processor, RAM, graphics card, drive and other system components. The chart directly displays the current load, while the specific...
</description></item><item><title>Download Real Cut 1D 11.13.8</title><pubDate> Sat, 14 Feb 2026 16:33:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-real-cut-1d-14555.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-real-cut-1d-14555.html
</guid><description>
Real Cut 1D is a computer program used to find the optimal cutting design for one-dimensional parts that may have non-90-degree angles at the ends. Real Cut 1D can be used to cut linear parts such as bars, tubes, beams, steel pipes, steel bars, roofing bars, railings, fence bars, wooden frames, aluminum bars, PVC bars, nylon bars, bridge railings, U-shaped posts, window frames, etc. Real Cut 1D creates optimal solutions by using minimal material.
Features of Real Cut 1D
	Flexible...
</description></item><item><title>Download The Bat! Professional 12.0.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 14 Feb 2026 16:32:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-the-bat-professional-3072.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-the-bat-professional-3072.html
</guid><description>
The Bat! Professional is an email program guest safety, developed to protect your correspondence against the side Tuesday. The Bat! Professional protection of your data through multi-threaded encoding with a choice encoding of your emails on disk and during communication through SSL / TLS connections. Free email providers global hosting your mail on the cloud and free for the Web clients, The Bat! ensure your data is kept private.
The Bat! Professional - mail application security
The...
</description></item><item><title>Download Carlson Civil Suite 2026 build 260120</title><pubDate> Sat, 14 Feb 2026 16:32:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-carlson-civil-suite-7248.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-carlson-civil-suite-7248.html
</guid><description>
Carlson Civil Suite is a quality software solution for land development professionals in the surveying, civil engineering, mining and construction sectors. This release brings more user-requested features and improved compatibility between CAD platforms.
Carlson Civil Suite offers the most powerful and easy-to-use automation among today's civil design solutions, and it performs dynamic updates without the need for a custom object. Carlson Civil's wide selection of power tools allows...
</description></item><item><title>Download QIAGEN CLC Genomics Workbench 26.0.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 14 Feb 2026 16:31:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qiagen-clc-genomics-workbench-13903.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qiagen-clc-genomics-workbench-13903.html
</guid><description>
CLC Genomics Workbench is a comprehensive analysis package for data analysis and visualization and supports all common NGS workflows. Additionally, it includes all the sequencing analysis tools of CLC Main Workbench.
Features
	Cross-platform desktop application with intuitive and user-friendly interface
	Incorporates cutting-edge technology and algorithms
	Includes a wide range of features in genomics, transcriptomics, and epigenomics
	Supports all major next-generation sequencing...
</description></item><item><title>Download VovSoft Sitemap Generator 4.5</title><pubDate> Sat, 14 Feb 2026 16:30:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-sitemap-generator-5365.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-sitemap-generator-5365.html
</guid><description>
VovSoft Sitemap Generator is software that creates sitemaps that can be submitted to search engines and helps visitors navigate your website. VovSoft Sitemap Generator is a lightweight application designed to help you create your sitemap in a few simple steps. It can be useful in some cases and it has a minimalistic, user-friendly GUI.
This application is great for those who need to create a sitemap as quickly as possible, as it doesn't require you to complete any complicated...
</description></item><item><title>Download HashiCorp Vault Enterprise 1.21.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 14 Feb 2026 16:28:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hashicorp-vault-enterprise-8618.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hashicorp-vault-enterprise-8618.html
</guid><description>
HashiCorp Vault Enterprise is a secret management solution that provides organizations with a centralized platform to store, manage and control access to sensitive information, such as passwords, certificates, and API keys.
HashiCorp Vault Enterprise provides organizations with a powerful solution to manage their secrets. The platform's combination of secret management, encryption, and role-based access control makes it a valuable tool for organizations looking to secure their sensitive...
</description></item><item><title>Download HashiCorp Boundary Enterprise 0.21.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 14 Feb 2026 16:16:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hashicorp-boundary-enterprise-9715.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hashicorp-boundary-enterprise-9715.html
</guid><description>
HashiCorp Boundary Enterprise centralizes remote access management and ensures access to infrastructure resources located on any public or private cloud environment. Easily integrates with leading identity providers such as Okta, Ping, and Azure Active Directory, and supports multiple service registries to automatically discover and maintain an up-to-date repository of servers and target service.
Features of HashiCorp Boundary Enterprise
	Authenticate with whatever trusted identity...
</description></item><item><title>Download HashiCorp Consul Enterprise 1.22.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 14 Feb 2026 16:15:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hashicorp-consul-enterprise-8616.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hashicorp-consul-enterprise-8616.html
</guid><description>
HashiCorp Consul Enterprise is a software solution for service discovery, configuration management, and network segmentation. It provides organizations with a centralized platform to manage and secure their infrastructure and applications across multi-cloud and multi-datacenter environments.
HashiCorp Consul Enterprise provides organizations with a powerful solution to manage and secure their infrastructure and applications. The platform's combination of service discovery, configuration...
</description></item><item><title>Download Monkeys Audio 12.14</title><pubDate> Sat, 14 Feb 2026 16:15:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-monkeys-audio-949.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-monkeys-audio-949.html
</guid><description>
Monkey\'s Audio is software that compresses digital music without loss of quality. Supports high quality WAV files and CD ripping. Monkeys Audio will compress .wav tracks into .ape files to reduce their size without loss of sound quality, decompress .ape, convert files, check file integrity and manage tags.
Unlike traditional methods like MP3 and OGG, which permanently remove quality to save space, Monkey\'s Audio only creates perfect copies with the same sound quality as the originals....
</description></item><item><title>Download The Dude 7.21.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 14 Feb 2026 16:14:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-the-dude-3238.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-the-dude-3238.html
</guid><description>
The Dude is a new application by MikroTik which can dramatically improve the way you manage your network environment. It will automatically scan all devices in the subnet is specified, draw and layout a map of your networks, monitor services of your devices and alert you in case some service has problems.is a new application by MikroTik which can dramatically improve the way you manage your network environment. It will automatically scan all devices in the subnet is specified, draw and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Simufact Joining Optimizer 2025.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 14 Feb 2026 13:25:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-simufact-joining-optimizer-14568.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-simufact-joining-optimizer-14568.html
</guid><description>
Simufact Joining Optimizer is specialized software developed to simulate and virtually optimize various joining processes (welding, mechanical joining, tin soldering, etc.) in manufacturing. The software focuses on minimizing defects such as deformation and residual stress, ensuring quality and optimizing process parameters to improve production efficiency. Users do not need in-depth CAE knowledge to use it.
Key Features
	The software supports simulation of self-piercing riveting,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Premiere Pro 2026 v26.0.1 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Sat, 14 Feb 2026 03:04:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-premiere-pro-0022-1361.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-premiere-pro-0022-1361.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Premiere Pro is the leading video editing software for film, TV, and the web. Creative tools, integration with other Adobe apps and services, and the power of Adobe Sensei help you turn footage into finished movies and videos in a seamless workflow. It offers high-quality video editing at 4K x 4K resolution and beyond, with 32-bit color, in both RGB and YUV color spaces. Edit audio samples, support for VST audio plug-ins (plug-ins), and 5.1 surround sound tracks. The Premiere Pro...
</description></item><item><title>Download CyberLink PowerDirector Ultimate 2026 v24.2.1410.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 14 Feb 2026 03:03:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-powerdirector-ultimate-425.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-powerdirector-ultimate-425.html
</guid><description>
CyberLink PowerDirector Ultimate is software editor, edit video and make movies on the computer from a variety of templates are made available, complete with effects, transitions, animations, and music. CyberLink PowerDirector 17 is a combination of video editing software with advanced video editing features powerful. Cblowing need to add your clips into the time line and click on 'Production'!
The tool design video in CyberLink PowerDirector have the ability to customize helps you...
</description></item><item><title>Download WonderFox DVD Video Converter 31.4</title><pubDate> Sat, 14 Feb 2026 03:02:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wonderfox-dvd-video-converter-189.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wonderfox-dvd-video-converter-189.html
</guid><description>
WonderFox DVD Video Converter is a software to convert Video DVD to the Video format the other with fast speed. Convenient program to convert the popular video formats and movie DVD, download WonderFox DVD Video Converter below. You can create videos that will be optimized for viewing on mobile devices. There is a simple video editor, it will allow you to add effects, crop photos, and etc.
WonderFox DVD Video Converter
WonderFox DVD Video Converter support rip DVD and videos to various...
</description></item></channel></rss>