<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 13:46:43 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 13:46:43 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Obsidian 1.10.3</title><pubDate> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 16:44:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-obsidian-10386.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-obsidian-10386.html
</guid><description>
Obsidian is a powerful knowledge base that operates on a local folder containing plain text Markdown files. It allows users to create internal links for notes and then display the connections as a graph. Additionally users can also organize and structure their thoughts and knowledge in a flexible, non-linear way.
Features of Obsidian
Personal notes:
	Links: Create connections between your notes.
	Graph: Visualize the relationships between your notes.
	Plugins: Build your ideal...
</description></item><item><title>Download AI Dream Art 1.2.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 16:42:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ai-dream-art-14017.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ai-dream-art-14017.html
</guid><description>
AI Dream Art helps you create beautiful AI art offline. Unleash your creativity and create breathtaking AI art right on your computer — completely independent of the internet. AI Dream Art is your private offline creative studio powered by a local pervasive model. No registration, no cloud processing, and no usage limits.
Notable features of the app:
	Create multiple images (up to 4) for each reminder with just one click
	Supports multiple image resolutions (512x512 to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ableton Live Suite 12.2.7</title><pubDate> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 16:41:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ableton-live-suite-663.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ableton-live-suite-663.html
</guid><description>
Ableton Live Suite is professional software to create, edit, music with effects, instruments, audio and all creative. Ableton Live Suite is the software fast, flexible and flexibility to create and perform music. Move freely between the musical elements and play with ideas, that don't stop the music and do not break the flow of your sound.
Features, Ableton Live Suite
	Meet Wavetable, Echo, Drum Buss and Pedal: the new equipment means new sounds, colorful can with the instruments and...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube Downloader 3.9.18 (1111)</title><pubDate> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 16:41:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube Downloader  is a dedicated software that helps users  downloading youtube videos  Favorites on PC for offline viewing. With MediaHuman YouTube  Downloader  you can download videos from youtube website to your computer with  fast speed , with special software development technology that automatically receives videos from Websites, in addition to the ability to download videos from software websites, can convert downloaded video formats to various formats for the purpose...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ashampoo Backup Pro 27.5.4</title><pubDate> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 16:39:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-backup-pro-716.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-backup-pro-716.html
</guid><description>
Ashampoo Backup Pro is software to backup and restore data professional to save the file, the important data for your computer. Ashampoo Backup Pro will remove the fear of viruses, ransomware, or hardware errors. Ashampoo® Backup Pro offers you various options to backup individual files or entire disk partitions on any storage media or on the cloud. User friendly, intuitive, fast. Even in case an error occurs the entire system, application integrated emergency can bring your...
</description></item><item><title>Download ClipGrab 3.9.14 Portable</title><pubDate> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 16:37:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-clipgrab-2450.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-clipgrab-2450.html
</guid><description>
ClipGrab package is multi-platform software to download videos from popular sites like YouTube, Vimeo, Dailymotion or Metacafe. It also provides the ability to convert the downloaded files to other file formats such as MP3, MPEG4, OGG Theora or WMV.
ClipGrab - Download online videos fast
ClipGrab that allows you to download videos from many online websites, including the website not for download because of copyright issues, with the fastest speed. ClipGrab support download via the URL...
</description></item><item><title>Download SILKYPIX RAW Converter 1.0.13.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 16:35:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-silkypix-raw-converter-10300.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-silkypix-raw-converter-10300.html
</guid><description>
SILKYPIX RAW Converter is software that converts RAW image data captured with a digital camera into RAW (DNG)/TIFF/JPEG data with resolution and quality. Image quality is higher than regular RAW data. After bringing out the best in an image, it can be imported and adjusted using other photo editing software such as Photoshop or SILKYPIX products.
By applying SILKYPIX's unique decolorization technology, the resolution of image details can be expressed in high definition. It can also be...
</description></item><item><title>Download DBF Recovery 4.60</title><pubDate> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 16:34:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbf-recovery-7931.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbf-recovery-7931.html
</guid><description>
DBF Recovery is software that gives users the ability to restore a damaged database back to its original condition without the expertise required to complete that task. It fixes headers and data structures in an automated process that doesn't involve user interaction. With DBF Recovery, you will truly have a lean, honest DBF repair machine without any functionality.
Features of DBF Recovery
	Quick and simple to use DBF file repair software.
	Repair almost any DBF...
</description></item><item><title>Download ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro 15.25.1111</title><pubDate> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 16:34:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-videotube-downloader-pro-1276.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-videotube-downloader-pro-1276.html
</guid><description>
ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro is the professional version support download videos and playlists from YouTube, videos from Dailymotion, BBC iPlayer, ITV Player, ABC,  FOX,CBS.com Vimeo, Prosieben, Metacafe, Blip.tv CBC.ca many more video sites. After the video is downloaded, you can convert them to the formats compatible with iPad, iPhone, iPod, MPEG-4, H. 264, MP3, AC3.
ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro - Download videos on Youtube
This is one of the software download the most...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cockos REAPER 7.53</title><pubDate> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 16:34:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cockos-reaper-889.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cockos-reaper-889.html
</guid><description>
Cockos REAPER is a powerful software for for windows, chp lets you record, arrange, edit, and display the audio waveform multi-track. Cockos REAPER offers an extensive feature set includes many effects and a sample project. REAPER supports ASIO, Kernel Streaming, WaveOut, and DirectSound for playback and recording. It reads the files in WAV, OGG and MP3 files and records WAV files. You can arrange any number of items in any number of tracks and use plug-in sound processing (DirectX and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Batch CHM to DOC Converter 2025.17.1105.3594</title><pubDate> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 16:33:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-batch-chm-to-word-converter-5412.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-batch-chm-to-word-converter-5412.html
</guid><description>
Batch CHM to Word Converter is a CHM to Word Document batch converter which can convert HTML Help to Word DOC and DOCX easily. Batch CHM to Word Converter supports searching multiple files in a powerful way. Compressed HTML Help Converter for Windows. Batch CHM to Word Converter supports project and command line. Batch CHM to Word Converter has a friendly GUI so it's very easy to use. Batch support CHM TO Word DOC Converter Drag and Explorer Context.
Batch CHM to Word Converter supports...
</description></item><item><title>Download Western Digital Kitfox 1.2.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 16:32:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-western-digital-kitfox-14009.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-western-digital-kitfox-14009.html
</guid><description>
Western Digital Kitfox is a software tool specifically designed to manage and maintain Western Digital (WD) hard drives, primarily HDDs, both internal and external. The tool provides functions such as hard drive health monitoring, temperature monitoring, hard drive testing, and secure data erasure. Kitfox helps users identify potential problems before data loss, check the health of WD hard drives, and maintain their performance and longevity. This tool supports a wide range of WD hard...
</description></item><item><title>Download Far Manager 3.0 Build 6591</title><pubDate> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 16:32:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-far-manager-1609.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-far-manager-1609.html
</guid><description>
Far Manager is an application for managing files and archives in Windows operating systems. Far Manager works in text mode and provides a simple interface and intuitive to perform the action.
Far Manager - Manage file documents
The main features of Far Manager include:
	Viewing files and directories; editing, copying and renaming files; and many other actions.
	The function of Far Manager is significantly expanded by the module DLL outside - the plugin, created by a special...
</description></item><item><title>Download Process Explorer 17.07</title><pubDate> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 16:31:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-process-explorer-370.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-process-explorer-370.html
</guid><description>
Process Explorer is a software to track and manage the active processes on your computer, at the same time, timely detection and debugging.  Process Explorer shows you information about the processing and the process DLL already open or download. Screen Process Explorer consists of two window. The top part always displays the list of processes that are currently active, including the name of the account owner of them
Process Explorer helps you get the look more depth, more details about...
</description></item><item><title>Download Silkypix Developer Studio Pro 12.0.5.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 16:31:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-silkypix-developer-studio-pro-738.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-silkypix-developer-studio-pro-738.html
</guid><description>
Silkypix Developer Studio Pro is photo editing software flexibility to provide the photo editing tool, and convert RAW images professional. SILKYPIX Developer Studio Pro is a image processing software RAW advanced can re-create high resolution. The software has editing functions powerful, supports RAW formats, JPEG and TIFF and primarily geared towards the experienced user.
Silkypix Developer Studio Pro - Handle RAW images professional
Features of Silkypix Developer Studio...
</description></item><item><title>Download Muziza YouTube Downloader Converter 8.16.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 16:30:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-muziza-youtube-downloader-converter-3972.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-muziza-youtube-downloader-converter-3972.html
</guid><description>
Muziza YouTube Downloader Converter is a tool to create conditions for an attractive interface and many features to help you to download video clips from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion, Instagram and other sites. Muziza YouTube Downloader Converter can also download the video UHD 8K, 5K, 4K, QHD 2K, HD 1080p and 720p from YouTube. The app allows you download only audio stream from YouTube and save as MP3. You don't need to download the entire video file.
Muziza YouTube Downloader...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter 3.9.18 (1111)</title><pubDate> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 16:30:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-to-mp3-converter-1744.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-to-mp3-converter-1744.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter is the software support download youtube video and convert video to mp3 format fast and most simple. MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter allows you download and convert videos from YouTube and other websites to MP3 format by pasting the YouTube URL into the application. When you paste the URL, the program will display thumbnails for videos and you have the option to customize the title information, artist and album before you begin the process of...
</description></item><item><title>Download DS Simulia XFlow 2026 Build 124.01</title><pubDate> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 16:29:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ds-simulia-xflow-1705.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ds-simulia-xflow-1705.html
</guid><description>
SIMULIA XFlow technology provider Lattice Boltzmann unique, based on seeds for dynamics calculations of high accuracy (CFD). This technology is state-of-the-art allows users to solve the problems related to CFD complex aerodynamic high frequency transient, the geometry property of multi-phase flow, complicated interaction fluid-structure and aero music.
DS Simulia XFlow
The features of the software
	The ability to generate mesh automatically and the ability to sift adaptation of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Batch Access Database Compactor 2025.17.1105.2626</title><pubDate> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 16:29:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-batch-access-database-compactor-5068.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-batch-access-database-compactor-5068.html
</guid><description>
Batch Access Database Compactor is a software to help optimize and help compact and repair database access in an easy way. Batch Access Database Compactor can compress and repair Access database without installing Office. Batch Access Database Compactor supports project and command line. Batch Access Database Compactor has friendly GUI so used very easily. Batch Access Database Compactor Drag and Explorer Context supported.
Batch Access Database Compactor supports a compression tool...
</description></item><item><title>Download Batch XLS to PDF Converter 2025.17.1105.2074</title><pubDate> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 16:29:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-batch-xls-to-pdf-converter-5077.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-batch-xls-to-pdf-converter-5077.html
</guid><description>
Batch XLS to PDF Converter is a tool to batch convert Excel to PDF, XLS / XLSX to PDF can convert Excel XLS / XLSX to PDF format (portable document) in an easy way. Batch XLS to PDF Converter supports powerful search for lots of files. Batch XLS to PDF Converter supports project and command line. Batch XLS to PDF Converter has user friendly GUI so used very easily. Batch XLS to PDF Converter Drag and Explorer Context supported.
Batch XLS to PDF Converter supports conversion tool...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sysinternals Suite 2025.11.11</title><pubDate> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 16:28:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sysinternals-suite-1447.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sysinternals-suite-1447.html
</guid><description>
Sysinternals Suite is a software monitoring and control system helps to find and fix errors most impressive. The software includes more than seventy utilities aimed at overcoming the problem related to managing files and disks, network problems and security, as well as information about processes and systems. Because of this very rich, the analysis of each ministry will take a significant period of time and therefore, we decided to focus on the most popular.
Sysinternals Suite - Set of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Inno Setup Compiler 6.6.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 16:28:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-inno-setup-compiler-2655.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-inno-setup-compiler-2655.html
</guid><description>
Inno Setup Compiler is a system installed based on free software created by Delphi by Jordan Russell. The first version was released in 1997. QuickStart of Inno Setup include main Inno Setup and also includes an option to install the script editor Inno Script Studio. The script editor is not official and is not mandatory for general use, but help Inno Setup easier to use.
Inno Setup Compiler - software create file setup.exe
The features of Inno Setup Compiler
	Support for every...
</description></item><item><title>Download FanControl v246</title><pubDate> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 16:27:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fancontrol-5749.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fancontrol-5749.html
</guid><description>
FanControl is a highly customizable fan control software for Windows. Stay in control of every aspect of your PC's GPU and CPU fan with the help of this highly customizable fan control app.
Features of FanControl
	Save, edit and load multiple configurations
	Multiple temperature sources (CPU, GPU, motherboard, hard drive, ".sensor" files)
	Custom fan curve
	Fine tune fan control response with steps,% start,% stop, response time and delay
	Mix different curves and sensors...
</description></item><item><title>Download XL-Connector 3.6.22.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 16:27:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xl-connector-12415.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xl-connector-12415.html
</guid><description>
XL-Connector is a popular plugin that securely integrates Excel and Salesforce to export, import, refresh and transform data seamlessly with ultra-fast api connection. It provides Salesforce administrators with a comprehensive toolbox that easily performs data and metadata management activities in a familiar Excel environment.
Features
Export from Salesforce to Excel
	Get data from existing Salesforce reports or build your own SOQL queries directly into Excel.
Import data into...
</description></item><item><title>Download Thesaurus Software BrightPay UK Bureau 2025-26 v25.6.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 16:26:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-brightpay-10870.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-brightpay-10870.html
</guid><description>
BrightPay is automatic payroll and registration software that makes payroll management easy. Safe, secure and intuitive payroll software minimizes payroll management, helping you pay your employees, automatically calculate tax and submit it to HMRC. Innovative payroll software features automate key processes to help you run an efficient business service or payroll office.
Cloud technology provides powerful features including automatic backup of payroll information to the cloud, online...
</description></item></channel></rss>