<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 20:03:16 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 20:03:16 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Free Download Manager 6.32.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 02 Jan 2026 16:54:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-download-manager-3105.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-download-manager-3105.html
</guid><description>
Free Download Manager is free application download manager, Free Download Manager will significantly increase downloads by splitting the files into several smaller parts and then downloads at the same time. Speed your download will be significantly increased. Manager download free can also continue to download at broken or not responding, so you don't need start downloading from the beginning after occasionally interrupted.
Free Download Manager - Manage and speed up downloads
You can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Argente System Repair 1.0.4.5</title><pubDate> Fri, 02 Jan 2026 16:53:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-argente-system-repair-13813.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-argente-system-repair-13813.html
</guid><description>
Argente System Repair is a lightweight utility designed to diagnose and fix common Windows system problems. It scans your system to identify errors in operating system components, file systems, installation files, and other system components, and then applies targeted fixes to resolve these problems. The tool provides different scan modes, including simple scan, recommended scan, and custom scan, allowing users to customize the repair process according to their needs.
System Repair...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft PC Manager 3.19.1.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 02 Jan 2026 16:46:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-pc-manager-7924.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-pc-manager-7924.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft PC Manager is a program that offers super-fast antivirus, one-click speed boost, and system-wide security testing. It is designed to keep your PC running smoothly through a number of maintenance and security features.
Features of Microsoft PC Manager
	Boost cleans up your temporary files and improves your memory usage.
	Health Check lets you clear system logs and recent files, and you can also disable unwanted startup applications to save resources.
	Store manager has four...
</description></item><item><title>Download Any Video Downloader Pro 10.1.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 02 Jan 2026 16:46:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-video-downloader-pro-3731.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-video-downloader-pro-3731.html
</guid><description>
Any Video Downloader Pro is software support you can download video HD 720p, 1080p, 2K, 4K and 8K from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion, Vimeo, Metacafe and thousands of video sharing sites, other. It is a tool to speed up multi-threading can speed up your download faster up to 5 times. This helpful program support download at the same time. Any Video Downloader Pro lets you download multiple videos at the same time. Moreover, it allows you to pause and resume downloads if you need more...
</description></item><item><title>Download Bitvise SSH Client 9.55</title><pubDate> Fri, 02 Jan 2026 16:46:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bitvise-ssh-client-2845.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bitvise-ssh-client-2845.html
</guid><description>
Bitvise SSH Client is a SSH terminal, tunneling and file transfer application SFTP for free with the command line interface and graphics. It supports all versions desktop and server of Windows! Bitvise SSH Client for free use! Bitvise SSH Client is an application multipurpose, fast and powerful in the transmission of the advanced file helps users control and manage the terminal remotely in a flexible manner. Bitvise SSH Client intensive support for establishing the secure connection...
</description></item><item><title>Download GoodSync Enterprise 12.9.22.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 02 Jan 2026 16:46:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-goodsync-enterprise-163.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-goodsync-enterprise-163.html
</guid><description>
GoodSync Enterprise is a software that saves files and files easily and is reliable. It automatically analyts, synchronize and backup your email, family photos, contacts, MP3, financial documentation and other important files-between desktop computers, laptops, servers, external drives and Windows Mobile devices as well as remotely via FTP , SFTP, WebDAV and more. The GoodSync synchronized software combines bulletproof reliability with an extremely easy interface to compare, synchronize...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tomabo MP4 Downloader Pro 6.1.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 02 Jan 2026 16:45:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tomabo-mp4-downloader-pro-3602.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tomabo-mp4-downloader-pro-3602.html
</guid><description>
Tomabo MP4 Downloader Pro is the app designed exclusively for Windows users to help them download videos from the Internet. In addition, it also increase download speeds by up to 500%, or even more. Tomabo MP4 Downloader Pro, interface design, simple, well-organized, beautifully. Here, users can view a list of videos has download with gravatar, URL, quality, duration and size of them. Software allows download video series at the same time, at the same time, support create a list of clips...
</description></item><item><title>Download AB Download Manager 1.8.4</title><pubDate> Fri, 02 Jan 2026 16:45:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ab-download-manager-12399.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ab-download-manager-12399.html
</guid><description>
With this application, you can easily download files from anywhere. Enjoy fast, free downloads with seamless browser extension support. It is built to be a desktop application that allows you to manage and organize your downloads better than before.
AB Download Manager features
	Simple and modern UI: Simple UI and dark mode by default
	Faster download speeds: Download files using multiple connections to increase your download speed by up to 500%
	Download Queue: Create and manage your...
</description></item><item><title>Download 4KSoftware 4K Downloader 6.1.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 02 Jan 2026 16:44:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-downloader-3858.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-downloader-3858.html
</guid><description>
4K Downloader is a Windows application small but powerful to download and convert video in 4K and 8K Ultra HD from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion and thousands of other video-based websites. It speeds up your download by up to 5 times. Consider that most smart phones, TVS, computers, and tablets all support the high definition format, don't be surprised when many users want to enjoy quality content on their device. 4K Downloader is a lightweight software designed to help you grab videos...
</description></item><item><title>Download Asset Manager 2026 Enterprise 4.10.3000</title><pubDate> Fri, 02 Jan 2026 16:37:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-asset-manager-5197.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-asset-manager-5197.html
</guid><description>
Asset Manager is a professional tool help you can print barcode labels for your assets and check them in / out to employees. Attach instructions for use, logbook service and more to maintain a complete history for each of your assets. The enterprise edition of Asset Manager is designed to share database on a network. In this version, the database located on a computer shared network can access all the workstations on the network. This version allows for the number of computers is not...
</description></item><item><title>Download Robin YouTube Video Downloader Pro 7.1.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 02 Jan 2026 16:37:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-video-downloader-pro-2828.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-video-downloader-pro-2828.html
</guid><description>
YouTube Video Downloader Pro is a Windows application professional to download and convert videos from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion and thousands of video sharing sites, other. It accelerates your download up to 5 times. YouTube Video Downloader Pro allows you to download multiple videos at the same time. It also allows you to pause, resume and cancel a download at any time.
YouTube Video Downloader Pro - Download online videos on social networks
Features of YouTube Video Downloader...
</description></item><item><title>Download Kotato All Video Downloader Pro 10.1.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 02 Jan 2026 16:36:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kotato-all-video-downloader-pro-5228.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kotato-all-video-downloader-pro-5228.html
</guid><description>
Kotato All Video Downloader Pro is a Windows application professional to download and convert your favorite videos from the video sharing website. It speeds up your downloads up to 5 times! Kotato All Video Downloader Pro can download videos from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion and hundreds of video sharing sites, other. After downloading, you will be able to play them smoother on your PC or your mobile device, even when you don't have Internet access.
The main features of Kotato All...
</description></item><item><title>Download Harmony Assistant 9.9.9i</title><pubDate> Fri, 02 Jan 2026 16:36:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-harmony-assistant-7765.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-harmony-assistant-7765.html
</guid><description>
Harmony Assistant is a piece of software used for composing and editing computer-aided music. Its mixing capabilities allow composers to quickly and efficiently construct melodies that include accompaniment, multiple instruments, and drum samples. Its full page engraving and editing modes make it easy to edit and set up the page for your score.
Features of Harmony Assistant
	A wide range of musical notation will allow editing of tracks of excellent quality: the possibilities for...
</description></item><item><title>Download Win10 BrightnessSlider 1.8.29</title><pubDate> Fri, 02 Jan 2026 16:35:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-win10-brightnessslider-3116.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-win10-brightnessslider-3116.html
</guid><description>
Win10 BrightnessSlider is an open source application, simple and light, will put a brightness control small screen on the Tray of your task bar. Utilities give you the ability to adjust the brightness of the screen just by a click of the mouse. Moreover, you will be able to adjust brightness for multiple screens using this program.
Win10 BrightnessSlider suitable mainly for laptops, allows you to adjust the brightness of the screen depending on the ambient light to have good visibility...
</description></item><item><title>Download TubeDownload Pro 7.1.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 02 Jan 2026 16:34:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubedownload-pro-12035.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubedownload-pro-12035.html
</guid><description>
TubeDownload Pro is a professional Windows application for downloading your favorite videos from YouTube and hundreds of other video sites. TubeDownload Pro can increase download speed up to 500% or even more.
Features of TubeDownload Pro
	Download your favorite videos from YouTube and hundreds of other video sites.
	Increase download speed up to 500% or even more.
	Download 720p, 1080p, 2K, 4K and 8K HD videos from YouTube.
	Download entire playlists in just a few clicks.
	Download...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Video Downloader 12.1.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 02 Jan 2026 16:34:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-video-downloader-9636.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-video-downloader-9636.html
</guid><description>
YT Video Downloader is software used to easily and quickly download any video or audio content from any website in HD quality using video downloader online. Save videos from almost any website supported by a video downloader on your local hard drive. Media search is a convenient way to do this.
Features of YT Video Downloader
	Download videos from hundreds of video sites.
	Really increase your download speed by up to 500% or even more!
	Download 8K, 5K, 4K Ultra HD, 2K Quad HD, 1080p...
</description></item><item><title>Download Muziza YouTube Downloader Converter 9.1.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 02 Jan 2026 16:34:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-muziza-youtube-downloader-converter-3972.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-muziza-youtube-downloader-converter-3972.html
</guid><description>
Muziza YouTube Downloader Converter is a tool to create conditions for an attractive interface and many features to help you to download video clips from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion, Instagram and other sites. Muziza YouTube Downloader Converter can also download the video UHD 8K, 5K, 4K, QHD 2K, HD 1080p and 720p from YouTube. The app allows you download only audio stream from YouTube and save as MP3. You don't need to download the entire video file.
Muziza YouTube Downloader...
</description></item><item><title>Download Secret Video Downloader 1.0.9</title><pubDate> Fri, 02 Jan 2026 16:33:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secret-video-downloader-13775.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secret-video-downloader-13775.html
</guid><description>
Secret Video Downloader is a free application designed to facilitate easy video downloading from various websites. It leverages the yt-dlp command line program to efficiently grab video content, allowing users to save videos in the highest quality available without complicated installation or configuration. The tool has a minimalist interface focused on simplicity: the user pastes the video URL into the built-in browser, clicks the Download button, and the video is added to the download...
</description></item><item><title>Download My Family Tree 16.0.1.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 02 Jan 2026 16:33:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-my-family-tree-1664.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-my-family-tree-1664.html
</guid><description>
My Family Tree is software to create family tree, free form "Tree" or enter the file GEDCOM is there to edit. My Family Tree offers a modern interface that does not require you to be a historian to use it and help you easily get started. The program provides support for genetic data, images, videos and attachments can be added to a document family member in a detailed manner. Browse through the tree view interactive, view a slideshow of photos of the family members, review family events on...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDF Scanner app - TapScanner 3.0.93 build 3093</title><pubDate> Fri, 02 Jan 2026 16:24:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pdf-scanner-app-tapscanner-12104.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pdf-scanner-app-tapscanner-12104.html
</guid><description>
TapScanner is a mobile application that allows you to scan documents with your smartphone camera and convert them into PDF files or image formats. It essentially turns your device into a portable scanner, making capturing and digitizing physical documents convenient on the go.
TapScanner Features
	Scan documents, receipts, QRs and business cards
	Document Scanner App - Automatic Border Detection
	Tweak your images with multiple filters to achieve perfection
	Easily manage your...
</description></item><item><title>Download Chat AI - AI Chatbot Assistant 231.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 02 Jan 2026 16:24:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-chat-ai-ai-chatbot-assistant-11260.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-chat-ai-ai-chatbot-assistant-11260.html
</guid><description>
AI Chatbot is a smart artificial intelligence interactive application that brings a unique and convenient experience to users. With AI Chatbot, you can communicate and ask questions directly with a powerful AI system that helps you find information, answer questions, and even provide solutions to complex problems.
Main features of Chatbot AI include
	Natural conversation: Chatbot AI uses advanced natural language technology to understand and respond to your questions and requests...
</description></item><item><title>Download Weather Live Wallpapers 2.21.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 02 Jan 2026 16:24:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-weather-live-wallpapers-11506.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-weather-live-wallpapers-11506.html
</guid><description>
The movement of the sun, rainfall and phases of the moon are realistic animations on the screen with beautifully crafted details. The picturesque landscape reflects the weather with astonishing accuracy. Enjoy the sunrise, the rainbow, the birds singing and all the bright sunshine!
You can use real weather apps as wallpaper on your screen, they will reflect the current weather and you will always know the weather conditions. You can also launch the weather app in a window or install a...
</description></item><item><title>Download Power VPN: Fast &amp;amp; Secure VPN 2.3 build 424</title><pubDate> Fri, 02 Jan 2026 16:23:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-power-vpn-fast-secure-vpn-10109.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-power-vpn-fast-secure-vpn-10109.html
</guid><description>
Power VPN - Free Unlimited VPN Master for Android. Now you can easily access blocked Internet Content with just one click with PowerVPN's Fast and Secure VPN Tunnel. Power VPN Free VPN is the fastest VPN with a secure server network worldwide.
Power VPN Features: Fast and Secure VPN
	This is the best VPN (free VPN) ever created. Create your IPVanish
	Simple interface. Just click to connect
	Over 30 different server locations worldwide to connect to.
	Allows torrenting, P2P, and file...
</description></item><item><title>Download My APK 3.2.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 02 Jan 2026 16:23:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-my-apk-9231.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-my-apk-9231.html
</guid><description>
My APK extracts your installed apps (including system apps) and saves the apk file for backup to your SD card (or your main storage). This version does not require root permissions. Share apk with friends via Bluetooth, email or social networking apps.
My APK Features
Application Manager
	List all your apps (including system apps)
	Filter apps by app type: system (pre-installed) or user (third-party apps)
	Sort apps by name, package name, installation and update date, app size...
</description></item><item><title>Download Myriad PDFtoMusic Pro 2.1.0i</title><pubDate> Fri, 02 Jan 2026 13:41:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-myriad-pdftomusic-pro-14429.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-myriad-pdftomusic-pro-14429.html
</guid><description>
Are the musical scores you created with your old music editing software no longer compatible with the new software? Do you own musical scores in PDF format and want to edit them using your favorite music editing software? Until now, the only solution has been to re-import the entire score or print it out and use optical character recognition software to convert it, with varying degrees of success, into an editable document.
This way of thinking is now outdated. From a document in PDF...
</description></item></channel></rss>