<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:48:48 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:48:48 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download UEFITool A73</title><pubDate> Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:02:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-uefitool-4063.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-uefitool-4063.html
</guid><description>
UEFITool allows edit, parse and extract images, UEFITool support analysis, pictures, BIOS full cover sets description flash or any binary files which contains the volume of UEFI; it is compatible with many types of image BIOS including ROM, BIN, FD, CAP, BIO, WPH and EFI, all of them will load and display convenient together with the appropriate details, including name, category / sub category and text such.
UEFITool - Extract images
UEFITool will allow you to extract data from an...
</description></item><item><title>Download KMPlayer (KMP) 2026.1.26.43 x64 / 4.2.3.31 x86</title><pubDate> Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:01:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kmplayer-kmp-902.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kmplayer-kmp-902.html
</guid><description>
KMPlayer (KMP) is software watch movies listen to music multi-function for video enthusiasts. KMPlayer development is many types of the format different. KMPlayer has improved on sound quality, images when listening to music and watching movies, the playback speed of video is faster, more codec player is added to the software video decoder is optimized.
KMPlayer also supports a variety of audio formats and video and offers a the interface can be customized with the preview coverflow and...
</description></item><item><title>Download RapidRAW 1.4.9</title><pubDate> Mon, 26 Jan 2026 16:54:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rapidraw-13957.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rapidraw-13957.html
</guid><description>
RapidRAW is a modern, high-performance, open-source RAW photo editor, designed to deliver a fast and clean editing experience with a lightweight footprint (under 30MB). Built with performance and usability in mind, the software is aimed at photographers who want a simple, efficient, and fun workflow without compromising performance.
Key Features
	GPU-accelerated processing: Uses a custom WGSL shader to process all image adjustments on the GPU, allowing for smooth, responsive editing...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinTools.one Professional / Home 26.1.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 26 Jan 2026 16:53:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wintoolsone-10808.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wintoolsone-10808.html
</guid><description>
WinTools.one is a program designed to help both regular and advanced users as well as computer engineers fine-tune the MS Windows operating system. It allows you to increase the performance of the operating system, maintain its performance at a high level, fix operating system errors, free up space on the computer's hard drive and control the operation of installed programs. In addition, the program allows you to store and protect your secret and confidential information, as well as work...
</description></item><item><title>Download O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Premium 22.2.1149</title><pubDate> Mon, 26 Jan 2026 16:53:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-diskimage-server-4547.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-diskimage-server-4547.html
</guid><description>
O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Server is software that is specially designed for use in enterprise environments, the software allows users to backup all the files you want and keep them safe from any incident or disaster computer. O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Server comes with a variety of easy to use utility that allows users to backup entire partitions of the specific files from their PC, as well as recover the version previous data of them, all from a simple interface.
O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Server - data...
</description></item><item><title>Download ExifTool 13.46</title><pubDate> Mon, 26 Jan 2026 16:52:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-exiftool-1685.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-exiftool-1685.html
</guid><description>
ExifTool is a library of Perl platform-independent plus a command line application for reading, writing, and editing meta information in various file types. ExifTool supports many metadata formats including EXIF , GPS , IPTC , XMP , JFIF , GeoTIFF , ICC Profile , Photoshop IRB , FlashPix , AFCP and ID3 , as well as notes of the manufacturer of many digital cameras by Canon , Casio , DJI , FLIR , FujiFilm , GE , GoPro , HP , JVC / Victor , Kodak , Leaf , Minolta / Konica-Minolta , Motorola...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinScript 1.4.7</title><pubDate> Mon, 26 Jan 2026 16:52:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winscript-12800.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winscript-12800.html
</guid><description>
WinScript is an open source tool built to help you build custom scripts for Windows 10 and 11. It includes scripts for debugging, privacy, performance, and more, along with the ability to install all your favorite apps with just one click.
Features
	Debloat: Remove Windows bloatware, CoPilot, Edge, OneDrive, and other pre-installed features preset.
	Privacy: Disable Windows and 3rd party data collection, tracking, app access, and telemetry.
	Performance: Set background services to...
</description></item><item><title>Download 4KSoftware 4K Downloader 6.1.6</title><pubDate> Mon, 26 Jan 2026 16:51:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-downloader-3858.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-downloader-3858.html
</guid><description>
4K Downloader is a Windows application small but powerful to download and convert video in 4K and 8K Ultra HD from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion and thousands of other video-based websites. It speeds up your download by up to 5 times. Consider that most smart phones, TVS, computers, and tablets all support the high definition format, don't be surprised when many users want to enjoy quality content on their device. 4K Downloader is a lightweight software designed to help you grab videos...
</description></item><item><title>Download Helium Music Manager Premium 17.4.564</title><pubDate> Mon, 26 Jan 2026 16:51:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-helium-music-manager-premium-164.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-helium-music-manager-premium-164.html
</guid><description>
Helium Music Manager is a music manager that can rip, tag, play, browse, search, rename, burn and synchronize your music with the mobile. You can control your music collection with Helium Music Manager. Stop using time looking for the file on your computer or looking through CDS, vinyl records and tapes - instead, simply enjoy and explore your music! Helium Music Manager can replace the ripper, the player, tag editor and related software to audio your other.
Helium Music Manager...
</description></item><item><title>Download Pepakura Designer 6.1.4</title><pubDate> Mon, 26 Jan 2026 16:51:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pepakura-designer-748.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pepakura-designer-748.html
</guid><description>
Pepakura Designer is software to create 2D models, 3D quick, easy and developed in Japan. Pepakura Designer helps easily design the template paper craft by importing data 3D model. No special knowledge is required to model papercraft. All you have to do is prepare the 3D model. You can use some software 3DCG released from other developers to make the 3D models for unfolding.
Pepakura Designer - Create model 2D 3D
Pepakura Designer to create the form of 2D images that you can share it...
</description></item><item><title>Download Eltima CloudMounter 3.6.2112</title><pubDate> Mon, 26 Jan 2026 16:49:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-eltima-cloudmounter-6553.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-eltima-cloudmounter-6553.html
</guid><description>
Eltima CloudMounter is a reliable system utility that allows mounting various cloud storages and web servers to your personal computer as a local disk . Connect to Microsoft OneDrive, Google Drive, Amazon S3, Dropbox, FTP, and WebDAV servers in Finder, just as if they were on your machine.
Eltima CloudMounter Features
	Mapping cloud storage as a network drive to manage files online the same way you manage files locally.
	Access the clouds easily with CloudMounter
	You can mount...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube Downloader 3.9.18 (2501)</title><pubDate> Mon, 26 Jan 2026 16:48:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube Downloader  is a dedicated software that helps users  downloading youtube videos  Favorites on PC for offline viewing. With MediaHuman YouTube  Downloader  you can download videos from youtube website to your computer with  fast speed , with special software development technology that automatically receives videos from Websites, in addition to the ability to download videos from software websites, can convert downloaded video formats to various formats for the purpose...
</description></item><item><title>Download Kotato All Video Downloader Pro 10.1.6</title><pubDate> Mon, 26 Jan 2026 16:48:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kotato-all-video-downloader-pro-5228.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kotato-all-video-downloader-pro-5228.html
</guid><description>
Kotato All Video Downloader Pro is a Windows application professional to download and convert your favorite videos from the video sharing website. It speeds up your downloads up to 5 times! Kotato All Video Downloader Pro can download videos from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion and hundreds of video sharing sites, other. After downloading, you will be able to play them smoother on your PC or your mobile device, even when you don't have Internet access.
The main features of Kotato All...
</description></item><item><title>Download Yellow Leads Extractor 9.3.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 26 Jan 2026 16:48:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yellow-leads-extractor-3729.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yellow-leads-extractor-3729.html
</guid><description>
Yellow Leads Extractor is the software that allows users to make 100% custom search in the browser. When you have this program then you don't need to do more work to retrieve information from the yellow pages. You just need to enter the category and location. After entering the information when you will click on the option data get then all the information will be extracted.
Yellow Leads Extractor - custom Search on the browser
The features of the Yellow Leads Extractor
	You can save...
</description></item><item><title>Download XMedia Recode 3.6.2.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 26 Jan 2026 16:47:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xmedia-recode-919.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xmedia-recode-919.html
</guid><description>
XMedia Recode is software to change the quality for video files on windows operating system, it has the ability to change quality, video format. XMedia Recode supports the format conversion such as 3GP, 3GPP, 3GPP2, AAC, AC3, AIFF, AMR, ASF, AU, AVI, DIVX, DTS, DVR-MS, FLV, H. 261, H. 263, H. 264, M4A, M1V, M2V, M4V, MKV.
Parameters advanced
The user can step into the more advanced and modify bitrate, frame interval the frame rate, modes, speed control and many other settings regarding...
</description></item><item><title>Download VidCoder 12.16 + Portable</title><pubDate> Mon, 26 Jan 2026 16:47:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vidcoder-534.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vidcoder-534.html
</guid><description>
VidCoder is software to convert movies to MKV and MP4, as well as extract video content from DVDS and Blu-ray. This is a software utility to help people extract the video content from the BD and DVD as well as convert the clips specific to MKV and MP4.
VidCoder has an interface that includes a clear design, including a menu bar, several buttons and a panel to display the queue. The file can be added with the help of the file browser or drag and drop-out.
Features VidCoder
	VidCoder...
</description></item><item><title>Download NWinfo 1.6.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 26 Jan 2026 16:46:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nwinfo-12590.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nwinfo-12590.html
</guid><description>
NWinfo is a Win32 program that allows you to obtain system and hardware information. It displays essential information about CPU, memory, disk, network, and even system operating details. Because it's portable, you can carry NWinfo on a USB stick and use it on any Windows machine, making it a useful tool for both tech enthusiasts and troubleshooters.
Features of NWinfo
	Get detailed information about SMBIOS, CPUID, S.M.A.R.T., PCI, EDID, etc.
	Supports export in JSON, YAML and LUA...
</description></item><item><title>Download BitRecover MSG to PDF Wizard 26.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 26 Jan 2026 16:46:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bitrecover-msg-to-pdf-wizard-01en-7576.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bitrecover-msg-to-pdf-wizard-01en-7576.html
</guid><description>
BitRecover MSG to PDF Wizard is a versatile file converter designed to batch convert Outlook messages to PDF using efficient algorithms. Users can selectively convert Outlook emails to adobe PDF files after successfully activating this program.
This tool has a clear GUI and is quick to use, so any user can save MSG files as PDF files quickly. No experience or technical skills are required to open MSG files in PDF format. For conversion, both ANSI and UNICODE MSG files are well...
</description></item><item><title>Download TubeDownload Pro 7.1.3</title><pubDate> Mon, 26 Jan 2026 16:45:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubedownload-pro-12035.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubedownload-pro-12035.html
</guid><description>
TubeDownload Pro is a professional Windows application for downloading your favorite videos from YouTube and hundreds of other video sites. TubeDownload Pro can increase download speed up to 500% or even more.
Features of TubeDownload Pro
	Download your favorite videos from YouTube and hundreds of other video sites.
	Increase download speed up to 500% or even more.
	Download 720p, 1080p, 2K, 4K and 8K HD videos from YouTube.
	Download entire playlists in just a few clicks.
	Download...
</description></item><item><title>Download Replay Media Catcher 2026.1.23.33</title><pubDate> Mon, 26 Jan 2026 16:45:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-replay-media-catcher-1560.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-replay-media-catcher-1560.html
</guid><description>
Replay Media Catcher is a tool to convert and download videos best today and support downloads, audio / MP3, or recording. Replay Media Catcher using technology download enhanced to record video, and MP3 files with playback speed up to 10 times. Integrates with iTunes, DropBox, Google Drive or SkyDrive for automatically copying files to your phone or tablet, Apple or Android your.
Replay Media Catcher - convert and download video
Software Replay Media Catcher software is download at...
</description></item><item><title>Download TubeMate Downloader 6.1.8</title><pubDate> Mon, 26 Jan 2026 16:44:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubemate-downloader-4250.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubemate-downloader-4250.html
</guid><description>
TubeMate Downloader is a smart application that lets you download any clip you want from the website hosting the main video and convert them in when download at or then. If you need a simple and effective tool to download videos, you can give it a try. With TubeMate Downloader, you can directly drag and drop video link from your browser into the drop-down box or application window to start downloading. You don't even need to copy and paste the video URL.
TubeMate Downloader - Support...
</description></item><item><title>Download Song List Generator 5.3.5</title><pubDate> Mon, 26 Jan 2026 16:44:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-song-list-generator-2376.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-song-list-generator-2376.html
</guid><description>
Song List Generator is software that support you to create song books professional from files MP3, karaoke, or video of you in just a few clicks. This tool is very useful for DJ, KJ or anyone storing their music on hard drive and want to have the song professionally without the hassle in maintaining the database.
The list of songs just read the music files right from your hard drive and create a song book can print, cut and chopped in any way you want (by artist, title, DiscID,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Social Media Downloader 8.1.5</title><pubDate> Mon, 26 Jan 2026 16:43:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-socialmediaapps-facebook-video-downloader-3742.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-socialmediaapps-facebook-video-downloader-3742.html
</guid><description>
SocialVideo Downloader (formerly SocialMediaApps Facebook Video Downloader) is a Windows application to download and convert your favorite videos from Facebook and hundreds of other video sharing sites. It increases your loading speed by up to 500%, or even more! The application has a simple and intuitive user interface, its main functions and features are quite obvious to anyone. , regardless of prior experience with similar purpose tools.
&amp;nbsp;
SocialVideo Downloader
The main...
</description></item><item><title>Download Nova Launcher 81018 (8.2.8) Final</title><pubDate> Mon, 26 Jan 2026 16:41:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-nova-launcher-10503.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-nova-launcher-10503.html
</guid><description>
Nova Launcher is a powerful, customizable, and flexible home screen replacement. Nova brings advanced features to enhance your home screen but remains a great, user-friendly choice for everyone. Whether you want to completely overhaul your home screen or are looking for a cleaner, faster home screen launcher, Nova is the answer.
Nova Launcher Features
	Latest features: Nova brings the latest Android launcher features to all other phones.
	Custom icon themes: Nova supports thousands of...
</description></item><item><title>Download YoWindow Weather - Unlimited 2.55.4</title><pubDate> Mon, 26 Jan 2026 16:41:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-yowindow-weather-unlimited-8421.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-yowindow-weather-unlimited-8421.html
</guid><description>
YoWindow is a unique new weather app. The magic of YoWindow is a living landscape that reflects your real-life weather. For example, if it rains - it will rain in YoWindow. Sunset and sunrise in YoWindow take place at the same time as in real life. But the cool thing is you can roll time forward. Just swipe the screen and you'll see how the weather changes throughout the day.
YoWindow Weather Features - Unlimited
	All the weather at your fingertips. You see the current weather,...
</description></item></channel></rss>