<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 05:34:03 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 05:34:03 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download LDPlayer 9.1.75.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 07 Nov 2025 01:05:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ldplayer-2331.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ldplayer-2331.html
</guid><description>
LDPlayer is an Android emulator that allows users to play games and run applications on Windows computers. LDPlayer supports heavy gaming, running chat applications, editing photos, videos, and many other Android applications. LDPlayer is compatible with Android 5.1 and above, supporting multitasking for an experience that is not inferior to that of using on Mobile.
Installation is a simple and quick process that does not require any special attention from you, there are more. settings,...
</description></item><item><title>Download ASUS GPU Tweak III 2.0.4.5</title><pubDate> Fri, 07 Nov 2025 01:04:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-asus-gpu-tweak-3252.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-asus-gpu-tweak-3252.html
</guid><description>
ASUS GPU Tweak is a tools overclocking powerful and full-featured allows you to significantly enhance the performance of the graphics processor ASUS. Utility that allows you to get the best results just by few mouse clicks. ASUS GPU Tweak has a number mode allows you to adjust the parameters of graphics according to the specific needs of his. Mode OC allows you to benefit from maximum performance supplied by your graphics card. Game play mode allows you to play the game using the default...
</description></item><item><title>Download Office Timeline Plus 12.00.00.00 Expert / Pro / Pro+ Edition</title><pubDate> Fri, 07 Nov 2025 01:03:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-timeline-2106.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-timeline-2106.html
</guid><description>
Office Timeline is an add-on very useful and powerful software for Microsoft PowerPoint. With add-ons, you can create PowerPoint documents look more beautiful. With add-ons, you can add the time Line on the project by yourself. Application time for the composition and different segments of the document, your PowerPoint will not only increase the beauty for your work, but also for customers and your manager. The people who created this product is also believe that add-ons this is the only...
</description></item><item><title>Download Capture One Pro 16.7.1.3218 + Enterprise</title><pubDate> Fri, 07 Nov 2025 01:03:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capture-one-pro-624.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capture-one-pro-624.html
</guid><description>
Capture One Pro is the software solution complete photo editing. With powerful tools to organize, color grading, editing grades, and more, you have full control over the images and process his work. Capture One has been developed with quality images and easy to use. Every tool is designed to give you full control over all aspects of the process editing - preserve, restore and optimize all information from the file RAW of you. Full the tool provides the ability to expand to always achieve...
</description></item><item><title>Download LicenseCrawler 2.16.2862</title><pubDate> Fri, 07 Nov 2025 01:02:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-licensecrawler-490.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-licensecrawler-490.html
</guid><description>
LicenseCrawler is software scans windows system to find the product key of the software purchased and registered. This software no need to install so that you can save on a USB flash drive, external drive or storage similar, save it to any computer and run it.
In addition, you can just drop application's files on any location of hard drive. Most important factor is that the Windows Registry does not receive new entries, and can't find the files, are left on the hard drive after removing...
</description></item><item><title>Download Diffchecker 6.6.3</title><pubDate> Fri, 07 Nov 2025 01:01:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-diffchecker-5025.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-diffchecker-5025.html
</guid><description>
Diffchecker is a application compare text, images and powerful file to desktop of your. Available for Windows, macOS. Compare text files, documents, PDF. Compare photos, graphics. Because Diffchecker Desktop running entirely on your computer, so it does not have to communicate with our servers to create your difference. This means that there is no other way in addition you can view your sensitive data, you.
Diffchecker Desktop run offline, that means you can use it anytime, anywhere and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Steinberg VST Live Pro 2.2.80</title><pubDate> Fri, 07 Nov 2025 01:01:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-steinberg-vst-live-pro-7557.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-steinberg-vst-live-pro-7557.html
</guid><description>
Steinberg VST Live Pro is a unique, stable software solution designed for musicians who want to deliver a great performance, including sound, light and video, wherever they are. VST Live comes with a wide range of virtual instruments, sync features for music, text and chord symbols showing on other devices, video, Cubase import, MIDI tracks for lighting control Live DMX and more.
Features of Steinberg VST Live Pro
The core of your live production.
Has all the functionality needed to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Acrobat Reader DC 2025.001.20844</title><pubDate> Fri, 07 Nov 2025 01:00:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-acrobat-reader-3707.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-acrobat-reader-3707.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Acrobat Reader DC is a system of application software and Web services developed by Adobe Systems to view, create, manipulate, print and manage PDF files. With Adobe Acrobat Reader DC, you can create, export, edit, and track PDF files from anywhere - and maintain connection with the recent set of files on all your devices.
Adobe Acrobat Reader current DC is connected with Adobe Document Cloud - help working on the computers and mobile devices becomes easier than ever before. This is...
</description></item><item><title>Download Awesome Miner Ultimate 11.3.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 07 Nov 2025 01:00:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-awesome-miner-9041.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-awesome-miner-9041.html
</guid><description>
Awesome Miner is a software application designed to manage and monitor cryptocurrency mining operations. It supports a wide variety of mining hardware, including ASICs and GPUs, and can be used to manage mining for a variety of cryptocurrencies, including Bitcoin, Ethereum, and Litecoin.
Powerful tool to manage and monitor cryptocurrency mining activities. With support for a wide variety of mining hardware and cryptocurrencies, mobile apps, and customizable alerting and performance...
</description></item><item><title>Download ChrisPC Free VPN Connection 4.25.1106</title><pubDate> Fri, 07 Nov 2025 00:59:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-free-vpn-connection-2887.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-free-vpn-connection-2887.html
</guid><description>
ChrisPC Free VPN Connection software allows you to create VPN connection (virtual private network) to the server for free from the United States, Germany, Canada, France, Germany, Russia, Singapore, the Netherlands. This will help you to unblock your favorite sites to watch free TV and on-demand television when living abroad, travelling, on business or vacation. In addition, here is the solution to overcome the limited area for the popular websites: Google, YouTube, Facebook, Instagram,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Service Trigger Editor 5.0.9.12</title><pubDate> Fri, 07 Nov 2025 00:46:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-service-trigger-editor-12140.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-service-trigger-editor-12140.html
</guid><description>
Service Trigger Editor allows Windows Services to start or stop when certain conditions are met. With this app, services can run efficiently, only when needed — instead of having to start at startup and run 24x7.
Controlling these rules will help prevent certain services from always running, which could potentially clog up your system resources. It is displayed from a clear interface that includes mouse-over help for different areas when needed. The top pane shows all the services...
</description></item><item><title>Download Inno Setup Unpacker 2.0.7</title><pubDate> Fri, 07 Nov 2025 00:46:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-inno-setup-unpacker-12546.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-inno-setup-unpacker-12546.html
</guid><description>
Inno Setup is a popular and reliable application that creates program installers by helping you create scripts. Extracting the installation files from their container, resulting from compiling code with Inno Setup, can only be done through self-extracting files. In other words, you need to create a self-extracting executable to shell the installation documents.
Inno Setup Unpacker can help you avoid such actions, which is especially useful because some system security protocols block...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaInfo 25.10</title><pubDate> Fri, 07 Nov 2025 00:45:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediainfo-1456.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediainfo-1456.html
</guid><description>
MediaInfo is a software that provides access to view the information of media files, such as technical information and tags of the video file and bad sound. Software displays detailed information including: format, profile, commercial name of the format, duration, bit rate overall, writing application and library, title, author, director, album, track number, updates.
MediaInfo - View file info media
The features and functions of MediaInfo
	Container: format, profile, commercial name...
</description></item><item><title>Download DBF Converter 7.67</title><pubDate> Fri, 07 Nov 2025 00:40:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbf-converter-6362.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbf-converter-6362.html
</guid><description>
DBF Converter is a common solution for all your DBF format conversion needs. Whenever you need to extract data from the DBF file to CSV, XLS, XLSX, SQL or pure text, the software will provide a simple way to do this with minimal effort.
Features of DBF Converter
	Work with DBF Converter is easy. You specify a DBF file or a directory with DBF files that you want to convert, select the fields and filter out the records you need. Then, just a click to DBF Converter to turn the source...
</description></item><item><title>Download Hasleo Backup Suite 5.5.2.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 07 Nov 2025 00:40:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hasleo-backup-suite-6588.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hasleo-backup-suite-6588.html
</guid><description>
Hasleo Backup Suite is a free backup and free Windows recovery, integration of backup features, recovery, and replication, it is designed for Windows operating system users and can be used on both Windows PC and Windows Server. The backup and recovery feature of Hasleo Backup Suite can help you backup and restore your Windows, disk and partition operating system to protect your Windows operating system and your personal data. The replication feature of Hasleo Backup Suite can help you...
</description></item><item><title>Download BackupAssist 15.0.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 06 Nov 2025 21:59:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-backupassist-4533.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-backupassist-4533.html
</guid><description>
BackupAssist is a software application that allows you to create backup for all file types, as well as recover and restore the item, follow the process is running and creating reports. BackupAssist is built for small and medium business is developing your. Select backup software Windows help to keep safe your data. Software backup storage to your server from the ruin. Never lose data again. Use BackupAssist to perform backups onsite and offsite to protect your server.
BackupAssist -...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tiny11 Builder September 2025 Release</title><pubDate> Thu, 06 Nov 2025 21:56:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tiny11-builder-14276.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tiny11-builder-14276.html
</guid><description>
Tiny11 Builder is a PowerShell script for creating a slimmed-down Windows 11 ISO file. Tiny11 is a lightweight version of Windows 11, stripped of unnecessary components and optimized for installation size - designed for practical use on older or low-end computers or virtual machines.
You can now use it on any Windows 11 release (not just a specific build), as well as any language. You can now create your own Tiny11 ISO file.
Script version:
tiny11maker.ps1: Standard script, removes...
</description></item><item><title>Download ViVeTool 0.3.4</title><pubDate> Thu, 06 Nov 2025 21:44:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vivetool-14275.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vivetool-14275.html
</guid><description>
ViVe is a C# library that you can use to create your own programs that interact with the A/B feature testing mechanism included in Windows 10 and later.
The FeatureManager class will cover most of your feature management needs, with the added benefit of having some of the complex operations done for you. Boot Persistence and LKG management are only provided by this class as it has been reimplemented.
In case you want to interface directly with NTDLL exports, you can use NativeMethods....
</description></item><item><title>Download Puran Utilities 3.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 06 Nov 2025 21:38:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-puran-utilities-14274.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-puran-utilities-14274.html
</guid><description>
Puran Utilities is a suite of over 20 software utilities, including but not limited to utilities that can help you get the most out of your computer's performance. It also provides automatic and one-click solutions to keep your computer clean and error-free.
Tools and Features Included
	Disk Check - Helps you fix errors and recover bad sectors on your hard drive using chkdsk.
	Uninstaller - Helps you uninstall unnecessary software and also software that cannot be uninstalled...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wise Care 365 Pro 7.3.2.716</title><pubDate> Thu, 06 Nov 2025 20:47:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wise-care-365-pro-106.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wise-care-365-pro-106.html
</guid><description>
Wise Care 365 pro is a package of utilities registry, disk, and other systems important for your PC. Easy to use and effective, Wise Care 365 is the best solution to improve the performance of your computer. Get Wise Care 365 and your computer will never run slow again!
Wise Care 365 pro is what?
Wise Care 365 Pro
	Check PC a clicks
	Pc cleaning &amp;amp; speed up
	Inventory hardware
	Protecting your privacy
	Protect real-time system
	Silent mode
	Boot speed faster
	Freeing up disk...
</description></item><item><title>Download EmEditor Pro 25.4.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 06 Nov 2025 20:47:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-emeditor-pro-69.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-emeditor-pro-69.html
</guid><description>
EmEditor Pro - the professional version of editor text powerful for programmers, web developers and ordinary users with illumination of syntax and Unicode support. The features of the editor such as search and replace in files using regular expressions, automatic code detect, bookmark link and address email, block selection mode, configure the button bar, menu, font and elements color. With each language you can set separate configuration.
EmEditor Pro - text Editor professional
The...
</description></item><item><title>Download CyberLink PhotoDirector Ultra 2026 v17.0.1031.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 06 Nov 2025 20:46:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-photodirector-ultra-129.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-photodirector-ultra-129.html
</guid><description>
Cyberlink PhotoDirector Ultra is known to be photo editing tools and videos with the effect is extremely rich, help you to change the style for the individual images or the videos of his favorite. This software integrated the 3D engine helps to speed up Video processing, which allows accessing the repository effect online and extract the Videos into the movies 3D Bru-ray, 3D AVCHD.
Cyberlink PhotoDirector Ultra to offer users a more professional tool to handle their images, remove...
</description></item><item><title>Download PhotoPad Image Editor Pro 14.48</title><pubDate> Thu, 06 Nov 2025 20:46:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photopad-image-editor-572.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photopad-image-editor-572.html
</guid><description>
PhotoPad Image Editor is a software to help edit photos and supports lots of features like edit, cut, rotate, resize and flip digital photos. With PhotoPad Image Editor, you can freely perform the basic editing for their images and also can add some neat effect. It has the option to create a photo collage and mosaic images from your photos, and you can also add text and captions. If you prefer, you can complete your masterpiece by adding the frame or contour is simple.
The main features...
</description></item><item><title>Download A4ScanDoc 2.0.9.30</title><pubDate> Thu, 06 Nov 2025 20:45:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-a4scandoc-4421.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-a4scandoc-4421.html
</guid><description>
A4ScanDoc is a software solution useful provide you with a set of features reasonable and support the document feeder and two-sided printing, at the same time provides a fast scanning engine handy based on the profile of users to create. It is very easy to use, and it has a minimalist interface, while somewhat outdated, has intuitive layout. However, the application does not provide materials to help first-time users.
A4ScanDoc - Scan and print documents
When one or more documents have...
</description></item><item><title>Download AmoyShare AnyVid 10.9.5</title><pubDate> Thu, 06 Nov 2025 20:45:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-amoyshare-anyvid-7833.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-amoyshare-anyvid-7833.html
</guid><description>
AmoyShare AnyVid is the best video downloader that allows you to download videos from 1000+ websites. It offers HD video downloads of various categories, including streaming videos, TV episodes, TV series and more. Besides video format, you can directly convert video to MP4 or MP3 with the best video downloader.
Easy to download videos from any website, such as TikTok, Facebook, Instagram, Reddit, Tumblr, Twitch, Niconico, V Live, Naver, Lynda, TED Talk. With AmoyShare AnyVid, you can...
</description></item></channel></rss>