<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 13:50:25 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 13:50:25 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download The Dude 7.20.6</title><pubDate> Wed, 31 Dec 2025 16:49:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-the-dude-3238.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-the-dude-3238.html
</guid><description>
The Dude is a new application by MikroTik which can dramatically improve the way you manage your network environment. It will automatically scan all devices in the subnet is specified, draw and layout a map of your networks, monitor services of your devices and alert you in case some service has problems.is a new application by MikroTik which can dramatically improve the way you manage your network environment. It will automatically scan all devices in the subnet is specified, draw and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Playnite 10.47</title><pubDate> Wed, 31 Dec 2025 16:49:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-playnite-6972.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-playnite-6972.html
</guid><description>
Playnite is an open-source video game library manager and manager with support for third-party libraries such as Steam, GOG, Origin, Battle.net and Uplay. Includes supporting the game, providing a unified interface for your game. With Playnite, you can comfortably enter the game from Steam, Battle.net, Origin, GOG and Uplay services, including uninstalled games.
You have three options to view when using Playnite. You also have the custom game option or add any game or program with...
</description></item><item><title>Download WPS Office - PDF, Word, Excel, PPT 18.24 build 1553</title><pubDate> Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:47:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wps-office-pdf-word-excel-ppt-8244.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wps-office-pdf-word-excel-ppt-8244.html
</guid><description>
WPS Office is a mobile office suite app that allows users to view, edit and create documents, spreadsheets, and presentations on their Android device. The app is available for download from the Google Play Store and is compatible with a wide range of file formats, including Microsoft Office documents.
WPS Office - Free Office suite for Word, PDF, Excel, is an all-in-one office suite that integrates Word, PDF, Excel, PowerPoint, Forms, Cloud Storage, Online Editing, Template library and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Super File Manager Explorer 1.5.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:47:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-esuper-file-explorer-9196.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-esuper-file-explorer-9196.html
</guid><description>
ESuper File Explorer is a file management app for Android devices that allows users to browse and manage files on their devices. Free, safe and simple, manage your files efficiently and easily with ESuper File Explorer. ESuper File Explorer is a simple and powerful file explorer for Android devices. It's free, fast and fully functional.
Features of ESuper File Explorer
	Shortcut bar: Supports all file operations
	Cleaner: Clean all junk files with just one click
	Disk analysis:...
</description></item><item><title>Download Device Info: System &amp;amp; CPU Info 3.4.1.3</title><pubDate> Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:46:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-device-info-system-cpu-info-8723.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-device-info-system-cpu-info-8723.html
</guid><description>
Device Information: System &amp;amp; CPU Information is a mobile application that provides users with detailed information about the hardware and software specifications of their device. This app is designed to help users better understand their device's capabilities and performance as well as diagnose any potential issues or problems.
With Device Info: System and CPU Info, users can view information about the processor, memory, storage, battery, sensors, and more. of equipment. This app...
</description></item><item><title>Download ProShot 8.32.5.2 build 543</title><pubDate> Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:46:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-proshot-8195.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-proshot-8195.html
</guid><description>
ProShot is a camera app for Android devices that offers advanced manual controls for photography enthusiasts. It allows users to manually adjust settings such as shutter speed, ISO, white balance, and focus. It also offers a level of integration, a powerful time-lapse mode, and many other features for advanced photography. It's designed for advanced users who want more control over their photos than the default camera app offers.
Camera features of ProShot
	Auto, Program, Manual and...
</description></item><item><title>Download 1Weather: Forecast &amp;amp; Radar 11.9.5</title><pubDate> Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:46:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-1weather-forecast-radar-8846.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-1weather-forecast-radar-8846.html
</guid><description>
1Weather is the most popular weather application on Google Play. Whether you want to check temperatures, forecast precipitation, Doppler radar, or simply track the current phases of the sun and moon, 1Weather has you covered. Plus, it's got an outstanding design that makes getting your weather information easy and fun.
Track current conditions and forecasts for your location and up to 12 locations of your choice. Access charts, precipitation forecasts, maps, weather information and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Photo Mate R3 4.1.0 build 210</title><pubDate> Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:45:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-photo-mate-r3-10159.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-photo-mate-r3-10159.html
</guid><description>
Organize your images!
	Photo Mate provides a photo library where you can filter and sort all your files based on metadata like camera, aperture or ISO as well as ratings, labels and custom keywords.&amp;lt; /li&amp;gt;
	The library can handle jpg as well as almost any camera raw format.
	You can rate, tag, and tag your images, and Photo Mate creates popular XMP Subfiles that are also compatible with desktop programs.
See your images!
	Photo Mate provides a solution to view your images...
</description></item><item><title>Download Auto Text: Schedule Messages 5.9.3</title><pubDate> Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:45:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-auto-text-auto-send-message-8447.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-auto-text-auto-send-message-8447.html
</guid><description>
Auto Text: Auto send WA &amp;amp; SMS is a feature or application that allows users to automatically send pre-written text messages at a specific time or in response to a request. specific activation. This feature can be useful in many situations, such as sending reminders, sending messages to loved ones at a specific time, or sending messages in response to certain events, such as calls to or location-based triggers.
Auto Text features: Auto send WA &amp;amp; SMS
	Automatically send happy...
</description></item><item><title>Download Black Screen: video screen off 1.9.9</title><pubDate> Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:44:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-black-screen-video-screen-off-8740.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-black-screen-video-screen-off-8740.html
</guid><description>
Black Screen allows you to play videos when the screen is off. Turn off the screen at any time and save battery. The black screen can be used to watch music videos, listen to podcasts, record videos, take selfies, and more. when your screen is off. This helps save battery in AMOLED and OLED devices because the screen turns off completely when displaying black.
Use the floating button to quickly turn off the screen and unlock it by tapping the screen.
Black Screen feature: turn off...
</description></item><item><title>Download Librera PRO - Book reader 9.2.20</title><pubDate> Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:44:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-librera-pro-all-my-books-9008.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-librera-pro-all-my-books-9008.html
</guid><description>
PRO Librera Reader is an easy-to-use and highly configurable reading application that supports most popular document formats, including: PDF, EPUB, EPUB3, MOBI, DjVu, FB2, FB2.zip, TXT, RTF, AZW, AZW3, CBR, CBZ, HTML, XPS, MHT and more. With a simple yet powerful interface, Librera Reader makes reading documents a real pleasure. Librera even has a unique hands-free, auto-scrolling music mode.
Some key features of Librera reader include:
Easily explore documents with optional and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Piktures: All-In-One Gallery 2.24 build 947</title><pubDate> Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:44:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-piktures-gallery-photo-video-9523.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-piktures-gallery-photo-video-9523.html
</guid><description>
Piktures is a simple photo gallery app with very advanced features. It supports dozens of cloud services like Google Drive and Microsoft Onedrive, your personal cloud server (WebDav), SD Cards, USB drives and even your computer! Piktures allows you to view your photos in grid, mosaic and list views. Organize them the way you like.
Features of Piktures
	Fast: Piktures has its own rendering engine so you can view photos very quickly.
	Secret Space: The secure space protects your most...
</description></item><item><title>Download Listen Audiobook Player 5.4.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:43:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-listen-audiobook-player-8511.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-listen-audiobook-player-8511.html
</guid><description>
Listen Audiobook Player is a mobile app for playing audiobooks on your phone or tablet. It lets you play, pause, rewind, and fast-forward audiobooks with ease, while also providing a convenient way to track your listening progress.
Some key features of Listen Audiobook Player include:
	Library Management: Allows you to store and organize your audiobooks in a virtual library for easy access.
	Bookmark: Automatically saves your listening position so you can pick up where you left...
</description></item><item><title>Download Block Apps &amp;amp; Sites | Wellbeing 10.1.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:43:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-block-apps-sites-wellbeing-8629.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-block-apps-sites-wellbeing-8629.html
</guid><description>
Block Apps &amp;amp; Sites&amp;nbsp;is an easy-to-use Android app that improves your self-control by blocking or limiting app usage and giving you insights into how you use it time on the phone. Whether you need to focus on your studies, don't want to be distracted at work, can't sleep at night, or want to socialize more, this app can help you out.
Select a group of apps and create a custom time schedule where these apps will be automatically blocked. The schedule is fully customizable,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Appteka 18.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:43:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-appteka-11075.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-appteka-11075.html
</guid><description>
Appteka is a free Android application market. Download Appteka to get access to hundreds of thousands of free Android apps created by talented developers around the world.
What's new
	Completely new authorization, using one-time email codes, solves the problem of forgotten passwords and misspellings in mailbox addresses.
	New session system improves security with further authorization management across different devices
	The smoothness of the application has been improved, switching...
</description></item><item><title>Download 365Scores: Live Scores &amp;amp; News 14.4.9</title><pubDate> Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:43:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-365scores-live-scores-news-8220.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-365scores-live-scores-news-8220.html
</guid><description>
365Scores is a sports app that provides users with real-time scores, statistics, and news for many sports including football, basketball, soccer, and more. Some features of the application include:
	Live scores and notifications: 365Scores provides live scores and push notifications for many sports, including football, soccer, basketball, baseball, etc.
	Match statistics: The app includes detailed match statistics such as ball control, number of shots on goal, etc.
	Latest News:...
</description></item><item><title>Download NYTimes: US and Global News 11.56.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:42:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-the-new-york-times-8235.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-the-new-york-times-8235.html
</guid><description>
Understand the world around you with original reporting from The New York Times. Free to download, The Times app gives you access to expert news from 1700 journalists in 160 countries worldwide. From breaking news to opinion, business, technology and the arts, subscribers get unlimited access to groundbreaking reporting, analysis and commentary.
Features of The New York Times
	Wake up with The Morning, your morning guide to what's happening and why it matters. It's the news you need...
</description></item><item><title>Download AnyViewer 5.5.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 31 Dec 2025 00:52:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anyviewer-8000.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anyviewer-8000.html
</guid><description>
AnyViewer is free yet powerful remote desktop connection software for Windows PC and Windows Server. AnyViewer helps you to complete a stable and fast remote connection, transfer files from one PC to another or multiple PCs at the same time with high image quality. With an intuitive and concise interface that guides you to access your remote computer easily. Meanwhile, the remote desktop manager has flexible connection methods, automatic updates, and support for multiple...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tablacus Explorer 25.12.30</title><pubDate> Wed, 31 Dec 2025 00:52:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tablacus-explorer-3674.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tablacus-explorer-3674.html
</guid><description>
Tablacus Explorer is a file manager open-source is designed to help you arrange the contents of your folders. Tablacus Explorer has a user interface very simple and you will be familiar with working with this program immediately. Folders and files can be sorted or grouped by name, type, size and date when they were last modified. App can automatically remember to set your tab if you close it and allows you to copy or move items to different positions and save the settings to format an XML...
</description></item><item><title>Download VectorStyler 1.3.005</title><pubDate> Wed, 31 Dec 2025 00:49:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vectorstyler-7917.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vectorstyler-7917.html
</guid><description>
VectorStyler provides a complete set of drawing, design and illustration tools needed for modern design. Create illustrations, logos, icons, drawings, typography, vector art for screen, print and web. With many new features, VectorStyler redefines and extends the tools available to illustrators and designers, improving the creation of complex illustrations and designs.
Shape effects can be used to adjust the shape of objects, create different distortions, or add detail to shapes. Shape...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare UniConverter 17.1.2.459</title><pubDate> Wed, 31 Dec 2025 00:48:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-uniconverter-4808.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-uniconverter-4808.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare UniConverter ( old name is Wondershare Video Converter Ultimate) which allows you to convert the video format. You can cut, splice, move, or add effects, subtitles a easy way. When using software you easily cut, splice, move, as well as add the effects, the subtitles to the video.... Or can switch the clods SD, HD video to any format popular for use with iPod (Classic, Nano and Touch), iPhone, Apple TV, Zune, PSP, Pocket PC...
Wondershare UniConverter helps convert formats...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare PDFelement Pro 12.1.5.3940</title><pubDate> Wed, 31 Dec 2025 00:48:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-pdfelement-pro-105.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-pdfelement-pro-105.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare PDFelement Pro support users to convert PDF to office documents for easier use, modify in every situation. Is one of the software conversion material is rated best today, integrated with many features. We recommend that you should use experience software many useful features this.
Wondershare PDFelement Pro - conversion Fie PDF more features, multi-language
Wondershare PDFelement Pro what?
Convert PDF into Word, Excel, PowerPoint...
• Convert PDF and protected PDF into...
</description></item><item><title>Download CalendarTask (formerly DesktopCal) 3.26.262.8327</title><pubDate> Wed, 31 Dec 2025 00:47:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopcal-1831.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopcal-1831.html
</guid><description>
CalendarTask (formerly DesktopCal) is a simple desktop calendar that blends into your desktop without blocking access to your desktop icons. You can double-click on a date to quickly add notes and also jump to specific dates in the past or future.
CalendarTask - Computer calendar
CalendarTask can use your current wallpaper or loop through images from your folder and update your desktop every few minutes. The program helps you make appointments, make plans... Not only that, the Screen...
</description></item><item><title>Download ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro 15.25.1230</title><pubDate> Wed, 31 Dec 2025 00:46:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-videotube-downloader-pro-1276.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-videotube-downloader-pro-1276.html
</guid><description>
ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro is the professional version support download videos and playlists from YouTube, videos from Dailymotion, BBC iPlayer, ITV Player, ABC,  FOX,CBS.com Vimeo, Prosieben, Metacafe, Blip.tv CBC.ca many more video sites. After the video is downloaded, you can convert them to the formats compatible with iPad, iPhone, iPod, MPEG-4, H. 264, MP3, AC3.
ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro - Download videos on Youtube
This is one of the software download the most...
</description></item><item><title>Download Musify 5.1.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 31 Dec 2025 00:46:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musify-4422.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musify-4422.html
</guid><description>
Musify is the convert YouTube Music best can download music from more than 1000 website share music to listen to offline without reducing sound quality. Such as: YouTube, Spotify, SoundCloud, Facebook, Instragram, and more. Easily convert music files mp3 to iPhone, iPad, iPod, Samsung and iOS devices and other Android. High speed and high quality. Musify is a YouTube converter is very efficient and fast, support format converting YouTube to MP3. You can batch convert mp3 files at the same...
</description></item></channel></rss>