<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 17:37:59 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 17:37:59 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download ImageMagick 7.1.2-7</title><pubDate> Wed, 15 Oct 2025 16:18:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-imagemagick-1319.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-imagemagick-1319.html
</guid><description>
ImageMagick is software image processing command line to create, edit, compose, or convert bitmap images. ImageMagick is completely free for users and you easily download it on taiwebs.com. Typical functions most of software is able to read and write images in many formats (over 100) including DPX, EXR, GIF, JPEG, JPEG-2000, PDF, PhotoCD, PNG, Postcript, SVG, and TIFF.
ImageMagick - image Processing
The Windows version of ImageMagick is installed. Just click on the appropriate version...
</description></item><item><title>Download HWiNFO 8.32 Build 5840</title><pubDate> Wed, 15 Oct 2025 16:14:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hwinfo-1828.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hwinfo-1828.html
</guid><description>
HWiNFO (HWiNFO32) is a diagnostic tool and hardware information, recognizes and displays detailed information about all the hardware components of you. HWiNFO will hold the component in the tree view and provide the report easy to read for each category.
HWiNFO - Hardware Diagnostics
HWiNFO is especially useful so you don't have to install it on each computer and completely for free. Just run the direct program and you will have full information of the computer that you need. The...
</description></item><item><title>Download Bulk Image Downloader 6.60</title><pubDate> Wed, 15 Oct 2025 16:14:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bulk-image-downloader-121.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bulk-image-downloader-121.html
</guid><description>
Bulk Image Downloader is an application specially developed to help you download the images in full size from the Bulk Image Downloader most of the web gallery or web forum.
Bulk Image Downloader what?
Support image storage - BID works with almost every archive page popular images, such as flickr, imagevenue, imagefap, imagebam, etc.
Social networking sites - BID supports downloading from sites such as facebook, myspace, and twitter as tweetphoto.com, twitpic.com, yfrog.com
Images are...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mozilla Thunderbird 144.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 15 Oct 2025 16:14:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thunderbird-1788.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thunderbird-1788.html
</guid><description>
Thunderbird is an email program full featured with controls spam integration, mail filter, address book, news groups and more. It provides a clean interface and easy to use (customizable). Thunderbird also provides the security features such as S / MIME, digital signing, message encryption, support for certificates and security devices.
Before using this feature, you should review the settings IMAP, SMTP, and SSL/TLS his. Now, what all you need to do is provide your name, email address,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft Office Pro Plus - Online Installer 3.3.7</title><pubDate> Wed, 15 Oct 2025 16:12:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-office-professional-plus-x86-x64-online-installer-7661.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-office-professional-plus-x86-x64-online-installer-7661.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft Office 2021 Professional Plus x86-x64 - Online Installer is a small script that helps users to download and install Microsoft Office 2021 Professional Plus including all updates directly from Microsoft CDN Server.
The version of Office 2021 downloaded and installed on your computer will include the following programs: Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Outlook, OneNote, Publisher, Access, Visio, Project, ProofingTools, OneDrive Desktop.
Usage:
Unzip the downloaded ZIP Archive...
</description></item><item><title>Download Claris FileMaker Pro 22.0.3.300</title><pubDate> Wed, 15 Oct 2025 16:11:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-filemaker-pro-advanced-487.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-filemaker-pro-advanced-487.html
</guid><description>
FileMaker Pro Advanced is software via internet easy manager database, contacts, projects and inventory data, and generate reports. FileMaker Pro will help users to build database customize and design them to fit with the activities and profile of their business. More than a million people around the world use platform FileMaker every day to complete the work faster and more efficient in work.
Features on FileMaker Pro Advanced
Anywhere access
	Use one unified platform to create the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Free YouTube Download 4.4.41.1014 Premium</title><pubDate> Wed, 15 Oct 2025 16:10:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-download-1177.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-download-1177.html
</guid><description>
Free YouTube Download Premium is the most popular application to download videos from YouTube. The program was released in 2006 and regularly updated since then. Use the program to download and convert YouTube videos to view offline anytime.
Free YouTube Download - added Support to download youtube
Download more videos! Save whole playlists and YouTube channels, videos from a playlist individually (history, video be favorite, favourites, Watch later), videos from many different...
</description></item><item><title>Download Google Chrome 141.0.7390.108</title><pubDate> Wed, 15 Oct 2025 16:10:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-chrome-1012.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-chrome-1012.html
</guid><description>
Google Chrome web browser is the most used today. Support surf the web, listen to music, watch movies, play web game effective no jerky lag with the internet connection stable. When you are surfing the web or performing an important task, whether it is operation big or small, work or entertainment, then Chrome has the smart features and the speed you need to make, create and explore on the net.
The latest version of Google Chrome is the third 114. But we are providing for users Google...
</description></item><item><title>Download HWiNFO Portable 8.32.5840</title><pubDate> Wed, 15 Oct 2025 16:08:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hwinfo-portable-11340.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hwinfo-portable-11340.html
</guid><description>
HWiNFO Portable is a professional hardware information and diagnostic tool that supports the latest components, technologies and industry standards. These tools are designed to collect and present the maximum amount of information possible about computer hardware, making them suitable for users looking for driver updates, computer manufacturers, system integrators as well as technical experts. Retrieved information is presented in a logical, easy-to-understand format and can be exported...
</description></item><item><title>Download Yamicsoft Windows 11/10 Manager 2.2.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 15 Oct 2025 16:08:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yamicsoft-windows-11-manager-6779.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yamicsoft-windows-11-manager-6779.html
</guid><description>
Windows 11 Manager is an all-in-one utility for Microsoft Windows 11 specially, it includes over forty different utilities to optimize, tweak, clean up, speed up and repair your Windows 11, helps make your system perform faster, eliminate system fault, increase stability and security, personalize your copy of Windows 11, and meet all of your expectations.
Features of Windows 11 Manager:
Information:
	Creates the system restore point manually;
	Gets detailed information about your...
</description></item><item><title>Download Transcend SSD Scope 4.28</title><pubDate> Wed, 15 Oct 2025 16:07:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-transcend-ssd-scope-7662.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-transcend-ssd-scope-7662.html
</guid><description>
Transcend SSD Scope is an advanced and user-friendly software that makes it easier than ever to clone and maintain a healthy and efficient SSD. It brings together the latest technology to determine the health and optimize the performance of your SSD.
Useful features of Transcend SSD Scope include:
	View drive information
	View SMART status
	Diagnostic scan
	Clear Security
	Updating the firmware
	Enable TRIM, Health Indicator, and System Clone.
</description></item><item><title>Download Avast Premium Security 25.10.10528</title><pubDate> Wed, 15 Oct 2025 16:06:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avast-premier-antivirus-security-1359.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avast-premier-antivirus-security-1359.html
</guid><description>
Avast! Premier Antivirus is antivirus software famous by combining all the technologies and methods virus advanced. The developer software this anti-virus have invested in all their knowledge about fighting viruses to create one of the software anti-virus best. Program anti-virus this combines all the technology and advanced methods to get the level of computer security highest. This product is ideal for all the Windows operating system.
Avast! Premier Antivirus - antivirus...
</description></item><item><title>Download CoolUtils PDF Combine Pro 4.2.0.152/103</title><pubDate> Wed, 15 Oct 2025 16:05:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-pdf-combine-pro-580.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-pdf-combine-pro-580.html
</guid><description>
CoolUtils PDF Combine Pro  is software that helps you combine  PDF, DOC, TXT, DOCX, HTML, XLS, images  h (TIFF, JPEG, PNG) and  email  as a  PDF  file. With PDF Combine Pro it is easier than ever to combine documents into one PDF file. Now you don't have to use some programs and converters to get a PDF. Everything for PDF Combine Pro to do for you.
Office, fax, email files - get combined PDF in seconds for personal use, commercial needs, electronic discovery, or manufacturing.  PDF...
</description></item><item><title>Download yt-dlp 2025.10.14</title><pubDate> Wed, 15 Oct 2025 16:04:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-dlp-6802.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-dlp-6802.html
</guid><description>
yt-dlp is a youtube-dl branch based on youtube-dlc currently not working. The main focus of this project is the addition of new features and patches while still updating the original project.
</description></item><item><title>Download XYplorer 28.00.0400 Beta</title><pubDate> Wed, 15 Oct 2025 16:04:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-533.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-533.html
</guid><description>
XYplorer - File Manager for Windows is software that supports users to manage files on the Window quickly and to arrange the folder tidy. XYplorer features tabbed browsing, search, files, powerful, preview, flexible, highly customizable interface, dual frame options and a variety of unique ways to automate effective tasks often repeat. It's fast, lightweight, and portable.
Features XYplorer
	XYplorer is a file manager mobile. It does not require any settings, store all configuration...
</description></item><item><title>Download Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium 4.4.41.1014</title><pubDate> Wed, 15 Oct 2025 16:03:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-to-mp3-converter-premium-844.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-to-mp3-converter-premium-844.html
</guid><description>
Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium version is a software used to convert YouTube to MP3, extract audio from playlists YouTube, show listings, charts, video responses, channels, favorites of the user. With Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium, you can download and convert playlists, channels, stream original tv series and get them into iTunes at the same time.
Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium - convert YouTube to MP3
Features Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium from the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft .NET Desktop Runtime 9.0.10</title><pubDate> Wed, 15 Oct 2025 16:03:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-net-desktop-runtime-5748.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-net-desktop-runtime-5748.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft .NET Desktop Runtime allows you to run existing Windows desktop applications. This release includes the .NET Runtime, which requires no separate installation. The Microsoft .NET Desktop Runtime redistributable package installs the .NET Desktop Runtime and related files needed to run many applications that use this programming language.
This is Microsoft's comprehensive and consistent programming model for building applications with stunningly intuitive user experiences,...
</description></item><item><title>Download SponsorBlock 6.0.3 (Chrome + FireFox)</title><pubDate> Wed, 15 Oct 2025 16:02:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sponsorblock-6960.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sponsorblock-6960.html
</guid><description>
SponsorBlock is an extension for Chrome and Firefox browsers that allows you to bypass sponsors, intros, registration prompts and other annoying parts of YouTube videos . SponsorBlock is a browser extension powered by community resources that allows anyone to submit the start and end times of sponsored segments and other segments of YouTube videos. When one person submits this, others with this extension will immediately skip the sponsored segment.
Features of SponsorBlock
	You can...
</description></item><item><title>Download QOwnNotes 25.10.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 15 Oct 2025 15:58:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qownnotes-3178.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qownnotes-3178.html
</guid><description>
QOwnNotes is notes bookmark file simple text (GPL) open source application for GNU / Linux , Mac OS X and Windows of Patrizio Bekerle ( pbek on GitHub and IRC) (optional) activity along with the notes application of ownCloud or Nextcloud. QOwnNote store your notes as plain text files and can be synchronized with synchronization function file of ownCloud / Nextcloud. You can also use other apps like Syncthing or Dropbox . Just write out your thoughts as they appear, and edit them if...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft Malicious Software Removal Tool 5.136</title><pubDate> Wed, 15 Oct 2025 15:58:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-malicious-software-removal-tool-1131.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-malicious-software-removal-tool-1131.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft Malicious Software Removal Tool is tools remove malicious software from your computer Microsoft help computer always clean and works well. The software runs on Windows XP, Windows 2000 and Windows Server 2003 to detect the file can harm the computer by tool Blaster, Sasser, and Mydoom.
Microsoft Malicious Software Removal Tool - Uninstall malware
If the scan detected malicious files, tool Microsoft Malicious Software Removal Tool will display a report describing the outcome,...
</description></item><item><title>Download VirtualDub2 2.4.3.944</title><pubDate> Wed, 15 Oct 2025 15:52:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-virtualdub2-12584.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-virtualdub2-12584.html
</guid><description>
VirtualDub2 (formerly VirtualDub FilterMod) has all the features of the original VirtualDub, plus built-in encoding/decoding functionality of H264 and other formats; Open and save MOV, MP4, MKV, etc. Improved navigation, display (full screen display when zoomed in, ...) and other UI bits (color format selection...); improve performance; and supports high bit depth color formats.
Features of VirtualDub2
	Just like the original VirtualDub, this application requires no installation. You...
</description></item><item><title>Download Viber for PC 26.4.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 15 Oct 2025 15:52:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-viber-2406.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-viber-2406.html
</guid><description>
Viber is a software of instant messaging, based on VoIP protocols, multi-platform due to the Viber Media development for smart phones used to send sms and make calls over the internet. Along with text messaging, users can exchange images, video and audio.
Viber - software news message, chat online
This is a program that is quite popular is mainly designed for mobile phones, but now we are talking about the version for Windows, so immediately. It will allow you to send messages to other...
</description></item><item><title>Download UpdatePack7R2 25.10.15</title><pubDate> Wed, 15 Oct 2025 15:51:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-updatepack7r2-6614.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-updatepack7r2-6614.html
</guid><description>
UpdatePack7R2 is software that allows you to update a working system and integrate software updates in the distribution. Can be installed on any version of Windows 7 and Server 2008 R2, any digit and any language. Includes updates for all versions of Internet Explorer, all critical, recommended, and security updates.
How to use UpdatePack7R2 software:
	The system must have at least 10 GB of free space on the hard drive and preferably no less than 1 GB of free RAM.
	Key / Reboot to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Executor 2.1.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 15 Oct 2025 15:49:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-executor-271.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-executor-271.html
</guid><description>
Executor for windows is a software alternative premium customization features for the Windows "Run" and "Search Programs". When you press WIN + Z and provides the search results instant, as-you-type for any keywords you enter. By default, Executor will index all the Desktop and Start Menu and you can easily expand the search range by adding the folder location additional.
Executor for windows
The program comes with a list of commands built in which you can use to quickly access many...
</description></item><item><title>Download AllMapSoft OpenstreetMap Downloader 6.624</title><pubDate> Wed, 15 Oct 2025 15:49:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-openstreetmap-downloader-4916.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-openstreetmap-downloader-4916.html
</guid><description>
AllMapSoft OpenstreetMap Downloader is a tool that can automatically download images OpenstreetMap on your PC. It can download the small cells and save them to your hard disk, including the regular classroom, transpot and cycle, opensea, etc. After downloading, you can view the map offline tool Maps Viewer or you can combine the small images into one image large map. If you want to make a map of their city, it is very useful for you.
The features of AllMapSoft OpenstreetMap...
</description></item></channel></rss>