<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 13:46:24 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 13:46:24 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Heredis 2026 v26.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 07 Nov 2025 16:46:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-heredis-5195.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-heredis-5195.html
</guid><description>
Heredis is a software provides all the features you need to become a pedigree of success. There is no genealogy software any better Heredis to create your family tree and to see the genealogy research of your rapid evolution. You will find a total of more than 150 features to help you create, improve, share, and related to the history of ancestors. There are countless features nothing but the best!
The features of Heredis
	Download, install and start working with your genealogy...
</description></item><item><title>Download Power-user Premium 1.7.62.204</title><pubDate> Fri, 07 Nov 2025 16:45:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-power-user-premium-3149.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-power-user-premium-3149.html
</guid><description>
Power-user is a plugin for software, Microsoft Excel, PowerPoint and Word help you to provide more visual content so you can create the spreadsheet attractive. It contains templates, icons, tables, drawings and charts, modern, professional, allows you to build professional looking documents. You can add custom content to your project just by a click of the mouse and surprise clients and colleagues with your skills on Excel, PowerPoint and Word.
Power-user Premium - Plugin Excel,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Power-user for PowerPoint and Excel 1.7.62.204</title><pubDate> Fri, 07 Nov 2025 16:45:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-power-user-for-powerpoint-and-excel-522.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-power-user-for-powerpoint-and-excel-522.html
</guid><description>
Power-user for PowerPoint and Excel is a utility providing you with a library of templates, icons, charts, maps and diagrams for spreadsheet and presentation. With Power-user for PowerPoint and Excel, you will attract the attention of your audience with stunning graphics will certainly impress.
Power-user comes with a collection of 2,000 icons to illustrate your slides. The icons are vector shapes so you can resize them without distortion and color back as you with. With Power-user, you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Chess King 2025 v25.0.0.2520</title><pubDate> Fri, 07 Nov 2025 16:45:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chess-king-13917.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chess-king-13917.html
</guid><description>
Chess King 2025 is the latest version of the Chess King software suite, designed for chess players of all levels to play, practice, analyze and improve their games with advanced tools and rich resources.
Chess King Analysis 25 is a new and versatile tool for chess players, an ideal software for beginners, a challenging opponent for amateurs and an invaluable trainer for aspiring players. Chess King Analysis 25 emphasizes simplicity of use in training players. However, it is more than just...
</description></item><item><title>Download EJ Technologies JProfiler 15.0.4</title><pubDate> Fri, 07 Nov 2025 16:45:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ej-technologies-jprofiler-1214.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ej-technologies-jprofiler-1214.html
</guid><description>
EJ Technologies JProfiler is a powerful tool that you can use to configure the application based on Java that allows you to analyze them with the hope of performance optimization. JProfiler has a number of exploration for you see data the higher level from the system interesting in the JRE. In addition to the system Java EE as JDBC, JPA / Hibernate, JSP / Servlets, JMS, web services and JNDI, JProfiler also presents high-level information about the calls, files, sockets and processes the...
</description></item><item><title>Download QOwnNotes 25.11.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 07 Nov 2025 16:44:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qownnotes-3178.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qownnotes-3178.html
</guid><description>
QOwnNotes is notes bookmark file simple text (GPL) open source application for GNU / Linux , Mac OS X and Windows of Patrizio Bekerle ( pbek on GitHub and IRC) (optional) activity along with the notes application of ownCloud or Nextcloud. QOwnNote store your notes as plain text files and can be synchronized with synchronization function file of ownCloud / Nextcloud. You can also use other apps like Syncthing or Dropbox . Just write out your thoughts as they appear, and edit them if...
</description></item><item><title>Download ezPaycheck 3.15.22</title><pubDate> Fri, 07 Nov 2025 16:43:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ezpaycheck-5319.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ezpaycheck-5319.html
</guid><description>
ezPaycheck is a payroll software easy to use is designed for the small business: simple, reliable and affordable. The developer of we have designed it to become a solution tax payroll internal for small businesses to calculate taxes, print paychecks for employees and contractors, generate reports and print tax forms.
The features of ezPaycheck
	Calculate payroll federal and state tax / deductions and local taxes (such as SDI tax, occupation tax, city)
	Print paychecks and tax...
</description></item><item><title>Download Boris FX Music Studio 2025.0.2.25265</title><pubDate> Fri, 07 Nov 2025 16:43:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-magix-samplitude-music-studio-5122.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-magix-samplitude-music-studio-5122.html
</guid><description>
MAGIX Samplitude Music Studio - Brings the vision of your music come to life. Compose, record, mix and master. Use the creative tools and workflows, object-oriented, to create the complex arrangement. Choose from a variety of audio tools needed to prepare your songs for the stage. Discover music studio Samplitude. Everything a musician needs.
This program allows you to record your own music in a professional way, from creating it to burn CDS. In a very simple interface, you can easily...
</description></item><item><title>Download Trillian 6.6 Build 9</title><pubDate> Fri, 07 Nov 2025 16:42:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-trillian-2638.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-trillian-2638.html
</guid><description>
Trillian is the chat help you sign in to more the registered name of a certain service or you can log on at the same time many services in a working window. It integrates multiple services such as Yahoo! MSN, IRC, AIM and ICQ. In addition, you can manage Email accounts, Facebook and Twitter friends - all in just one application.
Login is easy; just click on the network or the appropriate website and log in as normal. Trillian requires access your data (accepted) and post to friends...
</description></item><item><title>Download Qbitec for Revit 1.4.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 07 Nov 2025 16:42:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qbitec-for-revit-12759.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qbitec-for-revit-12759.html
</guid><description>
Qbitec for Revit helps users quickly load point clouds of any size with superior image quality, reduce manual adjustments with smart viewing, and seamlessly integrate panoramic views in 3D - from local storage, your network, or the cloud. With the latest version of QBitec for Revit, this extra step is no longer necessary. Now you can directly in Revit:
	Set the brightness and contrast of the view for a clearer image,
	Smoothly adjust the point size to highlight fine details
	Optimize...
</description></item><item><title>Download Boris FX Sequoia 2025.0.2 v17.4.3.25265</title><pubDate> Fri, 07 Nov 2025 16:41:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-magix-sequoia-12379.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-magix-sequoia-12379.html
</guid><description>
Sequoia is your go-to solution for professional audio production.
From the recording studio to the mastering desk – stability, seamless processing and innovative editing features are key for engineers around the world. Our partners, including Europe's most prominent broadcasters, rely on its scalable, flexible hardware integration and network.
Your Audio Production Toolkit
Sequoia's feature set covers every step of your daily production workflow. Check out the core functionality in...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cygwin 3.6.5</title><pubDate> Fri, 07 Nov 2025 16:41:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cygwin-3236.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cygwin-3236.html
</guid><description>
Cygwin is designed to provide functionality similar to Linux distribution on Windows with many application options to be compiled first. Cygwin is a *nix environments in Windows by creating a compatibility Layer. Through which Windows users can run the app which is still popular on Linux, Unix after program that is transferred through Cygwin. Current Cygwin running on the official version of Windows since Windows Vista.
Cygwin comes with the installer to ensure you have the latest...
</description></item><item><title>Download EF Commander 25.30</title><pubDate> Fri, 07 Nov 2025 16:41:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ef-commander-92.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ef-commander-92.html
</guid><description>
EF Commander is an application specialized software can help you to manage your files effectively can help you full control over the files and folders, suitable for both beginners to experts with interface according to the card format Tab. The application supports ID3 tags, enhanced sound quality and use less resources with the format OGG/ Vorbis, FLAC, WMA and WAV and other formats can be heard on Winamp,...
EF Commander - a file manager effectively 
With EF Commander : When starting...
</description></item><item><title>Download Code4Ward Royal TS 7.3.51009</title><pubDate> Fri, 07 Nov 2025 16:40:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-code4ward-royal-ts-10634.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-code4ward-royal-ts-10634.html
</guid><description>
Code4Ward Royal TS is a popular remote computer management solution for Windows operating systems. With an intuitive interface and advanced features. It can handle documents opened by multiple users simultaneously and allows you to synchronize document changes without the need for an SQL database back-end.
Features of Code4Ward Royal TS
	Integrated credential management. Secure group sharing feature.
	Share your connection list without sharing your personal credentials.
	SSH-based...
</description></item><item><title>Download KILHO AutoClick 1.4.5</title><pubDate> Fri, 07 Nov 2025 16:40:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kilho-autoclick-12515.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kilho-autoclick-12515.html
</guid><description>
AutoClick is a software or script designed to automate mouse clicking tasks, especially useful for repetitive actions in a variety of applications, including gaming and data entry. It allows users to define specific click points and automatically click at those locations. This tool is user-friendly and supports recording click sequences for repeated use.
AutoClick allows users to set precise time intervals and geographic coordinates for various click patterns. Additionally, AutoClick...
</description></item><item><title>Download ExifTool 13.41</title><pubDate> Fri, 07 Nov 2025 16:39:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-exiftool-1685.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-exiftool-1685.html
</guid><description>
ExifTool is a library of Perl platform-independent plus a command line application for reading, writing, and editing meta information in various file types. ExifTool supports many metadata formats including EXIF , GPS , IPTC , XMP , JFIF , GeoTIFF , ICC Profile , Photoshop IRB , FlashPix , AFCP and ID3 , as well as notes of the manufacturer of many digital cameras by Canon , Casio , DJI , FLIR , FujiFilm , GE , GoPro , HP , JVC / Victor , Kodak , Leaf , Minolta / Konica-Minolta , Motorola...
</description></item><item><title>Download FKFX Vocal Freeze 1.7.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 07 Nov 2025 16:38:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fkfx-vocal-freeze-11770.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fkfx-vocal-freeze-11770.html
</guid><description>
Captures the essence of every voice and instrument, preserving their spectral brilliance like a mesmerizing time lapse. Take your sound to the next level as it easily conveys a wide range of interconnected effects. Immerse yourself in unparalleled precision with our advanced high-speed, progressive scan FFT technology.
Vocal Freeze can record voices and instruments, maintain their spectral brightness with progressive scanning high-speed FFT technology, and create a time-lapse "Stop" on...
</description></item><item><title>Download FKFX Dyna Pro 1.4.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 07 Nov 2025 16:37:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fkfx-skylab-11790.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fkfx-skylab-11790.html
</guid><description>
FKFX Dyna Pro is an advanced distortion wave generator plugin developed by FKFX Audio, designed for designing deep and creative distortion sounds with rhythmic and dynamic modulation capabilities.
DYNA Pro Features
	Elastic morphing waveshaper: Sculpt distortion curves dynamically with an intuitive editor.
	Perturbator module: Add synchronized particle and resonance effects for unique textures. Includes controls for pitch, volume, perturbator oscillator shape, musical scale capture,...
</description></item><item><title>Download ezAccounting 3.15.16</title><pubDate> Fri, 07 Nov 2025 16:37:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ezaccounting-5300.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ezaccounting-5300.html
</guid><description>
ezAccounting is accounting software designed for the small business: simple, reliable and affordable. ezAccounting is the solution internal accounting suitable for small businesses need to record and report on cash flow in and out including sales, incomes and expenses and purchases. It also supports payroll processing and print tax forms.
The features of ezAccounting
	Company accounts unlimited
	Custom format form
	Custom format Czech
	Support multiple tax code
	Support multiple...
</description></item><item><title>Download Operant Peak Spectroscopy 4.00.533</title><pubDate> Fri, 07 Nov 2025 16:36:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-operant-peak-spectroscopy-7976.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-operant-peak-spectroscopy-7976.html
</guid><description>
Operant Peak Spectroscopy for Spectroscopy reads and converts over 60 spectral file formats. It includes library search, spectrum manipulation and many other functions. Mid IR, Near IR, FTIR, Raman, Fluorescence, LIBS, XRF, UV-VIS, Raman and EELS.
Features of Operant Peak Spectroscopy
	Peak can read data from more than 70 spectral file types.
	Convert files in bulk from closed proprietary formats.
	Peak is used worldwide in industry, education, government and military
	Peak has a...
</description></item><item><title>Download FKFX OF2 (Obvious Filter) 2.0.6</title><pubDate> Fri, 07 Nov 2025 16:36:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fkfx-obvious-filter-11746.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fkfx-obvious-filter-11746.html
</guid><description>
FKFX Obvious Filter opens up new creative dimensions for your music with enhanced LFO morphs, superb response quality, and depth filters. With advanced LFO morphing, excellent response quality, and depth filters, Clear Filters let you create truly unique sounds and set you apart from the rest.
It gives you full control over your sound, with 39 rare oscillators including emulation of some legendary synthesizers, and many advanced features like Polyrhythm, Drawing Pencil , Square &amp;amp;...
</description></item><item><title>Download FKFX Sylab 1.6.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 07 Nov 2025 16:36:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fkfx-sylab-11403.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fkfx-sylab-11403.html
</guid><description>
Introducing Sylab, the revolutionary vowel filter that turns your instrument into an eloquent storyteller. Discover the magic of vowels with their unique resonance patterns and frequencies. Sylab infuses a captivating energy that transforms your sounds into vivid expressions.
Sylab opens up a world of endless sonic variations, allowing you to create rhythmic and dynamic variations to breathe life into your electronic tracks.
Features:
	LFOGRID
	Editor selection mode.
	Additional...
</description></item><item><title>Download LDPlayer 9.1.75.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 07 Nov 2025 01:05:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ldplayer-2331.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ldplayer-2331.html
</guid><description>
LDPlayer is an Android emulator that allows users to play games and run applications on Windows computers. LDPlayer supports heavy gaming, running chat applications, editing photos, videos, and many other Android applications. LDPlayer is compatible with Android 5.1 and above, supporting multitasking for an experience that is not inferior to that of using on Mobile.
Installation is a simple and quick process that does not require any special attention from you, there are more. settings,...
</description></item><item><title>Download ASUS GPU Tweak III 2.0.4.5</title><pubDate> Fri, 07 Nov 2025 01:04:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-asus-gpu-tweak-3252.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-asus-gpu-tweak-3252.html
</guid><description>
ASUS GPU Tweak is a tools overclocking powerful and full-featured allows you to significantly enhance the performance of the graphics processor ASUS. Utility that allows you to get the best results just by few mouse clicks. ASUS GPU Tweak has a number mode allows you to adjust the parameters of graphics according to the specific needs of his. Mode OC allows you to benefit from maximum performance supplied by your graphics card. Game play mode allows you to play the game using the default...
</description></item><item><title>Download Office Timeline Plus 12.00.00.00 Expert / Pro / Pro+ Edition</title><pubDate> Fri, 07 Nov 2025 01:03:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-timeline-2106.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-timeline-2106.html
</guid><description>
Office Timeline is an add-on very useful and powerful software for Microsoft PowerPoint. With add-ons, you can create PowerPoint documents look more beautiful. With add-ons, you can add the time Line on the project by yourself. Application time for the composition and different segments of the document, your PowerPoint will not only increase the beauty for your work, but also for customers and your manager. The people who created this product is also believe that add-ons this is the only...
</description></item></channel></rss>