<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 17:37:13 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 17:37:13 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Argente Malware Cleaner 3.0.2.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 19:01:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-argente-malware-cleaner-13494.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-argente-malware-cleaner-13494.html
</guid><description>
Argente Malware Cleaner is a lightweight utility designed to detect and remove a wide range of malware, including spyware, adware, Trojans and other threats that can compromise your privacy and data. It works as a complementary tool alongside your main antivirus software, helping to detect malware that may slip through the cracks.
Key features of Argente Malware Cleaner include:
	Easy-to-use, clean, and user-friendly interface that suits both casual and advanced users.
	Deep scanning...
</description></item><item><title>Download Argente System Repair 1.0.2.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 19:01:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-argente-system-repair-13813.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-argente-system-repair-13813.html
</guid><description>
Argente System Repair is a lightweight utility designed to diagnose and fix common Windows system problems. It scans your system to identify errors in operating system components, file systems, installation files, and other system components, and then applies targeted fixes to resolve these problems. The tool provides different scan modes, including simple scan, recommended scan, and custom scan, allowing users to customize the repair process according to their needs.
System Repair...
</description></item><item><title>Download CCleaner Browser 139.0.31477.68</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 19:00:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ccleaner-browser-1851.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ccleaner-browser-1851.html
</guid><description>
Piriform, the company produces CCleaner - software cleanup system popular on Windows, has launched Chromium browser new of his own name CCleaner Browser. New browser comes with every feature have been Google's Chrome, and is integrated ad blockers. CCleaner Browser interface is quite similar to Google Chrome, the difference is the appearance of the icon CCleaner familiar on the bar enter the address of the browser, that's all.
CCleaner Browser - web browser ad blocker
In CCleaner...
</description></item><item><title>Download CPU-Z for Android 1.52</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 18:56:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-cpu-z-for-android-9218.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-cpu-z-for-android-9218.html
</guid><description>
CPU-Z for Android is a popular system information and monitoring tool that is available for Android devices. It is developed by CPUID, the same company behind the popular CPU-Z tool for desktops.
CPU-Z for Android provides detailed information about the device's hardware and system, including the CPU, GPU, RAM, storage, and battery. It also provides real-time monitoring of CPU and GPU usage, temperature, and clock speed, which can be useful for troubleshooting and optimizing...
</description></item><item><title>Download SD Maid 2/SE - System Cleaner 1.4.16-beta1</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 18:56:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sd-maid-2se-system-cleaner-10472.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sd-maid-2se-system-cleaner-10472.html
</guid><description>
SD Maid 2/SE - System Cleaner is a reliable helper for your Android, keeping the device clean &amp;amp; orderly. SD Maid SE has optional features that use the AccessibilityService API to automate tedious actions. Using the AccessibilityService API, SD Maid SE can click buttons for you to perform cross-app operations, for example, clear cache. SD Maid SE does not use the AccessibilityService API to collect information.
No one is perfect and neither is Android
	Apps you deleted will leave...
</description></item><item><title>Download All Document Reader and Viewer 2.8.4</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 18:56:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-all-document-reader-and-viewer-8877.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-all-document-reader-and-viewer-8877.html
</guid><description>
All Document Reader: PDF, excel, word, Documents is a smart office application that helps you read all documents downloaded from the internet, supports reading PDF files, PDF Reader, doc, docx xls, ppt, txt, excel, xlxs files... fast, easy and convenient.. All Document Reader: PDF, excel, word, Documents are providing multiple Document reading features including PDF Reader, Docs Reader &amp;amp; Docx, ppt reader, xls reader, txt, excel &amp;amp; documents different from readers.
All Document...
</description></item><item><title>Download BandLab - Music Making Studio 11.5.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 18:55:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-bandlab-music-making-studio-13487.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-bandlab-music-making-studio-13487.html
</guid><description>
The free BandLab app has everything you need to start making beats: whether you're creating your first loop or creating your next global release. With this powerful music creation tool in your pocket, you can produce, mix, and share your beats on the go. Dive into a massive sample library, create MIDI like a pro, and unlock next-level beatmaking tools - all from your phone.
Bring your ideas to life instantly in your DAW:
	Sampler: Create beats with over 100k royalty-free samples from...
</description></item><item><title>Download CCleaner – Phone Cleaner 25.15.0 build 800011220</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 18:55:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ccleaner-pro-for-android-3428.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ccleaner-pro-for-android-3428.html
</guid><description>
CCleaner is a system cleaning and optimization tool for Android devices. CCleaner for Android allows users to delete unnecessary files, such as temporary files and caches, as well as identify and uninstall applications that are taking up too much space on the device. It also includes a task kill to close running applications and free up memory. This can help free up storage space and improve device performance. In addition, CCleaner for Android also has a security feature that allows you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft Copilot 30.0.430818001</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 18:54:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-microsoft-copilot-13075.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-microsoft-copilot-13075.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft Copilot is your everyday AI companion. Chatting with Copilot is an easy way to learn, grow, and become more confident, all with the help of the latest AI models from OpenAI and Microsoft. Use our AI image generator to create images from words or ask AI anything and chat with AI to get a new perspective on your ideas. Copilot, your AI writing assistant, helps you save time, increase productivity, and drive business. When you talk to AI, you'll find the space to express your...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cross DJ Pro - Mix your music 4.0.13</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 18:54:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-cross-dj-pro-mix-your-music-8738.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-cross-dj-pro-mix-your-music-8738.html
</guid><description>
The best DJ Pro app on Android. Mix tracks in perfect sync on a powerful audio engine. Designed by Mixvibes, Pioneers of Digital DJing for 15 years.
Mix in perfect sync
	Detect the exact BPM of your music, down to the last decimal.
	Stable sync: One tap and 2 tracks never lose phase.
	No
	Progressive, manual pitch bend.
	Customizable, manual pitch range (4, 8, 16, 32, 100%).
	Precise beat grid editing: Make any track sync
	Parallel waveform mode to visually check if your tracks are in...
</description></item><item><title>Download SeriesGuide 2025.2.7</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 18:53:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-seriesguide-show-manager-8240.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-seriesguide-show-manager-8240.html
</guid><description>
With SeriesGuide, you can find shows and movies to watch, keep track of your watched episodes and movies, get notifications about upcoming episodes, and back up and sync across your devices. suffered.
Explore. Find shows with new, popular, or similar episodes to the ones you're watching. Discover movies currently in theaters, released digitally or on disc.
Backup and synchronization. Sign in to SeriesGuide Cloud to back up and sync your shows, lists, and movies.
Integration with...
</description></item><item><title>Download radio.net PRIME 5.17.3.0-app build 100043</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 18:53:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-radionet-prime-8335.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-radionet-prime-8335.html
</guid><description>
radio.net PRIME is a mobile application that allows users to listen to a variety of radio stations on their Android devices. This app provides access to more than 30,000 radio stations around the world, including local and international stations in a variety of genres and formats.
Features of radio.net PRIME
	Access to more than 30,000 radio stations around the world
	Supports multiple genres and formats, including news, music, sports, and chat
	Option to create a list of favorite...
</description></item><item><title>Download IPTV Pro 9.1.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 18:52:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-iptv-pro-9093.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-iptv-pro-9093.html
</guid><description>
IPTV Pro is an Android application that allows you to watch live TV channels and movies on your Android device. It provides access to many channels from around the world, including sports, news, movies, and entertainment channels. IPTV Pro supports both M3U and XSPF playlists, and allows you to add your own playlists.
IPTV Pro Features
	Supports M3U and XSPF playlists
	Playlist history
	Play a multicast stream using a UDP proxy (the proxy needs to be installed in your LAN)
	Grid, list...
</description></item><item><title>Download WiFi Direct + 10.0.15</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 18:52:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wifi-direct-10153.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wifi-direct-10153.html
</guid><description>
Wi-Fi Direct is a Wi-Fi standard for peer-to-peer wireless connections that allows two devices to establish a direct Wi-Fi connection without the need for an intermediate wireless access point, router, or Internet connection.
Features of WiFi Direct +
	Fast
	Completely free, no intrusive ads.
	Supports all file transfers.
	Supports multiple file transfers.
	Supports folder transfer.
	Supports file transfer to and from external sdcard.
	Tested on many devices.
	Advanced file chooser.
</description></item><item><title>Download Photo Lab Picture Editor &amp;amp; Art 3.13.70</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 18:52:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-photo-lab-picture-editor-art-13190.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-photo-lab-picture-editor-art-13190.html
</guid><description>
Join AI Photo Lab photo editor that lets you edit photos with face filters for photos, fashion photo effects and many photo art ideas. Amazing face collage maker, photo frames, photo effects and filters are here for you to enjoy. A smart and fast new way to turn any photo into a work of art — choose from over 50 preset styles and experience enhanced photo editing with the introduction of AI photo styles.
Key Features
	Photo Frames: Whether you want to highlight a memorable moment or...
</description></item><item><title>Download Omnia Music Player 1.8.1 build 134</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 18:51:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-omnia-music-player-10217.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-omnia-music-player-10217.html
</guid><description>
Omnia Music Player is a powerful music player for Android. It is an ad-free offline audio player. Its beautiful user interface matches every detail of material design principles. Omnia Music Player supports almost all audio formats, including mp3, ape, aac, flac, opus, ogg, wav, etc. It has a high-resolution output engine with the best sound quality and a 10-band equalizer, in a small footprint, under 5 MB.
Omnia Music Player contains almost every necessary feature to satisfy all your...
</description></item><item><title>Download Avast Cleanup – Phone Cleaner 25.15.0 build 800011220</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 18:48:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-avast-cleanup-phone-cleaner-8885.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-avast-cleanup-phone-cleaner-8885.html
</guid><description>
Avast Cleanup - Phone Cleaner is a mobile app for Android devices designed to help users optimize their phone's performance and free up storage space. This application provides many tools and features to clean and speed up your phone.
One of the main features of Avast Cleanup is the Junk Cleaner, which scans your phone for unnecessary files such as temporary files, app cache, and other junk data. The app will then provide a list of files that can be safely deleted to free up space on...
</description></item><item><title>Download BD File Manager File Explorer 1.8.0.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 18:48:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-bd-file-manager-file-explorer-10542.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-bd-file-manager-file-explorer-10542.html
</guid><description>
BD File Manager is a powerful and free local and network file manager that helps you manage files and applications effectively. You can also use the file analysis/memory analysis function to free up phone space.
Main functions of BD file manager
Powerful file analysis/storage analysis function
	Analyze internal memory, clean empty files, empty folders, log files, temporary files, cache files, redundant files, duplicate files and large files to free up storage space.&amp;lt;...
</description></item><item><title>Download Video Editor &amp;amp; Maker - InShot 2.151.1503</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 18:47:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-video-editor-maker-inshot-11806.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-video-editor-maker-inshot-11806.html
</guid><description>
InShot is a powerful all-in-one Video Editor and Video Maker with professional features. Add music, text, transitions to videos, create smooth slow motion, create video collages, blur the background, and more! An easy-to-use editing app, InShot makes vlogging easy and helps you become an influencer on YouTube, Instagram, TikTok, WhatsApp, Facebook, and more.
InShot is also a photo editor and collage maker. Edit photos and selfies, remove bg, add filters and adjust HSL, etc.
AI...
</description></item><item><title>Download Auto Text: Schedule Messages 5.7.8</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 18:47:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-auto-text-auto-send-message-8447.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-auto-text-auto-send-message-8447.html
</guid><description>
Auto Text: Auto send WA &amp;amp; SMS is a feature or application that allows users to automatically send pre-written text messages at a specific time or in response to a request. specific activation. This feature can be useful in many situations, such as sending reminders, sending messages to loved ones at a specific time, or sending messages in response to certain events, such as calls to or location-based triggers.
Auto Text features: Auto send WA &amp;amp; SMS
	Automatically send happy...
</description></item><item><title>Download Listen Audiobook Player 5.3.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 18:47:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-listen-audiobook-player-8511.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-listen-audiobook-player-8511.html
</guid><description>
Listen Audiobook Player is a mobile app for playing audiobooks on your phone or tablet. It lets you play, pause, rewind, and fast-forward audiobooks with ease, while also providing a convenient way to track your listening progress.
Some key features of Listen Audiobook Player include:
	Library Management: Allows you to store and organize your audiobooks in a virtual library for easy access.
	Bookmark: Automatically saves your listening position so you can pick up where you left...
</description></item><item><title>Download ACR Phone 0.373</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 18:46:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-acr-phone-10805.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-acr-phone-10805.html
</guid><description>
ACR Phone &amp;amp; Dialer Spam call blocker is a phone app that can replace your default dialer. This is a completely new application and we are constantly improving it.
Features of ACR Phone
	Blacklist/Block spam
	Call person to notify
	Call notes
	Backup
	Outgoing call blocker
	Call log
	Supports dual SIM
	Contacts
	Video call and photo call screen
	SIP client (on supported devices)
	Call recording (on supported devices)
	Cloud Upload
	Auto Dialer
	Visual voicemail
</description></item><item><title>Download Wallpaper 4K HD – Wallcraft 3.57.03</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 18:42:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wallcraft-cool-4k-wallpaper-4d-12029.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wallcraft-cool-4k-wallpaper-4d-12029.html
</guid><description>
Wallcraft - free wallpaper app that helps you find the best ultra 4K wallpapers and cool backgrounds in 4K HD quality. In Wallcraft live 6K wallpapers you can choose cool 4K wallpapers for every taste. From any wallpaper application only here you can download cool new 3D wallpapers (live 4D wallpapers, parallax and only 3D graphics), for those with aesthetic taste, we There are so many cool abstract wallpapers, try our special couple photos. We have a large amount of free wallpapers with...
</description></item><item><title>Download Textra SMS 4.82 build 48271</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 18:42:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-textra-sms-8697.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-textra-sms-8697.html
</guid><description>
Want a beautiful, super-fast, and highly customizable alternative to your stock Android messaging app? Well today is your day. Textra is simply outstanding! Comes with a bunch of great features, especially over 180 material design themes, bubble and app icon colors. Dark, light and auto night modes, multiple bubble styles, scheduled SMS &amp;amp; MMS (future), stop while sending, slide to delete, slide to call, snapshot camera, multi-select photo gallery select, quick reply SMS popup, great...
</description></item><item><title>Download Music Video Editor - Vidshow 2.35.614</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 18:42:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-music-video-editor-vidshow-11808.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-music-video-editor-vidshow-11808.html
</guid><description>
Want to make a music video with your photos and surprise everyone? Or impress your friends and fans with a stunning Insta story? Now you can use Vidshow, the best photo video editor and video maker with music for FREE! Easily convert and merge your photos into the most beautiful video clips with this best music video editor and create your own photo slideshow with music now!
Main features:
VidShow is an awesome photo music video editor with cool templates, unique transitions, trendy...
</description></item></channel></rss>