<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 01:53:11 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 01:53:11 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Google Drive (Backup and Sync) 119.0.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 15 Jan 2026 00:37:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-drive-6751.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-drive-6751.html
</guid><description>
Using Google Drive is a great way to store your files safely in secure data centers, where your files will not be lost. Even if your computer, phone or tablet is broken, the files you store in the Google Drive are safe. Download photos, videos, documents, and other files that are important to you up to Google Drive. Continue with the memory up to 15GB. Free. Google Drive helps you access your file faster by recognizing the objects in your image and text in the scanned documents.
Easy to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Google Chrome 144.0.7559.60</title><pubDate> Thu, 15 Jan 2026 00:37:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-chrome-1012.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-chrome-1012.html
</guid><description>
Google Chrome web browser is the most used today. Support surf the web, listen to music, watch movies, play web game effective no jerky lag with the internet connection stable. When you are surfing the web or performing an important task, whether it is operation big or small, work or entertainment, then Chrome has the smart features and the speed you need to make, create and explore on the net.
The latest version of Google Chrome is the third 114. But we are providing for users Google...
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 7.7.5</title><pubDate> Thu, 15 Jan 2026 00:35:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-11-7760.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-11-7760.html
</guid><description>
TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 is a program that allows users to discover hidden settings in Windows 11. This application is specially designed for Windows 11, groups many registry settings and distribute them from the easy and secure user interface. With TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 you can move the Windows taskbar to the top and resize the taskbar by editing the registry value. With any application that modifies the registry, we recommend that you have a backup copy...
</description></item><item><title>Download Digiarty Aiarty Video Enhancer 3.4</title><pubDate> Thu, 15 Jan 2026 00:34:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-digiarty-aiarty-video-enhancer-13862.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-digiarty-aiarty-video-enhancer-13862.html
</guid><description>
Digiarty Aiarty Video Enhancer is an AI-powered desktop software designed to upscale, denoise, deblur, and enhance videos up to 4K resolution with professional quality and speed. It uses advanced AI models optimized for GPU acceleration and Turbo mode, enabling real-time or near-real-time video processing, including frame interpolation for smooth motion up to 90fps, 120fps, or higher. This tool is effective in restoring low-resolution, old, blurry, jerky or underexposed footage,...
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 7.7.5</title><pubDate> Thu, 15 Jan 2026 00:34:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-10-7759.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-10-7759.html
</guid><description>
TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 is a utility that allows users to discover hidden settings in Windows 10. This application is specially designed for Windows 10, groups many registry settings and provide them from an easy and secure user interface. With TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 you can move the Windows taskbar to the top and resize the taskbar by editing the registry value. With any application that modifies the registry, we recommend that you have a backup copy to...
</description></item><item><title>Download LDPlayer 9.1.98.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 15 Jan 2026 00:34:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ldplayer-2331.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ldplayer-2331.html
</guid><description>
LDPlayer is an Android emulator that allows users to play games and run applications on Windows computers. LDPlayer supports heavy gaming, running chat applications, editing photos, videos, and many other Android applications. LDPlayer is compatible with Android 5.1 and above, supporting multitasking for an experience that is not inferior to that of using on Mobile.
Installation is a simple and quick process that does not require any special attention from you, there are more. settings,...
</description></item><item><title>Download VideoPad Video Editor Pro 18.03 Beta</title><pubDate> Thu, 15 Jan 2026 00:33:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-videopad-video-editor-pro-268.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-videopad-video-editor-pro-268.html
</guid><description>
VideoPad Video Editor Pro is software edit video from any camcorder, DV camcorder, VHS player or webcam for best quality. The interface of this utility is divided into several parts (for example: list of multi-media, Effects, transitions, Files, Clips, video track, audio track, overlay), which makes everything seem difficult to operate. You can capture videos from camcorder or other devices like webcam or capture card TV and after you have added files and sequence clips to the queue, you...
</description></item><item><title>Download NVIDIA App 11.0.6.379</title><pubDate> Thu, 15 Jan 2026 00:33:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nvidia-app-12646.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nvidia-app-12646.html
</guid><description>
NVIDIA App is an indispensable companion for PC gamers and creators. Make sure your PC is always updated with the latest NVIDIA drivers and technology. Optimize your games and apps with the new unified GPU control center, capture your favorite moments with powerful recording tools through in-game overlays, and explore new tools and features. Latest NVIDIA software.
The program consists of two main parts
	Game Ready Drivers: GeForce Game Ready Drivers are fine-tuned in collaboration...
</description></item><item><title>Download Aiarty Image Enhancer 3.8</title><pubDate> Thu, 15 Jan 2026 00:32:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aiarty-image-enhancer-12181.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aiarty-image-enhancer-12181.html
</guid><description>
Aiarty Image Enhancer is an AI-powered image enhancement software to de-noise, de-blur, enhance images and create more image details. It uses advanced deep learning technologies to enhance and upscale images while creating realistic details. Whether you want to enlarge low-resolution images by 200%, 400% or 800% for printing, deliver 2K/4K/8K images while preserving realistic details, correcting low-quality photos , remove blur and noise or restore compressed JPEGs, Aiarty Image Enhancer...
</description></item><item><title>Download TickTick Premium 8.0.0.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 15 Jan 2026 00:31:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ticktick-premium-7770.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ticktick-premium-7770.html
</guid><description>
TickTick Premium is a task management application that helps users stay organized, it is very suitable for educators and students with many incentives. TickTick turns your Windows PC device into a flexible, easy-to-use and highly efficient office platform. Join millions of people to capture ideas, organize their lives, and do something creative every day.
Whether there are work related tasks or personal goals, TickTick is here to help you manage all your to-dos. With five different...
</description></item><item><title>Download EasyUEFI Technician 6.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 15 Jan 2026 00:31:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easyuefi-enterprise-330.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easyuefi-enterprise-330.html
</guid><description>
EasyUEFI Enterprise is software manager boot option EFI / UEFI, comprehensive as create, delete, edit, clean up, backup system and restore the boot option EFI / UEFI, specify the boot once for the next boot or change the EFI / UEFI boot order, all these operations are performed in Windows without setting the BIOS.
EasyUEFI also released a feature that allows you to manage partition, EFI system, with this feature you can easily backup, restore, rebuild the system partition EFI (ESP), or...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tenorshare 4DDiG 10.6.14.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 15 Jan 2026 00:29:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tenorshare-4ddigs-pro-5629.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tenorshare-4ddigs-pro-5629.html
</guid><description>
Tenorshare 4DDiG is software to recover data from laptop / PC, external drive or USB flash disk. Recover Windows partitions, such as raw partitions, formatted partitions, damaged partitions, etc. Recover lost or deleted photos, videos, audio, videos, documents, etc.
With 4DDiG, you can recover many different types of data from this powerful Windows Data Recovery Tool feature. No matter what you have lost, 4DDiG is capable of recovering deleted files Windows 10 / 8.1 / 8/7 /...
</description></item><item><title>Download NTFS Permissions Reporter Enterprise 5.0.631.0 All Editions</title><pubDate> Thu, 15 Jan 2026 00:29:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ntfs-permissions-reporter-enterprise-6370.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ntfs-permissions-reporter-enterprise-6370.html
</guid><description>
System administrators are constantly required to check user rights for specific files and folders. This is often a time-consuming work, with multiple NTFS classes and repetitive adjustments over time creating a security maze. NTFS Permissions Reporter Enterprise allows you to confirm the security status of the entire file system quickly and efficiently. All have multiple export formats, command line support, integration scheduling, advanced filtration, and more.
Features of NTFS...
</description></item><item><title>Download Freemake Video Converter Gold 5.0.0.30</title><pubDate> Thu, 15 Jan 2026 00:21:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-freemake-video-converter-gold-167.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-freemake-video-converter-gold-167.html
</guid><description>
Freemake Video Converter Gold is a software to help convert tail high quality videos with many different formats on many devices. Freemake Video Converter - convert video to AVI, MP4, WMV, MKV, 3GP, DVD, MP3, iPad, iPhone, PSP, Android phone. Video to MP3 just with one click! Rip and burn DVD. Convert YouTube to MP4, AVI, etc. with Freemake! Results guaranteed. Freemake Video Converter has fast conversion speed, guarantee the output quality,support create HTML5 videos have the embed code...
</description></item><item><title>Download ZebraDesigner Professional 3.3.0.104</title><pubDate> Thu, 15 Jan 2026 00:20:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zebradesigner-pro-7203.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zebradesigner-pro-7203.html
</guid><description>
ZebraDesigner Pro is an easy-to-use disc label design software that helps users create high-quality barcode labels quickly. With ZebraDesigner Pro software, you can easily create a variety of labels, whether simple or complex. Thanks to its user-friendly, Windows-based interface, no training or technical know-how is required. Another benefit is that design and editing is done in one window.
ZebraDesigner Pro provides users with the most used disc label design features, and includes a...
</description></item><item><title>Download Hard Disk Sentinel Pro 6.30.7 Beta</title><pubDate> Thu, 15 Jan 2026 00:19:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hard-disk-sentinel-pro-562.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hard-disk-sentinel-pro-562.html
</guid><description>
Hard Disk Sentinel Pro is a tool for monitoring and optimal performance for hard drive HDD and help diagnose the HDD as well as SSD. Version of Hard Disk Sentinel Pro is a professional version, the most advanced of Hard Disk with many advanced features that meet basic needs, check the hard drive for the user.
The goal of it is to find, test, diagnose and repair the malfunction, hard drive, report and display the health status of the SSD and hard drive failure, decreased performance and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Directory Opus Pro 13.20.4 Beta</title><pubDate> Thu, 15 Jan 2026 00:14:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-opus-pro-779.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-opus-pro-779.html
</guid><description>
Directory Opus Pro is a software replacement for Explorer with traditional strength and function more than any manager other files. Directory Opus Pro full support for high DPI screen (for example 4K and 5K) with the rename dialog is redesigned, with new features. Besides being a recording macro only allows you to perform mass renaming complex that don't need regular expressions. In addition, Directory Opus Pro also enhances the ability to script.Better handling of renaming recursive and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Abelssoft SendMe (Send2Phone) 2026 v2.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 15 Jan 2026 00:13:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-abelssoft-send2phone-2198.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-abelssoft-send2phone-2198.html
</guid><description>
Abelssoft Send2Phone is a program that allows you to send files from personal computer to phone your mobile, you can now easily share links, images, any files from PC to mobile or vice versa. Traffic will be encrypted using AES-256, so the authors assure you that you should not worry about blocking data, but I won't believe in a hundred percent. Thanks to the user interface simple, clear and pleasant. you can send the file just by a click of the mouse, the software can be integrated into...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft Office Pro Plus - Online Installer 3.3.10</title><pubDate> Thu, 15 Jan 2026 00:06:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-office-professional-plus-online-installer-7661.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-office-professional-plus-online-installer-7661.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft Office 2021 Professional Plus x86-x64 - Online Installer is a small script that helps users to download and install Microsoft Office 2021 Professional Plus including all updates directly from Microsoft CDN Server.
The version of Office 2021 downloaded and installed on your computer will include the following programs: Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Outlook, OneNote, Publisher, Access, Visio, Project, ProofingTools, OneDrive Desktop.
Usage:
Unzip the downloaded ZIP Archive...
</description></item><item><title>Download CapCut PC 7.9.0.3294 / 8.0.0.3318 Beta 1</title><pubDate> Thu, 15 Jan 2026 00:05:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capcut-pc-9995.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capcut-pc-9995.html
</guid><description>
CapCut PC is a simple video editing tool that you can freely use anywhere. You can create videos on your browser, desktop and laptop, or on your phone. Versatile editing, magical AI tools, team collaboration, and built-in assets. Create videos in a whole new way.
You can edit videos based on editing the timeline, in the process you can add different elements and effects to the video to give the best effect to your work. It is a simple and intuitive set of editing tools and effects that...
</description></item><item><title>Download TablePlus 6.8.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 15 Jan 2026 00:03:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tableplus-2774.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tableplus-2774.html
</guid><description>
TablePlus is a software management database powerful and effective. In fact, the management and organization database with the software is extremely easy. Thanks to the powerful features and simple design, software, database management, data has become faster and more efficient. Benefits of using this program are many different options to keep them safe for database of you. These include authentication, multi-step, libssh original and TLS to encrypt your connection
TablePlus -...
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow QR Code Maker 4.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 14 Jan 2026 23:57:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qr-code-maker-9760.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qr-code-maker-9760.html
</guid><description>
QR Code Maker is a simple app to generate QR Code for text, link, email, Whatsapp, SMS, Call and Wifi. With QR Codes, you have complete flexibility, because only a short URL points to the encrypted content. So you can modify the links or stored files without having to generate and reprint the Codes. This will save resources and allow you to respond to any campaign changes as quickly as possible.
Features of QR Code Maker
	Generate QR Code for Text, Link, Email, Whatsapp, SMS, Call and...
</description></item><item><title>Download SysTools vCard Importer 7.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 14 Jan 2026 23:56:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-systools-vcard-importer-12239.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-systools-vcard-importer-12239.html
</guid><description>
SysTools vCard Importer is professionally designed software to easily upload VCF files to PST Outlook. This vCard to Outlook converter does not impose any restrictions on importing multiple vCards into PST of Outlook 2003/2007/2010/2013/2016/2019. This tool ensures that the process of transferring VCF contacts to Outlook does not result in data loss.
Main features:
	Import multiple vCard contacts into Outlook PST File
	Multiple Import Options: Save in New PST, New Outlook...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cash Register Pro 4.0.9</title><pubDate> Wed, 14 Jan 2026 23:56:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cash-register-pro-3853.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cash-register-pro-3853.html
</guid><description>
Cash Register Pro a software cash register full of features and creative for a Windows computer, it will help you to better handle all the activities of the computer money. The application comes with the user interface logical and user friendly allows you to work quickly and do not commit the common error. The program can be used on a number of computers and offers a wide range of authorization secure and reliable. Cash Register Pro will help you track products and goods remain...
</description></item><item><title>Download Imaginando VS 2.0.5</title><pubDate> Wed, 14 Jan 2026 23:55:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-imaginando-vs-11117.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-imaginando-vs-11117.html
</guid><description>
Take your music to another dimension with a captivating visual world. VS - Visual Synthesizer makes it easy to represent your sounds optically in a highly customizable way. At the core of Imaginando VS is a set of graphics shaders called materials, which render procedurally generated geometry in real time, based on each material's unique set of parameters. VS comes equipped with 50 beautifully hypnotic materials for you to customize and combine to create mesmerizing performances.
Visual...
</description></item></channel></rss>