<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 17:35:58 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 17:35:58 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Text Editor Pro 34.0.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 06 Oct 2025 17:58:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-text-editor-pro-800.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-text-editor-pro-800.html
</guid><description>
Text Editor Pro is software to handle text, HTML, Perl, Ruby, or Fortran with features syntax highlighting, professional. Text Editor provides syntax highlighting for over 50 scripts and has a simple interface and easy access. In addition, the Text Editor Pro also supports more than 50 programming languages like C ++, COBOL, graph DOT, DSP, DWScript, Fortran, Foxpro, Java, Perl, Python, Ruby, SQL and many other languages.
Text Editor Pro - text Processing professional
The software can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Any Video Downloader Pro 9.6.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 06 Oct 2025 17:55:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-video-downloader-pro-3731.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-video-downloader-pro-3731.html
</guid><description>
Any Video Downloader Pro is software support you can download video HD 720p, 1080p, 2K, 4K and 8K from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion, Vimeo, Metacafe and thousands of video sharing sites, other. It is a tool to speed up multi-threading can speed up your download faster up to 5 times. This helpful program support download at the same time. Any Video Downloader Pro lets you download multiple videos at the same time. Moreover, it allows you to pause and resume downloads if you need more...
</description></item><item><title>Download FxSound (FxSound Enhancer Premium) 1.2.1 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Mon, 06 Oct 2025 17:55:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fxsound-enhancer-premium-2013.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fxsound-enhancer-premium-2013.html
</guid><description>
FxSound Enhancer Premium formerly DFX Audio Enhance, is accessories multimedia software most popular in the world with over 46 million downloads worldwide. FxSound enhances the sound of most of the music content and online video is live streaming on the Web, including the streaming service, YouTube, Pandora, Spotify and Apple Music. FxSound Enhancer Premium also implemented enhanced real-time audio on the player PC multimedia most popular include iTunes, Windows Media Player, Winamp and...
</description></item><item><title>Download StartAllBack 3.9.16.5320</title><pubDate> Mon, 06 Oct 2025 17:53:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-startallback-6857.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-startallback-6857.html
</guid><description>
With the official release of Windows 11, chances are that most of you want to try it out. As the name suggests, StartAllBack is a small, lightweight tool that can help you enjoy the power of the new operating system while keeping the look and feel, especially because main work area, desktop of Windows 7, Windows 10 as taskbars and start menu styles.
StartAllBack is specially designed for Windows 11 and will not work on any older operating systems. If you want to get the start menu back...
</description></item><item><title>Download ScreenToGif 2.42.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 06 Oct 2025 17:53:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-screentogif-499.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-screentogif-499.html
</guid><description>
ScreenToGif is a software that allows you to capture anything on your screen and save it as animated GIF. Besides, ScreenToGif allows you can freely move the frame to record a video on your website or activity on the screen on the computer to your desk.
The recording can be paused and resumed and once you finish recording, the program will display a simple editing allows you to preview the recording and delete every frame is not necessary.
The downside is: Because ScreenToGif does not...
</description></item><item><title>Download Luanti 5.14.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 06 Oct 2025 17:52:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-luanti-13986.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-luanti-13986.html
</guid><description>
Luanti, formerly known as Minetest, is a free and open source voxel game engine, written primarily in C++. It uses a modified version of the Irrlicht Engine and allows users to create games and mods using the Lua programming language.
Player Features
	Choose from a Variety of Games: There are a variety of games to choose from. You can survive in harsh environments, build creatively, or fight other players. Just load the game or connect to the server.
	Huge map: With 62,000 × 62,000...
</description></item><item><title>Download Internet Download Manager Portable 6.42 Build 48</title><pubDate> Mon, 06 Oct 2025 17:51:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-internet-download-manager-portable-11965.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-internet-download-manager-portable-11965.html
</guid><description>
Internet Download Manager (IDM) is a popular software tool that helps users download files from the internet at faster speeds. It is designed to increase download speeds up to five times, resume and schedule downloads, and support multiple download queues. IDM also has many features that make it easy to use and customize to fit your needs.
IDM has a simple and friendly interface that makes it easy to use. The software integrates seamlessly with popular web browsers such as Google Chrome,...
</description></item><item><title>Download FreeFileSync Donation Edition 14.5</title><pubDate> Mon, 06 Oct 2025 17:51:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-freefilesync-donation-edition-13970.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-freefilesync-donation-edition-13970.html
</guid><description>
FreeFileSync Donation Edition is a special version of the FreeFileSync file synchronization software for donors who financially support projects. It is used to compare and synchronize folders, create and manage backups of all your important files. Instead of copying every file each time, FreeFileSync determines the difference between the source and destination folders and transfers only the minimum amount of data necessary.
FreeFileSync version with additional functionality and...
</description></item><item><title>Download FxSound Pro 1.2.1 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Mon, 06 Oct 2025 17:50:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fxsound-5966.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fxsound-5966.html
</guid><description>
FxSound Pro is a professional software that helps to enhance the quality of sound, volume, depth, and sound on your PC. FxSound brings you a great sound just with a downloadable download. After using FxSound, you will know if it is for you or not. Most people do n' t know what they ' re missing in their sound until they try their software/sound hardware better. It ' s hard to convey if you do n' t really experience yourself.
Reason to use FxSound Pro:
	The perfect sound on every...
</description></item><item><title>Download Photo Supreme 2025.3.3.8106</title><pubDate> Mon, 06 Oct 2025 17:48:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photo-supreme-430.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photo-supreme-430.html
</guid><description>
Photo Supreme is a software product management professional pictures of idimager. With Photo Supreme you can arrange, manage back stock photo archive of yourself and share them with you here and relatives easily via Email or Facebook. Photo Supreme provides users method to sort images effective, logical, as well as edit and share your photos with friends and relatives in the family. Especially the Photo Supreme allows to work with multiple image formats and support mounting support,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Free Music and Video Downloader 3.08</title><pubDate> Mon, 06 Oct 2025 17:47:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-music-and-video-downloader-123.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-music-and-video-downloader-123.html
</guid><description>
Free Music &amp;amp; Video Downloader (formerly the Free Music Downloader) allows you to download his favorite music at the form of MP3 files from many different online sources, including Last.FM, Grooveshark, Sogou, VKontakte, SoundCloud, and many other things.Just enter name of artist or song you are looking for and click the Search button to see a list of results and download the songs you want.You can customize the services that applications will use to search, put the download folder...
</description></item><item><title>Download Broot 1.51.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 06 Oct 2025 17:47:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-broot-8588.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-broot-8588.html
</guid><description>
Broot is an open source command line tool for browsing and navigating file systems. Broot provides a fast and intuitive way to navigate the file system with a tree-like interactive interface. It provides various features like searching for files, opening files and folders, copying file paths to clipboard, etc. It also supports customizing keys and color themes.
Features of Broot
	Fast file browsing: Lets you quickly navigate through large directory structures with a tree-like...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Video Downloader 11.28.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 06 Oct 2025 17:46:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-video-downloader-9636.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-video-downloader-9636.html
</guid><description>
YT Video Downloader is software used to easily and quickly download any video or audio content from any website in HD quality using video downloader online. Save videos from almost any website supported by a video downloader on your local hard drive. Media search is a convenient way to do this.
Features of YT Video Downloader
	Download videos from hundreds of video sites.
	Really increase your download speed by up to 500% or even more!
	Download 8K, 5K, 4K Ultra HD, 2K Quad HD, 1080p...
</description></item><item><title>Download Altium Designer 26.0.0.14</title><pubDate> Mon, 06 Oct 2025 17:45:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-altium-designer-01en-625.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-altium-designer-01en-625.html
</guid><description>
Altium Designer is the PCB design software (circuit board) professional helps you connect seamlessly with every aspect of design. Altium Designer is a within the automation software design, PCB and electronics for the motherboard in good and most popular today. It was developed by software company Altium Limited based in Australia.
Features Altium Designer:
	Analyzing the similar circuits using Spice.
	Have the perfect tool with the ability to simulate and debug the code and design...
</description></item><item><title>Download Kenney Asset Forge Deluxe 2.5.3</title><pubDate> Mon, 06 Oct 2025 17:45:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kenny-asset-forge-11015.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kenny-asset-forge-11015.html
</guid><description>
Kenney Asset Forge is a software tool designed for game developers and digital artists. It simplifies the process of creating 2D and 3D models, especially for use in video games. There are currently over 900 pre-made blocks, categorized into different sections. You can place an unlimited number of blocks in your creation, which can then be exported and used in any game engine of your choice.
Models created in Asset Forge can be exported to a variety of formats suitable for use in many...
</description></item><item><title>Download Thimeo ST-Enterprise 10.71</title><pubDate> Mon, 06 Oct 2025 17:44:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thimeo-st-enterprise-10422.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thimeo-st-enterprise-10422.html
</guid><description>
Thimeo ST-Enterprise is for larger media groups running multiple stations or channels. It does everything that Stereo Tools does and more! With ST-Enterprise, you can run up to 50(*) FM and/or HD processors on a single computer, with a single interface to control them and an overview screen showing the status of them all. incoming and outgoing signals.
Features of Thimeo ST-Enterprise
	It makes more efficient use of available resources, mainly processing power, and allows you to share...
</description></item><item><title>Download VovSoft Image Splitter 1.4</title><pubDate> Mon, 06 Oct 2025 17:43:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-image-splitter-8344.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-image-splitter-8344.html
</guid><description>
VovSoft Image Splitter is a simple software tool that allows you to split any image file into small parts, supporting all popular formats. You can crop multiple images with the quality of the original with this easy-to-use software. You can add individual images, drag and drop or select a folder containing them and let the application extract all compatible images. All images are displayed in a list, along with their width and height. You can easily change the number of output images...
</description></item><item><title>Download Grub2Win 3.0.0.4</title><pubDate> Mon, 06 Oct 2025 17:43:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-grub2win-3177.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-grub2win-3177.html
</guid><description>
Grub2Win is a open source program to dual boot Windows and Linux safely. Grub2Win boot code the GNU Grub version 2.04. Everything is in a folder of 20 MB on Windows drive C: On the EFI system, a few small modules to be installed into the EFI partition of your.
Grub2Win - Boot system, Windows
Using GUI Windows and simple instructions you can install Grub2Win quickly and safely. Notice the boot time and help can be displayed in multiple languages. After installing interface, it's easy to...
</description></item><item><title>Download FinalMesh Professional 6.1.1.674</title><pubDate> Mon, 06 Oct 2025 17:42:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-finalmesh-professional-1278.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-finalmesh-professional-1278.html
</guid><description>
FinalMesh Professional is a software easy and powerful the incredible to create PDF document with 3D or the website WebGL. FinalMesh Professional will help your 3D model will be converted into application WebGL complete HTML or PDF with 3D content. In addition, FinalMesh is viewer and 3D switch with amazing user interface modern, fast and has many useful features.
FinalMesh Professional
The function of FinalMesh Professional
The 3D viewer
	Lighting in pixels
	Display mode...
</description></item><item><title>Download Thimeo Stereo Tool 10.71</title><pubDate> Mon, 06 Oct 2025 17:41:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stereo-tool-4066.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stereo-tool-4066.html
</guid><description>
Stereo Tool is an audio processor based on software, provide sound quality superior and comes with many unique features. It is used by over 1500 FM stations, from the station of the small local to the station 50 - 100 kW and nationwide network with dozens of generators, thousands of stations online and many radio DAB +, HD, AM and TV. Stereo Tool can make recordings sound equal and consistent in volume and sound color, highlight details and increase the stereo effect is there. It can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Thimeo Relay 10.71</title><pubDate> Mon, 06 Oct 2025 17:41:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thimeo-relay-10423.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thimeo-relay-10423.html
</guid><description>
Thimeo Relay uses your sound card (internal or external) as a Relay detector and converts on/off signals into RDS commands that can be sent to most devices. RDS encoders, including those in Stereo Engine and STXtreme.
Features of Thimeo Relay
	It minimizes audio latency, ensuring real-time audio processing and synchronization with video content or virtual instruments.
	It offers multiple connection options to meet different audio needs.
	Use your sound card (internal or external) as a...
</description></item><item><title>Download Password Tech (PwTech) 3.5.9</title><pubDate> Mon, 06 Oct 2025 17:40:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-password-tech-5036.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-password-tech-5036.html
</guid><description>
Password Tech is a program to create strong passwords have the ability to create a large number of passwords is secured by a password, the password can pronounce is, password-based form, the passphrase including of from and password written in the script. The password can be stored in the database is encrypted along with the user name, URL, notes, etc. Password Tech offers many options to customize the password according to the different needs of users, and individual commands with Lua...
</description></item><item><title>Download DiskBoss Ultimate 16.0.12 + Pro + Enterprise</title><pubDate> Mon, 06 Oct 2025 17:40:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-diskboss-ultimate-1289.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-diskboss-ultimate-1289.html
</guid><description>
DiskBoss Ultimate is a software application professional, built to help you analyze disks, directories and network shares, arrange files and folders, perform the operation the advanced search and delete duplicate items, as well as perform management activities file automatically based on user-defined rules and policies.
DiskBoss Ultimate - analyzing disk and file manager
This tool also can synchronize disks, directories and network shares, perform the task delete data securely in batch...
</description></item><item><title>Download Social Media Downloader 7.8.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 06 Oct 2025 17:39:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-socialmediaapps-facebook-video-downloader-3742.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-socialmediaapps-facebook-video-downloader-3742.html
</guid><description>
SocialVideo Downloader (formerly SocialMediaApps Facebook Video Downloader) is a Windows application to download and convert your favorite videos from Facebook and hundreds of other video sharing sites. It increases your loading speed by up to 500%, or even more! The application has a simple and intuitive user interface, its main functions and features are quite obvious to anyone. , regardless of prior experience with similar purpose tools.
&amp;nbsp;
SocialVideo Downloader
The main...
</description></item><item><title>Download Display Driver Uninstaller (DDU) 18.1.3.5</title><pubDate> Mon, 06 Oct 2025 17:10:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-display-driver-uninstaller-1999.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-display-driver-uninstaller-1999.html
</guid><description>
Display Driver Uninstaller (DDU) help to easily completely remove the packages and drivers graphics cards AMD, NVIDIA and Intel from your system without leaving any rest whatsoever. Display Driver Uninstaller will automatically detect your current GPU and allows you to delete drivers, registry and files related only by the click of a button. It will also prevent Windows automatically re-install drivers when you reboot your computer, leaving you a drivers graphics common until you install...
</description></item></channel></rss>