<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 21:33:05 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 21:33:05 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download KORG Multipoly Native 1.1.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 00:32:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-korg-multipoly-native-12830.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-korg-multipoly-native-12830.html
</guid><description>
Inspired by the legendary KORG Mono/Poly, the new KORG multi/poly analog modeling synthesizer delivers breathtaking analog sounds combined with extraordinary digital power and versatility. It has already received acclaim as one of the best synthesizers of the year.
Now, Korg is pleased to announce multi/poly native, software that is fully compatible with the hardware multi/poly synthesizer. multi/poly native is available in VST3, AAX, and standalone formats on both macOS and Windows, as...
</description></item><item><title>Download Exacoustics GHOST 1.1.11</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 00:31:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-exacoustics-ghost-13879.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-exacoustics-ghost-13879.html
</guid><description>
Exacoustics GHOST is a powerful and innovative synthesis plugin that uniquely combines Wavetable synthesis and Frequency Modulation (FM) synthesis into one integrated instrument. Released in August 2024 by Brisbane-based developer Exacoustics, the plugin quickly gained attention for its fresh approach and deep sound design capabilities.
Key Features:
	Hybrid Synthesis Engine: Combines the flexibility of wavetable oscillators with the complexity and richness of FM synthesis.
	Six...
</description></item><item><title>Download SmartGit 25.1.102</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 00:30:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-smartgit-13978.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-smartgit-13978.html
</guid><description>
SmartGit is a cross-platform, graphical Git application designed for professional users to simplify and enhance Git version control workflows. SmartGit supports major Git hosting services like GitHub, Bitbucket, GitLab, and Azure DevOps with built-in features to handle pull requests, comments, and code reviews directly in the app.
Why choose SmartGit as your Git Client?
	One for all.
	SmartGit helps new Git users as well as helps experienced developers work more efficiently.
	SmartGit...
</description></item><item><title>Download KORG Modwave Native 1.4.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 00:30:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-korg-modwave-native-10310.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-korg-modwave-native-10310.html
</guid><description>
Modwave, released in 2021, builds on the DW legacy and transforms it into a modern monster synth, featuring incredibly deep wavetable oscillators, stunning filters , extremely flexible modulation, complex sample sequencing, and macro controls for unique, powerful, and easy-to-customize sounds and phrases.
The software is fully compatible with hardware modwave synthesizers. KORG Modwave Native is available in VST3, AAX, and standalone formats on both macOS and Windows, as well as AU on...
</description></item><item><title>Download KORG Wavestate Native 1.5.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 00:29:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-korg-wavestate-native-10309.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-korg-wavestate-native-10309.html
</guid><description>
KORG Wavestate Native is designed from the ground up for a new generation of musicians, producers and composers, taking cues from sources as diverse as modular synths, groove boxes and layouts algorithm. It is available in VST3, AAX, and standalone formats on both macOS and Windows, as well as AU on macOS. You can seamlessly exchange audio between hardware and software. Produce in your DAW with the original wave state, then play the same sounds on stage using the wave state...
</description></item><item><title>Download Dragonrise Games YoloX 1.6.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 00:29:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dragonrise-games-yolox-11598.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dragonrise-games-yolox-11598.html
</guid><description>
Use YoloX to change your game crosshair.Including color inversion, sound sensor, motion sensor, heat safety and other features never seen before.Development your target with the next revolution in crosshair technology!
YoloX Features
	Effect: Invert colors and other effects.
	Animation: Separate animations for primary fire, secondary fire, and jump.
	Sound sensor: Animated response to game sounds. Now you can listen to your own music without missing any key sounds.
	Motion sensor:...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sequence Generator Pro QSI Edition 4.5.0.1554 Beta</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 00:28:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sequence-generator-pro-6985.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sequence-generator-pro-6985.html
</guid><description>
Sequence Generator Pro is astrophotography software that makes it possible to organize and coordinate all your gear to make the most of your time under the sky dark. With it, you can coordinate a variety of devices including cameras, color filters, focus controllers and telescopes. Chain any different goals and events you can imagine to capture frames of the night sky.
Sequence Generator Pro's powerful software autofocus reduces the frustration of conditions like rapidly changing...
</description></item><item><title>Download Unicodia 3.0.5</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 00:09:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-unicodia-8521.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-unicodia-8521.html
</guid><description>
Unicodia is free, open source software that can be used as an alternative character map for your Windows machine. The interface contains everything you need, allowing you to easily cycle through all the available ASCII symbols and copy them to the clipboard. Uncicodia is a great alternative to your standard Unicode characters and is filled with symbols/characters that make it useful for a number of different uses.
Features of Unicodia
	In Windows 10/11 — all characters of Unicode 15...
</description></item><item><title>Download Seamless3d 3.038.12</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 00:08:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-seamless3d-10257.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-seamless3d-10257.html
</guid><description>
Seamless3d is one of the easiest 3D modeling and animation programs that offers artistic freedom. It is designed to be a powerful and practical way to create 3D models that will appeal to anyone who wants to create quality 3D animated content for the web. A versatile NURBS-based 3D Modeler/Animator designed for ease of use without compromising artistic freedom, allowing you to create unique models.
Features of Seamless3d
	WYSIWYG
	Undo/Redo
	Export clean, efficient files
	Dedicated...
</description></item><item><title>Download FreeVimager 9.9.27</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 23:59:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-freevimager-3440.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-freevimager-3440.html
</guid><description>
FreeVimager is a simple and quick image editing for Windows. There are many tools around to do it, but the purpose of this program is to become a tool small and handy does what it says and run as a file exe standalone (no installation required).
FreeVimager - See and simple photo editing
The features of FreeVimager
	Gesture touch screen support zoom in / out and for next / previous
	View image location in Google Map. Check the faq section, this
	View and edit graphics file types:...
</description></item><item><title>Download ContaCam 9.9.27</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 23:58:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-contacam-3439.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-contacam-3439.html
</guid><description>
ContaCam provides for you software free video surveillance and live webcam reliable for Windows. It is extremely easy for system resources and does not contain the ballooning not necessary. ContaCam fast, lightweight, and flexible enough to meet all the security needs of you, while still being very user friendly and can run on both those systems have the best.
ContaCam - video Surveillance security
ContaCam features security Surveillance CCTV with motion detection and digital video...
</description></item><item><title>Download Winaero Tweaker 1.64.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 17:19:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winaero-tweaker-1063.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winaero-tweaker-1063.html
</guid><description>
Winaero Tweaker is a customization tool is provided for windows for you to change the default settings, and personalization Windows liking. The program includes the tweaks for all version of operating system from Windows 7 to Windows 10. Winaero Tweaker automatically detect OS version of Windows you're running and show the custom and custom custom. Software can be installed as a mobile app so that you can carry with you when you move from this computer to another computer.
Winaero...
</description></item><item><title>Download Advanced System Repair Pro 2.0.1.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 17:15:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-system-repair-pro-80.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-system-repair-pro-80.html
</guid><description>
Advanced System Repair Pro gives you all the tools you need in a program to clean, repair, protect, optimize and increase your PC!
Advanced System Repair Pro speed 300% faster help your computer run faster by increasing the launch speed, optimizing registry, as well as get rid of unwanted apps and files, useless other causing your computer to run slower.
Advanced System Repair Pro - optimized system
Features, characteristics, Advanced System Repair Pro
Get a computer cleaner in a few...
</description></item><item><title>Download JRiver Media Center 35.0.29</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 17:14:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jriver-media-center-110.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jriver-media-center-110.html
</guid><description>
JRiver Media Center can help you strictly manage all your files media and enjoy them in a completely new way. Launching the application for the first time, users will be immediately impressed with the intuitive and eye-catching interface with many interesting features to explore. Most people who have used JRiver Media Center evaluate that the software interface design is youthful and modern.
The software for arranging cover art of music files is also extremely neat, especially Insert...
</description></item><item><title>Download StartIsBack ++ 2.9.21</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 17:13:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-startisback-402.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-startisback-402.html
</guid><description>
StartIsBack ++ is software customizable start menu and taskbar support, booting the computer and showing the feature started working on the start menu. StartIsBack is for the screen is not upside down when booting, help easy yùy variables and configuration rich; And much more.
The main features StartIsBack ++
Computer support:
	Launch programs you use frequently
	Open the document you are working
	Find content you are looking for
	To place the system just by a click of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Audacity 3.7.7</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 17:13:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-audacity-1648.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-audacity-1648.html
</guid><description>
Audacity software to record audio along with editing features such as noise filtering, distortion noise, insert unique effects. The latest version of Audacity include the improvement of effects, interface, updates Nyquist and libflac. A number of bugs have also been fixed to help the software operate more smoothly. Audacity accompanied by the link to various sources, assist you learn how to use all the features of the program. These sources include Quick Help Guide (quick help), a guide,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Remote Desktop Manager Enterprise 2025.3.27</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 17:12:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-remote-desktop-manager-enterprise-242.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-remote-desktop-manager-enterprise-242.html
</guid><description>
Remote Desktop Manager Enterprise software is the complete management of remote connections and virtual machines from a single location, at the same time access support data online and cloud storage. Remote Desktop Manager supports multiple types of connections, not only connections for the protocol connect remote computer Remote Desktop Protocol (RDP).
Remote Desktop Manager easily add, edit, delete, share, organize and find your remote connection of you quickly. Compatible with...
</description></item><item><title>Download Avast Premium Security 25.12.10659</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 17:12:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avast-premier-antivirus-security-1359.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avast-premier-antivirus-security-1359.html
</guid><description>
Avast! Premier Antivirus is antivirus software famous by combining all the technologies and methods virus advanced. The developer software this anti-virus have invested in all their knowledge about fighting viruses to create one of the software anti-virus best. Program anti-virus this combines all the technology and advanced methods to get the level of computer security highest. This product is ideal for all the Windows operating system.
Avast! Premier Antivirus - antivirus...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft Edge 143.0.3650.80</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 17:01:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-edge-3940.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-edge-3940.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft Edge is web browser developed specifically for Windows operating system 10 alternatives to Internet Explorer is the default browser on Windows. Browser Microsoft Edge built-in assistant Cortana brings content and website based on the user's preferences, there are also system utilities quite extensive help you to customize according to individual. Microsoft Edge has the similarity with Google Chrome quite large, except the target is marked more of the interface and the rounded...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Downloader 10.0.9</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 17:00:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html
</guid><description>
YTD Youtube Downloader is an application that reliable and intuitive, allowing you to quickly download YouTube videos and save them to your computer. You can also convert the media files to the format desired video or extract audio streams and save separately. YTD Youtube Downloader lets you save your favorite clips of yourself from Youtube, Facebook, Vimeo and Dailymotion to your desktop. The software supports URLS from many web site hosting, multimedia and allows you to download desired...
</description></item><item><title>Download PassFab 4EasyPartition 3.9.0.12</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 17:00:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-passfab-4easypartition-7983.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-passfab-4easypartition-7983.html
</guid><description>
After using your PC for many years, there are bound to be many files you want to transfer to your new PC. PassFab 4EasyPartition can perform a one-click migration saving you hours of reinstalling operating systems and applications. It has an intuitive interface and step-by-step wizard that makes migrating the system in just a few steps. PassFab 4EasyPartition will effectively solve the problem of low disk space, speed up your computer and make it run faster.
Features of PassFab...
</description></item><item><title>Download SoftPerfect Network Scanner 25.12</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 16:59:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-softperfect-network-scanner-465.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-softperfect-network-scanner-465.html
</guid><description>
SoftPerfect Network Scanner is software scan ip address fast with many features for the programmer. With SoftPerfect Network Scanner you can completely scan IPv4 / IPv6 universal fast with many options. Program this powerful can ping computers, scan ports, discover the folder is shared and comes with filtering options and flexible display. It can take practically any information about the network device through WMI, SNMP, HTTP, SSH , and PowerShell. In addition, it can scan the remote...
</description></item><item><title>Download Internet Download Accelerator Pro 7.3.1.1745</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 16:58:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-internet-download-accelerator-pro-234.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-internet-download-accelerator-pro-234.html
</guid><description>
Internet Download Accelerator Pro is software acceleration support download support users in the download file like IDM running on multiple network protocols, including FTP. Internet Download Accelerator will help your computer be file download speed is fast even when the transmission line do not have high speed. Internet Download Accelerator Pro is completely compatible with most web browsers such as Internet Explorer, Firefox, Mozilla, Opera,..
Internet Download Accelerator also...
</description></item><item><title>Download Kotato All Video Downloader Pro 10.0.6</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 16:58:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kotato-all-video-downloader-pro-5228.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kotato-all-video-downloader-pro-5228.html
</guid><description>
Kotato All Video Downloader Pro is a Windows application professional to download and convert your favorite videos from the video sharing website. It speeds up your downloads up to 5 times! Kotato All Video Downloader Pro can download videos from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion and hundreds of video sharing sites, other. After downloading, you will be able to play them smoother on your PC or your mobile device, even when you don't have Internet access.
The main features of Kotato All...
</description></item><item><title>Download Viber for PC 26.8.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 12 Dec 2025 16:57:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-viber-2406.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-viber-2406.html
</guid><description>
Viber is a software of instant messaging, based on VoIP protocols, multi-platform due to the Viber Media development for smart phones used to send sms and make calls over the internet. Along with text messaging, users can exchange images, video and audio.
Viber - software news message, chat online
This is a program that is quite popular is mainly designed for mobile phones, but now we are talking about the version for Windows, so immediately. It will allow you to send messages to other...
</description></item></channel></rss>