<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 15:39:14 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 15:39:14 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Visual Studio Code 1.104.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 18:35:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-visual-studio-code-3182.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-visual-studio-code-3182.html
</guid><description>
Visual Studio Code is the encryption tool of Microsoft has met most of the needs of the developer. Environment this encoding was introduced to compete with other products such as Sublime and Nodepad ++ . Microsoft, in its new product, has not been released in many years, has provided many features in a simple environment. In addition to the familiar with a dozen programming languages, the syntax and get to know coding language as soon as be encrypted and allows for syntax highlighting, it...
</description></item><item><title>Download pdfFactory Pro 9.17</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 18:32:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdffactory-pro-277.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdffactory-pro-277.html
</guid><description>
pdfFactory Pro is software to create PDF files according to standards in a simple and secure documents secure. pdfFactory Pro on taiwebs.com that support encryption (40 or 128bit) and control access to the PDF file.
pdfFactory Pro has all the features of pdfFactory and adds bookmarks, job order, title a letter and the email function automatically. Only pdfFactory allows printing to paper or PDF without printing twice. Acrobat is not needed for the printing. Increases the convenience of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Photoshop 2025 v26.11.0 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 18:32:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-0010-adobe-photoshop-737.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-0010-adobe-photoshop-737.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Photoshop is a powerful raster graphics editor developed by Adobe Systems, primarily used for image editing, photo editing, and graphic design. Currently,&amp;nbsp;Adobe Photoshop 2025 is considered a graphic design software, creating and enhancing images, illustrations, and 3D artwork. In addition, it also supports website and mobile app design, video editing, real-life painting simulation, and more.
Adobe Photoshop 2025 - Graphic design
When it comes to Adobe Photoshop, it is...
</description></item><item><title>Download Topaz Video AI Pro 7.1.5 / 1.0.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 18:30:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-video-enhance-ai-3733.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-video-enhance-ai-3733.html
</guid><description>
Topaz Video Enhance AI is a tool to increase video quality with this great technology ONE. Topaz Video Enhance WHO wide open your video to resolutions up to 8K with the details and consistency of motion. Until the present, there is no way to re-create a perfect high resolution video from the footage is low resolution. From the family film to SD low quality to DVD quality and more than that, Video Enhance WHO will convert your video into the footage is upgrade clear with resolutions up to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Photoshop Elements 2026 v26.0 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 18:29:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photoshop-elements-0001-5433.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photoshop-elements-0001-5433.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Photoshop Elements is this full-featured program that guides you when you first learn how to edit photos and grows with you as your skills develop. If you're looking for a program that maintains usability and offers plenty of support, then Adobe Photoshop Elements is worth a look.
Creating amazing pictures has never been easier. Bring your best shots forward with auto-generated compositions and smart editing options. Easily organize your photos and share them in fun ways. Cool photo...
</description></item><item><title>Download FinePrint 12.17</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 18:28:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fineprint-276.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fineprint-276.html
</guid><description>
FinePrint is a software support you work in text saves paper and increases the lifespan of your printer. FinePrint is a software connected printer, you can print 4 or 8 pages file on the computer on a page of paper that still ensure the font is clear, easy to read.
With FinePrint works for you, the incidents of printing annoyances will disappear. Below are just some examples of incidents in which FinePrint can fix. Read more part of our Business for the benefit of the FinePrint in the...
</description></item><item><title>Download CoolUtils PDF Combine Pro 7.5.0.62</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 18:28:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-pdf-combine-pro-580.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-pdf-combine-pro-580.html
</guid><description>
CoolUtils PDF Combine Pro  is software that helps you combine  PDF, DOC, TXT, DOCX, HTML, XLS, images  h (TIFF, JPEG, PNG) and  email  as a  PDF  file. With PDF Combine Pro it is easier than ever to combine documents into one PDF file. Now you don't have to use some programs and converters to get a PDF. Everything for PDF Combine Pro to do for you.
Office, fax, email files - get combined PDF in seconds for personal use, commercial needs, electronic discovery, or manufacturing.  PDF...
</description></item><item><title>Download Helium Music Manager Premium 17.4.529</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 18:27:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-helium-music-manager-premium-164.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-helium-music-manager-premium-164.html
</guid><description>
Helium Music Manager is a music manager that can rip, tag, play, browse, search, rename, burn and synchronize your music with the mobile. You can control your music collection with Helium Music Manager. Stop using time looking for the file on your computer or looking through CDS, vinyl records and tapes - instead, simply enjoy and explore your music! Helium Music Manager can replace the ripper, the player, tag editor and related software to audio your other.
Helium Music Manager...
</description></item><item><title>Download VideoPad Video Editor Pro 17.43 Beta</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 18:27:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-videopad-video-editor-pro-268.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-videopad-video-editor-pro-268.html
</guid><description>
VideoPad Video Editor Pro is software edit video from any camcorder, DV camcorder, VHS player or webcam for best quality. The interface of this utility is divided into several parts (for example: list of multi-media, Effects, transitions, Files, Clips, video track, audio track, overlay), which makes everything seem difficult to operate. You can capture videos from camcorder or other devices like webcam or capture card TV and after you have added files and sequence clips to the queue, you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Power-user Premium 1.7.55.173</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 18:26:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-power-user-premium-3149.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-power-user-premium-3149.html
</guid><description>
Power-user is a plugin for software, Microsoft Excel, PowerPoint and Word help you to provide more visual content so you can create the spreadsheet attractive. It contains templates, icons, tables, drawings and charts, modern, professional, allows you to build professional looking documents. You can add custom content to your project just by a click of the mouse and surprise clients and colleagues with your skills on Excel, PowerPoint and Word.
Power-user Premium - Plugin Excel,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Power-user for PowerPoint and Excel 1.7.55.173</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 18:26:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-power-user-for-powerpoint-and-excel-522.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-power-user-for-powerpoint-and-excel-522.html
</guid><description>
Power-user for PowerPoint and Excel is a utility providing you with a library of templates, icons, charts, maps and diagrams for spreadsheet and presentation. With Power-user for PowerPoint and Excel, you will attract the attention of your audience with stunning graphics will certainly impress.
Power-user comes with a collection of 2,000 icons to illustrate your slides. The icons are vector shapes so you can resize them without distortion and color back as you with. With Power-user, you...
</description></item><item><title>Download QueueExplorer Professional 5.0.56</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 18:26:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-queueexplorer-professional-4823.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-queueexplorer-professional-4823.html
</guid><description>
QueueExplorer is a tool indispensable to work with queues and messages: understand and manage your system, find the error and fix it. Or you can use QueueExplorer to sort them by any field available. Because of the sort display the messages in another order with them will be handled, QueueExplorer more columns of Ms Ms # # so you can still see what is processed first.
The features of QueueExplorer
Move, copy or delete messages
	Messages can be handled the same as in process explorer,...
</description></item><item><title>Download VCap Downloader Pro 0.1.36.6705</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 18:26:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vcap-downloader-pro-8474.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vcap-downloader-pro-8474.html
</guid><description>
VCap Downloader Pro (VCapDL) is a popular piece of software that allows you to record video and audio from websites on the internet. The interface of the software is similar to a normal browser, making it easy for users to get used to and work with this software. User just need to copy video url from favorite browser and convert it to VCap Downloader Pro. It will capture the video and make the quality available for download. You can also extract the audio track from any video and convert...
</description></item><item><title>Download Calibre 8.11.0 + Portable</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 18:25:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-calibre-1669.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-calibre-1669.html
</guid><description>
Calibre  is an eBook library management application that allows you to manage your eBook collection, convert eBooks between different formats, Sync with popular e-reading devices and read your e-books with included viewer. You can sort books by author, title, date and other details, download meta information and book covers, add personalized tags and comments, and view your images in the cover display.
Collection of essential tools for adding metadata editing books or managing your...
</description></item><item><title>Download Systweak PDF Editor 1.0.0.8220</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 18:25:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-systweak-pdf-editor-11484.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-systweak-pdf-editor-11484.html
</guid><description>
Systweak PDF Editor is a fast and simple solution to edit, convert, sign, protect, compress PDF files and make scanned PDF files searchable and can choose. With Systweak PDF Editor, quickly convert your PDF files into a variety of editable formats. Converting PDF files to and from any MS Office files, images, ebooks, web pages, and other formats just got easier.
For working and editing PDF files, Systweak PDF editor offers many features and tools. Using them, you can mark text for...
</description></item><item><title>Download Macrium Reflect Workstation / Server / Server Plus 10.0.8665</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 18:24:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-macrium-reflect-1444.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-macrium-reflect-1444.html
</guid><description>
Macrium Reflect is software backup and recovery files, image files, with big improvements in speed, simplicity and strength. The software we provide taiwebs.com 've included 3 version is Macrium Reflect Workstation / Server / Server Plus. Whole our focus is to help organizations protect critical data and business systems, without fuss and budget breaking.
Macrium Reflect - backup and restore files
The function of Macrium Reflect
	Backup tool new: image gradually increases and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Screencapt Professional 2.005</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 18:24:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-screencapt-professional-12260.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-screencapt-professional-12260.html
</guid><description>
Screencapt Professional is powerful Windows software for screen recording that allows you to accurately and easily record any on-screen activity. Whether you want to create tutorials, record webinars, or simply record your favorite games, Screencapt gives you all the tools you need.
With Screencapt, you can record the entire screen, a selected area, or a specific window. This flexibility makes Screencapt the perfect screen recorder for any type of application. Thanks to the built-in...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft PIX 2509.25</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 18:19:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-pix-4100.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-pix-4100.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft PIX is a free program designed for all game developers, professional and amateur, give them reviews, game performance, debugging and tuning applications. Microsoft PIX will optimize the resource consumption is essential, especially for the game that requires high resources. Microsoft PIX can provide insight about the whole process of the production and how it affects the performance of the server system. Therefore, it can prove to be a real asset in the toolbox of developers,...
</description></item><item><title>Download MAME 0.281</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 18:18:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mame-3320.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mame-3320.html
</guid><description>
MAME is an emulator of open source and free are designed to recreate the hardware of the game system arcade in software on the personal computer modern and other platforms. The goal is to preserve gaming history by preventing classic games from being lost or being forgotten.
MAME - emulator classic game
MAME (Multiple Arcade Machine Emulator) is a software that has the ability to simulate an arcade machine, allowing you to play the classic arcade game on his computer. This tool can...
</description></item><item><title>Download BLEASS Complete Effects Bundle 2025.9</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 18:17:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bleass-complete-effects-bundle-11452.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bleass-complete-effects-bundle-11452.html
</guid><description>
BLEASS Complete Effects Bundle is a unique collection of 19 different sound plugins as well as 8 additional preset packs for the amazing BLEASS Alpha Synthesizer.
Sound plugins include:
	BLEASS Chorus
	BLEASS Compressor
	BLEASS Delay
	BLEASS Filter
	BLEASS Flanger
	BLEASS Phaser
	BLEASS Reverb
	BLEASS Saturator
	BLEASS Shimmer
	BLEASS Dragonfly
	BLEASS Fusion
	BLEASS Granulizer
	BLEASS Motion EQ
	BLEASS Motion FX
	BLEASS Phase Mutant
	BLEASS Sidekick
	BLEASS Slow Machine
	BLEASS...
</description></item><item><title>Download Network Monitor II 32.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 18:16:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-network-monitor-ii-3628.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-network-monitor-ii-3628.html
</guid><description>
Network Monitor II is a lightweight utility that lets you quickly view important information about your network connection. The program allows you to view information about IP addresses, network traffic and much more. No extra tools or libraries needed. Network Monitor II comes with a customizable interface can be adjusted according to your wishes. You can choose what information will be displayed, change the interface of the program, change the color of each category are displayed, and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Syncovery Premium 11.8.3.104</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 18:15:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncovery-pro-enterprise-232.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncovery-pro-enterprise-232.html
</guid><description>
Syncovery Pro Enterprise is a great application used to back up data and to synchronize personal computers, servers, laptops, notepads and storage online. The software comes with support for FTP and secure FTP servers, SSH, WebDAV, Amazon S3, http, update the part file, ZIP compression, data encryption, and schedule automatic backups.
Syncovery Pro Enterprise have the ability to freely select files and folders across the whole folder hierarchy in tree view and supports email...
</description></item><item><title>Download Grub2Win 3.0.0.3</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 18:14:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-grub2win-3177.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-grub2win-3177.html
</guid><description>
Grub2Win is a open source program to dual boot Windows and Linux safely. Grub2Win boot code the GNU Grub version 2.04. Everything is in a folder of 20 MB on Windows drive C: On the EFI system, a few small modules to be installed into the EFI partition of your.
Grub2Win - Boot system, Windows
Using GUI Windows and simple instructions you can install Grub2Win quickly and safely. Notice the boot time and help can be displayed in multiple languages. After installing interface, it's easy to...
</description></item><item><title>Download PentaLogix CAMMaster Designer 11.24.62</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 18:14:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pentalogix-cammaster-designer-13705.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pentalogix-cammaster-designer-13705.html
</guid><description>
CAMMaster Designer is the CAM software of choice for designers for their most demanding jobs. Experience the industry's best CAD companion to get your work done. Panelization is easy with all the features included in this package. Netlist and DRC extraction set the industry standard.
Highlights
	Contour-based netlist extraction
	Advanced DFM inspection
	Automatic aperture conversion
	Layer comparison
	Network conversion
	Automatic conversion from draw to flash
	Solder mask...
</description></item><item><title>Download FanControl v241</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 18:13:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fancontrol-5749.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fancontrol-5749.html
</guid><description>
FanControl is a highly customizable fan control software for Windows. Stay in control of every aspect of your PC's GPU and CPU fan with the help of this highly customizable fan control app.
Features of FanControl
	Save, edit and load multiple configurations
	Multiple temperature sources (CPU, GPU, motherboard, hard drive, ".sensor" files)
	Custom fan curve
	Fine tune fan control response with steps,% start,% stop, response time and delay
	Mix different curves and sensors...
</description></item></channel></rss>