<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 17:42:56 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 17:42:56 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download ControlMyMonitor 1.40</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Dec 2025 17:23:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-controlmymonitor-1801.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-controlmymonitor-1801.html
</guid><description>
ControlMyMonitor allows you to view and modify most settings of the screen (brightness, contrast, sharpness, color balance, red / green / blue, etc.) without using the OSD. You can modify the settings from the application interface or from the command line, at the same time export all the settings into a config file and then reload them to quickly switch between the configuration screen. ControlMyMonitor works with any monitor which supports DDC / CI.
ControlMyMonitor - Modified The...
</description></item><item><title>Download RepairKit 1.3.5</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Dec 2025 17:23:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-repairkit-11968.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-repairkit-11968.html
</guid><description>
RepairKit is an all-in-one Java-based Windows repair and maintenance toolkit. RepairKit aims to provide a package that provides users with a dedicated system repair tool as well as quick access to some operating system features and some other PC maintenance software that comes with it. it.
If you want to keep your PC running smoothly and want to do it conveniently, RepairKit offers a simple and effective solution for that, with an automatic repair/cleanup module , as well as access to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Advanced SystemCare Pro 19.1.0.176</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Dec 2025 17:21:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-systemcare-pro-368.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-systemcare-pro-368.html
</guid><description>
Advanced SystemCare Pro is software that provides features to optimize a PC system professional cleanup, repair, speed up and protect PC.  Advanced SystemCare Pro tab Protect new is added, is designed to provide quick access to protect browsing from being tracked by automatically delete traces of privacy when browser closed and detect and resist the attack of the plugin / malicious toolbar by Browser Anti -Backing and Plugin / toolbar cleaner.
Program speed up pc top
Advanced SystemCare...
</description></item><item><title>Download StartAllBack 3.9.20.5345</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Dec 2025 17:20:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-startallback-6857.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-startallback-6857.html
</guid><description>
With the official release of Windows 11, chances are that most of you want to try it out. As the name suggests, StartAllBack is a small, lightweight tool that can help you enjoy the power of the new operating system while keeping the look and feel, especially because main work area, desktop of Windows 7, Windows 10 as taskbars and start menu styles.
StartAllBack is specially designed for Windows 11 and will not work on any older operating systems. If you want to get the start menu back...
</description></item><item><title>Download Systweak PDF Editor 1.0.0.8447</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Dec 2025 17:20:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-systweak-pdf-editor-11484.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-systweak-pdf-editor-11484.html
</guid><description>
Systweak PDF Editor is a fast and simple solution to edit, convert, sign, protect, compress PDF files and make scanned PDF files searchable and can choose. With Systweak PDF Editor, quickly convert your PDF files into a variety of editable formats. Converting PDF files to and from any MS Office files, images, ebooks, web pages, and other formats just got easier.
For working and editing PDF files, Systweak PDF editor offers many features and tools. Using them, you can mark text for...
</description></item><item><title>Download USB Drive Letter Manager (USBDLM) 5.7.3.50</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Dec 2025 17:20:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-usb-drive-letter-manager-3382.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-usb-drive-letter-manager-3382.html
</guid><description>
USB Drive Letter Manager is a lightweight software written for use in Windows it will give you full control over the assigned drive letter of the system for the USB drive. The application will run as a system service, independent of the privileges of the user that logged in. Thanks to this feature, you will be able to easily change the drive letter without admin privileges.
USB Drive Letter Manager - control the drive of Windows system
USB Drive Letter Manager automatically solves...
</description></item><item><title>Download Auslogics Driver Updater 2.1.0.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Dec 2025 17:19:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-auslogics-driver-updater-1204.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-auslogics-driver-updater-1204.html
</guid><description>
Auslogics Driver Updater is a product for detection, backup, restore and update drivers in your system. In just a few mouse clicks, you can list the device drivers installed in the system, unzip or backup all or the driver files selected in a folder and check out the newer version of drivers already installed from the database program. The driver updates of Auslogics Driver Updater is certified by Microsoft Gold Application Developer. Microsoft confirms the high professionalism of...
</description></item><item><title>Download MusConv 4.10.437 Lifetime</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Dec 2025 17:19:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html
</guid><description>
MusConv transfers playlists, albums, followed artists and liked songs across a variety of services – Spotify, Apple Music, Amazon Music, YouTube, YouTube Music, iTunes, Deezer, Tidal, SoundCloud, Pandora and more 125 music services!
Features of MusConv Ultimate
	Transfer playlists, albums, followed artists and liked tracks between over 125 music servicesManage playlists (Delete, Merge, Split, Copy...)
	More than 125 music services supported
	Access DAILY updated music charts on...
</description></item><item><title>Download 3D Youtube Downloader 1.25</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Dec 2025 17:18:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-3d-youtube-downloader-1631.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-3d-youtube-downloader-1631.html
</guid><description>
3D Youtube Downloader is application support users to download the videos from Youtube website with great quality. The advantage of this software is the ability to download the videos in 3D, make the download process is fully automated and the download speed is extremely fast. In addition to Youtube, this tool also allows to download videos from many other sites, so users can own any favorite videos yet. 3D Youtube Downloader is a downloads simple but powerful from Youtube, Vimeo,...
</description></item><item><title>Download AnyLogic Pro 8.9.7</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Dec 2025 17:18:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anylogic-pro-14165.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anylogic-pro-14165.html
</guid><description>
AnyLogic is the only simulation engine that supports all of today's most popular simulation approaches: System Dynamics, Process-Centric Modeling, and Agent-Based Modeling.
The unique flexibility of the modeling language allows users to capture the complexity and heterogeneity of business, economic, and social systems at any desired level of detail. AnyLogic's graphical interface, tools, and object libraries enable you to quickly model diverse areas such as manufacturing and logistics,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Hard Configurator 7.0.1.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Dec 2025 17:17:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hard-configurator-4869.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hard-configurator-4869.html
</guid><description>
Hard Configurator is the user interface graphics only for advanced users to manage policies, software restriction (SRP) and hardening the version Windows Home from Vista and above. You can configure integrated security Windows to harden the system. When you close it it will close all processes of it. Real-time protection to from the Windows installation to be reconfigured. Hard Configurator can be viewed as rejection setting default smart Rate integrity-average, based on reputation...
</description></item><item><title>Download Kali Linux 2025.4</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Dec 2025 17:17:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kali-linux-7735.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kali-linux-7735.html
</guid><description>
Kali contains a wide range of hacker tools and utilities (password attacks, sniffing and spoofing, reverse engineering, ...). Foreign WiFi/WLAN attacks (wireless attacks) and more. Kali is designed for digital forensics and penetration testing. Kali, the most advanced and flexible penetration testing distribution ever created. Kali has grown far beyond its humble origins as a live DVD and is now a full-fledged operating system.
Features of Kali Linux
	The most advanced penetration...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Acrobat Reader DC 2025.001.20997</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Dec 2025 17:17:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-acrobat-reader-3707.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-acrobat-reader-3707.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Acrobat Reader DC is a system of application software and Web services developed by Adobe Systems to view, create, manipulate, print and manage PDF files. With Adobe Acrobat Reader DC, you can create, export, edit, and track PDF files from anywhere - and maintain connection with the recent set of files on all your devices.
Adobe Acrobat Reader current DC is connected with Adobe Document Cloud - help working on the computers and mobile devices becomes easier than ever before. This is...
</description></item><item><title>Download QueueExplorer Professional 5.0.64</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Dec 2025 17:16:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-queueexplorer-professional-4823.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-queueexplorer-professional-4823.html
</guid><description>
QueueExplorer is a tool indispensable to work with queues and messages: understand and manage your system, find the error and fix it. Or you can use QueueExplorer to sort them by any field available. Because of the sort display the messages in another order with them will be handled, QueueExplorer more columns of Ms Ms # # so you can still see what is processed first.
The features of QueueExplorer
Move, copy or delete messages
	Messages can be handled the same as in process explorer,...
</description></item><item><title>Download ManicTime Pro 2025.3.4</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Dec 2025 17:16:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-manictime-18.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-manictime-18.html
</guid><description>
ManicTime is a software automatically collect information about how to use your computer. It records the time of operation of the machine, see the change data in the machine, how much data you share, received on or moved away, what software you use, use at any time
ManicTime allows you to keep up the work of the staff, send progress reports accurately and manage your time better than ever. This type of software can help your business more efficient when it comes to the internal problems...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mozilla Firefox 146.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Dec 2025 17:15:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-firefox-quantum-501.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-firefox-quantum-501.html
</guid><description>
Firefox Quantum is a web browser independently provide the tabbed browsing combined with numerous handy features like pop-up blocker, Bookmarks, direct (integrated RSS), password manager, and more. Functionality can be extended with dozens of plugins available for free (extensions).
Firefox Quantum are interface completely new, beautiful, neat, minimalistic and delicate, eats less RAM to 30% compared with the old version and solve the condition consuming capacity
Firefox can import all...
</description></item><item><title>Download Power-user Premium 1.7.69.238</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Dec 2025 17:14:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-power-user-premium-3149.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-power-user-premium-3149.html
</guid><description>
Power-user is a plugin for software, Microsoft Excel, PowerPoint and Word help you to provide more visual content so you can create the spreadsheet attractive. It contains templates, icons, tables, drawings and charts, modern, professional, allows you to build professional looking documents. You can add custom content to your project just by a click of the mouse and surprise clients and colleagues with your skills on Excel, PowerPoint and Word.
Power-user Premium - Plugin Excel,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Power-user for PowerPoint and Excel 1.7.69.238</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Dec 2025 17:14:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-power-user-for-powerpoint-and-excel-522.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-power-user-for-powerpoint-and-excel-522.html
</guid><description>
Power-user for PowerPoint and Excel is a utility providing you with a library of templates, icons, charts, maps and diagrams for spreadsheet and presentation. With Power-user for PowerPoint and Excel, you will attract the attention of your audience with stunning graphics will certainly impress.
Power-user comes with a collection of 2,000 icons to illustrate your slides. The icons are vector shapes so you can resize them without distortion and color back as you with. With Power-user, you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Database Workbench Pro 6.9.0.870</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Dec 2025 17:14:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-database-workbench-pro-12498.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-database-workbench-pro-12498.html
</guid><description>
Database Workbench Pro is a comprehensive integrated development environment (IDE) designed for developers and database administrators. It supports multiple database systems, including InterBase, SQL Server, Firebird, MySQL, Oracle, NexusDB, MSDE, and Sybase SQL Anywhere, making it a versatile tool for cross-database development.
It provides both database-specific and database-independent visual design tools. Users can create new databases or create visual diagrams from existing...
</description></item><item><title>Download KeyScrambler Premium 3.19.0.0 + Professional</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Dec 2025 17:13:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-keyscrambler-premium-professional-143.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-keyscrambler-premium-professional-143.html
</guid><description>
KeyScrambler Premium / Professional allows users to search for and remove the malicious program, the spy program on the computer system. This program support users to handle a number of spy programs send user information to the server by way thoroughly remove them from the system.
KeyScrambler Premium Key key encryption real-time encryption key, every key you type deep in the Windows. It protects the personal information of you against all malware keylog already know and not know on...
</description></item><item><title>Download Synchredible Professional 9.006</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Dec 2025 17:07:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-synchredible-professional-1923.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-synchredible-professional-1923.html
</guid><description>
Synchredible Professional is the most advanced version help synchronize the folder and your drive quickly and easily. Whether it is a single file or an entire drive - Synchredible Professional will synchronize, copy and save them for you. The software guide will assist you to identify the work that is scheduled in advance or be done through the USB connection. This way, you can keep your files in sync - automatically.
In the past years, the advanced technology of the us in Synchredible...
</description></item><item><title>Download Synchredible 9.006</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Dec 2025 17:07:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-synchredible-53.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-synchredible-53.html
</guid><description>
Synchredible is an easy to use tool to synchronize folders and files. It provides a wizard interface lets you set up the sync job, select files to exclude, schedule the job to execute automatically, and more.Additional features include support for network and external drives, check CRC32, and more.
Synchredible - synchronization of folders and files
Among other things, you can use the filter for the file type specific data synchronization according to the time or routine deletion of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Full Convert Ultimate 25.12.1693</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Dec 2025 17:06:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-full-convert-enterprise-997.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-full-convert-enterprise-997.html
</guid><description>
Full Convert Enterprise is a conversion software database. Full Convert Enterprise create all the tables, copy all of your data. Full Convert Enterprise has the custom features and mapped powerful at your disposal, your data will be moved out of the box without custom. Full Convert automatically adjusted the basis of your data and use copy modes optimized for each separate table to achieve information best possible quality.
Full Convert Enterprise - convert data base
Full Convert...
</description></item><item><title>Download DBeaver Ultimate 25.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Dec 2025 17:06:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbeaver-6829.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbeaver-6829.html
</guid><description>
DBeaver is a comprehensive and efficient software solution aimed at developers and database administrators who need to manage and organize tables, triggers, views, and stored procedures from multiple databases. Regardless of the database you choose to work with, here referring to MySQL, SQLite, PostgreSQL, Oracle, Microsoft SQL Server, IBM DB2 and Firebird, the application comes in handy for users who need to handle a lot of connections, therefore Organize and edit various database...
</description></item><item><title>Download RadioMaximus Pro 2.33.13</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Dec 2025 17:05:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-radiomaximus-pro-747.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-radiomaximus-pro-747.html
</guid><description>
RadioMaximus Pro is a software support listen to the radio and record thousands of radio stations available on the Internet. When using the RadioMaximus Pro you will experience the ability to hear radio the most wonderful. The quality of radio is very good, there are many channels to choose from and the software continuously updates the news, latest music in the world to take to the listening station.
RadioMaximus Pro - Listen to the radio
Features RadioMaximus Pro
	Listen to and...
</description></item></channel></rss>