<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 11:45:00 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 11:45:00 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Ant Download Manager Pro 2.15.9.91212</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 00:47:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ant-download-manager-pro-137.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ant-download-manager-pro-137.html
</guid><description>
Ant Download Manager Pro is software support download has the same features as IDM, even it has many prominent features, more user friendly more and have speed download data incredible. Ant Download Manager is a Internet content downloader quickly with support download at video! Function: fully Integrated with the web browsers most popular: Internet Explorer 8+, Mozilla Firefox 32 +, Google Chrome 31+ and the copies of them (Pale Moon, Opera, Vivaldi, Slimjet, ComodoDragon, etc.). you...
</description></item><item><title>Download VirtualBox 7.2.0 + Extension Pack</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 00:46:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-virtualbox-285.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-virtualbox-285.html
</guid><description>
VirtualBox is a virtualization software open source allows you to run one or more operating system in a virtual machine while running Windows. It is used for purposes such as experience app or try to play the game new in a safe environment, do not affect the main operating system of you. With this software, users will better control multiple virtual machines at the same time.
VirtualBox - Create virtual drive allows running multiple operating systems at the same time
The program comes...
</description></item><item><title>Download Clean Space Pro 2025 v713</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 00:45:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-clean-space-pro-545.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-clean-space-pro-545.html
</guid><description>
Clean Space Pro is the professional software remove junk files from the system to release the hard drive and improve computer performance. From time to time when using computer files as buffers, temporary files of various programs, files, internet cookies, internet browsing history, diary, file index.dat, registry entries and even the Windows will gradually increase, occupy wise space your hard drive and make the computer suffer from stagnation. The best solution is to use the Clean Space...
</description></item><item><title>Download Batch Image Converter 2.1.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 00:44:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-batch-image-converter-7430.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-batch-image-converter-7430.html
</guid><description>
Batch Image Converter is software that helps you batch convert image files. It can work with many image types (*.bmp, *.gif, *.jpg, *.png, *.tiff, *.tif, *.psd, *.pcx, *.pbm, *.pgm , *. ppm, *.tga, *.tpic, etc.).
Features of Batch Image Converter
	Easy, intuitive, one-click configuration.
	Save/load session for easy use again.
	Support command line execution.
	Execute automatically at specific time.
</description></item><item><title>Download Directory Opus Pro 13.17.9 Beta</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 00:44:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-opus-pro-779.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-opus-pro-779.html
</guid><description>
Directory Opus Pro is a software replacement for Explorer with traditional strength and function more than any manager other files. Directory Opus Pro full support for high DPI screen (for example 4K and 5K) with the rename dialog is redesigned, with new features. Besides being a recording macro only allows you to perform mass renaming complex that don't need regular expressions. In addition, Directory Opus Pro also enhances the ability to script.Better handling of renaming recursive and...
</description></item><item><title>Download DBF Converter 7.60</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 00:43:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbf-converter-6362.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbf-converter-6362.html
</guid><description>
DBF Converter is a common solution for all your DBF format conversion needs. Whenever you need to extract data from the DBF file to CSV, XLS, XLSX, SQL or pure text, the software will provide a simple way to do this with minimal effort.
Features of DBF Converter
	Work with DBF Converter is easy. You specify a DBF file or a directory with DBF files that you want to convert, select the fields and filter out the records you need. Then, just a click to DBF Converter to turn the source...
</description></item><item><title>Download Photo Supreme 2025.3.1.8012</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 00:43:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photo-supreme-430.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photo-supreme-430.html
</guid><description>
Photo Supreme is a software product management professional pictures of idimager. With Photo Supreme you can arrange, manage back stock photo archive of yourself and share them with you here and relatives easily via Email or Facebook. Photo Supreme provides users method to sort images effective, logical, as well as edit and share your photos with friends and relatives in the family. Especially the Photo Supreme allows to work with multiple image formats and support mounting support,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Pazu Apple Music Converter 1.8.8</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 00:42:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pazu-apple-music-converter-11027.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pazu-apple-music-converter-11027.html
</guid><description>
Pazusoft Apple Music Converter for Windows allows you to easily download Apple Music songs, albums and playlists to M4A, MP3, AAC, FLAC, WAV, AIFF. So you can play Apple Music songs offline wherever you want, without the Music app or iTunes.
Pazu Apple Music Converter helps you download songs, albums, and Apple Music playlists to M4A/MP3/AAC/FLAC/WAV/AIFF while preserving the original sound quality (up to 256kbps). Additionally, custom output settings such as audio quality, file name...
</description></item><item><title>Download ezAccounting 3.15.13</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 00:42:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ezaccounting-5300.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ezaccounting-5300.html
</guid><description>
ezAccounting is accounting software designed for the small business: simple, reliable and affordable. ezAccounting is the solution internal accounting suitable for small businesses need to record and report on cash flow in and out including sales, incomes and expenses and purchases. It also supports payroll processing and print tax forms.
The features of ezAccounting
	Company accounts unlimited
	Custom format form
	Custom format Czech
	Support multiple tax code
	Support multiple...
</description></item><item><title>Download 3C All-in-One Toolbox 3.1.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 14 Aug 2025 22:41:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-3c-all-in-one-toolbox-8399.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-3c-all-in-one-toolbox-8399.html
</guid><description>
3C All-in-One Toolbox combines many features into one giant toolbox with a modern and easy-to-use interface. All the tools you need to monitor, control and fine-tune all your Android devices. This app uses the Accessibility service to help you stop the app on non-rooted devices but will never collect any information.
Features of 3C All-in-One Toolbox
	Device Manager offers very powerful configurations, task scheduling, and device watchdogs that you can find to optimize performance and...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDF editor &amp;amp; PDF converter pro 9.5.0 build 111</title><pubDate> Thu, 14 Aug 2025 22:41:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pdf-editor-pdf-converter-pro-9852.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pdf-editor-pdf-converter-pro-9852.html
</guid><description>
PDF Converter &amp;amp; PDF Editor is a very comprehensive tool to perform various operations on pdf files
	Convert Word files to PDF: Now you can convert doc files to pdf files.
	Convert images to PDF files: Convert your jpg to PDF. Click image from camera or select an image from gallery and convert it.
	Website to PDF: Convert html website to PDF and save all articles/news reports to read later.
	Merge pdf: Combine pdf documents into a single document.
	Split documents: Is the file too...
</description></item><item><title>Download Digital Compass 16.3 Build 156</title><pubDate> Thu, 14 Aug 2025 22:40:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-digital-compass-13590.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-digital-compass-13590.html
</guid><description>
This app is a smart compass with high accuracy and a great tool for outdoor activities. This compass app allows you to easily determine the direction you are facing. This app is built using the device's gyroscope, accelerometer, magnetometer, gravity sensor to determine the direction. Make sure your device has an accelerometer and magnetometer sensor or it will not work.
Features
	Show current location (longitude, latitude, address)
	Show altitude
	Show magnetic field strength
	Show...
</description></item><item><title>Download File Manager 3.6.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 14 Aug 2025 22:40:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-file-manager-8886.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-file-manager-8886.html
</guid><description>
File Manager+ is an easy and powerful file browser for Android devices. It's free, fast, and full-featured. Because of its simple user interface, it is extremely easy to use. With File Manager+, you can easily manage files and folders on your devices, NAS (Network Attached Storage), and cloud storage. What's more, you can quickly see how many files and apps you have on your device right after opening File Manager+.
It supports all file management actions (opening, searching, navigating...
</description></item><item><title>Download BBVPN VPN: Unlimited Fast VPN 5.1.3</title><pubDate> Thu, 14 Aug 2025 22:40:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-bbvpn-vpn-fast-unlimited-10161.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-bbvpn-vpn-fast-unlimited-10161.html
</guid><description>
BBVPN VPN - Unlimited fast VPN. Are you looking for a reliable, fast and secure VPN to protect your online privacy and access unrestricted content? Look no further than BBVPN VPN, the best free and unlimited VPN app for Android! With BBVPN, you can enjoy a seamless and protected Internet experience on your mobile device, completely free!
Experience the power of BBVPN VPN and enjoy unrestricted Internet access while ensuring your online privacy. Whether you're a frequent traveler, a...
</description></item><item><title>Download TuneIn Radio Pro - Live Radio 39.8.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 14 Aug 2025 22:39:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-tunein-radio-pro-live-radio-8217.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-tunein-radio-pro-live-radio-8217.html
</guid><description>
TuneIn Radio Pro allows users to listen to many radio stations and podcasts from around the world. The Pro version offers additional features like the ability to record live stations, remove ads, and access more premium content. It is available for download on Google Play Store as an apk file.
All your sounds in one app:
	News: Listen and update live news 24/7 from local, national and global news sources, including CNBC, CNN, MSNBC and FOX News Radio.
	Sports: Listen live to NFL, NHL...
</description></item><item><title>Download AR Ruler App: Tape Measure Cam 3.1.4</title><pubDate> Thu, 14 Aug 2025 22:39:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ar-ruler-app-tape-measure-cam-8721.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ar-ruler-app-tape-measure-cam-8721.html
</guid><description>
AR Ruler app is a mobile app that uses augmented reality (AR) technology to measure distances, angles, and sizes of objects in real-world environments. This app works by using the device's camera and sensors to create a virtual 3D representation of a real-life environment.
The AR Ruler app uses augmented reality (AR) technology to measure the real world using your smartphone's camera. Target the detected plane and start using the AR
tape measure tool
Features of AR Ruler...
</description></item><item><title>Download KMPlayer Plus (Divx Codec) 35.08.120</title><pubDate> Thu, 14 Aug 2025 22:39:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-kmplayer-plus-divx-codec-8720.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-kmplayer-plus-divx-codec-8720.html
</guid><description>
KMPlayer Plus with DivX codec is also available for Android devices, providing a powerful media player that supports many video and audio formats. These features include ad-free playback, cloud storage support, and high-resolution video playback support.
With support for DivX, KMPlayer Plus for Android allows users to watch high-quality DivX encoded videos on their mobile devices without the need for additional codecs or software. This is a convenient feature for users who want to watch...
</description></item><item><title>Download WiFi Direct + 10.0.14</title><pubDate> Thu, 14 Aug 2025 22:39:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wifi-direct-10153.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wifi-direct-10153.html
</guid><description>
Wi-Fi Direct is a Wi-Fi standard for peer-to-peer wireless connections that allows two devices to establish a direct Wi-Fi connection without the need for an intermediate wireless access point, router, or Internet connection.
Features of WiFi Direct +
	Fast
	Completely free, no intrusive ads.
	Supports all file transfers.
	Supports multiple file transfers.
	Supports folder transfer.
	Supports file transfer to and from external sdcard.
	Tested on many devices.
	Advanced file chooser.
</description></item><item><title>Download AIDA64 for Android 2.11</title><pubDate> Thu, 14 Aug 2025 22:38:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-aida64-for-android-9749.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-aida64-for-android-9749.html
</guid><description>
Hardware and software information utility for devices running Android. Building on the extensive hardware knowledge of the AIDA64 for Windows app, AIDA64 for Android is capable of displaying a variety of diagnostic information for phones, tablets, smartwatches and TVs.&amp;lt; /p&amp;gt;
Features of AIDA64 for Android
	Detect CPU, measure core clock in real time
	Screen size, pixel density and camera information
	Monitor battery level and temperature
	Information about WiFi and mobile...
</description></item><item><title>Download PM Pro: Password Manager 4.6.8</title><pubDate> Thu, 14 Aug 2025 22:38:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-passwords-manager-pro-for-android-10925.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-passwords-manager-pro-for-android-10925.html
</guid><description>
Passwords Manager Pro for Android is a 100% offline password locker app that allows users to store, organize and manage passwords, notes and other sensitive information locally on their device without no need to rely on cloud-based services.
Features of Password Manager Pro for Android
Highly secure offline password management application
	This app is 100% offline even there is no internet connection in this app. It only stores data on the user's device and encrypts it with AES-256...
</description></item><item><title>Download English Idioms &amp;amp; Slang Phrases 2.0.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 14 Aug 2025 22:38:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-english-idioms-slang-phrases-10458.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-english-idioms-slang-phrases-10458.html
</guid><description>
Are you just starting to learn English or looking to improve your current English skills? English Idioms &amp;amp; Slang Phrases are a great vocabulary builder for beginners and advanced language learners who want to reach native speaker level. Also, it will be useful for those who want to find a good job or higher education in the US, UK, Canada, Australia. This is a great way to prepare to successfully pass TOEFL and IELTS.
In our English learning app, we have collected over 700 of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download IELTS® Vocabulary Flashcards 2.0 build 22</title><pubDate> Thu, 14 Aug 2025 22:37:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ielts-vocabulary-flashcards-10183.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ielts-vocabulary-flashcards-10183.html
</guid><description>
The International English Language Testing System (IELTS) has become the world's most popular English test for study, work and migration. IELTS Vocabulary Flashcards is an app that covers the most important words used for the real IELTS test and helps you achieve your goals.
The words are intelligently extracted by their repetition and importance in 52 tests from Cambridge exams. Cambridge Tests is a comprehensive set of practice IELTS tests (13 books are covered and each book contains...
</description></item><item><title>Download Edge Card Launcher: Side Panel 4.7.9</title><pubDate> Thu, 14 Aug 2025 22:37:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-edge-card-launcher-side-panel-10233.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-edge-card-launcher-side-panel-10233.html
</guid><description>
Edge Card Launcher is an overlay launcher with beautiful material design and pleasant animations available from anywhere with a single swipe. Using your device with one hand has never been easier! You can open the launcher from any screen just by swiping on the edge of the screen (drag &amp;amp; release). You can also double tap the edge of the screen to open the launcher.
tons of functionality
	Adjust volume for active music or phone calls
	Add app and contact shortcuts
	Control media...
</description></item><item><title>Download Pacer Pedometer &amp;amp; Step Tracker 12.8.1 build 2025081100</title><pubDate> Thu, 14 Aug 2025 22:36:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pacer-pedometer-step-tracker-11194.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pacer-pedometer-step-tracker-11194.html
</guid><description>
Pacer App: “Pedometer, Pedometer, and Weight Loss Tracker App” that syncs steps and calories with MyFitnessPal and Fitbit! Track your steps, walking and weight loss with this free health counter. Lose weight and track distance walked and calories burned using 24/7 step counting from our pedometer, pedometer and health tracker app.
Main features:
	Best pedometer for any phone
	Accurate activity and step tracking
	Lose weight, track BMI and count calories burned
	Daily exercise...
</description></item><item><title>Download Yoga &amp;amp; Meditation | Gotta Yoga 2.1.21</title><pubDate> Thu, 14 Aug 2025 22:35:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-yoga-meditation-gotta-yoga-13510.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-yoga-meditation-gotta-yoga-13510.html
</guid><description>
Gotta Yoga is a versatile yoga and meditation app designed for users of all levels, from beginners to advanced practitioners. The app offers over 350 classes, including styles like Vinyasa, Yin, Hatha, Ashtanga, Iyengar, meditation and pranayama, with session lengths ranging from 5 to 90 minutes, many of which can be taken offline.
Key features include:
	Live classes via Zoom with certified yoga teachers, providing real-time interaction and feedback.
	Integrated with Apple Health and...
</description></item></channel></rss>