<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 00:01:15 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 00:01:15 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download DriverMax Pro 17.11.0.12</title><pubDate> Sat, 21 Feb 2026 00:45:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-drivermax-pro-156.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-drivermax-pro-156.html
</guid><description>
DriverMax Pro : utility that allows to download the update the latest driver for your computer. In addition, DriverMax collects information about the drivers installed in system and prints a list of devices that use them. It scans and collects information about drivers installed in the system and create a list of the driver version, date, digital signature and many more.
DriverMax Pro offers information about the driver version, date, developer, number of files and you have digital...
</description></item><item><title>Download VueScan Pro 9.8.52</title><pubDate> Sat, 21 Feb 2026 00:44:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vuescan-pro-75.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vuescan-pro-75.html
</guid><description>
VueScan Pro l  is one of the software  Scan quality pictures  First and appeared quite soon,  VueScan Pro  always asserted its No. 1 position on the technology pages, awards as well as user reviews. Through many versions, VueScan Pro 9 is greatly improved in terms of interface and features. Supporting most popular image formats today, this software will help you scan images quickly, easy to use and high quality output. With the color balance mode, you won't have to worry about blurring the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Screenpresso Pro 2.2.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 21 Feb 2026 00:43:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-screenpresso-pro-1362.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-screenpresso-pro-1362.html
</guid><description>
Screenpresso Pro is a program easy to take great photos on your screen! Screenpresso blocked Print Screen key and screen capture the best in a few seconds. Allows you to capture windows and screen area, roll the part of the screen, edit the images obtained, add effects, resize a group of images, send screenshots by email and post them to Web resources.
Screenpresso Pro - Shooting the computer screen
Features of Screenpresso Pro
	Take the window and screen area. Take a partial screen...
</description></item><item><title>Download Photomatix Pro 7.1.4 Final</title><pubDate> Sat, 21 Feb 2026 00:42:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photomatix-pro-2535.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photomatix-pro-2535.html
</guid><description>
Photomatix Pro is software to help merge the photos were taken at the level of different exposures into a HDR image only for see all the details, highlights and shadows, with the option to automatically align the photo handheld, removing ghosts, and reducing noise and chromatic aberration. Then, the picture is mixed can be adjusted by a variety of options and settings to get the look that users want from the results look natural by using fusion to photos, graphics, super real or surreal...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Camera Raw 18.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 21 Feb 2026 00:41:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-camera-raw-02en-785.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-camera-raw-02en-785.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Camera Raw is Plugin edit photo on photoshop with the ability to handle the raw photos after the shoot to create beautiful photos and quality than the input image initially, this program helps support the photographers in editing and photography, make the photo beautiful.
Adobe Camera Raw - edit Raw images Photoshop
Adobe Camera Raw is a plugin which is integrated accompanied by a number of software photo editing such as Photoshop, Photoshop Elements, After Effects and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Aeon Timeline 3.5.40</title><pubDate> Sat, 21 Feb 2026 00:40:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aeon-timeline-4952.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aeon-timeline-4952.html
</guid><description>
Aeon Timeline is a tool line-time for creative thinking. Most of the application time line traditional designed to suit a single need: to create attractive screen on time one way. They are present, static, and perfectly aligned with the slide and overhead projector.
With Aeon Timeline, you can split your timeline into logical groups, projects or arcs at the same time. You can model the relationships between events and people, places, and ideas. Aeon calculate ages of people for you. And...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe DNG Converter 18.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 21 Feb 2026 00:39:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-dng-converter-2452.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-dng-converter-2452.html
</guid><description>
Adobe DNG Converter, a free utility that converts files from more than 350 cameras to DNG, enables you to easily convert the files raw exclusively for camera file raw DNG more universal. A program strong enough which allows you to convert the source files RAW to DNG format popular and more convenient with a few clicks of the mouse.
DNG allows photographers to archive files, raw images of them in a single format for easy cataloging and access in the future. With specification formats are...
</description></item><item><title>Download VideoPad Video Editor Pro 18.11 Beta</title><pubDate> Sat, 21 Feb 2026 00:37:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-videopad-video-editor-pro-268.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-videopad-video-editor-pro-268.html
</guid><description>
VideoPad Video Editor Pro is software edit video from any camcorder, DV camcorder, VHS player or webcam for best quality. The interface of this utility is divided into several parts (for example: list of multi-media, Effects, transitions, Files, Clips, video track, audio track, overlay), which makes everything seem difficult to operate. You can capture videos from camcorder or other devices like webcam or capture card TV and after you have added files and sequence clips to the queue, you...
</description></item><item><title>Download PhraseExpress 18.0.61</title><pubDate> Sat, 21 Feb 2026 00:36:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-phraseexpress-41.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-phraseexpress-41.html
</guid><description>
PhraseExpress is a useful application that helps users save time when typing frequently used text or commands. This application allows users to create shortcuts to automatically insert text quickly and conveniently.
With PhraseExpress, users can create "templates" for common commands, regular emails, chat messages, or any text they have to retype frequently. Users only need to set up shortcuts for each template and when needed, just type that shortcut and the text will automatically...
</description></item><item><title>Download UltraSearch Professional 4.9.0.1203</title><pubDate> Sat, 21 Feb 2026 00:35:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ultrasearch-professional-10252.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ultrasearch-professional-10252.html
</guid><description>
UltraSearch Professional is the professional version that helps you find your files and documents on all connected hard drives and network drives. Search by file type, document content, or file properties. Take back your valuable time and let UltraSearch do the searching for you.
UltraSearch Professional does not maintain an index stored on your hard disk. It achieves speed by working directly on the Master File Table (MFT) of NTFS partitions. So it even identifies NTFS hardlinks. That...
</description></item><item><title>Download Chaos Corona 14.1.1 for 3ds Max 2018 - 2026</title><pubDate> Sat, 21 Feb 2026 00:35:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chaos-corona-2986.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chaos-corona-2986.html
</guid><description>
Corona Renderer is the name of the plug-in technique and dedicated powerful, but have high functionality for Autodesk software 3ds Max. Plug before you is a standalone application known to the CLI. In addition, users can use this tool to promote their business on software Maxon Cinema 4D is also used. The manufacturers of this product believe that working with this tool is very simple and in fact you only need to press the activities rendered. With this tool easier than ever can do the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Whonix 18.1.4.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 21 Feb 2026 00:33:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-whonix-13336.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-whonix-13336.html
</guid><description>
Whonix is an anonymous operating system that runs as an application and routes all Internet traffic through the Tor anonymity network. Whonix hides your real IP address by forcing all traffic through Tor, preventing websites and ISPs from identifying your location or identity. It also protects against browser fingerprinting and other advanced tracking techniques like keystrokes and time-of-flight attacks.
It is also designed to prevent DNS leaks and other data leaks that could reveal...
</description></item><item><title>Download SysNucleus WebHarvy 7.11.0.248</title><pubDate> Sat, 21 Feb 2026 00:32:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sysnucleus-webharvy-881.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sysnucleus-webharvy-881.html
</guid><description>
SysNucleus WebHarvy is software to extract data website such as Text, image, URL &amp;amp; email from the website and save the content... WebHarvy is a tool which scans website intuitive. Absolutely no need to write any scripts or code to scrape data. You will use the browser built-in of WebHarvy to navigate the website.
WebHarvy automatically identifies patterns of data occurring in web pages. So if you need a list of items (name, address, email, price etc) from a website, you do not need to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Chaos Corona 14.1.1 for Cinema 4D R17 - 2026</title><pubDate> Sat, 21 Feb 2026 00:31:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-corona-renderer-for-cinema-4d-6499.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-corona-renderer-for-cinema-4d-6499.html
</guid><description>
Corona Renderer  is the name of a powerful, but highly functional engineering and dedicated plug-in for Autodesk 3ds Max software. Plug in before you are a known CLI standalone application. In addition, users can use this tool to advertise their business on Maxon Cinema 4D software which is also used. The manufacturers of this product firmly believe that working with this tool is very simple, and in fact you just need to hit render the rendering operations. With this tool it's easier...
</description></item><item><title>Download HitmanPro.Alert 3.21.1 Build 2041</title><pubDate> Sat, 21 Feb 2026 00:30:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hitmanpro-alert-112.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hitmanpro-alert-112.html
</guid><description>
HitmanPro is a lightweight application that can monitor your browser activity and detect the hidden threats may include security systems. Tool HitmanPro is built specifically to add an additional layer of security for system of you, to protect you whenever you shop on the Internet , or perform banking activities online. It offers computer protection in real time against the exploitation of software, download at in drive, encryption software, online fraud and identity...
</description></item><item><title>Download RocketCake Professional 7.1.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 21 Feb 2026 00:29:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rocketcake-professional-2632.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rocketcake-professional-2632.html
</guid><description>
RocketCake Professional is a WYSIWYG HTML editor that allows you to create a website based on the responsive template without coding. Simply choose your template and customize it or create a new design from scratch.In addition to text content you can add images, galleries, slideshows, YouTube videos, Flash, buttons, audio / video HTML5, table and many page elements enhance the other.
RocketCake Professional - design application Website
Allows you to create a website as quickly as...
</description></item><item><title>Download UltraSearch 4.9.0.1203</title><pubDate> Sat, 21 Feb 2026 00:28:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ultrasearch-5751.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ultrasearch-5751.html
</guid><description>
UltraSearch finds files and folders on local NTFS drives and provides results in seconds. UltraSearch does not maintain an index stored on your hard disk, but achieves its speed by working directly on the Main File Table (MFT) of an NTFS partition. UltraSearch even identifies NTFS hard links. Just enter a filename or template like * .exe and see the first result while you're still typing.
Features of UltraSearch
	Additional information such as file size and file date (last changed,...
</description></item><item><title>Download lessmsi 2.12.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 21 Feb 2026 00:28:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lessmsi-12392.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lessmsi-12392.html
</guid><description>
Lessmsi (Less MSIerables) is a free and portable application that allows users to view and extract the contents of MSI files.
How does it work? Files with the .msi extension are not as widely used as their .exe cousins, but both contain programs for Windows. The main difference between them is that the latter does not always come with an installer, while it comes standard with the former. However, there will be cases where you just need to view or want to extract specific content from...
</description></item><item><title>Download CCExtractor 0.96.6</title><pubDate> Sat, 21 Feb 2026 00:27:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ccextractor-6675.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ccextractor-6675.html
</guid><description>
CCExtractor is a tool used to produce subtitles for TV recordings from almost anywhere in the world. We plan to update all sources and formats. Subtitles are very important to many people. If you're learning a new language, subtitles are a great way to learn it from movies or TV shows. If you're hard of hearing, subtitles can help you better understand what's happening on screen. We aim to make it easy to create subtitles using command line tools or Windows GUI.
Features of...
</description></item><item><title>Download AllMapSoft Universal Maps Downloader 10.237</title><pubDate> Sat, 21 Feb 2026 00:27:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-universal-maps-downloader-736.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-universal-maps-downloader-736.html
</guid><description>
AllMapSoft Universal Maps Downloader is software download map images on the computer for offline viewing support many types such as Google Maps, Yahoo maps, Bing maps, OpenStreet Maps, Yandex Maps, Ovi Maps, MapQuest Maps. All the downloaded photos will be saved on disk. You can view downloaded maps by Maps Viewer Or you can combine them into one big bmp, or jpg file tif by Maps Combiner, and also you can export all the tiles into a database format MBTiles.
AllMapSoft Universal Maps...
</description></item><item><title>Download Internet Download Manager Portable 6.42 Build 61</title><pubDate> Sat, 21 Feb 2026 00:25:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-internet-download-manager-portable-11965.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-internet-download-manager-portable-11965.html
</guid><description>
Internet Download Manager (IDM) is a popular software tool that helps users download files from the internet at faster speeds. It is designed to increase download speeds up to five times, resume and schedule downloads, and support multiple download queues. IDM also has many features that make it easy to use and customize to fit your needs.
IDM has a simple and friendly interface that makes it easy to use. The software integrates seamlessly with popular web browsers such as Google Chrome,...
</description></item><item><title>Download KILHO AutoClick 1.4.9</title><pubDate> Sat, 21 Feb 2026 00:24:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kilho-autoclick-12515.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kilho-autoclick-12515.html
</guid><description>
AutoClick is a software or script designed to automate mouse clicking tasks, especially useful for repetitive actions in a variety of applications, including gaming and data entry. It allows users to define specific click points and automatically click at those locations. This tool is user-friendly and supports recording click sequences for repeated use.
AutoClick allows users to set precise time intervals and geographic coordinates for various click patterns. Additionally, AutoClick...
</description></item><item><title>Download Geometric Glovius Prime 6.7.0.182</title><pubDate> Sat, 21 Feb 2026 00:23:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-geometric-glovius-pro-754.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-geometric-glovius-pro-754.html
</guid><description>
Geometric Glovius Pro is viewer CAD 3D modern for files CATIA, NX, STEP, IGES, Pro/ENGINEER and Creo, SolidWorks, Inventor and Solid Edge. The work of Geometric Glovius Pro is made exact measurements, cut dynamic sections, compare differences between models and export to 3D PDF, STL and Glovius Mobile.
Geometric Glovius Pro - manager, and view CAD 3D
The features of Geometric Glovius Pro
	Modern interface, simple, easy to use
	Mobile app for free for iOS &amp;amp; Android powerful...
</description></item><item><title>Download FX Math Tools Manifest 26.02.20</title><pubDate> Sat, 21 Feb 2026 00:22:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fx-draw-tools-multidocs-8814.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fx-draw-tools-multidocs-8814.html
</guid><description>
MultiDocs is a new way to create self-modifying Word documents. MultiDocs' amazing new document reproduction features allow you to create reproducible tests and quizzes in minutes. Get new numbers, new diagrams and even brand new solutions! MultiDocs combines the power of Word with two leading products: FX Draw and FX Equation in a new and exciting way.
Features of FX Draw Tools MultiDocs
	Create multiple documents: The software allows users to create multiple math and evaluation...
</description></item><item><title>Download AVS Media Player 26.0.2.217</title><pubDate> Sat, 21 Feb 2026 00:22:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs-media-player-1890.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs-media-player-1890.html
</guid><description>
AVS Media Player is software media player brings you a space to enjoy music, video, vivid. AVS Media Player supports all audio formats, different image is a necessity. AVS Media Player allows you can open to near 100 format sounds, different images from common to most rare. Name the audio format, video, audio that programs can read, including: .AVI, .MPEG, .MP3, or .FLV, .JPG, .PNG ... and so very many other formats again.
AVS Media Player - The Media player
Features of AVS Media...
</description></item></channel></rss>