<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 00:00:10 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 00:00:10 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Xreveal 2.9.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jan 2026 00:11:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xreveal-7252.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xreveal-7252.html
</guid><description>
Xreveal is an application similar to AnyDVD. This is an interactive research and purpose project. Xreveal does NOT contain any decryption key, it is based solely on the official public AACS specification. You need the decryption key or key database to make it work.
Features of Xreveal
	Remove Blu-ray AACS 1.0 protection
	Remove Blu-ray AACS 2.0 (UHD) protection
	Remove BD+ protection
	Remove BDAV Protection
	Remove DVD CSS protection
	Remove CPRM Protection
	Remove CPPM...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wipe Pro 2026.01</title><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jan 2026 00:08:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wipe-pro-710.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wipe-pro-710.html
</guid><description>
Wipe Pro is software that helps clean up litter, increase in hard drive space besides also protect your privacy on the Internet, it removes records about personal activity on the computer. You will be able to delete browser history and the cache, the file index.dat, registry, files, cookies, internet history, auto complete, temporary internet files and many other items. This program also delete all activities other individuals that you made when using the PC and regardless of which...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ashampoo Driver Updater 2.5.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jan 2026 00:08:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-driver-updater-4608.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-driver-updater-4608.html
</guid><description>
Ashampoo Driver Updater is software that helps you to search, download and install the version latest drivers for the cluster of PC computer and external devices and keyboard. Ashampoo Driver Updater operates on the basis of Internet database maintained by the manufacturer of the program. The database has more than 400,000 controller for more than 150,000 devices. Ashampoo Driver Updater is also equipped with the ability to create and restore a backup (backup) of drivers and driver updates...
</description></item><item><title>Download WonderFox HD Video Converter Factory Pro 28.3</title><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jan 2026 00:07:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hd-video-converter-factory-pro-1458.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hd-video-converter-factory-pro-1458.html
</guid><description>
WonderFox HD Video Converter Factory Pro is a software powerful video conversion . This program can convert the video files the quality standard of the file SD card, the files HD as HD MP4, HD MKV, HD AVI, HD MTS, HD TRP. This can also in the opposite direction. This software includes more than 100 video formats, while maintaining quality output, faster than 50 times compared to some software. This software also supports VBR or VBR, using this option will keep the original quality of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download O&amp;amp;O DeskInfo 2.0.1033.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jan 2026 00:07:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-deskinfo-7096.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-deskinfo-7096.html
</guid><description>
O&amp;amp;O DeskInfo is a mobile application that displays various system information right on your screen. O&amp;amp;O DeskInfo gets and displays almost anything related to possible system information like CPU, memory usage, network info, operating system etc. You can customize the display, update rate, opacity, text color, and desktop position, to name a few. You can also copy the data to the clipboard if needed. You can also set it to start with Windows or start it manually.
Features of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ashampoo Photo Commander 19.0.3</title><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jan 2026 00:06:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-photo-commander-273.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-photo-commander-273.html
</guid><description>
Ashampoo Photo Commander software brings user photo management tool effectively cover view, sort, edit, convert photos and images to the web. Ashampoo Photo Commander 16 will surprise you immediately! Interface modern user will quickly learn the features of your favorite and adjust accordingly for faster access. The slideshow images appear in the mode 4K stunning and the panoramic feature will steals the show.
Ashampoo Photo Commander - photo editing
Software Ashampoo Photo Commander...
</description></item><item><title>Download Steinberg WaveLab Pro 13.0.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jan 2026 00:06:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-steinberg-wavelab-pro-7920.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-steinberg-wavelab-pro-7920.html
</guid><description>
WaveLab is a complete total solution, with all the tools you'll need to cover your workflow from start to finish.
Backed by a global network of expert engineers who all use it, WaveLab is the key to turning every aspect of your proficient engineers into a real pro.
With improved multi-channel file processing, multiple sub-lanes and analysis clocks, multi-core processing and more, WaveLab further elevates its status as a true art of mastering . With comprehensive controls that make...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter 3.9.18 (2601)</title><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jan 2026 00:05:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-to-mp3-converter-1744.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-to-mp3-converter-1744.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter is the software support download youtube video and convert video to mp3 format fast and most simple. MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter allows you download and convert videos from YouTube and other websites to MP3 format by pasting the YouTube URL into the application. When you paste the URL, the program will display thumbnails for videos and you have the option to customize the title information, artist and album before you begin the process of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Final Draft 13.3.0 Build 105</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 22:39:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-final-draft-1241.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-final-draft-1241.html
</guid><description>
Final Draft is a professional program to write scripts for movies, tv shows and performances. This program is a word processor text window with a lot of ability to script specialized. To use the program, you absolutely do not need to know the rules to design the scenario - draft ultimate will automatically convert scripts you write by world standards.
Final Draft - script Writing professional
The features of Final Draft
	Send a copy of the index cards with the summary directly to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ashampoo Photo Converter 3.0.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 22:39:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-photo-converter-14004.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-photo-converter-14004.html
</guid><description>
Ashampoo Photo Converter is a Windows software tool designed for efficient image conversion and editing. The software supports more than 18 image formats and includes popular formats such as BMP, GIF, JPG, PNG, PDF and many more. The software can process individual photos or entire folders in batch mode, suitable for processing large photo collections.
Ashampoo Photo Converter Features
	Extensive format support allows conversion between multiple file types.
	Batch processing for...
</description></item><item><title>Download Net Monitor for Employees Professional 6.5.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 22:38:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-network-lookout-net-monitor-for-employees-professional-2098.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-network-lookout-net-monitor-for-employees-professional-2098.html
</guid><description>
Network LookOut Net Monitor for Employees Professional is a software platform to help manage user activity, gives the ability to inspect and control computer activities, as well as record activity on the screen as AVI file. Net Monitor for Employees Professional allows access from remote computers. This feature proved particularly useful when you want to see the activity of each user on the computer, or assist them perform the work on the computer with the mouse manipulation or the...
</description></item><item><title>Download JixiPix Pastello 6.0.104</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 22:38:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jixipix-pastello-2660.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jixipix-pastello-2660.html
</guid><description>
JixiPix Pastello is a companion app with completely new Imixi Pro of JixiPix. Pastello take you back in time to the 15th century. Leave brush and big strokes and in the kingdom of means dry with colors just brilliant and exquisite. "Method of color dry" the famous Leonardo da Vinci's very powerful by the simplicity and beauty of it with black chalk and red chalk, yellow highlights. Then, the artist will paint the portrait charm styled blend very smooth. Moving forward a few centuries later...
</description></item><item><title>Download JixiPix Chromatic Edges 1.0.36</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 22:37:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jixipix-chromatic-edges-4997.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jixipix-chromatic-edges-4997.html
</guid><description>
JixiPix Chromatic Edges gives customers more angular and professional to create many photography pop your own way. With JixiPix, customers can create the classic products or flares for your image. The products have the collection of glass, silver and paper help processing your images more easily and create many typical photos with a few taps.
The features of JixiPix Chromatic Edges
	Add an edge image, edge color and edge outside
	Use create edges to create edges
	Save the edge to use...
</description></item><item><title>Download MusConv 4.10.450 Lifetime</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 22:37:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html
</guid><description>
MusConv transfers playlists, albums, followed artists and liked songs across a variety of services – Spotify, Apple Music, Amazon Music, YouTube, YouTube Music, iTunes, Deezer, Tidal, SoundCloud, Pandora and more 125 music services!
Features of MusConv Ultimate
	Transfer playlists, albums, followed artists and liked tracks between over 125 music servicesManage playlists (Delete, Merge, Split, Copy...)
	More than 125 music services supported
	Access DAILY updated music charts on...
</description></item><item><title>Download Classroom Spy Professional 5.5.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 22:37:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-classroom-spy-professional-916.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-classroom-spy-professional-916.html
</guid><description>
Classroom Spy Professional is a software classroom management effective. Manage and track activities of all the computers of students remotely. Plus, you can share your screen with the activity record of the student, the computer controls for performance, limit the use of the Internet, the application blocks and more.
Classroom Spy Professional - software classroom management
The main features of Classroom Spy Professional
	Display live images of the remote computer.
	You can control...
</description></item><item><title>Download Jixipix Premium Pack 1.2.18</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 22:36:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jixipix-premium-pack-2656.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jixipix-premium-pack-2656.html
</guid><description>
Jixipix Premium Pack or the full name is Jixipix Software Premium Pack is a pack of 18 application incredible creative into a powerful package: Aquarella, Artista Haiku, Artista Oil, Artista Sketch, Artoon, Powderspirst, Dramatic Black &amp;amp; White, Grungetastic, Kyoobik Photo Moku Hanga NIR Color Pop Dot Comics Portrait Painter Rainy Daze, romantic Photo, simply HDR, Snow Daze, and classic Landscape. Premium Pack comes wrapped together for convenience - one application, one installation,...
</description></item><item><title>Download JixiPix Spektrel Art 1.1.22</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 22:36:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jixipix-spektrel-art-2657.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jixipix-spektrel-art-2657.html
</guid><description>
JixiPix Spektrel Art is a program convenience and style allows you to easily change the sharpness of the image to highlight motifs and attract the user's attention on the essential elements of the layout. All what we request is to transfer image into main window, select the preset, squeeze the slider to the right, then you can save results and satisfaction. Apply with photo, this medium of artistic form imaginative and magical beyond the ordinary to the extraordinary to create something...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wise Program Uninstaller 3.2.8.272</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 22:35:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wise-program-uninstaller-519.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wise-program-uninstaller-519.html
</guid><description>
Wise Program Uninstaller is a software that manages the application program was installed on the computer and support the user uninstall the application from your computer. Wise Program Uninstaller can fully uninstall applications on the system in just a few seconds. Special tool to completely remove these apps and not leave traces on the system.
Thanks features uninstall, clean the application system of Wise Program Uninstaller, you will be able to cleanup the file data garbage save...
</description></item><item><title>Download JixiPix Artista Impresso Pro 1.8.29</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 22:35:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jixipix-artista-impresso-pro-2659.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jixipix-artista-impresso-pro-2659.html
</guid><description>
JixiPix Artista Impresso Pro is an interesting program that allows you to convert photos into paintings quite beautiful, done in impressive style, they will contain the brushstrokes and color combinations, impressive. Thanks to the presets, integrated attention to the smallest details, you can get a great result in few minutes.
JixiPix Artista Impresso Pro
In addition, the program can operate as a plug-in more for popular programs such as Photoshop, Lightroom and Elements. Among the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Blue Cat Audio 2026.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 22:35:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blue-cat-audio-751.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blue-cat-audio-751.html
</guid><description>
Blue Cat Audio develops and distributes the app and the plug-in real-time audio for PC and Mac platforms, focuses on sound analysis, feedback, image accuracy and flexibility. Check out our software and convert audio workstation digital of a processing environment sounds professional.
Blue Cat Audio - Plugins audio standard
The products Plugins inside Blue Cat Audio
Blue Cat's Axiom v1.1.2
Blue Cat's Destructor v1.4.1
Blue Cat's DP Meter Pro v4.1.0
Blue Cat's Dynamics v4.2.0
Blue Cat's...
</description></item><item><title>Download Zoom Player Max 22.2 Beta 1</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 22:34:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zoom-player-max-104.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zoom-player-max-104.html
</guid><description>
Zoom Player MAX help you to see the film on DVD, Blu-ray, Flash movies and HD format with high quality and the ability to display subtitles in English very well. The advantage of software is that takes up very little system resources to play the movie with quick speed, change the wallpaper options while viewing movies.
Zoom Player MAX is the movies, browse high-quality photos on the computer with the advantages such as compact size, quick start, built-in codec. The application supports...
</description></item><item><title>Download JixiPix Photo Formation 1.0.27</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 22:33:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jixipix-photo-formation-2670.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jixipix-photo-formation-2670.html
</guid><description>
JixiPix Photo Formation is photo effects automatically convert images into paper form super creative then use the lighting tool 3D to create the ball extremely cool. Use it to segment, engage, woven, cut pieces and fold the images into each piece eye-catching appeal, with all the folds, delicate curls, and bent as if carefully assembled by hand.
The software comes with friendly interface with the user and includes dozens of presets. The effects are applied in real time and you will be...
</description></item><item><title>Download iTop Easy Desktop 4.0.0.272</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 22:33:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-itop-easy-desktop-7879.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-itop-easy-desktop-7879.html
</guid><description>
iTop Easy Desktop is a lightweight and easy-to-use desktop manager that organizes desktop icons, files and folders according to your rules, helping you Freed from the tedious arrangement of icons on the screen. It provides various practical features including but not limited to grouping desktop items, awakening live search, and quickly accessing icons and files even across multiple desktop sites. desktop.
Untidy desktop If you're not one to diligently organize your Windows desktop icons...
</description></item><item><title>Download Jixipix Watercolor Studio 1.4.22</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 22:33:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jixipix-watercolor-studio-74.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jixipix-watercolor-studio-74.html
</guid><description>
Jixipix Watercolor Studio Watercolor Studio create water color effect, liquid, matte, natural. Jixipix Watercolor Studio is built on a system of rendering incredible use of practical techniques, this application performs original work, created water colors immediately, then allows you to customize the painting of himself using a series of sliders, Class, brush, Color wash, and Artistic finish . The end result - the colors of water quality in flooded the transparency and sheer...
</description></item><item><title>Download JixiPix Hand Tint Pro 1.0.27</title><pubDate> Wed, 28 Jan 2026 22:32:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jixipix-hand-tint-pro-2658.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jixipix-hand-tint-pro-2658.html
</guid><description>
JixiPix Hand Tint Pro is another program by JixiPix Software, popular with the development in the field of graphics processing. Now you will have everything in hand to make color, craft and coloring for the photos of you, and the goal of this event is to give them a vintage style or art.
Hand Tint Pro offers everything you need - the color palette, paper and palm smart - to create the photograph beautiful, hand-painted and timeless. Like all art forms, prepare a good base to color by hand...
</description></item></channel></rss>