<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 21:33:59 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 21:33:59 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download IrfanView 4.73 Commercial + Plugin</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 23:44:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-irfanview-377.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-irfanview-377.html
</guid><description>
IrfanView version Commercial multilingual is photo slideshows with editor functions compact photo, such as color correction, resizing, image format.  This is a very simple software and in accordance with the beginners. IrfanView supports all the graphic format itself, including BMP, DIB, JPEG, GIF, animated GIF, PNG, PCX, TIFF, TGA, etc., in Addition, it features support for drag and drop, see folder support, TWAIN, slide shows, batch conversion, and modifications such as color depth,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Opera One 124.0.5705.15</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 23:44:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-972.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-972.html
</guid><description>
Opera is a fast, safe, configurable and compliant intranet web browser, which includes both the reader and the application. The Opera browser supports web browsing, listening to music, watching high speed movies, you can open many tabs on the Opera without affecting your browsing speed. Opera now supports almost all devices and operating systems such as windows, IOS, Android, linux, MacOS ...
Opera is a beautiful interface and many interesting features, operating on both PCs and mobile,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Freemake Video Converter Gold 5.0.0.20</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 23:43:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-freemake-video-converter-gold-167.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-freemake-video-converter-gold-167.html
</guid><description>
Freemake Video Converter Gold is a software to help convert tail high quality videos with many different formats on many devices. Freemake Video Converter - convert video to AVI, MP4, WMV, MKV, 3GP, DVD, MP3, iPad, iPhone, PSP, Android phone. Video to MP3 just with one click! Rip and burn DVD. Convert YouTube to MP4, AVI, etc. with Freemake! Results guaranteed. Freemake Video Converter has fast conversion speed, guarantee the output quality,support create HTML5 videos have the embed code...
</description></item><item><title>Download MacX DVD Ripper Pro 8.11.3.171</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 23:43:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-macx-dvd-ripper-pro-4306.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-macx-dvd-ripper-pro-4306.html
</guid><description>
MacX DVD Ripper Pro is the ripping DVD fastest for windows (10/8/7) to backup DVD to ISO / hard drive, rip DVD to MP4, FLV, MOV, MPEGAVI, WMV, etc for iPhone SE / 6s / 6s Plus, iPad Air 2, iPad 4/3 / Mini with Retina, new Apple TV, Android, HTC One M9, Samsung Galaxy S6 / edge +, Galaxy Note 5 / Edge, WP8, Surface, WP8, etc with 100% quality. MacX DVD Ripper Pro gives you full access to the DVD movies are protected by eliminating protection measures copy. It removes encryption CSS...
</description></item><item><title>Download Stretchly 1.19.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 23:43:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stretchly-1877.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stretchly-1877.html
</guid><description>
Stretchly is a reminder application break time automatically remind you to take breaks while you are working on your computer. By default, the program runs in the system tray and display the window prompts and press the bell for 20 seconds violation just after 10 minutes and take a 5 minute break every 30 minutes. You can customize the duration of the stay as well as the time between the times, to violate or ignore them if you like.
Stretchly - software automatic reminders
Stretchly is...
</description></item><item><title>Download AI Image Object Replacer Pro 1.1.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 23:42:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ai-image-object-replacer-pro-14249.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ai-image-object-replacer-pro-14249.html
</guid><description>
Are you tired of unwanted objects, people, or text cluttering up your perfect photos? Do you wish you could magically replace a dull sky or fix a buggy background without having to learn complicated software?
AI Image Object Replacer Pro brings the power of advanced image-rendering AI right to your desktop. Easily remove, replace, or add anything you can imagine to your photos with just a few clicks and a simple text prompt. Our intuitive tools and powerful AI models make professional...
</description></item><item><title>Download 4K YouTube to MP3 25.4.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 23:42:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-youtube-to-mp3-622.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-youtube-to-mp3-622.html
</guid><description>
4K YouTube to MP3 is a software to convert video youtube to mp3 quickly and easily by the manipulation drag-and-drop simple. With 4K YouTube to MP3 you just drag and drop the link to the favorite songs of you and get the MP3 files to your computer, as easy as that. Transfer songs directly to iPod, iPhone and iPad everywhere you go. No install annoying and complex to solve, just a clean interface, user friendly and functional.
When using 4K YouTube to MP3, users will get the playlists,...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinX DVD Ripper Platinum 8.22.4.247</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 23:41:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winx-dvd-ripper-platinum-520.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winx-dvd-ripper-platinum-520.html
</guid><description>
WinX DVD Ripper Platinum is a software ability to extract the contents of the DVD to other formats like AVI, MOV, FLV, WMV, MPEG, MP4, 3GP. In addition, the software can extract the DVD various (including DVD encrypted) for Sony PSP, Apple iPhone, iPod, iPad, iTouch, Apple TV, Zune, mobile phone.
WinX DVD Ripper Platinum is software development based on the support multi-core CPU and is fully compatible with Windows 7. Besides converting DVD to video formats typically WinX DVD Ripper...
</description></item><item><title>Download Opera GX (Gaming Browser) 123.0.5669.76</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 23:41:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-gx-3170.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-gx-3170.html
</guid><description>
Opera GX is a special version of the Opera browser is built to complement gamers avid. Browser this game comes with the unique features to help users make maximum use of both the game and their browser. Opera GX is built specifically to support the game. This browser includes the unique features to help users have the best experience when gaming and surfing the web.
Opera GX - special browser for gamers
GX Control allows you to set a limit on the level of use RAM, CPU and network where...
</description></item><item><title>Download Vivaldi for macOS 7.7.3851.48</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 23:40:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/mac/download-vivaldi-for-macos-3443.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/mac/download-vivaldi-for-macos-3443.html
</guid><description>
The Vivaldi for MacOS browser does not track users and offers more features than any other modern browser. Managed by Jon von Tetzchner (co-founder of Opera browser), Vivaldi for MacOS is driven by the real needs of today's users and ensures that they have the best tools to browse and get work done.
Vivaldi for MacOS - Modern web browser
Users can adjust Vivaldi to suit their browsing needs them without limiting customization options. Vivaldi takes the browser to the next level with a...
</description></item><item><title>Download Vivaldi Browser 7.7.3851.48</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 23:40:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vivaldi-159.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vivaldi-159.html
</guid><description>
Vivaldi is a browser designed for users who have power and offer the option to customize high. You can choose the location of the tabs and the address bar, put the hotkeys for the common tasks and many other features. Also, Vivaldi also provides a number of improvements such as Tab Stacks to group multiple open tabs into a tab, leads to interface less cluttered. Can notes and added a screenshot of a web page while browsing, storing an attachment, and add the URL to easily sort and locate...
</description></item><item><title>Download VovSoft OCR Reader 3.4</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 23:39:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-ocr-reader-7875.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-ocr-reader-7875.html
</guid><description>
VovSoft OCR Reader is an image-based text recognition program that converts images of typed, handwritten or printed text into machine-encoded text. , whether from a scanned document or an image of a document. VovSoft OCR Reader can easily digitize scanned image files and documents on your laptop or desktop computer. This application uses the Tesseract OCR engine, which supports more than 100 languages. It uses a neural network-based OCR (LSTM) engine that focuses on line recognition, but...
</description></item><item><title>Download O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro 21.2.207</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 23:39:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-diskimage-pro-218.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-diskimage-pro-218.html
</guid><description>
O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro is software backup data comprehensive and effective is provided to protect the data of the computer system, it creates images for individual drives or the entire system that still does not affect your system.
O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro allows the user to backup the entire computer or drive, the and files whenever you want even while the computer is being used. Or can use O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro to create a copy chinh sac of computer disk drives, can be used instead of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download MassTube 2026 v21.2.1.179 Ultra</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 23:39:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-masstube-plus-461.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-masstube-plus-461.html
</guid><description>
MassTube Plus is a small utility used to download the favorite videos of you on youtube on your computer. This is a software compact, has a simple design with few options to download videos fastest. The you complete peace of mind because the software is easy to use, built exclusively for a single goal: to retrieve the video file from YouTube, so it doesn't pack the other useful features such as search engine integrated and a download audio file.
MassTube can work with multiple output...
</description></item><item><title>Download VovSoft Search Text in Files 4.7</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 23:38:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-search-text-in-files-5417.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-search-text-in-files-5417.html
</guid><description>
VovSoft Search Text in Files is an application that searches through text files with simple queries, and the application will quickly find the file. Select the folder, enter the search text and filename filter, then click the Start button. All files including the search text will be listed. You can export the list to text or a CSV file. You can open, copy or delete files by right clicking. You can also display file sizes and file icons by using checkboxes.
VovSoft Features Search Text...
</description></item><item><title>Download All PDF Editor &amp;amp; Reader | Xodo 10.9.0 build 210090003</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 23:37:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-xodo-pdf-reader-editor-8451.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-xodo-pdf-reader-editor-8451.html
</guid><description>
Xodo PDF Reader &amp;amp; Editor is a mobile application for reading and editing PDF documents on Android and iOS devices. The app allows users to view, annotate, and edit PDF files using a variety of tools, including highlighting, underlining, and adding notes. With Xodo, you can read, annotate, sign, and share PDFs and fill out PDF forms, all while syncing with Google Drive, Dropbox, and OneDrive.
Xodo PDF Reader &amp;amp; Editor Features
	PDF Viewer: Application that allows users to view...
</description></item><item><title>Download YoWindow Weather - Unlimited 2.53.12</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 23:37:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-yowindow-weather-unlimited-8421.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-yowindow-weather-unlimited-8421.html
</guid><description>
YoWindow is a unique new weather app. The magic of YoWindow is a living landscape that reflects your real-life weather. For example, if it rains - it will rain in YoWindow. Sunset and sunrise in YoWindow take place at the same time as in real life. But the cool thing is you can roll time forward. Just swipe the screen and you'll see how the weather changes throughout the day.
YoWindow Weather Features - Unlimited
	All the weather at your fingertips. You see the current weather,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tails 7.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 23:09:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tails-3241.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tails-3241.html
</guid><description>
Tails is a live operating system that you can boot on almost any computer from a USB memory stick or DVD. Tails does this by using the distribution classic Gnome of Linux. The top navigation bar allows you quick access to "Applications" and "Places" so you can easily access what you need quickly and easily and not lost.
Tails - independent operating System for security
Menu "apps" provide shortcuts for bundled software, including graphics, audio and video, office, system tools, and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Hasleo Disk Clone 5.5.2.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 23:08:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hasleo-disk-clone-6017.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hasleo-disk-clone-6017.html
</guid><description>
Hasleo Disk Clone is a free Windows copy software and all of one can help you move Windows to another disk, copy one disk to another or copy a partition to another.
The benefits of Hasleo Disk Clone:
1. Move Windows to SSD or HDD (smaller or larger) without reinstalling Windows and applications.
2. Copy one disc to another (smaller or larger) disk as backup.
3. Copy a partition to another location without losing any data.
Features of Hasleo Disk Clone
	System, Disk and...
</description></item><item><title>Download OsmAnd+ — Maps &amp;amp; GPS Offline 5.2.9</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 23:08:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-osmand-maps-gps-offline-8245.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-osmand-maps-gps-offline-8245.html
</guid><description>
OsmAnd+ (OSM Automatic Navigation Directions) is a mapping and navigation application with access to free, global, and high-quality OpenStreetMap (OSM) data. Enjoy voice and optical navigation, view POIs (points of interest), create and manage GPX routes, use contour visualization and elevation information, choose between driving modes, cyclists, pedestrians, OSM editing, etc.
This is a mobile navigation app that uses OpenStreetMap (OSM) data to provide users with detailed maps and...
</description></item><item><title>Download 3C All-in-One Toolbox 3.1.4e</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 23:07:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-3c-all-in-one-toolbox-8399.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-3c-all-in-one-toolbox-8399.html
</guid><description>
3C All-in-One Toolbox combines many features into one giant toolbox with a modern and easy-to-use interface. All the tools you need to monitor, control and fine-tune all your Android devices. This app uses the Accessibility service to help you stop the app on non-rooted devices but will never collect any information.
Features of 3C All-in-One Toolbox
	Device Manager offers very powerful configurations, task scheduling, and device watchdogs that you can find to optimize performance and...
</description></item><item><title>Download PhotoDirector: AI Photo Editor 20.7.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 23:07:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-photodirector-photo-editor-8144.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-photodirector-photo-editor-8144.html
</guid><description>
PhotoDirector is a photo editing app for Android devices that allows you to edit and enhance your photos with a variety of tools and effects. With PhotoDirector, you can adjust your photo's color and lighting, remove blemishes and other imperfections, and apply filters to give your photos a unique look. You can also use PhotoDirector to create photo collages and slideshows, add text and stickers to photos, and share your edited photos on social networks or through other sharing...
</description></item><item><title>Download Duolingo: language lessons 6.55.3</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 23:07:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-duolingo-language-lessons-8265.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-duolingo-language-lessons-8265.html
</guid><description>
Duolingo is a popular language learning app that offers interactive lessons to help users learn new languages. This application offers many languages for you to choose from, including Spanish, French, German, Italian, Portuguese, Chinese, Japanese and many more.
This app offers an gamified learning experience with interactive lessons, exercises, and quizzes designed to help users learn new words, phrases, and grammar rules. This app is designed to be easy to use and suitable for people...
</description></item><item><title>Download StbEmu (Pro) 2.0.17.04</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 23:06:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-stbemu-pro-9840.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-stbemu-pro-9840.html
</guid><description>
StbEmu is an application for Android 5.0+, allowing downloading IPTV web portals, designed to run on IPTV STB (Set-Top-Box), on devices running Android, such as phones, tablets tablets and TV boxes. Currently, the application supports simulation of many STBs created by the Ukrainian company Infomir, such as MAG 250, MAG 270 or MAG 322.
StbEmu (Pro) for IPTV: Remember that this application is configured for a demo IPTV portal for testing purposes. If you want to use the app, you must...
</description></item><item><title>Download WiFi Direct + 10.0.25</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 23:06:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wifi-direct-10153.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wifi-direct-10153.html
</guid><description>
Wi-Fi Direct is a Wi-Fi standard for peer-to-peer wireless connections that allows two devices to establish a direct Wi-Fi connection without the need for an intermediate wireless access point, router, or Internet connection.
Features of WiFi Direct +
	Fast
	Completely free, no intrusive ads.
	Supports all file transfers.
	Supports multiple file transfers.
	Supports folder transfer.
	Supports file transfer to and from external sdcard.
	Tested on many devices.
	Advanced file chooser.
</description></item></channel></rss>