<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 20:00:50 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 20:00:50 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Simplenote 2.24.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 21:00:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-simplenote-6243.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-simplenote-6243.html
</guid><description>
Simplenote is Markdown support. In addition to being accessible through most web browsers, multi-platform applications are available on Android, Linux, Windows, iOS and macOS. You will be able to share the notes that have created with other users, it can be useful when you participate in a group project. You can share your notes and allow others to edit their contents by adding an email address or their account name to the note card.
Features of Simplenote
	Notes are always updated on...
</description></item><item><title>Download ON1 Resize AI 2026.1 v20.1.0.17740</title><pubDate> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 20:58:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-on1-resize-2055.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-on1-resize-2055.html
</guid><description>
ON1 Resize 2019 is the edited final image when you need to zoom in the highest quality - with technology genuine Fractals® - to resize your photo to print. You can quickly change the image size without losing sharpness or detail. ON1 Resize also includes one of the fastest ways to view, remove and edit photos.
ON1 Resize - Zoom, change photo size
The features of ON1 Resize
	ON1 Resize using interpolation algorithm based on fractal - helps quickly change the image size without losing...
</description></item><item><title>Download CyberLink PowerDirector Ultimate 2026 v24.0.1119.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 20:58:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-powerdirector-ultimate-425.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-powerdirector-ultimate-425.html
</guid><description>
CyberLink PowerDirector Ultimate is software editor, edit video and make movies on the computer from a variety of templates are made available, complete with effects, transitions, animations, and music. CyberLink PowerDirector 17 is a combination of video editing software with advanced video editing features powerful. Cblowing need to add your clips into the time line and click on 'Production'!
The tool design video in CyberLink PowerDirector have the ability to customize helps you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Topaz Gigapixel Pro 1.0.4</title><pubDate> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 20:57:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-ai-gigapixel-1318.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-ai-gigapixel-1318.html
</guid><description>
Topaz ONE Gigapixel is the first app and only use the power of artificial intelligence to enhance your photos, add natural details, for great results. Use technology to learn deep, AIGigapixel ™ can zoom in and fill in the details that the products change in size other are not included. The traditional method this created blurred image, a non-realistic and do not have the detail present in the image have high resolution.
Topaz A.I. Gigapixel - enhance image quality
The content of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Apowersoft Video Download Capture 6.6.2.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 20:56:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-apowersoft-video-download-capture-1556.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-apowersoft-video-download-capture-1556.html
</guid><description>
Apowersoft Video Download Capture is a comprehensive tool with advanced technologies for media streaming to choice cost-effective to download videos from YouTube, Dailymotion, Vimeo, Yahoo Screen and Hulu, as well as millions of other websites. Apowersoft Video Download Capture is your download video powerful and effective this can download and save videos, movies, tv episodes and music videos online. It also has the switch function, supports convert any video to MP4, AVI, MKV, WMV and the...
</description></item><item><title>Download ALLPlayer 9.5.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 20:56:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allplayer-2522.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allplayer-2522.html
</guid><description>
ALLPlayer is perhaps the most popular program for watching movies with subtitles matching . It play all media formats know files, RAR and more can LiveUpdate function is implemented to update the latest codecs if there is a problem with opening a movie file. The program also automatically searches for matching subtitles in all languages . Subtitles smart to keep subtitles on the screen for the period of time required for you to read them. AVI Doctor helps when you are downloading a torrent...
</description></item><item><title>Download XYplorer (32 Bit) 27.20.0600</title><pubDate> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 20:55:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-portable-12066.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-portable-12066.html
</guid><description>
XYplorer Portable is a file management software application that provides a comprehensive set of features for organizing and managing files and folders on your computer. This is a portable version of XYplorer that you can run directly from a portable storage device, such as a USB drive, without installation.
XYplorer Portable Features
	File Management: XYplorer Portable provides a two-window interface, allowing you to view and work with two folders at the same time. It provides easy...
</description></item><item><title>Download CyberLink PowerDVD Ultra 24.0.1105.62</title><pubDate> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 20:55:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-powerdvd-ultra-191.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-powerdvd-ultra-191.html
</guid><description>
CyberLink PowerDVD Ultra is a software Development, multimedia such as video, audio, images, content, VR 360, and even YouTube or Vimeo, PowerDVD. PowerDVD unlock the potential of Ultra HD HDR TV and surround sound system, immersed in the virtual world with access to collection 360, or simply relax anywhere with playback support matchless and improved nicely on PC or laptop by you.
CyberLink PowerDVD Ultra have integrated the 4K UHD HDR latest TV and audio system multi-channel without...
</description></item><item><title>Download GoodSync Enterprise 12.9.17.7</title><pubDate> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 20:54:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-goodsync-enterprise-163.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-goodsync-enterprise-163.html
</guid><description>
GoodSync Enterprise is a software that saves files and files easily and is reliable. It automatically analyts, synchronize and backup your email, family photos, contacts, MP3, financial documentation and other important files-between desktop computers, laptops, servers, external drives and Windows Mobile devices as well as remotely via FTP , SFTP, WebDAV and more. The GoodSync synchronized software combines bulletproof reliability with an extremely easy interface to compare, synchronize...
</description></item><item><title>Download Any Video Downloader Pro 9.7.5</title><pubDate> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 20:54:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-video-downloader-pro-3731.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-video-downloader-pro-3731.html
</guid><description>
Any Video Downloader Pro is software support you can download video HD 720p, 1080p, 2K, 4K and 8K from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion, Vimeo, Metacafe and thousands of video sharing sites, other. It is a tool to speed up multi-threading can speed up your download faster up to 5 times. This helpful program support download at the same time. Any Video Downloader Pro lets you download multiple videos at the same time. Moreover, it allows you to pause and resume downloads if you need more...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tor Browser 15.0.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 20:53:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tor-browser-1833.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tor-browser-1833.html
</guid><description>
Tor Browser also has full name is Tor Browser Bundle is a web browser give you ability to access the internet safety and security your personal information as well as sensitive documents absolutely. By Tor Browser Bundle will automatically change the IP address on the machine to hide the identity when surfing the web. Tor Browser is free web browser full-featured basic and advanced allows you to leverage the Tor network anonymously without need to make any configuration changes or install...
</description></item><item><title>Download SQL Backup Master 8.0.1017 All Editions</title><pubDate> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 20:53:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sql-backup-master-6687.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sql-backup-master-6687.html
</guid><description>
SQL Backup Master backup your SQL Server database into any popular cloud hosting service such as Dropbox, OneDrive, Amazon S3, Microsoft Azure, Box and Google Drive. It can also backup the database to the FTP server-or a directory on your local machine, network server or storage device.
The backup of your SQL Server database to the cloud will not be complex or expensive. SQL Backup Master is born by providing an easy way to download copies of your database to one or more of the most...
</description></item><item><title>Download MusConv 4.10.433 Lifetime</title><pubDate> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 20:52:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html
</guid><description>
MusConv transfers playlists, albums, followed artists and liked songs across a variety of services – Spotify, Apple Music, Amazon Music, YouTube, YouTube Music, iTunes, Deezer, Tidal, SoundCloud, Pandora and more 125 music services!
Features of MusConv Ultimate
	Transfer playlists, albums, followed artists and liked tracks between over 125 music servicesManage playlists (Delete, Merge, Split, Copy...)
	More than 125 music services supported
	Access DAILY updated music charts on...
</description></item><item><title>Download VovSoft OCR Reader 4.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 20:52:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-ocr-reader-7875.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-ocr-reader-7875.html
</guid><description>
VovSoft OCR Reader is an image-based text recognition program that converts images of typed, handwritten or printed text into machine-encoded text. , whether from a scanned document or an image of a document. VovSoft OCR Reader can easily digitize scanned image files and documents on your laptop or desktop computer. This application uses the Tesseract OCR engine, which supports more than 100 languages. It uses a neural network-based OCR (LSTM) engine that focuses on line recognition, but...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cash Register Pro 4.0.3</title><pubDate> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 20:51:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cash-register-pro-3853.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cash-register-pro-3853.html
</guid><description>
Cash Register Pro a software cash register full of features and creative for a Windows computer, it will help you to better handle all the activities of the computer money. The application comes with the user interface logical and user friendly allows you to work quickly and do not commit the common error. The program can be used on a number of computers and offers a wide range of authorization secure and reliable. Cash Register Pro will help you track products and goods remain...
</description></item><item><title>Download DroidKit 2.3.7.20251119</title><pubDate> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 20:51:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-droidkit-6578.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-droidkit-6578.html
</guid><description>
DroidKit is data recovery software for your mobile device, it will quickly scan your phone memory and save photos, WhatsApp chats and files, messages Messages, contacts and more essential data up to 13 categories, covering almost everything you need every day. All Android phones and tablets are supported. Without rooting your device. No tech skills required. No need to wait many days. You can get back what you've lost with just a few simple clicks, instantly.
Besides, DroidKit also has...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cypheros TS-Doctor 4.2.17</title><pubDate> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 20:51:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cypheros-ts-doctor-9146.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cypheros-ts-doctor-9146.html
</guid><description>
Cypheros TS-Doctor is a software tool designed to edit and repair MPEG2 and H.264 transport streams. Easily create your own movie library, easy, fast and without loss of picture and sound quality. TS-Doctor is the perfect tool for editing and repairing recordings from Sat, Cable and DVB-T Receivers. This software is specifically designed for use with digital TV recordings and can process recordings from a variety of digital TV sources, including satellite, cable and terrestrial...
</description></item><item><title>Download XL-Connector 3.6.26</title><pubDate> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 20:50:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xl-connector-12415.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xl-connector-12415.html
</guid><description>
XL-Connector is a popular plugin that securely integrates Excel and Salesforce to export, import, refresh and transform data seamlessly with ultra-fast api connection. It provides Salesforce administrators with a comprehensive toolbox that easily performs data and metadata management activities in a familiar Excel environment.
Features
Export from Salesforce to Excel
	Get data from existing Salesforce reports or build your own SOQL queries directly into Excel.
Import data into...
</description></item><item><title>Download Filmworkz Loki 2025.3.000</title><pubDate> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 20:50:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-filmworkz-loki-14176.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-filmworkz-loki-14176.html
</guid><description>
Filmworkz Loki is a file-based, automated software application designed for image processing tasks such as restoring, enhancing, denoising, and sharpening archival footage and digital media. The latest version, Loki offers an easy-to-use platform with a web browser interface, dynamic preview windows, and automated batch processing to save time and reduce manual labor in the workflow.
It integrates Emmy Award-winning DVO tools that tackle a variety of image processing challenges,...
</description></item><item><title>Download ON1 Photo RAW 2026.1 v20.1.0.17740</title><pubDate> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 19:58:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-on1-photo-raw-1791.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-on1-photo-raw-1791.html
</guid><description>
ON1 Photo RAW 2023  includes the essential tools and features every photographer needs in their workflow. Our state-of-the-art, super-fast, non-destructive processing engine gives you an extremely smooth and efficient editing experience.
ON1 Photo RAW focuses on letting you get the most out of every photo. Photographers now have a quick photo management engine, hundreds of customizable photo effects, fast and beautiful HDR, masking and selection tools, layers and more in one app. Quickly...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinPE 11-10-8 Sergei Strelec 2025.11.19</title><pubDate> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 19:58:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winpe-10-8-sergei-strelec-8027.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winpe-10-8-sergei-strelec-8027.html
</guid><description>
WinPE 11-10-8 Sergei Strelec is a Windows 11, 10 and 8 PE boot disk for computer maintenance, hard disks and partitions, disk and partition backup and restore, computer diagnostics, data recovery, installation Windows.
Assembly components include:
	WinPE 11 x64
	WinPE 10 x64
	WinPE 10 x86
	WinPE 8 x86
	WinPE 8 x86 (Native)
System Requirements:
1. RAM 1 GB or more
2. PC can boot from CD/DVD or USB drive.
</description></item><item><title>Download ON1 Photo RAW MAX 2026.1 v20.1.0.17740</title><pubDate> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 19:57:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-on1-photo-raw-max-10717.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-on1-photo-raw-max-10717.html
</guid><description>
ON1 Photo RAW MAX 2024 is powerful photo editing software that provides photographers with many tools and features to enhance and edit their images. With a user-friendly interface, it offers advanced editing capabilities, including non-destructive editing, AI-powered adjustments, and precise control over color and tone. It also supports raw files from over 800 cameras and works with JPEG, TIF, PSD, PSB, PNG and DNG files. Additionally, it also includes photo organization tools to manage...
</description></item><item><title>Download Windows Video Converter 2025 v10.0.3.5</title><pubDate> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 19:57:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-video-converter-6371.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-video-converter-6371.html
</guid><description>
Windows Video Converter is a comprehensive software with many features such as Transaction, Download and Rapid Video Editing. Windows Video Converter supports video conversion to 1000 formats at a rate of 30 times faster without reducing the quality. Download and convert video online. Cut, Cut, Add Text, Effect, Appendix, And More.
Features of Windows Video Converter
	The conversion of video to over 1000 formats.
	The speed is 30 times faster.
	The quality is not reduced.
	Download...
</description></item><item><title>Download Secret Video Downloader 1.0.6</title><pubDate> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 19:56:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secret-video-downloader-13775.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secret-video-downloader-13775.html
</guid><description>
Secret Video Downloader is a free application designed to facilitate easy video downloading from various websites. It leverages the yt-dlp command line program to efficiently grab video content, allowing users to save videos in the highest quality available without complicated installation or configuration. The tool has a minimalist interface focused on simplicity: the user pastes the video URL into the built-in browser, clicks the Download button, and the video is added to the download...
</description></item><item><title>Download Windows Video Editor Pro 2025 v10.0.3.5</title><pubDate> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 19:56:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-video-editor-6420.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-video-editor-6420.html
</guid><description>
Windows Video Editor is the 2021 editing tool collection that has everything you need to edit your video file. You can easily Cut, Crop, Rotate, Split, Trim or Join your videos. You can add Effects, Text, Animations, Watermarks, Subtitles, Music to your videos. You can adjust video speed, brightness, contrast, saturation or anything else of your videos. You can do almost everything to edit your videos! And You can edit videos in batch!
Features of Windows Video Editor
	With Windows...
</description></item></channel></rss>