<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 22:03:57 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 22:03:57 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Adobe Acrobat Reader DC 2025.001.21184</title><pubDate> Sat, 07 Feb 2026 00:04:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-acrobat-reader-3707.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-acrobat-reader-3707.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Acrobat Reader DC is a system of application software and Web services developed by Adobe Systems to view, create, manipulate, print and manage PDF files. With Adobe Acrobat Reader DC, you can create, export, edit, and track PDF files from anywhere - and maintain connection with the recent set of files on all your devices.
Adobe Acrobat Reader current DC is connected with Adobe Document Cloud - help working on the computers and mobile devices becomes easier than ever before. This is...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinPE 11-10-8 Sergei Strelec 2026.02.05</title><pubDate> Sat, 07 Feb 2026 00:03:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winpe-10-8-sergei-strelec-8027.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winpe-10-8-sergei-strelec-8027.html
</guid><description>
WinPE 11-10-8 Sergei Strelec is a Windows 11, 10 and 8 PE boot disk for computer maintenance, hard disks and partitions, disk and partition backup and restore, computer diagnostics, data recovery, installation Windows.
Assembly components include:
	WinPE 11 x64
	WinPE 10 x64
	WinPE 10 x86
	WinPE 8 x86
	WinPE 8 x86 (Native)
System Requirements:
1. RAM 1 GB or more
2. PC can boot from CD/DVD or USB drive.
</description></item><item><title>Download Altium Designer 26.3.0 Build 6</title><pubDate> Sat, 07 Feb 2026 00:02:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-altium-designer-01en-625.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-altium-designer-01en-625.html
</guid><description>
Altium Designer is the PCB design software (circuit board) professional helps you connect seamlessly with every aspect of design. Altium Designer is a within the automation software design, PCB and electronics for the motherboard in good and most popular today. It was developed by software company Altium Limited based in Australia.
Features Altium Designer:
	Analyzing the similar circuits using Spice.
	Have the perfect tool with the ability to simulate and debug the code and design...
</description></item><item><title>Download O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Premium WinPE 22.4.1206</title><pubDate> Sat, 07 Feb 2026 00:02:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-diskimage-workstation-4548.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-diskimage-workstation-4548.html
</guid><description>
O&amp;amp;O DiskImage WinPE is a program user friendly designed to help users create images of partitions and hard disk to keep them safe for their data in case disaster strikes. O&amp;amp;O DiskImage WinPE includes a set the ability to backup files and drives strong, helping users to easily keep data they want to secure. Users can create images of partitions or entire computer with just a few mouse clicks and they can also create the disk can boot if necessary.
Features of O&amp;amp;O DiskImage...
</description></item><item><title>Download Daemon Tools Lite 12.4.0.2391</title><pubDate> Sat, 07 Feb 2026 00:00:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-daemon-tools-lite-3391.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-daemon-tools-lite-3391.html
</guid><description>
DAEMON Tools Lite is based on two key features, simulation of virtual disks and building the file disk image as iso. DAEMON Tools Lite can emulate up to 4 virtual drives, DVD, CD or Blu-ray on your computer. The virtual units will be present in your system the same as the unit. After you select the virtual drive you want, you will choose a disc image (nrg, iso, mdf, bin, cue, etc.) that you want to mount. Visit My Computer at the device have The mobile storage and you will find the disk...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare UniConverter 17.2.0.497</title><pubDate> Sat, 07 Feb 2026 00:00:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-uniconverter-4808.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-uniconverter-4808.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare UniConverter ( old name is Wondershare Video Converter Ultimate) which allows you to convert the video format. You can cut, splice, move, or add effects, subtitles a easy way. When using software you easily cut, splice, move, as well as add the effects, the subtitles to the video.... Or can switch the clods SD, HD video to any format popular for use with iPod (Classic, Nano and Touch), iPhone, Apple TV, Zune, PSP, Pocket PC...
Wondershare UniConverter helps convert formats...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mp3Tag 3.33.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 06 Feb 2026 23:59:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mp3tag-150.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mp3tag-150.html
</guid><description>
Mp3tag is a powerful tool and easy to use to edit ID3 tags and OGG comments about the files MP3 - and Ogg Vorbis. It can rename files based on the tag information, replace characters or words from tags and filenames. Help users create and add the tag information for MP3 files to manage the information that is reasonable.
The program supports lookup database freedb online for the selected files, allowing you to automatically gather tag information appropriate for the files or CD selection....
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Substance 3D Modeler 1.22.6 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Fri, 06 Feb 2026 23:59:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-substance-3d-modeler-7876.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-substance-3d-modeler-7876.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Substance 3D Modeler is a 3D sculpting and modeling application that helps you create on both desktop and VR. Modelers aim to make working in 3D as intuitive as working with clay in real life. To help achieve this, with Adobe Substance 3D Modeler you don't have to worry about adjusting vertices or managing UVs, you can instead focus on the creative process.
With its intuitive design, Adobe Substance 3D Modeler frees you from the technical constraints of traditional 3D modeling....
</description></item><item><title>Download LDPlayer 9.2.0.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 06 Feb 2026 23:58:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ldplayer-2331.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ldplayer-2331.html
</guid><description>
LDPlayer is an Android emulator that allows users to play games and run applications on Windows computers. LDPlayer supports heavy gaming, running chat applications, editing photos, videos, and many other Android applications. LDPlayer is compatible with Android 5.1 and above, supporting multitasking for an experience that is not inferior to that of using on Mobile.
Installation is a simple and quick process that does not require any special attention from you, there are more. settings,...
</description></item><item><title>Download UPDF 2.1.4</title><pubDate> Fri, 06 Feb 2026 23:57:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-updf-14160.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-updf-14160.html
</guid><description>
UPDF for Windows is easy-to-use PDF software for Windows! Enjoy powerful editing tools for text, images, links, and more in your PDFs. Customize backgrounds, watermarks, and page sizes as easily as in Word. AI-powered PDF editor and manager that offers a wide range of features including editing, annotating, converting, OCR (Optical Character Recognition), organizing, protecting, sharing, printing, summarizing, translating, and interpreting PDF files.
Features of UPDF
Analyze PDFs with...
</description></item><item><title>Download TransMac 15.5</title><pubDate> Fri, 06 Feb 2026 23:56:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-transmac-2280.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-transmac-2280.html
</guid><description>
TransMac is a program that can copy files to and from the disk Macintosh that lets you create and burn CD or DVD image with ease. There is a solution powerful software allows you to copy any type of file to and from disk Mac OS X format that can't be accessed from Microsoft's operating system.
TransMac - Open and create DMG files on Windows
Thanks the interface is very clean and easy to navigate, TransMac is designed to allow users to transfer files to and from the disk HFS (Mac OS...
</description></item><item><title>Download WonderFox HD Video Converter Factory Pro 28.5</title><pubDate> Fri, 06 Feb 2026 23:36:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hd-video-converter-factory-pro-1458.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hd-video-converter-factory-pro-1458.html
</guid><description>
WonderFox HD Video Converter Factory Pro is a software powerful video conversion . This program can convert the video files the quality standard of the file SD card, the files HD as HD MP4, HD MKV, HD AVI, HD MTS, HD TRP. This can also in the opposite direction. This software includes more than 100 video formats, while maintaining quality output, faster than 50 times compared to some software. This software also supports VBR or VBR, using this option will keep the original quality of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download SQL Backup Master 8.1.1031</title><pubDate> Fri, 06 Feb 2026 23:34:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sql-backup-master-6687.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sql-backup-master-6687.html
</guid><description>
SQL Backup Master backup your SQL Server database into any popular cloud hosting service such as Dropbox, OneDrive, Amazon S3, Microsoft Azure, Box and Google Drive. It can also backup the database to the FTP server-or a directory on your local machine, network server or storage device.
The backup of your SQL Server database to the cloud will not be complex or expensive. SQL Backup Master is born by providing an easy way to download copies of your database to one or more of the most...
</description></item><item><title>Download Social Media Downloader 8.2.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 06 Feb 2026 23:34:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-socialmediaapps-facebook-video-downloader-3742.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-socialmediaapps-facebook-video-downloader-3742.html
</guid><description>
SocialVideo Downloader (formerly SocialMediaApps Facebook Video Downloader) is a Windows application to download and convert your favorite videos from Facebook and hundreds of other video sharing sites. It increases your loading speed by up to 500%, or even more! The application has a simple and intuitive user interface, its main functions and features are quite obvious to anyone. , regardless of prior experience with similar purpose tools.
&amp;nbsp;
SocialVideo Downloader
The main...
</description></item><item><title>Download Window Inspector 3.9.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 06 Feb 2026 23:22:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-window-inspector-2921.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-window-inspector-2921.html
</guid><description>
Window Inspector is a lightweight software application but the effect allows you to easily view the attributes and properties of an open window, such as text, window class and many other attributes. This program is very easy to use, allows you to access and view information just by your mouse cursor on the target window.
Window Inspector - Management application on windows
Window Inspector comes with a set of hot keys integrated will help you to freeze the information displayed, save...
</description></item><item><title>Download ClassicDesktopClock 5.21</title><pubDate> Fri, 06 Feb 2026 22:56:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-classicdesktopclock-3986.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-classicdesktopclock-3986.html
</guid><description>
ClassicDesktopClock is a simple clock, and can customize allow you to see the current time on the computer to your desk. The program provides a number of topics that will help you change the look just by a click of the mouse. In addition, you can set the clock anywhere you want on your screen. ClassicDesktopClock comes with a variety of features and rich options, such as transparency, the ability to show or hide the second hand, some themes, multiple language support, portability, etc.,...
</description></item><item><title>Download EverNote 11.2.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 06 Feb 2026 22:56:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-evernote-3261.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-evernote-3261.html
</guid><description>
EverNote is the all in one tool allows you to track notes, todo items, memos, outlines, excerpts, websites, ideas and other things and automatically synchronize them between multiple computers and mobile devices (iPhone, Android, etc.). You can choose to sort their notes into categories, password protect them, export them to XML and more. EverNote supports a number of pattern notes allow you to add to-do list, spreadsheet like Excel to calculate costs (automatic sum), notes, phone, contact...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Substance 3D Designer 15.1.2 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Fri, 06 Feb 2026 20:57:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-substancee-designer-adobe-908.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-substancee-designer-adobe-908.html
</guid><description>
Substance Designer is the tool aggregated structure to help design, create 3D material. Create the file Quality or texture bitmap. Substance Designer helps users to create materials with full control and infinite variations. Edit the texture complete immediately and create texture, Quality and material of MDL will be handled directly in the renderer or game engine of you.
Substance Designer - design, create 3D material
The main features of Substance Designer
	Substance Designer...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe InDesign 2026 v21.2.0.030 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Fri, 06 Feb 2026 20:38:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-001en-adobe-indesign-334.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-001en-adobe-indesign-334.html
</guid><description>
Adobe InDesign is the industry-leading page design and layout software for print and digital media. Create beautiful graphic designs with typography from the world's leading foundries and images from Adobe Stock. Quickly share content and feedback as PDFs. Easily manage production with Adobe Experience Manager. InDesign has everything you need to create and publish books, digital magazines, eBooks, posters, interactive PDFs, and more.
Adobe InDesign was developed by Adobe Systems, first...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Bridge 2026 v16.0.2.23 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Fri, 06 Feb 2026 20:37:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-bridge-0003-1338.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-bridge-0003-1338.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Bridge is a versatile digital asset management application developed by Adobe Inc., first released in 2005 as part of the Adobe Creative Suite. It acts as a powerful tool for organizing, previewing, and managing creative assets across various Adobe applications. By downloading the program on taiwebs.com, you can easily edit elements in batch mode, add watermarks and even set color options centrally - Adobe Bridge CC will simplify your work and help maintain order.
Adobe Bridge...
</description></item><item><title>Download Kotato All Video Downloader Pro 10.2.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 06 Feb 2026 20:36:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kotato-all-video-downloader-pro-5228.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kotato-all-video-downloader-pro-5228.html
</guid><description>
Kotato All Video Downloader Pro is a Windows application professional to download and convert your favorite videos from the video sharing website. It speeds up your downloads up to 5 times! Kotato All Video Downloader Pro can download videos from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion and hundreds of video sharing sites, other. After downloading, you will be able to play them smoother on your PC or your mobile device, even when you don't have Internet access.
The main features of Kotato All...
</description></item><item><title>Download Photo Mechanic All-in-One 2026.1 build 9024</title><pubDate> Fri, 06 Feb 2026 20:35:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photo-mechanic-all-in-one-12282.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photo-mechanic-all-in-one-12282.html
</guid><description>
Photo Mechanic All-in-One is an image management software, photo collection and categorization of all photos on your computer, it allows you to Import, Edit and Export quickly, helping you reduce your work. work in the workflow. Powerful batch processing, full support for image variables, IPTC and Exif metadata, make it the perfect tool for any digital photographer.
Photo Mechanic All-in-One Features
	Photo Mechanic takes this step further by automating other tasks at the same time,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe InCopy 2026 v21.2.0.030 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Fri, 06 Feb 2026 20:35:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-incopy-3894.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-incopy-3894.html
</guid><description>
Adobe InCopy 2023 is a solution to write and edit professional, tightly integrated with the software Adobe InDesign. Adobe InCopy allows a process to work in parallel between design staff and editorial copy, accurate copy to layout and efficiently meet editorial deadline. Adobe software this is designed to expand according to the needs of the content publishers, small, medium and large. You will be able to deliver content that will support both print and digital, thereby simplifying the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Directory Opus Pro 13.21.1 Beta</title><pubDate> Fri, 06 Feb 2026 20:34:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-opus-pro-779.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-opus-pro-779.html
</guid><description>
Directory Opus Pro is a software replacement for Explorer with traditional strength and function more than any manager other files. Directory Opus Pro full support for high DPI screen (for example 4K and 5K) with the rename dialog is redesigned, with new features. Besides being a recording macro only allows you to perform mass renaming complex that don't need regular expressions. In addition, Directory Opus Pro also enhances the ability to script.Better handling of renaming recursive and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Imagine 2.4.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 06 Feb 2026 20:33:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-imagine-7369.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-imagine-7369.html
</guid><description>
Imagine is an application that allows you to view images and animations in a variety of formats, including JPG, BMP, PNG and GIF. With Imagine you can view file properties and EXIF ​​information, copy, move, delete and rename images. Additionally, you can also flip, resize and rotate them, swap colors, set transparency levels, import, export, and edit palettes, and change color depth.
Features of Imagine
	View and save image/animation files at lightning speed
	Multiple...
</description></item></channel></rss>