<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 20:06:32 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 20:06:32 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download MobiOffice: Word, Sheets, PDF 16.0.58406</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 22:43:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-officesuite-word-sheets-pdf-8508.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-officesuite-word-sheets-pdf-8508.html
</guid><description>
OfficeSuite allows you to easily view, edit, and create Word, Excel, and PowerPoint documents and perform advanced PDF operations. Our integrated file manager, Chat app with document exchange capabilities, and tons of other handy tools make this the most feature-rich mobile office solution available on Android. Pre-installed by leading manufacturers including Sony, ZTE, Amazon, Sharp, Acer, CAT, Alcatel, Kyocera, Toshiba, etc.
Features of OfficeSuite for Android
	View, create, and...
</description></item><item><title>Download PhotoDirector: AI Photo Editor 20.8.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 22:43:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-photodirector-photo-editor-8144.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-photodirector-photo-editor-8144.html
</guid><description>
PhotoDirector is a photo editing app for Android devices that allows you to edit and enhance your photos with a variety of tools and effects. With PhotoDirector, you can adjust your photo's color and lighting, remove blemishes and other imperfections, and apply filters to give your photos a unique look. You can also use PhotoDirector to create photo collages and slideshows, add text and stickers to photos, and share your edited photos on social networks or through other sharing...
</description></item><item><title>Download Revo Uninstaller for Android 3.4.480G</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 22:42:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-revo-uninstaller-for-android-10156.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-revo-uninstaller-for-android-10156.html
</guid><description>
Revo uninstaller for Android helps you uninstall Android apps as well as organize and clean your device. Remove all leftover and hidden files for a clean and bloatware-free device. Easy-to-use tool to uninstall Android apps, their leftovers and hidden files. We specialize in uninstalling apps and optimizing smartphone storage space.
Every application leaves residual data after uninstallation. Revo Uninstall Mobile detects these leftovers and deletes them after showing you the files, so...
</description></item><item><title>Download Pacer Pedometer &amp;amp; Step Tracker vp12.12.1 build 2025120100</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 22:42:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pacer-pedometer-step-tracker-11194.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pacer-pedometer-step-tracker-11194.html
</guid><description>
Pacer App: “Pedometer, Pedometer, and Weight Loss Tracker App” that syncs steps and calories with MyFitnessPal and Fitbit! Track your steps, walking and weight loss with this free health counter. Lose weight and track distance walked and calories burned using 24/7 step counting from our pedometer, pedometer and health tracker app.
Main features:
	Best pedometer for any phone
	Accurate activity and step tracking
	Lose weight, track BMI and count calories burned
	Daily exercise...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mock Locations (fake GPS path) 1.35.9</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 22:42:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-mock-locations-fake-gps-path-10782.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-mock-locations-fake-gps-path-10782.html
</guid><description>
Mock Locations allows you to fake information about your phone's location according to GPS and network operator. You just need to navigate the route on the map and press the "Go!" there are apps all over your phone that provide fake location information. This will help with application development or if you don't want anyone to know where you really are.
Simulated Location Features
	Simulated GPS location and according to service provider.
	Ability to create routes on the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Equalizer &amp;amp; Bass Booster - XEQ 31.21.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 22:41:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-equalizer-bass-booster-xeq-10095.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-equalizer-bass-booster-xeq-10095.html
</guid><description>
This XEQ app is a powerful yet easy-to-use Music Equalizer with Bass Boost, Volume Boost, Auto Volume Boost and 3D Virtualizer effects, which can improve the sound quality of your device. your Android device.
This is the only equalizer fx app you will ever need for your smartphone. With this feature, you can not only equalize the bass boost, but also increase the normal sound volume of your Android phone, add virtual 3D effects, save custom presets, automatically recall presets of audio...
</description></item><item><title>Download IPTV Pro 9.1.14</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 22:41:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-iptv-pro-9093.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-iptv-pro-9093.html
</guid><description>
IPTV Pro is an Android application that allows you to watch live TV channels and movies on your Android device. It provides access to many channels from around the world, including sports, news, movies, and entertainment channels. IPTV Pro supports both M3U and XSPF playlists, and allows you to add your own playlists.
IPTV Pro Features
	Supports M3U and XSPF playlists
	Playlist history
	Play a multicast stream using a UDP proxy (the proxy needs to be installed in your LAN)
	Grid, list...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tap To Translate Screen 1.110</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 22:41:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-tap-to-translate-screen-10152.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-tap-to-translate-screen-10152.html
</guid><description>
Tap to translate screen is an effective screen translation tool to serve all the needs of users. The ability to translate quickly combined with different languages ​​makes the application special. The diversity of Tap to translate screen languages ​​has users excited. With hundreds of languages ​​and different translations, the application will stand out more than ever. Users just need to select the target language and then translate it immediately; A paragraph will match...
</description></item><item><title>Download Digital Compass 18.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 22:41:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-digital-compass-13590.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-digital-compass-13590.html
</guid><description>
This app is a smart compass with high accuracy and a great tool for outdoor activities. This compass app allows you to easily determine the direction you are facing. This app is built using the device's gyroscope, accelerometer, magnetometer, gravity sensor to determine the direction. Make sure your device has an accelerometer and magnetometer sensor or it will not work.
Features
	Show current location (longitude, latitude, address)
	Show altitude
	Show magnetic field strength
	Show...
</description></item><item><title>Download Net Signal Pro: WiFi &amp;amp; 5G Meter 3.9</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 22:40:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-net-signal-pro-wifi-5g-meter-9658.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-net-signal-pro-wifi-5g-meter-9658.html
</guid><description>
This app is a useful tool that allows you to check your WiFi Signal Strength and Mobile Signal Strength anywhere using your mobile device. It helps to find areas with good WiFi or cellular connectivity to set up smart home devices. View mobile signal 2G, 3G, 4G, 5G, network carrier, sim operator, phone type, network type, network strength in dBm, IP address,...
Features of Net Signal Pro: WiFi &amp;amp; 5G Meter
	Mobile signal information
	WiFi signal information
	Accurate Wi-Fi and...
</description></item><item><title>Download YoWindow Weather - Unlimited 2.54.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 22:40:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-yowindow-weather-unlimited-8421.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-yowindow-weather-unlimited-8421.html
</guid><description>
YoWindow is a unique new weather app. The magic of YoWindow is a living landscape that reflects your real-life weather. For example, if it rains - it will rain in YoWindow. Sunset and sunrise in YoWindow take place at the same time as in real life. But the cool thing is you can roll time forward. Just swipe the screen and you'll see how the weather changes throughout the day.
YoWindow Weather Features - Unlimited
	All the weather at your fingertips. You see the current weather,...
</description></item><item><title>Download AdGuard Ad Blocker 4.14.21 Nightly</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 22:40:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-adguard-block-ads-without-root-8215.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-adguard-block-ads-without-root-8215.html
</guid><description>
AdGuard for Android is the only root-free ad blocker for Android that removes ads in apps and browsers, protects your privacy, and helps you manage your apps. Adguard is designed to block unwanted ads, pop-ups and banners while you browse the web on your device. It uses a combination of local VPN technology and a custom DNS server to block ads, meaning it can block ads in apps as well as in web browsers.
In addition, Adguard also blocks tracking scripts from collecting information about...
</description></item><item><title>Download Solid Explorer File Manager 3.2.5</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 22:39:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-solid-explorer-file-manager-8924.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-solid-explorer-file-manager-8924.html
</guid><description>
Solid Explorer is a file management application inspired by old file management applications. Solid Explorer is a popular file management app for Android devices that allows users to manage and organize their files and folders in an intuitive and user-friendly interface. It offers many features that make it stand out from other file management apps.
Solid Explorer allows you to navigate to files stored on your device and automatically organize them into collections. You can view,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Voice Recorder Plus: Rec Sound 1.13.5</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 22:39:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sound-recorder-plus-voice-rec-13795.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sound-recorder-plus-voice-rec-13795.html
</guid><description>
Unlock the full potential of your recordings with Sound Recorder Plus &amp;amp; Dictaphone, your solution for perfect audio quality at your fingertips. Designed with a beautiful, intuitive interface, this app is suitable for both beginners and seasoned professionals. Whether it is for working, studying, listening to music or recording the essence of everyday life, Audio Recorder Free is the embodiment of high-quality and flexible audio recording or voice recording.
Key features of Voice...
</description></item><item><title>Download Librera PRO - Book reader 9.1.29</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 22:39:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-librera-pro-all-my-books-9008.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-librera-pro-all-my-books-9008.html
</guid><description>
PRO Librera Reader is an easy-to-use and highly configurable reading application that supports most popular document formats, including: PDF, EPUB, EPUB3, MOBI, DjVu, FB2, FB2.zip, TXT, RTF, AZW, AZW3, CBR, CBZ, HTML, XPS, MHT and more. With a simple yet powerful interface, Librera Reader makes reading documents a real pleasure. Librera even has a unique hands-free, auto-scrolling music mode.
Some key features of Librera reader include:
Easily explore documents with optional and...
</description></item><item><title>Download My Voice Text To Speech (TTS) Pro 2.0.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 22:38:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-my-voice-text-to-speech-tts-8129.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-my-voice-text-to-speech-tts-8129.html
</guid><description>
My Voice is a simple Text To Speech (TTS) app that helps you find your voice again. Simply type the text you want and let My Voice speak it aloud for you using the Text To Speech (TTS) engine you've chosen.
Note that the list of languages ​​available on your device will depend on your default Text To Speech (TTS) engine. For best results, we recommend using Google Text To Speech (TTS) as the default. You can change this in your device settings. If you use an alternative text to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Smart Launcher 6 ‧ Home Screen 6.5 build 054</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 22:38:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-smart-launcher-8412.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-smart-launcher-8412.html
</guid><description>
Smart Launcher is a mobile app that provides users with a customized home screen and app launcher on their Android devices. It includes features like minimalist interface, automatic app sorting, and gesture controls. The app also includes many customizable settings, such as the ability to change the theme, icon size, and screen layout, as well as the ability to create custom categories for the app.
Smart Launcher Features
	Ambient theme: Smart launcher automatically changes theme...
</description></item><item><title>Download SnapTube for Android 7.51.1.75170201</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 22:37:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-snaptube-youtube-downloader-hd-video-8351.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-snaptube-youtube-downloader-hd-video-8351.html
</guid><description>
SnapTube is a mobile application that allows users to download videos from various platforms, such as YouTube, Vimeo, and Dailymotion. It provides video resolution in multiple formats 144p, 720p, 1080p HD, 2K HD, 4K HD and audio formats MP3 and M4A. With Snaptube, users can search for content across all their platforms without using multiple apps.
Features of SnapTube for Android
Download in multiple resolutions
	MP4 videos are available in resolutions: choose small 360 pixels or...
</description></item><item><title>Download Accumulator PDF creator 2.37</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 22:37:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-accumulator-pdf-creator-11512.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-accumulator-pdf-creator-11512.html
</guid><description>
The application's simple operation allows you to select images, videos or PDF files and perform the desired functions with a simple press of a button. With countless functions, your creativity is your main asset and this application is your ultimate tool.
Features of Accumulator PDF creator
	Convert images and GIFs to PDF.
	Convert PDF to image.
	Write or paste text into PDF.
	Create professional PDF pages and presentations from scratch, implementing your own design on each...
</description></item><item><title>Download Magnifying Glass 4.1.6</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 22:37:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-magnifying-glass-9389.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-magnifying-glass-9389.html
</guid><description>
Magnifier is a simple app for Android devices used to magnify the appearance of objects or text that are small and difficult to see with the naked eye.
Features of Magnifier for Android
	Zoom: from 1x to 10x.
	Flashlight: Use a flashlight in dark places or at night.
	Freeze: After freezing, you can view a more detailed enlarged image.
	Take a photo: Save an enlarged photo on your phone.
	Completely free.
</description></item><item><title>Download Moon+ Reader Pro 10.3 build 1003000</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 22:36:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-moon-reader-pro-8577.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-moon-reader-pro-8577.html
</guid><description>
Moon+ Reader Pro is an all-in-one ebook document manager and better designed book reader with powerful and fully functional controls, supporting EPUB, PDF, DJVU, AZW3, MOBI, FB2, PRC, CHM, CBZ, CBR, UMD, DOCX, ODT, RTF, TXT, HTML, MD(MarkDown), WEBP, RAR, ZIP or OPDS formats.
This is a versatile e-book reading application that gives users a rich reading experience, while helping them easily access and manage their e-book library. Whether you're looking to read your favorite novels,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Today Weather: Radar &amp;amp; Widgets 2.4.1-2</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 22:36:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-today-weather-alerts-widgets-8915.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-today-weather-alerts-widgets-8915.html
</guid><description>
Weather Today is a beautiful and easy-to-use weather app that provides the world's most accurate local weather forecasts.
Features of Weather Today for Android
	Displays clear, easy-to-understand weather forecasts.
	Enjoy every moment you open the app with thousands of beautiful photos corresponding to the weather and day.
	Prepare for any situation with 24/7 weather forecasts and chance of rain.
	Protect your health with air quality, UV index and pollen count.
	Capture beautiful...
</description></item><item><title>Download NokoPrint - Mobile Printing 5.24.6</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 22:36:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-nokoprint-mobile-printing-8528.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-nokoprint-mobile-printing-8528.html
</guid><description>
Print photos and share them with family and friends. Print documents, PDFs, invoices, receipts, boarding passes, and more. at home, at work or on the go! You can print images, photos, web pages, PDF and Microsoft Office documents without downloading any additional apps or printing tools anytime, anywhere on almost any WiFi, Bluetooth or USB printer .
Features of NokoPrint for Android
	Print directly from your Android phone or tablet to almost any inkjet, laser or thermal...
</description></item><item><title>Download Relax Rain: sleep sounds 9.1.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 22:35:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-relax-rain-sleep-sounds-13416.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-relax-rain-sleep-sounds-13416.html
</guid><description>
The largest collection of relaxing rain sounds for Android. Over 50 rain sounds (free and HD) that can be combined with thunder and music to reach a state of complete relaxation. You can adjust the volume of rain, thunder and music individually to find the ideal combination and thus promote deep relaxation of the mind.
Rain sounds and relaxing music have a beneficial effect on the body and calm the mind because, by masking the noise of the external environment, they promote relaxation...
</description></item><item><title>Download Omnia Music Player 1.8.3 build 138</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 22:35:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-omnia-music-player-10217.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-omnia-music-player-10217.html
</guid><description>
Omnia Music Player is a powerful music player for Android. It is an ad-free offline audio player. Its beautiful user interface matches every detail of material design principles. Omnia Music Player supports almost all audio formats, including mp3, ape, aac, flac, opus, ogg, wav, etc. It has a high-resolution output engine with the best sound quality and a 10-band equalizer, in a small footprint, under 5 MB.
Omnia Music Player contains almost every necessary feature to satisfy all your...
</description></item></channel></rss>