<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 05:49:18 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 05:49:18 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Subtitle Edit 4.0.15</title><pubDate> Sat, 07 Feb 2026 17:05:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-subtitle-edit-2177.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-subtitle-edit-2177.html
</guid><description>
Subtitle Edit is software can both create new and edit captions already on your hard drive and added videos. The program will give the user a set of tools reliable and of high quality. If you believe that the author of the development and simply reviews on the Internet, then that is a large number of useful tools can distinguish this product with other similar substances, also provides the ability to overlay subtitles on the video. With Subtitle Edit you can easily configure caption,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Topaz Photo Pro 1.2.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 07 Feb 2026 17:03:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-photo-ai-8105.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-photo-ai-8105.html
</guid><description>
What is Topaz Photo AI?
Topaz Photo AI is a professional software that automatically adjusts for your image quality needs. Simply import images into Topaz Photo AI and it will use specially trained AI models to first detect unique details, clarity, and resolution issues before applying the intelligently adjusts to maximize your image quality.
For users experienced with Topaz Labs image quality applications, it combines the functionality of DeNoise AI, Sharpen AI and Gigapixel AI into...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ashampoo Backup Pro 27.5.43</title><pubDate> Sat, 07 Feb 2026 17:03:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-backup-pro-716.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-backup-pro-716.html
</guid><description>
Ashampoo Backup Pro is software to backup and restore data professional to save the file, the important data for your computer. Ashampoo Backup Pro will remove the fear of viruses, ransomware, or hardware errors. Ashampoo® Backup Pro offers you various options to backup individual files or entire disk partitions on any storage media or on the cloud. User friendly, intuitive, fast. Even in case an error occurs the entire system, application integrated emergency can bring your...
</description></item><item><title>Download MobaXterm Professional 26.0 / Personal / Educational</title><pubDate> Sat, 07 Feb 2026 17:02:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mobaxterm-professional-2026.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mobaxterm-professional-2026.html
</guid><description>
MobaXterm Professional is an SSH Client application server administration remotely via SSH for the client quite well and are more convenient. MobaXterm Professional offers a multitude of functions suitable for programmers, webmasters, IT administrators and pretty much the user need to handle the job from far more simple way. MobaXterm provides all the tools network key remote (SSH, X11, RDP, VNC, FTP, MOSH, ...) and Unix commands (bash, ls, cat, sed, grep, awk, rsync, ...) , in a file exe...
</description></item><item><title>Download Lyric Video Creator Professional 6.6.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 07 Feb 2026 17:02:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lyric-video-creator-professional-2192.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lyric-video-creator-professional-2192.html
</guid><description>
Lyric Video Creator Professional is the professional version the most help support more lyrics on music video very suitable for those who want to evolve to create video karaoke. All what you need, please visit the news below, there is a link to download the Lyric Video Creator with key free. Interface like a the media player classic, but with optional integration responsible for creating. At first glance, you can see the preview screen where all the videos or photos that you upload will be...
</description></item><item><title>Download OneCommander Pro 3.107.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 07 Feb 2026 17:01:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-one-commander-4232.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-one-commander-4232.html
</guid><description>
One Commander is a file manager for Microsoft Windows with function improved user interface and navigation experience, system file and manipulating the files. Utilities use the tree view to sort the folder, subfolders, and files your, make sure that the current location of you always clear. It supports multiple tabs, allowing you to easily switch between them and access the folder you need.
One Commander - a filemanager for Windows
Depending on the format of the files, some files can...
</description></item><item><title>Download AB Download Manager 1.8.5</title><pubDate> Sat, 07 Feb 2026 17:01:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ab-download-manager-12399.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ab-download-manager-12399.html
</guid><description>
With this application, you can easily download files from anywhere. Enjoy fast, free downloads with seamless browser extension support. It is built to be a desktop application that allows you to manage and organize your downloads better than before.
AB Download Manager features
	Simple and modern UI: Simple UI and dark mode by default
	Faster download speeds: Download files using multiple connections to increase your download speed by up to 500%
	Download Queue: Create and manage your...
</description></item><item><title>Download ExamDiff Pro Master Edition 16.0.1.22</title><pubDate> Sat, 07 Feb 2026 17:00:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-examdiff-pro-master-312.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-examdiff-pro-master-312.html
</guid><description>
ExamDiff Pro Master is a tool to compare files and folders intuitive and easy to use, intuitive and easy to use for Windows. ExamDiff Pro Master has unique features distinguishes ExamDiff Pro with the program compare other. ExamDiff Pro Master to help perform reviews of code and share other reports with your colleagues and compare local website with FTP server by plug-ins more integrated.
ExamDiff Pro Master can create a snapshot folder for comparison and storage in the future, compare...
</description></item><item><title>Download Minimal Firewall 2.6.6</title><pubDate> Sat, 07 Feb 2026 16:59:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minimal-firewall-13877.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minimal-firewall-13877.html
</guid><description>
Minimal Firewall works in conjunction with Windows Firewall to block all unknown connections by default, prompting you to create application-based rules to mitigate malware, telemetry, and data leaks. Completely eliminate applications that call home without your knowledge. Minimal Firewall provides a more secure and integrated approach by interacting directly with the native Windows Firewall, eliminating the need for risky system modifications.
Core Features
	Lockdown Mode: The core...
</description></item><item><title>Download Picture Window Pro 8.0.548</title><pubDate> Sat, 07 Feb 2026 16:59:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-picture-window-pro-7452.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-picture-window-pro-7452.html
</guid><description>
Picture Window Pro is a powerful image editing tool designed for serious photographers with strict creative and quality standards. Its comprehensive set of photo editing and editing tools let you control and shape every aspect of your images.
Picture Window Pro 8 is a complete rewrite of Picture Window Pro 7. It features non-destructive image editing through a novel interface based on an image tree. It also fully supports large, high-resolution displays and can be used in dual monitor...
</description></item><item><title>Download Source Insight 4.00.0150</title><pubDate> Sat, 07 Feb 2026 16:59:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-source-insight-2185.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-source-insight-2185.html
</guid><description>
Source Insight is an editor, programming-oriented strong project, browse the code and the analysis help you understand the code in when you work and plan. Source insight has built-in analysis for C / C ++, C #, Java, Objective-C, and much more. Source Insight is a powerful program created to give you a browser, as well as tools to view and edit the source code for the application is written in the programming language different. Everyone knows that the analysis and processing of the source...
</description></item><item><title>Download Total Network Inventory 6.7.1.7318</title><pubDate> Sat, 07 Feb 2026 16:58:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-total-network-inventory-professional-4729.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-total-network-inventory-professional-4729.html
</guid><description>
Computers and servers based on Windows, OS X, Linux, FreeBSD and ESX / ESXi can be scanned without the agent is pre-installed - you just need to know the password of the administrator. Scan the button menu, address range or network structure of Active Directory. Every computer only takes up a few tens of kilobytes in storage TNI concentration. Property group, add comments to them, and attach additional information. It will show your network in all its beauty!
Total Network Inventory...
</description></item><item><title>Download Vehicle Fleet Manager 2026.2.6</title><pubDate> Sat, 07 Feb 2026 16:58:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vehicle-fleet-manager-2326.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vehicle-fleet-manager-2326.html
</guid><description>
Vehicle Fleet Manager is an application easy to use for automotive companies want to manage the entire list with detailed information about expense tracking for car, employees, suppliers, parts and services. The interface of the tool at the time the first reviews seem too download, if you don't know English, it will be difficult to find it.
In fact, the program allows you to create a basic list of services, facilities, suppliers and employees, along with the maintenance schedule,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tenorshare iCareFone iTransGo 1.1.4.4</title><pubDate> Sat, 07 Feb 2026 16:57:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tenorshare-icarefone-itransgo-9615.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tenorshare-icarefone-itransgo-9615.html
</guid><description>
Tenorshare iCareFone iTransGo is software developed by Tenorshare, a company specializing in iOS and Windows data management solutions. Tenorshare iCareFone iTransGo is designed to help users transfer data between different iOS and Android devices. It provides a convenient and simple way to transfer various types of data, such as photos, videos, contacts, messages, etc.
Features of Tenorshare iCareFone iTransGo
	Transfer data from iPhone to Android in minutes.
	iTransgo helps you...
</description></item><item><title>Download TurboVNC 3.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 07 Feb 2026 16:57:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-turbovnc-7782.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-turbovnc-7782.html
</guid><description>
TurboVNC is a high quality, enterprise VNC version based on TightVNC, TigerVNC and X.org that allows efficient VNC server connectivity. TurboVNC was forked from TightVNC in 2004 and still includes all the features of TightVNC 1.3.x, but TurboVNC contains many feature enhancements and bug fixes related to TightVNC, and also compresses workloads. much better 3D and video work than TightVNC while using only 5-20%.
TurboVNC is capable of streaming more than 50 Megapixels/sec over 100...
</description></item><item><title>Download InvokeAI 6.11.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 07 Feb 2026 16:56:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-invokeai-11059.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-invokeai-11059.html
</guid><description>
InvokeAI is a leading creation engine designed to leverage the capabilities of Steady Diffusion models. It enables professionals, artists, and enthusiasts to create and produce visual media using advanced AI-driven technologies. This platform offers a powerful and user-friendly Web Interface.
Incorporating the most advanced open source research, Invoke empowers creative professionals to enhance their work, streamline workflows, and get work done in seconds. Use styles, renderings,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Markdown Monster 4.1.4</title><pubDate> Sat, 07 Feb 2026 16:55:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-markdown-monster-2640.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-markdown-monster-2640.html
</guid><description>
Markdown Monster is the edit and view Markdown allows you to edit Markdown by syntax highlighting and fast text input. Live preview can collapse, synchronized allows you to see the output of when you enter. You can easily embed images, links, emoticons and code in text form or by using the support UI lightness of we to simplify many operations. You can also paste and drag images directly into the editor.
Markdown Monster is a solution comprehensive software designed to solve almost any...
</description></item><item><title>Download Materialise Magics 29.1.0.35</title><pubDate> Sat, 07 Feb 2026 16:55:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-materialise-magics-0001-1477.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-materialise-magics-0001-1477.html
</guid><description>
Materialize Magics is the name of the specialized software and 3D printing techniques. Of course, in recent years, you've read articles about 3D printing. The software you're looking for is a powerful tool and is a provider editor software STL top. With this software, you will be able to turn your files into STL and identified and corrected after the error. You will also be able to edit your layout and provide the background you need to 3D print.
Materialise Magics - software engineer,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Atlantis Word Processor 5.0.1.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 07 Feb 2026 16:53:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-atlantis-word-processor-585.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-atlantis-word-processor-585.html
</guid><description>
Atlantis Word Processor is a word processor app with features format, standard text, autocorrect, and spell check.  Atlantis is a word processor in accordance with most of the tasks handled daily text. The interface is very easy to use and offers the toolbars, hotkeys and sound effects thanh can customize (can turn off). It includes a clip library for quick access to the text or images used regular preview, font format and many other features aimed at improving the process of your...
</description></item><item><title>Download High-Logic FontCreator Professional 15.0.0.3048</title><pubDate> Sat, 07 Feb 2026 16:52:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-high-logic-fontcreator-professional-1533.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-high-logic-fontcreator-professional-1533.html
</guid><description>
High-Logic FontCreator Professional allows you to create and edit TrueType fonts and OpenType. It has the powerful drawing tools that typographers and graphic designers require, and an intuitive interface that allows beginners to become productive immediately.
When you create or open a font, FontCreator displays an overview of all available characters. You can only add the characters missing, or select an existing character, and modify its appearance. You can import (scanned) signature...
</description></item><item><title>Download iZotope Neutron 5.2.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 07 Feb 2026 16:51:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-izotope-neutron-advanced-1727.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-izotope-neutron-advanced-1727.html
</guid><description>
iZotope Neutron Advanced is software audio control perfect reach blend clear, balanced with analysis tools and mixing new creative of the Neutron. Control every aspect of your music, from the visual field of music of your number of mixture-all of you with signal processing, digital award-winning iZotope.
iZotope Neutron 3 Advanced
iZotope Neutron 3 new introduction visual analytics, the first in the industry and communicate with all versions of neutron, so you can shape a mixture of...
</description></item><item><title>Download JOPDF 2.2.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 07 Feb 2026 16:51:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jopdf-14313.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jopdf-14313.html
</guid><description>
If you want the best free PDF editor, you'll definitely like JOPDF, a reliable, user-friendly, and lightweight editor. The software puts a lot of emphasis on speed and ease of use, even when handling large files. It includes all the essential editing features that are even found in paid programs. This best free PDF editor saves time, money, and effort for small businesses and students who need both basic and powerful features.
JOPDF helps you handle any PDF task with ease. Edit, create,...
</description></item><item><title>Download StaxRip 2.50.7</title><pubDate> Sat, 07 Feb 2026 16:50:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-staxrip-2930.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-staxrip-2930.html
</guid><description>
StaxRip app is a comprehensive and powerful, allowing you to convert all video files DVB, DVD, or DV video into a variety of file formats. The program is open Source, meaning completely free to download and use. StaxRip can support many video formats such as x264, MPEG-4, DivX, XviD, MPEG-2 and many other formats. The format sounds different also be supported, including MP2 / MPA, AAC, WAV, Ogg Vorbis, MP3, AC3, DTS and other formats. Moreover, the program also supports a variety of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Advanced CSV Converter 7.91</title><pubDate> Sat, 07 Feb 2026 16:50:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-csv-converter-4508.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-csv-converter-4508.html
</guid><description>
Advanced CSV Converter is a conversion tool CSV to DBF, Excel (XLS, XLSX), TXT, HTML, PRG, XML, SQL, RTF. To convert a file, the program provides an interface controlled by the wizard, guides you step by step conversion. Use the wizard, you select file input, select the format and destination folder. If necessary, you can set the filter switch according to the example and select columns you want to exclude from the process. When the conversion process is started, the program will extract...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mercuriall Audio Ampbox 1.8.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 07 Feb 2026 16:49:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mercuriall-audio-ampbox-8841.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mercuriall-audio-ampbox-8841.html
</guid><description>
Mercuriall Audio Ampbox is a software-based guitar amplifier emulation that uses advanced digital signal processing algorithms to reproduce sound and feel of classical guitar amplifiers. It can be used as a standalone plugin in a digital audio workstation (DAW) or as a standalone application for live performances or rehearsals.
This software includes a wide range of amplifier models, including classic models such as the Marshall JCM800, Fender Twin Reverb and Mesa Boogie Dual Rectifier....
</description></item></channel></rss>