<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 19:58:09 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 19:58:09 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download JRiver Media Center 34.0.64</title><pubDate> Thu, 28 Aug 2025 18:33:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jriver-media-center-110.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jriver-media-center-110.html
</guid><description>
JRiver Media Center can help you strictly manage all your files media and enjoy them in a completely new way. Launching the application for the first time, users will be immediately impressed with the intuitive and eye-catching interface with many interesting features to explore. Most people who have used JRiver Media Center evaluate that the software interface design is youthful and modern.
The software for arranging cover art of music files is also extremely neat, especially Insert...
</description></item><item><title>Download Bluebeam Revu 21.7.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 28 Aug 2025 18:32:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bluebeam-revu-extreme-629.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bluebeam-revu-extreme-629.html
</guid><description>
Bluebeam Revu eXtreme is support software file converter Microsoft® Office and CAD drawings into a pdf file and supports editing, markup and collaboration PDF. Bluebeam Revu eXtreme will help you increase productivity by leveraging data markers across the entire project lifecycle, and streamline processes to get more done in less time.
Features Bluebeam Revu eXtreme
Create
	Convert the number of Microsoft® Office documents and CAD drawings without limitation of PDF file in 2D or 3D...
</description></item><item><title>Download Allavsoft Video Downloader Converter 3.28.3.9369</title><pubDate> Thu, 28 Aug 2025 18:32:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allavsoft-video-downloader-converter-248.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allavsoft-video-downloader-converter-248.html
</guid><description>
Allavsoft Video Downloader Converter software supports download movies, music videos, playlist, sport videos from video sharing website for free like Facebook, Youtube and over 100 video sharing sites.
Allavsoft is many users favorite thanks to the combined features simultaneous transmission of multiple videos and speed limit download video. Besides, the program also supports pause and resume data transmission, to help you interfere with the process of transmitting download data to...
</description></item><item><title>Download S.O.S Security Suite 2.9.9</title><pubDate> Thu, 28 Aug 2025 18:31:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sos-security-suite-6227.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sos-security-suite-6227.html
</guid><description>
S.O.S Security Suite is a free, user-friendly app that helps you remove malware, ad software, and spy software, and also prevent infection. There is also a hardware error detection and security error detection and system optimization module. All these features combine to bring you what stands for the application: A more secure and optimal system.
S.O.S Security Suite is a successor to UVK and is designed to help you remove malware, ad software, and spy software, and help you not get...
</description></item><item><title>Download Any Video Downloader Pro 9.5.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 28 Aug 2025 18:31:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-video-downloader-pro-3731.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-video-downloader-pro-3731.html
</guid><description>
Any Video Downloader Pro is software support you can download video HD 720p, 1080p, 2K, 4K and 8K from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion, Vimeo, Metacafe and thousands of video sharing sites, other. It is a tool to speed up multi-threading can speed up your download faster up to 5 times. This helpful program support download at the same time. Any Video Downloader Pro lets you download multiple videos at the same time. Moreover, it allows you to pause and resume downloads if you need more...
</description></item><item><title>Download MusConv Ultimate 4.10.410</title><pubDate> Thu, 28 Aug 2025 18:31:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html
</guid><description>
MusConv transfers playlists, albums, followed artists and liked songs across a variety of services – Spotify, Apple Music, Amazon Music, YouTube, YouTube Music, iTunes, Deezer, Tidal, SoundCloud, Pandora and more 125 music services!
Features of MusConv Ultimate
	Transfer playlists, albums, followed artists and liked tracks between over 125 music servicesManage playlists (Delete, Merge, Split, Copy...)
	More than 125 music services supported
	Access DAILY updated music charts on...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cockos REAPER 7.44</title><pubDate> Thu, 28 Aug 2025 18:30:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cockos-reaper-889.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cockos-reaper-889.html
</guid><description>
Cockos REAPER is a powerful software for for windows, chp lets you record, arrange, edit, and display the audio waveform multi-track. Cockos REAPER offers an extensive feature set includes many effects and a sample project. REAPER supports ASIO, Kernel Streaming, WaveOut, and DirectSound for playback and recording. It reads the files in WAV, OGG and MP3 files and records WAV files. You can arrange any number of items in any number of tracks and use plug-in sound processing (DirectX and...
</description></item><item><title>Download IObit Malware Fighter Pro 12.5.0.1545</title><pubDate> Thu, 28 Aug 2025 18:30:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iobit-malware-fighter-pro-257.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iobit-malware-fighter-pro-257.html
</guid><description>
IObit Malware Fighter Pro is security software, remove malicious program with many advanced features that help protect safety for your system. IObit Malware Fighter Pro integration inside is the power of technology Dual-Core help quick scan and deep scan the entire system to detect and eliminate concerns about the virus.
IObit Malware Fighter Pro a lot of attention by the ability to detect and remove programs spyware from the system with fast speed and the most accurate. More special is...
</description></item><item><title>Download Fort Firewall 3.19.4</title><pubDate> Thu, 28 Aug 2025 18:29:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fort-firewall-6439.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fort-firewall-6439.html
</guid><description>
Fort Firewall is a network security system that monitors and controls network traffic and goes based on predefined security rules. A firewall often establishes a barrier between a trusted internal network and untrusted external networks, such as the Internet.
Features of Fort Firewall
	Filter by network address, application group
	Support of representative characters in the name path name
	Application group speed limit
	Access Traffic Statistics
	Display bandwidth
	Based on the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Youtube Downloader HD 5.9.9.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 28 Aug 2025 18:28:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-downloader-hd-3122.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-downloader-hd-3122.html
</guid><description>
Youtube Downloader HD is the best application to download and save Youtube videos. And it's completely free :) You can also convert the downloaded video into various formats easily. Youtube Downloader HD is the download at video free. Download at your videos easily and convert to AVI video format or into MP4 video format (compatible with iPad, iPhone). You can download high quality videos, high definition videos and Full HD from YouTube.
Youtube Downloader HD - Download Youtube videos...
</description></item><item><title>Download yt-dlp 2025.08.27</title><pubDate> Thu, 28 Aug 2025 18:28:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-dlp-6802.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-dlp-6802.html
</guid><description>
yt-dlp is a youtube-dl branch based on youtube-dlc currently not working. The main focus of this project is the addition of new features and patches while still updating the original project.
</description></item><item><title>Download Vizoo3D xTex 2.7.3</title><pubDate> Thu, 28 Aug 2025 18:27:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vizoo3d-xtex-6257.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vizoo3d-xtex-6257.html
</guid><description>
Vizoo3D xTex is the xTex software that works with the texture scanned or with any other image. Vizoo3D xTex uses the most complex tools to create seamless structures. You can choose between three different algorithms to achieve the best possible outcome for any case of use.
Now, you can make a profit from the XTEX process that is undefeated even if you do n' t own one of our scanners. Use images from the internet, from flat scanners or digital cameras and create seamless materials and...
</description></item><item><title>Download n-Track Studio Suite 10.2.2.10180</title><pubDate> Thu, 28 Aug 2025 18:27:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-n-track-studio-2991.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-n-track-studio-2991.html
</guid><description>
n-Track Studio is a recording software allows you record and create MIDI music and sounds top quality. The software allows you to add effects, VST3, DirectX, AU (Mac), VST and ReWire different on each track or channel. This program also allows you to automatically fade out, fade in and fade out or increase the volume of the music to indicate the voice of the singer.
n-Track Studio can record and playback the number of audio, MIDI and sound unlimited. In addition, you can handle the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Brave Browser 1.81.137</title><pubDate> Thu, 28 Aug 2025 18:23:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-brave-browser-2874.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-brave-browser-2874.html
</guid><description>
Brave Browser is a browser based on Chromium, the basic principle is that operation fast and privacy of users. The program can block pop-up windows and other ads, plus it blocked the mechanism for monitoring the online activities of your. Therefore, you can purchase and safely browse the website you are interested in without having to worry about the fact that your activity will be monitored and then you will be shown the necessary advertising or service provider of parties...
</description></item><item><title>Download 4KSoftware 4K Downloader 5.17.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 28 Aug 2025 18:22:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-downloader-3858.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-downloader-3858.html
</guid><description>
4K Downloader is a Windows application small but powerful to download and convert video in 4K and 8K Ultra HD from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion and thousands of other video-based websites. It speeds up your download by up to 5 times. Consider that most smart phones, TVS, computers, and tablets all support the high definition format, don't be surprised when many users want to enjoy quality content on their device. 4K Downloader is a lightweight software designed to help you grab videos...
</description></item><item><title>Download GetWindowText 5.25</title><pubDate> Thu, 28 Aug 2025 18:22:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-getwindowtext-2844.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-getwindowtext-2844.html
</guid><description>
GetWindowText is a program that is small and portable that you can read text on windows. It can be read almost all the texts, e.g. from edit, Static, groupbox - controls, etc. this Program also supports directory trees (SysTreeView32), combo box and list view (SysListView32) to read the entire content. When you release the mouse button, the reading will end.
GetWindowText - Read the text on windows
"GetWindowText" no need to be installed and can be executed easily from the desktop....
</description></item><item><title>Download ExperienceIndexOK 4.58</title><pubDate> Thu, 28 Aug 2025 18:19:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-experienceindexok-3180.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-experienceindexok-3180.html
</guid><description>
ExperienceIndexOK is a program benchmarking mobile to reviews and show Only the number of your Windows experience or to easily start a new calculation on performance metrics. Suitable for Microsoft: Windows 10, Windows 8.1, Windows 8, Windows 7, Server 2000-2016, XP, Vista, x64 / x32 / x86.
ExperienceIndexOK - reviews system Windows
It can be executed easily from the desktop and can be carried on a memory card, USB device or other memory. For portable use , please create in active...
</description></item><item><title>Download Intelligent Editing PerfectIt Pro 6.4.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 28 Aug 2025 18:14:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intelligent-editing-perfectit-pro-6048.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intelligent-editing-perfectit-pro-6048.html
</guid><description>
Intelligent Editing PerfectIt Pro is the leading software among professional editors. Professional writers and editors in 72 countries have been using PerfectIt since 2009. If you 're working on contracts, suggestions, reports, technical documents, articles and books, Intelligent Editing PerfectIt Pro will save time editing copies, so that the author may pay more attention to what' s most important: their words and meanings.
Features of Intelligent Editing PerfectIt Pro
	consistency...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ultra Adware Killer 10.9.9</title><pubDate> Thu, 28 Aug 2025 18:14:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ultra-adware-killer-2137.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ultra-adware-killer-2137.html
</guid><description>
Ultra Adware Killer is a software dedicated to block and remove adware annoying, sluggish in performance of your operating system. Ultra Adware Killer interface is quite good-looking when the functions are arranged in tabs for easy control and use. App has the ability to scan the system and detect Adware on the browsers Internet Explorer, Chrome, FireFox. All the processes, the file contains Adware or doubt are software, ads are displayed for you to conduct screening and removal.
Ultra...
</description></item><item><title>Download Robin YouTube Video Downloader Pro 6.16.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 28 Aug 2025 18:08:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-video-downloader-pro-2828.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-video-downloader-pro-2828.html
</guid><description>
YouTube Video Downloader Pro is a Windows application professional to download and convert videos from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion and thousands of video sharing sites, other. It accelerates your download up to 5 times. YouTube Video Downloader Pro allows you to download multiple videos at the same time. It also allows you to pause, resume and cancel a download at any time.
YouTube Video Downloader Pro - Download online videos on social networks
Features of YouTube Video Downloader...
</description></item><item><title>Download System Scanner 1.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 28 Aug 2025 18:08:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-system-scanner-12807.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-system-scanner-12807.html
</guid><description>
System Scanner collects and displays important information about your computer's hardware, software, and overall performance. This program allows users to dig deep into the specifications of various components, including the operating system, central processing unit (CPU), random access memory (RAM), video card, hard drive, motherboard, and more.
System Scanner provides a comprehensive overview of your hard drive by detailing essential specifications such as total capacity, amount of...
</description></item><item><title>Download DriverHub 1.3.19</title><pubDate> Thu, 28 Aug 2025 18:07:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-driverhub-6486.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-driverhub-6486.html
</guid><description>
DriverHub  is a tool that helps provide the user an efficient way to keep the drivers in the computer up to date. The driver storage facility in the cloud keeps updating the latest drivers and ensures that you always get the most relevant and latest.
DriverHub quickly scans your pc for any outdated drivers, then finds and displays the latest available drivers to install. It's important to make sure you have all the latest drivers installed, etc. on your device to keep it working...
</description></item><item><title>Download HashMyFiles 2.50</title><pubDate> Thu, 28 Aug 2025 18:02:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hashmyfiles-6991.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hashmyfiles-6991.html
</guid><description>
HashMyFiles is a small utility that allows you to calculate the MD5 and SHA1 hashes of one or more files in your system. You can easily copy the list of MD5/SHA1 hashes to the clipboard or save them to a text/html/xml file.
HashMyFiles can also be launched from the Windows Explorer context menu and displays the MD5/SHA1 hashes of the selected file or folder.
</description></item><item><title>Download Converseen 0.15.0.2-2</title><pubDate> Thu, 28 Aug 2025 18:02:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-converseen-7644.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-converseen-7644.html
</guid><description>
Converseen is a free cross-platform batch image processor for Windows and Linux that allows you to convert, resize, rotate, and flip countless images with just one click. Moreover, Converseen can convert an entire PDF file into a series of images with the characteristics you like: you can choose one of more than 100 formats, you can set the size, resolution and name file.
Conversion, thanks to ImageMagick, the powerful image manipulation library on which the program is based, can...
</description></item><item><title>Download S3 Browser Pro 12.6.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 28 Aug 2025 18:01:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-s3-browser-pro-6806.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-s3-browser-pro-6806.html
</guid><description>
S3 Browser Pro is a Windows client application for Amazon S3 and Amazon CloudFront. Amazon S3 provides a simple web service interface that can be used to store and retrieve any data, at any time, from anywhere on the web. Amazon CloudFront is a content distribution network (CDN).
Features of S3 Browser Pro
	Download and download your files in a reliable way to and from Amazon S3.
	Export your Content by Amazon S3.
	Browse, Create, Delete Amazon S3 Group.
	Share your Group with other...
</description></item></channel></rss>