<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 15:32:48 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 15:32:48 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download AutoPowerOptionsOK 6.26</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 17:44:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-autopoweroptionsok-1820.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-autopoweroptionsok-1820.html
</guid><description>
AutoPowerOptionsOK is a small program that can automatically turn off your screen, put your computer in sleep mode or switch between the power options. Each action can be triggered based on the absence of events keyboard and / or mouse for a specified time interval. For example, you can automatically turn off the screen if the mouse or keyboard has not been used in 10 minutes.
AutoPowerOptionsOK - power Management automatically
AutoPowerOptionsOK is a compact tool designed to help you...
</description></item><item><title>Download K-Lite Codec Pack Update 19.2.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 17:44:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-update-5145.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-update-5145.html
</guid><description>
K-Lite Codec Pack Update is the update of the set of codecs and related tools. Codec stands for Compressor-decompressor. Codec is necessary to encode and decode (play) audio and video. K-Lite Codec Pack Update is designed as a user-friendly solution with users to play all movie files your. With Codec Pack K-Lite, you can play 99% of all the movies found on your computer. A number of packages codec is not friendly with computers, as they tend to slow down Windows, break down multimedia...
</description></item><item><title>Download Typora 1.12.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 17:44:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-typora-6764.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-typora-6764.html
</guid><description>
Typora gives you a seamless experience as both a reader and a writer. It removes the preview window, the mode switcher, the syntax symbols of the markup source code, and all other unnecessary distractions. Instead, it provides an actual live preview to help you focus on the content itself.
Features of Typora:
	Typora allows you to manage your files easily, providing both a file tree panel and a side panel (file list).
	Automatically view the Outline structure of your document in the...
</description></item><item><title>Download WindowTop Pro 5.28.6</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 17:43:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windowtop-6955.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windowtop-6955.html
</guid><description>
WindowTop is a program that pins windows on Desktop, in other words it sets the window to float above all other program windows, creating transparency for the windows. that window via a dedicated slider, which supports adjusting transparency, changing the color of application windows or similar programs with the dark theme of the Windows 10 operating system, creating contrast and reducing tension straight, painful for the eyes.
Features of WindowTop
	Put window on top
	Set window to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Charles Web Debugging Proxy 5.0.3</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 17:42:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-charles-web-debugging-proxy-987.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-charles-web-debugging-proxy-987.html
</guid><description>
Charles Web Debugging Proxy is a software proxy the web (HTTP Proxy / HTTP Monitor) that runs on the computer to help diagnose and fix the problem Proxy. Charles will record and display for you all data is sent and received in the browser of you. In the process of web development and the Internet Charles Web Debugging Proxy will diagnose and fix the Proxy error, which you normally can't see.
Charles Web Debugging Proxy - Debugging Proxy
The features of Charles Web Debugging...
</description></item><item><title>Download PhoneRescue for iOS 4.3.1.20250920</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 17:41:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-phonerescue-for-ios-2851.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-phonerescue-for-ios-2851.html
</guid><description>
PhoneRescue for iOS is the solution to restore lost data of iOS devices such as iPhone, iPad with the ability to work quickly find back all the data on the device such as music, videos, photos, call logs, contacts, or even sms. With PhoneRescue is that you don't need to connect iPhone device with the computer directly, the software works through the index and account, now you can completely assured when using data on the iPhone, by all user's data are lost, you can restore back...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Downloader 9.17.3</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 17:41:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html
</guid><description>
YTD Youtube Downloader is an application that reliable and intuitive, allowing you to quickly download YouTube videos and save them to your computer. You can also convert the media files to the format desired video or extract audio streams and save separately. YTD Youtube Downloader lets you save your favorite clips of yourself from Youtube, Facebook, Vimeo and Dailymotion to your desktop. The software supports URLS from many web site hosting, multimedia and allows you to download desired...
</description></item><item><title>Download AllMapSoft Bing Maps Downloader 7.534</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 17:40:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-bing-maps-downloader-6063.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-bing-maps-downloader-6063.html
</guid><description>
AllMapSoft Bing Maps Downloader is a tool that can automatically download Bing Maps down your PC. It can download small squares and save them into your hard disk, including the usual map, satellite map, hybrid map. After downloading, you can view the offline map with its Viewer Maps tool, or you can combine small images into a large map image. If you want to make a map of your own city, it is very useful for you.
Features of AllMapSoft Bing Maps Downloader
	Light software and easy to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Monkeys Audio 11.53</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 17:34:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-monkeys-audio-949.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-monkeys-audio-949.html
</guid><description>
Monkey\'s Audio is software that compresses digital music without loss of quality. Supports high quality WAV files and CD ripping. Monkeys Audio will compress .wav tracks into .ape files to reduce their size without loss of sound quality, decompress .ape, convert files, check file integrity and manage tags.
Unlike traditional methods like MP3 and OGG, which permanently remove quality to save space, Monkey\'s Audio only creates perfect copies with the same sound quality as the originals....
</description></item><item><title>Download TikTok Bot Pro 3.6.5</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 17:34:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tiktok-bot-pro-11635.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tiktok-bot-pro-11635.html
</guid><description>
TikTok Bot Pro is software designed to automate activities and interactions on TikTok to attract real followers on TikTok. It automates your “likes” and “comments,” finds new followers categorized by similar accounts, and attracts followers who are actually interested in your content.
Here is a list of features you will find in this software:
	GET FOLLOWERS: Export your TikTok followers from those who follow other profiles and/or users based on specific tags.
	AUTO-FOLLOW:...
</description></item><item><title>Download Muziza YouTube Downloader Converter 8.15.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 17:34:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-muziza-youtube-downloader-converter-3972.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-muziza-youtube-downloader-converter-3972.html
</guid><description>
Muziza YouTube Downloader Converter is a tool to create conditions for an attractive interface and many features to help you to download video clips from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion, Instagram and other sites. Muziza YouTube Downloader Converter can also download the video UHD 8K, 5K, 4K, QHD 2K, HD 1080p and 720p from YouTube. The app allows you download only audio stream from YouTube and save as MP3. You don't need to download the entire video file.
Muziza YouTube Downloader...
</description></item><item><title>Download Simcore Processing Modflow X 11.0.6</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 17:33:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-simcore-processing-modflow-x-3396.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-simcore-processing-modflow-x-3396.html
</guid><description>
Simcore Processing Modflow X a comprehensive software and integrated for modeling groundwater is that by many organizations, such as organizations , lawyers, companies, and organizations and institutions of different countries used to be. With this software, you will be able to easily make all kinds of patterns on groundwater and then export your model. You can also run previous model the previous version of the software. Simcore Treatment Modflow 10 continues the success of version 10 and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Audio Modeling SWAM Solo Strings 3.10.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 17:33:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-audio-modeling-swam-solo-strings-bundle-10440.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-audio-modeling-swam-solo-strings-bundle-10440.html
</guid><description>
Audio Modeling SWAM Solo Strings Bundle is a collection of products including SWAM Violin, SWAM Viola, SWAM Cello and SWAM Double Bass. Embark on a new creative journey with our SWAM technology and expressive virtual tools. Combine that with the power of Camelot Pro and you'll find the joy of making music again. Add these innovative tools to your arsenal and experience the fresh approach to music production and performance that awaits you.
Main features:
	All-in-one virtual string...
</description></item><item><title>Download TubeMate Downloader 5.23.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 17:32:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubemate-downloader-4250.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubemate-downloader-4250.html
</guid><description>
TubeMate Downloader is a smart application that lets you download any clip you want from the website hosting the main video and convert them in when download at or then. If you need a simple and effective tool to download videos, you can give it a try. With TubeMate Downloader, you can directly drag and drop video link from your browser into the drop-down box or application window to start downloading. You don't even need to copy and paste the video URL.
TubeMate Downloader - Support...
</description></item><item><title>Download AllMapSoft OpenstreetMap Downloader 6.623</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 17:31:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-openstreetmap-downloader-4916.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-openstreetmap-downloader-4916.html
</guid><description>
AllMapSoft OpenstreetMap Downloader is a tool that can automatically download images OpenstreetMap on your PC. It can download the small cells and save them to your hard disk, including the regular classroom, transpot and cycle, opensea, etc. After downloading, you can view the map offline tool Maps Viewer or you can combine the small images into one image large map. If you want to make a map of their city, it is very useful for you.
The features of AllMapSoft OpenstreetMap...
</description></item><item><title>Download DtSearch Engine 2025.02 Build 8842 Beta</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 17:31:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dtsearch-engine-619.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dtsearch-engine-619.html
</guid><description>
DtSearch Engine is a search tool and retrieve text support on multiple platforms like windows, mac, linux. Tool dtSearch also works on the cloud platform such as Azure and AWS. dtSearch can index over a terabyte of text in a single index, spanning multiple directories, emails and attachments, online data and other databases. The products can create and search any number of indexes and can search the index during the update. Time search is indexing often less than a second, even across...
</description></item><item><title>Download DtSearch Desktop 2025.02 Build 8842 Beta</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 17:31:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dtsearch-desktop-620.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dtsearch-desktop-620.html
</guid><description>
DtSearch Desktop is software that provides the ability to search instant files can be accessed on a desktop computer. dtSearch can instantly search terabytes of text because it builds a search index storage position of the words in the document. Indexing is easy - simply select folders or entire drives to index and dtSearch does the rest. Once dtSearch has created an index, it can automatically update it using The task scheduler in Windows to reflect the addition, delete and modification...
</description></item><item><title>Download AllMapSoft Yandex Maps Downloader 5.831</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 17:30:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-yandex-maps-downloader-4915.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-yandex-maps-downloader-4915.html
</guid><description>
AllMapSoft Yandex Maps Downloader is a tool that can automatically download images Yandex Maps on your PC. It can download the small cells and save them to your hard disk, including the normal map, satellite map, hybrid map. After downloading, you can view the map offline tool map viewer or you can combine the small images into one image large map. If you want to make a map of their city, it is very useful for you.
The features of AllMapSoft Yandex Maps Downloader
	Lightweight and...
</description></item><item><title>Download 112dB Mikron Bundle 1.1.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 17:30:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-112db-mikron-bundle-10669.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-112db-mikron-bundle-10669.html
</guid><description>
112dB Mikron Bundle is a sound plugin package aimed at simplicity. It is available in VST (64-bit), AU (64-bit) and AAX (64-bit) formats.
Plugins include:
	Mikron Reverb
	Mikron Delay
	Mikron Crusher
	Mikron Cascade
	Mikron Compressor
	Mikron Phaser
	Mikron Orbiter
	Mikron Chorus
</description></item><item><title>Download Audio Modeling SWAM Solo Woodwinds 3.10.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 17:29:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-audio-modeling-swam-solo-woodwinds-bundle-10444.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-audio-modeling-swam-solo-woodwinds-bundle-10444.html
</guid><description>
Audio Modeling SWAM Solo Woodwinds Bundle is a collection of sound musical instruments including: Clarinets, Saxophones, Flutes, Double Reeds. These tools are developed using a synergistic combination of innovative performance techniques, physical modeling, behavioral modeling, and multi-vector, phase-synchronized pattern morphing.
It enables composers, musicians and performers to play - both in the recording studio and in live performances - the most realistic and expressive virtual...
</description></item><item><title>Download Multi Calculator 1.9.4 build 474</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 16:48:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-multi-calculator-9018.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-multi-calculator-9018.html
</guid><description>
A general-purpose calculator is a type of calculator that allows users to perform many types of calculations in a single application. It often includes features like basic arithmetic operations, scientific functions, unit conversions, currency conversions, etc.
Universal Calculator apps are typically available for smartphones and other mobile devices as well as for desktop computers. They can be useful for many users, including students, professionals, and anyone who needs to perform...
</description></item><item><title>Download ES File Explorer File Manager 4.4.3.3</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 16:48:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-es-file-explorer-file-manager-8150.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-es-file-explorer-file-manager-8150.html
</guid><description>
ES File Explorer File Manager is a file management application for Android devices. It allows you to manage files on your device, including documents, images, and videos, as well as manage your device's storage and memory usage. The app also includes features like a built-in media player, task killer, and support for cloud storage services like Dropbox and Google Drive.
ES File Explorer (File Manager) is a full-featured file (Pictures, Music, Movies, Documents, applications) manager for...
</description></item><item><title>Download Glitch! (glitch4ndroid) 4.5.17</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 16:47:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-glitch-glitch4ndroid-8777.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-glitch-glitch4ndroid-8777.html
</guid><description>
Quickly create your digital artwork with the best glitch photo editing app. Become a digital artist, create real and completely random glitches to add that "nerdy" touch to your photos!
	Upload your photos and edit with 26 unique effects including Pixelsort, Datamosh, JPEG|PNG|WEBP glitch.
	Export your artwork in Jpg format or record an Mp4 or GIF animation
HOW TO USE: You just need to swipe the screen multiple times to create errors in your photo.
Imperfections create uniqueness in...
</description></item><item><title>Download Device Info: System &amp;amp; CPU Info 3.4.0.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 16:47:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-device-info-system-cpu-info-8723.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-device-info-system-cpu-info-8723.html
</guid><description>
Device Information: System &amp;amp; CPU Information is a mobile application that provides users with detailed information about the hardware and software specifications of their device. This app is designed to help users better understand their device's capabilities and performance as well as diagnose any potential issues or problems.
With Device Info: System and CPU Info, users can view information about the processor, memory, storage, battery, sensors, and more. of equipment. This app...
</description></item><item><title>Download IPTV Pro 9.1.8</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 16:47:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-iptv-pro-9093.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-iptv-pro-9093.html
</guid><description>
IPTV Pro is an Android application that allows you to watch live TV channels and movies on your Android device. It provides access to many channels from around the world, including sports, news, movies, and entertainment channels. IPTV Pro supports both M3U and XSPF playlists, and allows you to add your own playlists.
IPTV Pro Features
	Supports M3U and XSPF playlists
	Playlist history
	Play a multicast stream using a UDP proxy (the proxy needs to be installed in your LAN)
	Grid, list...
</description></item></channel></rss>