<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 10:19:11 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 10:19:11 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download RustDesk 1.4.4</title><pubDate> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 01:09:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rustdesk-12244.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rustdesk-12244.html
</guid><description>
RustDesk is a full-featured open source remote alternative for self-hosting and security with minimal configuration. It allows users to access and control their computers remotely from anywhere in the world, providing a convenient solution for remote work, technical support, or accessing files and applications on the go. transfer.
RustDesk is continuously updated and improved, providing a reliable and effective remote desktop solution. Whether you work remotely, need remote technical...
</description></item><item><title>Download Google Drive (Backup and Sync) 117.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 01:09:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-drive-6751.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-drive-6751.html
</guid><description>
Using Google Drive is a great way to store your files safely in secure data centers, where your files will not be lost. Even if your computer, phone or tablet is broken, the files you store in the Google Drive are safe. Download photos, videos, documents, and other files that are important to you up to Google Drive. Continue with the memory up to 15GB. Free. Google Drive helps you access your file faster by recognizing the objects in your image and text in the scanned documents.
Easy to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Calcpad 7.5.4</title><pubDate> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 01:08:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-calcpad-12576.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-calcpad-12576.html
</guid><description>
Calcpad is free software for mathematical and engineering calculations. It is a flexible and modern programmable calculator with Html report generator. Calcpad uses a simple programming language that is fast and easy to learn. It does not require any special programming skills, which makes it suitable for engineers without any computer programming background. You can create calculation notes simply by writing your formula and text, enclosed in 'quotation marks'.
The program includes...
</description></item><item><title>Download Remote Utilities Viewer 7.7.3.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 01:05:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-remote-utilities-viewer-474.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-remote-utilities-viewer-474.html
</guid><description>
Remote Utilities Viewer is the software that controls the device is connected remotely have high configuration like TeamViewer. Remote Utilities Viewer allows you to perform the task WOL, arrange the system on the network map, control the source function basic (off / reboot), collect information, hardware and software, deploy server component in the network domain, access and edit registry entries, check running processes in the task manager remotely, view and control multiple screens at...
</description></item><item><title>Download MEmu Android Emulator 9.3.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 01:04:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-memu-2975.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-memu-2975.html
</guid><description>
MEmu or also known as Android Emulator is the Android emulator light and free, allowing Windows users to enjoy Android experience the original on the computer and device Microsoft their. This app provides outstanding performance, allowing you to play on PC a series of games designed to run on Android devices. This app allows you to play the game favorite Android on larger screens, to bring you a better gaming experience.
MEmu - Android emulator, lightweight and free
Software MEmu also...
</description></item><item><title>Download EaseUS Video Editor Pro 2.4.1 Build 20241028</title><pubDate> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 01:04:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-video-editor-4001.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-video-editor-4001.html
</guid><description>
EaseUS Video Editor is video editing software easy to use for beginners and even the expert video edit. With EaseUS Video Editor creating video effects incredible more than ever. Whether you are a weekend GoPro shooter, or a vlogger, full-time, you need video editing software powerful, but easy to do for the video professional impression. Your work is just a bit of imagination to cut, cut, split, merge, rotate, mix video clips, apply video effects, fashion, speed up / slow down the speed...
</description></item><item><title>Download iDownerGo 10.9.3</title><pubDate> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 01:03:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idownergo-12439.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idownergo-12439.html
</guid><description>
iDownerGo is the best tool that allows users to download videos, music and playlists from more than 10,000 streaming sites. It can easily convert videos to MP4, MOV, MKV, 3GP, AAC, WAV, FLAC and other formats on PC and Mac. With this amazing program, users can enjoy their favorite media content without restrictions.
iDownerGo Features
	Download any video up to 8K resolution
	Download 1080p videos online from over 10,000 popular streaming sites easily.
	Save any video in various...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Substance 3D Painter 11.1.0 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 01:03:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-substance-painter-1279.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-substance-painter-1279.html
</guid><description>
Substance Painter is a drawing application 3D completely new with the possibility of unprecedented and workflow is optimized, help in creating graphics easier than ever. To create sprites or 3D characters, no need to have knowledge about a painters professional animation, now it has become easy and accessible for the average user . The program is recognized in the world is creative tool and the most convenient to draw 3D create character models.
Substance Painter - App 3D drawing
The...
</description></item><item><title>Download iTubeGo YouTube Downloader 10.9.3</title><pubDate> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 01:02:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-itubego-youtube-downloader-3681.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-itubego-youtube-downloader-3681.html
</guid><description>
iTubeGo YouTube Downloader  is the best way to download live video from 1000+ streaming sites. iTubeGo YouTube Downloader is a powerful download tool that allows you to save video and audio for free. The output format of high speed converter is high quality MP4, MP3. Fully compatible with iPhone, iPad, iTunes, iMovie, Android Phone and more.
iTubeGo YouTube Downloader - Solution for downloading high quality Youtube video 
Features of iTubeGo YouTube Downloader
	Download videos from...
</description></item><item><title>Download MaxCut Business Edition 2.9.6</title><pubDate> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 01:02:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-maxcut-business-edition-3912.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-maxcut-business-edition-3912.html
</guid><description>
MaxCut Business Edition is a software to create cutting diagrams, accurate, and cost estimate for the wood industry, cabinets and metal,.. You enter the size and material, MaxCut will do the rest! Produce optimized cutting diagrams, create estimates, orders, and labels - it's just a click. Run the application MaxCut Business Edition brings a pretty clean interface and slick quickly get you up and running. Most space represents the editing area, with the main function are stored cleverly in...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinSCP 6.5.5</title><pubDate> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 00:55:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winscp-371.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winscp-371.html
</guid><description>
WinSCP is the software supports uploading data to Server high speed, or download to your computer quickly and safely.  SCP (Secure CoPy) uses SSH (Secure Shell). Its main purpose is safe copying files between local computer and remote. In addition to this basic function, WinSCP manages a number of other actions with the file.
Besides, WinSCP can transfer multiple data files simultaneously with high speed to save time and effort for the user. All data is transmitted on the Server are...
</description></item><item><title>Download Red Gate SmartAssembly Professional 8.4.0.6650</title><pubDate> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 00:55:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-red-gate-smartassembly-1593.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-red-gate-smartassembly-1593.html
</guid><description>
Red Gate SmartAssembly is a tool that helps protect your application against reverse engineering or modifications prevent side Tuesday access to source code. This comprehensive solution protects the data card of you and more likely to report errors. This program makes files difficult can disassemble and injection code does not use, to help engineer can reverse and understand the core structure of the code. With your smartphone, you will have many features to tamper with the code as the...
</description></item><item><title>Download ProtonVPN 4.3.5</title><pubDate> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 00:54:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-protonvpn-10433.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-protonvpn-10433.html
</guid><description>
ProtonVPN app for Windows is the best way to stay safe and private while surfing the internet. It is open source, easy to use, and packed with useful security features. ProtonVPN will secure your connection by routing your traffic through multiple servers to protect you against advanced network-based attacks.
It helps keep your IP address safe if something goes wrong with your VPN connection. If your VPN connection fails, the kill switch feature will prevent your device from connecting...
</description></item><item><title>Download FxSound (FxSound Enhancer Premium) 1.2.3 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 00:54:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fxsound-enhancer-premium-2013.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fxsound-enhancer-premium-2013.html
</guid><description>
FxSound Enhancer Premium formerly DFX Audio Enhance, is accessories multimedia software most popular in the world with over 46 million downloads worldwide. FxSound enhances the sound of most of the music content and online video is live streaming on the Web, including the streaming service, YouTube, Pandora, Spotify and Apple Music. FxSound Enhancer Premium also implemented enhanced real-time audio on the player PC multimedia most popular include iTunes, Windows Media Player, Winamp and...
</description></item><item><title>Download MyLanViewer Enterprise 6.7</title><pubDate> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 00:50:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mylanviewer-enterprise-1274.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mylanviewer-enterprise-1274.html
</guid><description>
MyLanViewer is a program for scanning IP address, Netbios and LAN / Network powerful for Windows tool whois and traceroute, remote shutdown and process management Wake On LAN (WOL), scan and monitor wireless networks. This app will help you find all IP addresses, MAC addresses and shared folders of computers on the network wired or wireless (Wi-Fi).
MyLanViewer Enterprise - Scan IP address LAN/Network
The program scans network and displays the computer network in your window, friends...
</description></item><item><title>Download PPTube 10.9.3</title><pubDate> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 00:49:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pptube-12556.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pptube-12556.html
</guid><description>
PPTube Video Downloader allows you to download HD videos easily, from 720p, 1080p, 2K, 4K and 8K. You can save multiple videos at the same time. Just copy multiple video URLs from various websites and paste them into PPTube Downloader, then you can download multiple videos in seconds.
In addition, you can download HD videos from Instagram, TikTok, Facebook, Apple Music, Vimeo, adult websites, etc. and convert them to MP4, MP3, MOV, AAC and more than 20 other output formats. PPTube...
</description></item><item><title>Download DBF Converter 7.68</title><pubDate> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 00:49:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbf-converter-6362.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbf-converter-6362.html
</guid><description>
DBF Converter is a common solution for all your DBF format conversion needs. Whenever you need to extract data from the DBF file to CSV, XLS, XLSX, SQL or pure text, the software will provide a simple way to do this with minimal effort.
Features of DBF Converter
	Work with DBF Converter is easy. You specify a DBF file or a directory with DBF files that you want to convert, select the fields and filter out the records you need. Then, just a click to DBF Converter to turn the source...
</description></item><item><title>Download Atlantis Word Processor 5.0.0.10</title><pubDate> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 00:42:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-atlantis-word-processor-585.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-atlantis-word-processor-585.html
</guid><description>
Atlantis Word Processor is a word processor app with features format, standard text, autocorrect, and spell check.  Atlantis is a word processor in accordance with most of the tasks handled daily text. The interface is very easy to use and offers the toolbars, hotkeys and sound effects thanh can customize (can turn off). It includes a clip library for quick access to the text or images used regular preview, font format and many other features aimed at improving the process of your...
</description></item><item><title>Download Coder Technologies Coder 2.27.6</title><pubDate> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 00:37:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coder-oss-enterprise-8726.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coder-oss-enterprise-8726.html
</guid><description>
Coder OSS Enterprise is a development platform that provides a complete cloud-based solution for software development, testing and deployment. It is designed to simplify the software development process by providing developers with a collaborative and streamlined environment.
Coder offloads development from local workstations to your on-premises infrastructure and public cloud. Boost developer productivity with powerful server resources and instant integration. Keep the code and data...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Saver Pro 10.9.3</title><pubDate> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 00:36:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-saver-6830.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-saver-6830.html
</guid><description>
YT Saver is a software that supports downloading Video, Audio, Playlist from 10,000+ websites, Convert Video to MP4, MOV, AAC, WAV and more. YT Saver is a powerful downloader that allows you to save video and audio for free. The output format of the high-speed converter is high-quality MP4, MP3. Fully compatible with iPhone, iPad, iTunes, iMovie, Android Phone and more.
Supported Input Formats:
	Video: MP4, M4V, 3GP, MPEG, DAT, AVI, ASF, WMV, VOB, MKV, FLV, 3GS, 3G2, F4V, WEBM, TS,...
</description></item><item><title>Download LINQPad Premium 8.9.5</title><pubDate> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 00:36:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-linqpad-premium-7181.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-linqpad-premium-7181.html
</guid><description>
LINQPad is a software utility targeting .NET Framework and .NET Core development. It is used to interactively query SQL databases using LINQ, as well as to write C# code interactively without an IDE. LINQPad will be where C# code can be rapidly prototyped outside of Visual Studio. It can also be used to code in VB.NET, SQL and F#.
With LINQPad, you can interactively query databases using a modern query language: LINQ. LINQPad includes a tool optimized for on-the-fly context creation of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft PowerToys for Windows 10/11 0.96.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 20 Nov 2025 00:35:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-powertoys-for-windows-6014.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-powertoys-for-windows-6014.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft PowerToys is a user-proficiency set to adjust and streamline their Windows experience for higher productivity. Inspired by Windows 95's PowerToys project, this reboot provides users with proficiency in ways to exploit the more efficient Windows 10 and customisable processes it provides for each work process.
Utility of Microsoft PowerToys
	FancyZones is a window manager that allows you to easily create complex windows layout and quickly locate windows in those layout.
	Image...
</description></item><item><title>Download Topaz Photo Pro 1.0.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 22:05:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-photo-ai-8105.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-photo-ai-8105.html
</guid><description>
What is Topaz Photo AI?
Topaz Photo AI is a professional software that automatically adjusts for your image quality needs. Simply import images into Topaz Photo AI and it will use specially trained AI models to first detect unique details, clarity, and resolution issues before applying the intelligently adjusts to maximize your image quality.
For users experienced with Topaz Labs image quality applications, it combines the functionality of DeNoise AI, Sharpen AI and Gigapixel AI into...
</description></item><item><title>Download Typemock Isolator Complete 9.3.8.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 22:00:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-typemock-isolator-complete-14300.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-typemock-isolator-complete-14300.html
</guid><description>
Typemock Isolator Complete is a comprehensive unit testing and mocking solution for .NET developers. It allows you to mock anything needed for testing, including static methods, private methods, constructors, events, LINQ, reference arguments, and even static constructors. It can mock the entire object model with just one command and supports testing legacy code without code changes.
The product integrates real-time code coverage, displaying coverage instantly in the editor as you write...
</description></item><item><title>Download SysTools Outlook Deleted Items Recovery 4.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 19 Nov 2025 21:53:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-systools-outlook-deleted-items-recovery-14299.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-systools-outlook-deleted-items-recovery-14299.html
</guid><description>
SysTools Outlook Deleted Items Recovery is a dedicated software tool designed to recover permanently deleted items from Outlook data files, including OST, PST, and BAK formats. The software uses RAW scanning mode to perform bit-by-bit scanning of Outlook files, which helps to effectively recover deleted emails, contacts, calendars, tasks, notes, journals, and distribution lists, even if they have been hard-deleted. The software displays deleted items in red for easy identification and...
</description></item></channel></rss>