<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 23:31:50 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 23:31:50 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download iCare SD Memory Card Recovery 4.0.1.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Sep 2025 02:31:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-icare-sd-memory-card-recovery-5894.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-icare-sd-memory-card-recovery-5894.html
</guid><description>
You can easily lose the file on multiple storage devices and it ' s absolutely not your fault. The drives may be corrupted or items may have been deleted due to confusion. Regardless of the case, iCare SD Memory Card Recovery can help you recover them from the USB flash drive and the broken SD memory card. After a scan operation, the application will display an organized set of navigation. On one side, you find a list of folders to navigate comfortably, while the second table is where...
</description></item><item><title>Download Viber for PC 26.3.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Sep 2025 02:26:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-viber-2406.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-viber-2406.html
</guid><description>
Viber is a software of instant messaging, based on VoIP protocols, multi-platform due to the Viber Media development for smart phones used to send sms and make calls over the internet. Along with text messaging, users can exchange images, video and audio.
Viber - software news message, chat online
This is a program that is quite popular is mainly designed for mobile phones, but now we are talking about the version for Windows, so immediately. It will allow you to send messages to other...
</description></item><item><title>Download FotoJet Collage Maker 1.3.7</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Sep 2025 02:25:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fotojet-collage-maker-8003.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fotojet-collage-maker-8003.html
</guid><description>
FotoJet Collage Maker is a FotoJet collage maker that has 800+ stunning collage layouts and templates, including birthday collages, wedding collages, baby collages, family collages, love collages, and more, all designed to help you create online collages quickly and easily.
Thanks to FotoJet Collage Maker, everyone can become a professional designer delivering impressive results with this powerful graphic design tool! Whenever you feel inspired, you can always create amazing designs...
</description></item><item><title>Download FotoJet Designer 1.4.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Sep 2025 02:25:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fotojet-designer-568.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fotojet-designer-568.html
</guid><description>
FotoJet Designer is an enterprise software design, brand design, logo with easy visual effects without losing costs. If it is about the design of Banner, the most professional logo is probably one of the most likely to mention Adobe Photoshop-One of the top software currently. But the use of Adobe Photoshop is very difficult for new people. Therefore, the choice of FotoJet Designer is the optimal solution for you.
With FotoJet Designer, you can absolutely design the logo, banner,...
</description></item><item><title>Download FTPie Pro 2025.9.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Sep 2025 02:24:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ftpie-pro-12319.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ftpie-pro-12319.html
</guid><description>
FTPie Pro is a powerful FTP and Cloud application that integrates seamlessly with Google Docs and Microsoft 365 Apps. This program will integrate seamlessly with Google Docs and Microsoft 365 applications, support many different cloud storage services, making file management on different platforms easy.
Features of FTPie Pro
	File Transfer: Easily transfer, upload and manage files between your PC, cloud storage and FTP
	Embedded app: Manage files easily with FTPie's built-in viewer...
</description></item><item><title>Download Revo Registry Cleaner Free 2.0.0 + Portable</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Sep 2025 02:24:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-revo-registry-cleaner-free-12717.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-revo-registry-cleaner-free-12717.html
</guid><description>
Revo Registry Cleaner Free is a powerful tool designed to clean, tune and optimize the Windows Registry. Explore the powerful Registry Cleaner with over 15 scanning categories to find and remove invalid and unnecessary Registry entries. Customize your cleaning routine with custom key inclusions/exclusions and 4 different deep scan modes.
In addition, it also supports custom backups for user-specified keys as well as full Registry backups providing peace of mind as they ensure the safety...
</description></item><item><title>Download CopyQ 12.0.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Sep 2025 02:23:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-copyq-1368.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-copyq-1368.html
</guid><description>
CopyQ is software clipboard manager for windows that helps you easily copy, save, text, clipboard. CopyQ absolutely free on taiwebs.com it allows you to save more than one default entry to the clipboard is limited to Windows. Each time you copy or cut something, it will be saved to the clipboard expansion of CopyQ , both files and text can all be saved.
CopyQ - clipboard Manager
Features of CopyQ
	Support for Linux, Windows and OS X 10.9+
	Store text, HTML, image or any customized...
</description></item><item><title>Download SysTools DBX to PST Converter 8.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Sep 2025 02:23:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-systools-dbx-to-pst-converter-8286.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-systools-dbx-to-pst-converter-8286.html
</guid><description>
SysTools DBX to PST Converter is a software tool that allows users to convert DBX (Outlook Express) files to PST (Microsoft Outlook) format. This can be useful for individuals or organizations that need to access their email data from a damaged or corrupted Outlook Express installation, or for those who want to import their email data into Microsoft Outlook. The software can convert multiple DBX files into a single PST file, or it can create a separate PST for each DBX file. It also...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sinevibes Complete Effects Bundle 2025.9</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Sep 2025 02:22:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sinevibes-collection-7149.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sinevibes-collection-7149.html
</guid><description>
Explore Sinevibes' innovative music technologies with their unique audio effects. Get seven of Sinevibes' powerful effects Albedo, Blend v2, Corrosion v2, Droplet v2, Dipole v2, Dispersion v2, Eternal v2, Luminance v2 and Whirl v2 in a single bundle.
Sinevibes Collection 2024 included:
	Albedo: v1.1.2
	Blend v2: v2.1.3
	Corrosion v2: v2.0.3
	Dipole v2: v2.1.1
	Dispersion v2: v2.0.2
	Droplet v2: v2.0.3
	Eternal v2: v2.1.0
	Hollow: v1.0.1
	Integer: v1.0.0
	Luminance v2: v2.1.0
	Rerun...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft Teams 1.8.00.26073</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Sep 2025 02:21:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-teams-6904.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-teams-6904.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft Teams is a system that provides chat, meetings, notes and attachments. Whether you're working with teammates on a project or planning a weekend away with loved ones, Microsoft Teams helps bring people together so they can get things done. It's the only app that has chats, meetings, files, tasks, and calendars in one place, so you can easily connect with people and make plans come true.
Features of Microsoft Teams:
	Meeting safely with teammates, family, and friends.
	Live...
</description></item><item><title>Download Universal Media Server 15.0.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Sep 2025 02:21:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-universal-media-server-2364.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-universal-media-server-2364.html
</guid><description>
Universal Media Server is a media server UPnP compatible multi-platform DLNA. The purpose of this software is to give you a chance to stabilize to make the exchange quick and convenient files necessary. Server the device supports the different output and facilitate the process of exchanging information between a computer and necessary equipment. The development is based on PS3 Media Server, which means you can interact with the Playstation 3, Xbox 360, as well as TV Samsung or...
</description></item><item><title>Download dbForge Studio for Oracle Enterprise 2025.2.37</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Sep 2025 02:20:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbforge-studio-for-oracle-enterprise-14049.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbforge-studio-for-oracle-enterprise-14049.html
</guid><description>
dbForge Studio for Oracle is a trusted integrated development environment (IDE) for Oracle SQL developers. This database solution speeds up PL/SQL coding, synchronizes data between different Oracle servers, and automates the process of managing schema changes during development. The solution is equipped with a graphical user interface (GUI) and versatile data editing tools, making it easy to manage both internal and external data.
Key features of the studio include a PL/SQL coding...
</description></item><item><title>Download Browser History Examiner 1.22.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Sep 2025 02:20:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-browser-history-examiner-6402.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-browser-history-examiner-6402.html
</guid><description>
Browser History Examiner is a forensic software tool for collecting, extracts and analyzing internet history from the main web browsers on desktop computers. Many types of data can be analyzed including web page access, search, downloads, and files stored in the cache.
Features of Browser History Examiner
	The web page visit is displayed along with the interactive graph that indicates the number of sites that have been accessed within a specific time period. This is very useful to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Dup Scout Ultimate 17.3.12 + Enterprise + Pro</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Sep 2025 02:19:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dup-scout-ultimate-1460.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dup-scout-ultimate-1460.html
</guid><description>
Dup Scout Ultimate is professional software with the aim of helping you detect files duplicate is stored in your computer and delete them to free some space on disk. Management utility this file can clean up the file to duplicate from disc, folder, network share or storage device NAS.
Dup Scout Ultimate - Find and delete file duplicate
Dup Scout Ultimate offers you the ability to build a new profile by specifying the name and select the folder or network share, all hard disks, servers...
</description></item><item><title>Download VirtualDJ Home 2025 Build 8752</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Sep 2025 02:19:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-virtual-dj-home-4801.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-virtual-dj-home-4801.html
</guid><description>
Virtual DJ Home is software compiled and mix of tracks with many music formats various. It has the features as there are 2 installation mode for the program is automatically or manually transformed the structure of music has to arrange after the claim theft of Remix music, record your mixes, burn a CD, rip DVD, vinyl rip, create radio on the Internet.
Although VirtualDJ is integrated with many features but still very easy to learn. You can start with the basics and advance as you learn...
</description></item><item><title>Download Vovsoft Auto Change Screensavers 2.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Sep 2025 02:19:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-auto-change-screensavers-2784.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-auto-change-screensavers-2784.html
</guid><description>
Vovsoft Auto Change Screensavers is a tool to the desktop mini will change the screen saver of you. App Auto Change Screensavers allows you to automatically change the screen saver of his. Have you installed more screensavers interesting? Sometimes people spend a lot of time trying to choose which one to make default. Manager this screensaver solves that problem.
Now you can have all your savers run on your screen and this does not need to adjust the Windows settings every time you want...
</description></item><item><title>Download SAPIEN PowerShell Studio 2025 v5.9.260</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Sep 2025 02:18:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sapien-powershell-studio-7201.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sapien-powershell-studio-7201.html
</guid><description>
PowerShell Studio is the premier editing and tooling environment for PowerShell. Create graphical tools using PowerShell with an easy-to-use GUI designer. Eliminates the need to manually write hundreds of lines of code. Use PowerShell Studio's built-in templates and wired controls to create advanced GUIs quickly. Create a PowerShell script module in minutes with PowerShell Studio. Easily convert your existing functions into a deliverable module. PowerShell Studio has a powerful editor...
</description></item><item><title>Download LibreWolf 143.0.1-1</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Sep 2025 02:18:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-librewolf-11967.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-librewolf-11967.html
</guid><description>
LibreWolf is a customized and independent version of Firefox, with the main goals being user privacy, security and freedom. LibreWolf is designed to provide increased protection against tracking and fingerprinting techniques and includes a number of security enhancements. This is achieved through our security and privacy oriented settings and patches. LibreWolf also aims to remove all telemetry, data collection and annoyances, as well as disable anti-free features like DRM.
LibreWolf...
</description></item><item><title>Download Voxeldance Additive 5.1.2.25</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Sep 2025 23:30:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-voxeldance-additive-14185.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-voxeldance-additive-14185.html
</guid><description>
VoxelDance Additive is a powerful 3D print preparation software designed for common 3D printing applications such as prototyping, shoe molds, and plastic/metal printing. The software offers advanced features including importing and repairing multiple CAD file formats and meshes, orientation optimization, model editing, support creation (including smart supports and multiple support types), mesh structure optimization, slicing tools, and analysis tools.
Voxeldance Additive includes all the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Visual C++ Redistributable Runtimes AIO Repack 0.101.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Sep 2025 19:01:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-visual-c-redistributable-runtimes-aio-repack-7825.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-visual-c-redistributable-runtimes-aio-repack-7825.html
</guid><description>
Visual C++ Redistributable Runtimes AIO Repack is a setup package that includes all the latest Microsoft Visual C++ Redistribution Runtimes without the initial setup payload.
	Built on VBCRedis_AIO_x86_x64.exe
	This process is handled by a command set of windows command, which runs hidden in the background by default.
	Before installation, the script will check and remove the existing Visual C + + runtime settings, including the original EXE or MSI setup or the older MSI package...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft Visual C++ 2015-2022 Redistributable 14.50.35615</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Sep 2025 18:57:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-visual-c-4856.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-visual-c-4856.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft Visual C++ Redistributable Package contains the component run-time libraries of Visual C ++ required to run the application on a PC without installed Visual C ++. Microsoft Visual C++ or also known as MSVC development environment integrated (IDE) for the programming language C, C++, at the same time integrated tools for developing and debugging C++ source code. Microsoft Visual C++ supports the function of automatic completion of the coding and the debugging function...
</description></item><item><title>Download Glary Utilities Pro 6.32.0.36</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Sep 2025 18:57:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-utilities-pro-76.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-utilities-pro-76.html
</guid><description>
Glary Utilities Pro is a collection of tools and system utilities to fix, speed up, maintain and protect your computer. Glary Utilities Pro allows you to clean junk files, system downloads, as well as the subscriptions are not valid and Internet traces (that support the plug-in more for the 45+ program outside). You can also manage and delete add-ons of the browser, analyze the use of disk and find the file duplicate.
Glary Utilities Pro - optimized system
Key features Glary Utilities...
</description></item><item><title>Download Topaz Video AI Pro 7.1.6 / 1.0.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Sep 2025 18:56:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-video-enhance-ai-3733.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-video-enhance-ai-3733.html
</guid><description>
Topaz Video Enhance AI is a tool to increase video quality with this great technology ONE. Topaz Video Enhance WHO wide open your video to resolutions up to 8K with the details and consistency of motion. Until the present, there is no way to re-create a perfect high resolution video from the footage is low resolution. From the family film to SD low quality to DVD quality and more than that, Video Enhance WHO will convert your video into the footage is upgrade clear with resolutions up to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ant Download Manager Pro 2.15.11 Build 91423</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Sep 2025 18:55:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ant-download-manager-pro-137.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ant-download-manager-pro-137.html
</guid><description>
Ant Download Manager Pro is software support download has the same features as IDM, even it has many prominent features, more user friendly more and have speed download data incredible. Ant Download Manager is a Internet content downloader quickly with support download at video! Function: fully Integrated with the web browsers most popular: Internet Explorer 8+, Mozilla Firefox 32 +, Google Chrome 31+ and the copies of them (Pale Moon, Opera, Vivaldi, Slimjet, ComodoDragon, etc.). you...
</description></item><item><title>Download UPDF 2.0.9.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Sep 2025 18:54:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-updf-14160.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-updf-14160.html
</guid><description>
UPDF for Windows is easy-to-use PDF software for Windows! Enjoy powerful editing tools for text, images, links, and more in your PDFs. Customize backgrounds, watermarks, and page sizes as easily as in Word. AI-powered PDF editor and manager that offers a wide range of features including editing, annotating, converting, OCR (Optical Character Recognition), organizing, protecting, sharing, printing, summarizing, translating, and interpreting PDF files.
Features of UPDF
Analyze PDFs with...
</description></item></channel></rss>