<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 09:25:01 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 09:25:01 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Intel Graphics Driver for Windows 10 / 11 32.0.101.7026</title><pubDate> Sun, 24 Aug 2025 00:01:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intel-graphics-driver-for-windows-10-5954.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intel-graphics-driver-for-windows-10-5954.html
</guid><description>
Intel Graphics Driver for Windows 10 supports Intel ' s latest 8th-generation Core processor, introducing the Intel ® UHD graphics, with the ability to immerve in the top 4K UHD entertainment from your laptop for a maximum of 10 hours. Along with some security fixes, this driver also optimised the system's inactivity to reduce power consumption.
Look at the complete new interface of gameplay.intel.com, where you will find the proposed game settings for many of your favorite PC games....
</description></item><item><title>Download Universal Media Server 14.13.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 23 Aug 2025 23:54:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-universal-media-server-2364.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-universal-media-server-2364.html
</guid><description>
Universal Media Server is a media server UPnP compatible multi-platform DLNA. The purpose of this software is to give you a chance to stabilize to make the exchange quick and convenient files necessary. Server the device supports the different output and facilitate the process of exchanging information between a computer and necessary equipment. The development is based on PS3 Media Server, which means you can interact with the Playstation 3, Xbox 360, as well as TV Samsung or...
</description></item><item><title>Download Windows XP Professional SP3 x86 Integral Edition August 2025</title><pubDate> Sat, 23 Aug 2025 23:52:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-xp-professional-4484.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-xp-professional-4484.html
</guid><description>
Windows XP Professional SP3 x86 Integral April 2020 based on the images original English with automatic installation and updates and latest patches for Windows XP and POSReady 2009 until January 4, 2020. Includes more than 350 MB drivers, LAN, WLAN, Chipset, SATA / AHCI and NVMe. Windows XP Professional goes beyond the benefits of XP Home Edition with advanced capabilities designed specifically to optimize productivity using the latest advancements in the digital world. Built on the solid...
</description></item><item><title>Download Agisoft Metashape Professional 2.2.2 Build 21026</title><pubDate> Sat, 23 Aug 2025 23:46:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-agisoft-metashape-professional-1731.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-agisoft-metashape-professional-1731.html
</guid><description>
Agisoft Metashape (formerly PhotoScan) is a software product independently perform image processing and digital data creation, 3D space used in GIS applications, material cultural heritage and the production visual effects as well as the indirect measurement of the different subjects scale. Technical digital photography is deployed wisely is applied with the method of computer vision led to the system processor, smart auto, on the one hand, can be managed by a new person in the field of...
</description></item><item><title>Download BitComet 2.16</title><pubDate> Sat, 23 Aug 2025 23:45:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bitcomet-1220.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bitcomet-1220.html
</guid><description>
BitComet is the program that supports the download of torrent files quickly supports multiple security protocols and modern interface. BitComet is free software file-sharing p2p fully compatible with Bittorrent, this is one of the p2p protocols the most popular is designed for high-speed distribution of files with size 100MB or GB. BitComet is a bittorrent client powerful, clean, fast and easy to use. It support to download at the same time, download queue, downloads the selected in...
</description></item><item><title>Download Calcpad 7.3.4</title><pubDate> Sat, 23 Aug 2025 23:45:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-calcpad-12576.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-calcpad-12576.html
</guid><description>
Calcpad is free software for mathematical and engineering calculations. It is a flexible and modern programmable calculator with Html report generator. Calcpad uses a simple programming language that is fast and easy to learn. It does not require any special programming skills, which makes it suitable for engineers without any computer programming background. You can create calculation notes simply by writing your formula and text, enclosed in 'quotation marks'.
The program includes...
</description></item><item><title>Download MusConv Ultimate 4.10.409</title><pubDate> Sat, 23 Aug 2025 23:44:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html
</guid><description>
MusConv transfers playlists, albums, followed artists and liked songs across a variety of services – Spotify, Apple Music, Amazon Music, YouTube, YouTube Music, iTunes, Deezer, Tidal, SoundCloud, Pandora and more 125 music services!
Features of MusConv Ultimate
	Transfer playlists, albums, followed artists and liked tracks between over 125 music servicesManage playlists (Delete, Merge, Split, Copy...)
	More than 125 music services supported
	Access DAILY updated music charts on...
</description></item><item><title>Download Pepakura Designer 6.1.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 23 Aug 2025 23:44:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pepakura-designer-748.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pepakura-designer-748.html
</guid><description>
Pepakura Designer is software to create 2D models, 3D quick, easy and developed in Japan. Pepakura Designer helps easily design the template paper craft by importing data 3D model. No special knowledge is required to model papercraft. All you have to do is prepare the 3D model. You can use some software 3DCG released from other developers to make the 3D models for unfolding.
Pepakura Designer - Create model 2D 3D
Pepakura Designer to create the form of 2D images that you can share it...
</description></item><item><title>Download SystemRescueCd 12.02</title><pubDate> Sat, 23 Aug 2025 23:43:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-systemrescuecd-3452.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-systemrescuecd-3452.html
</guid><description>
SystemRescueCd is a Linux system on CD-ROM can boot to repair your system or recover your information after a crash. SystemRescueCd aims to provide a simple way to perform the action administrator on your PC, such as creating and editing the partitions of the hard drive. It includes many system tools (partimage, parted, fstools) and basic options (commander midnight, editors, network tools). It is very simple to use: just boot the CDROM. Staff handle most of the system files needed (ext2 /...
</description></item><item><title>Download Centurion Setup 49.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 23 Aug 2025 23:43:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-centurion-setup-4401.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-centurion-setup-4401.html
</guid><description>
Centurion Setup is a comprehensive app and easy to use, helps you quickly create the installation software for their products in an executable file are compressed, self-contained. The application installer is contained in a file single executable. This way, your customers will be able to easily download and install the product of your software without having to use additional tools, such as WinZip, to unzip the installation package.
Centurion Setup - Create a file installed
Centurion...
</description></item><item><title>Download FFmpeg 8.0-2025-08-22</title><pubDate> Sat, 23 Aug 2025 23:42:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ffmpeg-6232.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ffmpeg-6232.html
</guid><description>
FFmpeg is an open and open-source software project, consisting of a large set of libraries and programs for handling videos, sounds as well as files and multimedia streams. It is a free software consisting of a giant suite of libraries and programs for video processing, audio, multimedia files and streams. Its core is the FFmpeg program itself, which is designed to handle videos and audio based on the command line and is widely used for switching formats, basic editing (cutting and...
</description></item><item><title>Download ES File Explorer File Manager 4.4.3.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 23 Aug 2025 23:17:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-es-file-explorer-file-manager-8150.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-es-file-explorer-file-manager-8150.html
</guid><description>
ES File Explorer File Manager is a file management application for Android devices. It allows you to manage files on your device, including documents, images, and videos, as well as manage your device's storage and memory usage. The app also includes features like a built-in media player, task killer, and support for cloud storage services like Dropbox and Google Drive.
ES File Explorer (File Manager) is a full-featured file (Pictures, Music, Movies, Documents, applications) manager for...
</description></item><item><title>Download MobiPDF: PDF Editor &amp;amp; Scanner 11.8.267277</title><pubDate> Sat, 23 Aug 2025 23:17:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pdf-extra-scan-edit-sign-8390.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pdf-extra-scan-edit-sign-8390.html
</guid><description>
PDF Extra PDF Editor &amp;amp; Scanner is a mobile application that allows users to create, edit and sign PDF documents on their Android or iOS devices. It includes many tools and features that make it easy to work with PDF files, including scanning, editing, and signing. This application also allows users to combine multiple PDF files into a single document and export PDF files in various file formats, such as JPEG, PNG, and Microsoft Word.
Features of PDF Extra PDF Editor &amp;amp;...
</description></item><item><title>Download Document Scanner - PDF Creator 6.8.16</title><pubDate> Sat, 23 Aug 2025 23:16:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-document-scanner-pdf-creator-9783.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-document-scanner-pdf-creator-9783.html
</guid><description>
Sometimes in a day, you need to scan your different documents multiple times. In that situation, if everything is planned, you will definitely not have to suffer any more. But if the need to scan those documents arises one by one, it will definitely be a disaster. To rescue you from that situation CV Infotech brings you a mobile Doc Scanner. This document scanner allows you to scan your documents anytime, anywhere.
The application also has some additional features that help your scanned...
</description></item><item><title>Download ScanWritr Pro: docs, scan, fax 3.2.17</title><pubDate> Sat, 23 Aug 2025 23:16:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-scanwritr-pro-docs-scan-fax-12143.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-scanwritr-pro-docs-scan-fax-12143.html
</guid><description>
ScanWritr is perfect for business, educational and home purposes. It turns your Android device with camera into an all-in-one scanner, document editor and storage tool, suitable for scanning, organizing, editing, printing, faxing, emailing, synchronizing with the cloud, share and export various documents such as contracts, articles, business cards, notes, receipts, warranties, and more. Image capture is done with the help of Real-time Edge Detection (auto-crop).
This scanner app also...
</description></item><item><title>Download Reverso Translate and Learn 14.5.0 build 12000057</title><pubDate> Sat, 23 Aug 2025 23:16:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-reverso-translate-and-learn-8356.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-reverso-translate-and-learn-8356.html
</guid><description>
Reverso is a comprehensive tool that helps you get high-quality translations and continuously improve your language skills. The best part about the Reverso app? It is available for free. Teachers or translators, students or business professionals, beginners or advanced learners use Reverso to enrich their vocabulary and read, write and speak more accurately and confidently.
Download the Reverso app and you'll have millions of words and expressions at your fingertips, with their...
</description></item><item><title>Download All PDF Editor &amp;amp; Reader | Xodo 10.5.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 23 Aug 2025 23:15:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-xodo-pdf-reader-editor-8451.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-xodo-pdf-reader-editor-8451.html
</guid><description>
Xodo PDF Reader &amp;amp; Editor is a mobile application for reading and editing PDF documents on Android and iOS devices. The app allows users to view, annotate, and edit PDF files using a variety of tools, including highlighting, underlining, and adding notes. With Xodo, you can read, annotate, sign, and share PDFs and fill out PDF forms, all while syncing with Google Drive, Dropbox, and OneDrive.
Xodo PDF Reader &amp;amp; Editor Features
	PDF Viewer: Application that allows users to view...
</description></item><item><title>Download Lightroom Photo &amp;amp; Video Editor 10.5.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 23 Aug 2025 23:15:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-adobe-lightroom-photo-video-editor-8401.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-adobe-lightroom-photo-video-editor-8401.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Photoshop Lightroom is a powerful, free camera app and photo editor that empowers your photography, helping you capture and edit stunning images. Easy image editing tools like sliders and filters simplify photo editing. Edit full-resolution photos, apply photo filters, or start editing photos anytime, anywhere.
It offers a variety of editing tools, including basic adjustments like cropping, rotation, and brightness control as well as advanced features like color grading, selective...
</description></item><item><title>Download Duolingo: language lessons 6.44.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 23 Aug 2025 23:15:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-duolingo-language-lessons-8265.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-duolingo-language-lessons-8265.html
</guid><description>
Duolingo is a popular language learning app that offers interactive lessons to help users learn new languages. This application offers many languages for you to choose from, including Spanish, French, German, Italian, Portuguese, Chinese, Japanese and many more.
This app offers an gamified learning experience with interactive lessons, exercises, and quizzes designed to help users learn new words, phrases, and grammar rules. This app is designed to be easy to use and suitable for people...
</description></item><item><title>Download Speak &amp;amp; Translate all Language 4.6</title><pubDate> Sat, 23 Aug 2025 23:14:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-speak-translate-all-language-13181.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-speak-translate-all-language-13181.html
</guid><description>
Speak &amp;amp; translate provides both voice and text translator features, just speak and it will translate your voice into the desired language and the same goes for text. It is based on real conversation translator where two people can translate their voice and text into different languages, it works like a real conversation between two people which makes it easier while translating. Voice to voice translator helps to translate the speech of both people into desired languages ​​and it...
</description></item><item><title>Download Digital Compass 16.7 Build 160</title><pubDate> Sat, 23 Aug 2025 23:14:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-digital-compass-13590.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-digital-compass-13590.html
</guid><description>
This app is a smart compass with high accuracy and a great tool for outdoor activities. This compass app allows you to easily determine the direction you are facing. This app is built using the device's gyroscope, accelerometer, magnetometer, gravity sensor to determine the direction. Make sure your device has an accelerometer and magnetometer sensor or it will not work.
Features
	Show current location (longitude, latitude, address)
	Show altitude
	Show magnetic field strength
	Show...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mirror Plus - HD Mirror app 4.4.8</title><pubDate> Sat, 23 Aug 2025 23:14:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-mirror-plus-mirror-with-light-8703.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-mirror-plus-mirror-with-light-8703.html
</guid><description>
Mirror Plus is a unique experience. With great camera quality, a beautiful classic design, and easy gesture controls, you'll have the ability to share your best images right in the app. Check your appearance after a few seconds, then freeze the screen and save the photo.
Or go one step further and use our special features:
	The 3D feature captures your appearance from left to right or top to bottom, so you can show off your amazing outfit or hairstyle to your friends!
	Create a...
</description></item><item><title>Download Shazam: Find Music &amp;amp; Concerts 16.6.0-250814</title><pubDate> Sat, 23 Aug 2025 23:13:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-shazam-music-discovery-10763.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-shazam-music-discovery-10763.html
</guid><description>
Shazam will identify any song in seconds. Discover, artists, lyrics, videos &amp;amp; playlists, all for free. Over 1 billion installs and counting. Use Pop-up Shazam to identify music in any app - Instagram, YouTube, TikTok... No connection? No problem! Shazam while offline.
Features of Shazam: Music Discovery
	Find the name of any song in seconds.
	Listen and add to Apple Music playlists.
	Follow along with time-synced lyrics.
	Watch music videos from Apple Music or YouTube.
	Enable...
</description></item><item><title>Download Handy GPS 44.4</title><pubDate> Sat, 23 Aug 2025 23:13:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-handy-gps-8741.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-handy-gps-8741.html
</guid><description>
The perfect companion for your next outdoor adventure. Search, find, record and return home with handy GPS. This app is a powerful navigation tool designed for outdoor sports such as hiking, backpacking, mountain biking, kayaking, canoeing and horseback riding. It is also useful for surveying, mining, archeology and forestry applications.
This application is simple and works even in the most remote countries because it does not require a network connection. It allows you to work in UTM...
</description></item><item><title>Download OPlayer - Video Player 5.00.43</title><pubDate> Sat, 23 Aug 2025 23:09:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-oplayer-video-player-8275.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-oplayer-video-player-8275.html
</guid><description>
Oplayer is a video player app for Android devices. It is designed to play a wide range of video formats, including popular formats like MP4, AVI, MKV, MOV, etc. It supports all video formats, 4K/Ultra HD video files and plays them in high resolution. This is one of the best HD video players for Android tablets and Android phones.
Features of Oplayer - Video Player
	Support all video formats, including MKV, MP4, M4V, AVI, MOV, 3GP, FLV, WMV, RMVB, TS, etc.
	Support all audio formats,...
</description></item></channel></rss>