<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 20:02:43 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 20:02:43 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Hard Configurator 7.0.1.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Dec 2025 17:10:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hard-configurator-4869.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hard-configurator-4869.html
</guid><description>
Hard Configurator is the user interface graphics only for advanced users to manage policies, software restriction (SRP) and hardening the version Windows Home from Vista and above. You can configure integrated security Windows to harden the system. When you close it it will close all processes of it. Real-time protection to from the Windows installation to be reconfigured. Hard Configurator can be viewed as rejection setting default smart Rate integrity-average, based on reputation...
</description></item><item><title>Download Audacity 3.7.6</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Dec 2025 17:08:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-audacity-1648.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-audacity-1648.html
</guid><description>
Audacity software to record audio along with editing features such as noise filtering, distortion noise, insert unique effects. The latest version of Audacity include the improvement of effects, interface, updates Nyquist and libflac. A number of bugs have also been fixed to help the software operate more smoothly. Audacity accompanied by the link to various sources, assist you learn how to use all the features of the program. These sources include Quick Help Guide (quick help), a guide,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Internet Download Manager (IDM) 6.42 Build 57</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Dec 2025 17:05:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-inetnet-download-manager-161.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-inetnet-download-manager-161.html
</guid><description>
Internet Download Manager is the download acceleration software, the best download support now, it can help you speed up the download up to five times, continue and schedule downloads. The latest version of IDM adds the compatibility of Windows 10 and Windows 11, it has supported all current popular browsers such as Internet Explorer, Mozilla Firefox, Opera, Google Chrome, ..
Download IDM with the latest version on taiwebs.com making it easy to download and manage your downloaded files...
</description></item><item><title>Download QontrolPanel (QuickSoundSwitcher) 1.10.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Dec 2025 17:05:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quicksoundswitcher-14033.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quicksoundswitcher-14033.html
</guid><description>
QuickSoundSwitcher is a lightweight, open-source Windows utility designed to quickly and easily manage audio input and output devices. It allows users to switch between multiple audio devices (e.g. speakers, headphones, microphones) and control the volume directly from the system tray without navigating to complex Windows settings.
The program also provides an application volume mixer, allowing for volume adjustment and muting for individual programs. This tool is especially useful for...
</description></item><item><title>Download IDM Retail 6.42 Build 57</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Dec 2025 17:04:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-internet-download-manager-retail-3609.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-internet-download-manager-retail-3609.html
</guid><description>
IDM - Internet Download Manager Retail is a reliable utility and high efficiency will help you to increase your download speed and manage download at better. The program allows you to easily schedule, pause and resume downloads with a single click. Moreover, the application provides error resilience robust and can restart the download at the interrupted or broken. You can restore the download is interrupted due to network problems, lost connections, unexpected power outages, computer...
</description></item><item><title>Download Calibre 8.16.0 + Portable</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Dec 2025 17:04:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-calibre-1669.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-calibre-1669.html
</guid><description>
Calibre  is an eBook library management application that allows you to manage your eBook collection, convert eBooks between different formats, Sync with popular e-reading devices and read your e-books with included viewer. You can sort books by author, title, date and other details, download meta information and book covers, add personalized tags and comments, and view your images in the cover display.
Collection of essential tools for adding metadata editing books or managing your...
</description></item><item><title>Download Bulk Image Downloader 6.61</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Dec 2025 17:03:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bulk-image-downloader-121.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bulk-image-downloader-121.html
</guid><description>
Bulk Image Downloader is an application specially developed to help you download the images in full size from the Bulk Image Downloader most of the web gallery or web forum.
Bulk Image Downloader what?
Support image storage - BID works with almost every archive page popular images, such as flickr, imagevenue, imagefap, imagebam, etc.
Social networking sites - BID supports downloading from sites such as facebook, myspace, and twitter as tweetphoto.com, twitpic.com, yfrog.com
Images are...
</description></item><item><title>Download XnViewMP 1.9.8</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Dec 2025 17:02:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xnview-mp-1074.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xnview-mp-1074.html
</guid><description>
XnViewMP "XnView MP" is the enhanced version of XnView Classic. This is the view and convert images multi-platform powerful, compatible with more than 500 image formats, different today. XnView MP easily export images to about 70 file format is different. Similar to XnConvert, XnView MP also features integrated switch at the same time batch file to help you process photos faster. XnView is another version of the photo viewer but with the ability to support formats more limited.
XnView...
</description></item><item><title>Download K-Lite Codec Pack Full 19.3.5</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Dec 2025 17:02:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-115.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-115.html
</guid><description>
K Lite Codec Pack Full brings pc users an optimal solution for watching movies, listening to music, support most popular format today by using collection codec rich. This software also allows you to refine the quality of videos and music to enjoy, create a list of music and video to comfortable enjoy.
Prompt to software, listen to music, watch movies, currently, part, user will prompt to programs like VLC or KMP ... With VLC, it was too familiar with users, not just watch videos, listen...
</description></item><item><title>Download Android Studio 2025.2.2.7</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Dec 2025 17:02:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-android-studio-3890.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-android-studio-3890.html
</guid><description>
Android Studio is an Android development environment, completely new, provides many improvements and new features compared to Eclipse ADT. This software solution will is IDE the official Android when is finishing. This tool provides many tools and features such as editing, layout, rich set of tools to capture usability, compatibility version, performance and other issues, create a lot APK, build system based on Gradle flexibility, extended support for Google Services, integrated support...
</description></item><item><title>Download QOwnNotes 25.12.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Dec 2025 17:01:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qownnotes-3178.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qownnotes-3178.html
</guid><description>
QOwnNotes is notes bookmark file simple text (GPL) open source application for GNU / Linux , Mac OS X and Windows of Patrizio Bekerle ( pbek on GitHub and IRC) (optional) activity along with the notes application of ownCloud or Nextcloud. QOwnNote store your notes as plain text files and can be synchronized with synchronization function file of ownCloud / Nextcloud. You can also use other apps like Syncthing or Dropbox . Just write out your thoughts as they appear, and edit them if...
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 7.5.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Dec 2025 17:01:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-11-7760.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-11-7760.html
</guid><description>
TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 is a program that allows users to discover hidden settings in Windows 11. This application is specially designed for Windows 11, groups many registry settings and distribute them from the easy and secure user interface. With TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 you can move the Windows taskbar to the top and resize the taskbar by editing the registry value. With any application that modifies the registry, we recommend that you have a backup copy...
</description></item><item><title>Download K-Lite Codec Pack Mega 19.3.5</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Dec 2025 17:01:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-mega-3202.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-mega-3202.html
</guid><description>
K-Lite Mega Codec Pack is a collection of components needed for audio playback and the video in the player DirectShow like Windows Media Player, Media Center, and Media Player Classic. This is the latest beta version, Pack Codec K-Lite latest stable. The Mega variant is the biggest of the four variants of the codec pack. It provides everything you need to play all audio and video files. In addition, it also contains some codecs ACM / VFW can be used by the application coding / video...
</description></item><item><title>Download Chris-PC RAM Booster 7.25.1204</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Dec 2025 17:00:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chris-pc-ram-booster-1181.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chris-pc-ram-booster-1181.html
</guid><description>
ChrisPC RAM Booster is software speed up your system by managing and acceleration of the RAM in the operating system. RAM Booster will monitor the RAM usage (memory random access) and upon reaching the threshold memory certain low, it will trigger the process of freeing up memory for the new program open while moving at the same time the old programs from the RAM memory into virtual memory on disk.
Chris-PC RAM Booster - speed up processing RAM
Certainly this is a slower process...
</description></item><item><title>Download dBpoweramp Music Converter Reference 2025-12-04</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Dec 2025 17:00:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbpoweramp-music-converter-4222.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbpoweramp-music-converter-4222.html
</guid><description>
dBpoweramp Music Converter audio converter is perfect, easy to convert to mp3, FLAC, Apple lossless and more. dBpoweramp Music Converter has become the standard tool for audio conversion, more than 30 million users world trust their switch to dBpoweramp. dBpoweramp Music Converter integrates into Windows Explorer, an mp3 converter as simple as right-click on source files; convert into. Tip information Popup, edit tags ID are provided.
dBpoweramp Music Converter - audio converter...
</description></item><item><title>Download Draftable Desktop 25.12.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Dec 2025 16:58:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-draftable-desktop-3749.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-draftable-desktop-3749.html
</guid><description>
Draftable Desktop is comparison tool documents the fastest. Compare over 300 pages in a few seconds. Draftable Desktop 2.0 is now available - faster and stronger than ever! See all the changes in your documents, locally and online. Take your work to the next level. Compare secret and private do not use the internet and your documents never leave your computer. Specifically, Draftable Desktop compatible with .xls, .xlsx, .xlsxm. With Office 2013, 2016 or 365, you can compare text in...
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 7.5.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Dec 2025 16:57:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-10-7759.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-10-7759.html
</guid><description>
TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 is a utility that allows users to discover hidden settings in Windows 10. This application is specially designed for Windows 10, groups many registry settings and provide them from an easy and secure user interface. With TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 you can move the Windows taskbar to the top and resize the taskbar by editing the registry value. With any application that modifies the registry, we recommend that you have a backup copy to...
</description></item><item><title>Download FileVoyager 25.12.5.0 Full</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Dec 2025 16:57:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-filevoyager-3322.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-filevoyager-3322.html
</guid><description>
FileVoyager is a OFM free and efficient (The file manager main system) is designed for the computer MS Windows. OFM is a file manager use two separate tab of browser drive. Tabbed interface, this simplifies the operation, file transfer, and ensure speed and efficiency. FileVoyager provide increased functionality and includes a set of rich tools. Using this tool, you will be able to easily browse the disk, archive, folder, FTP and FTPS of quickly and efficiently. You can browse your files...
</description></item><item><title>Download Advanced Installer Architect 23.3.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Dec 2025 16:56:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-installer-128.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-installer-128.html
</guid><description>
Advanced Installer is a Windows utility designed to help you build the package Windows Installer in a working environment clean and intuitive.
Although it has many parameters dedicated but the user interface is very simple and gives users the ability to create new projects by selecting the type, namely installer (for example: application Visual Studio or .NET, pack 32/64-bit mixture), Java , updates, support, mobile devices, and other things.
Advanced Installer - An environment for...
</description></item><item><title>Download Media Player Classic Home Cinema 2.5.6</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Dec 2025 16:55:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-media-player-classic-home-cinema-2839.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-media-player-classic-home-cinema-2839.html
</guid><description>
Media Player Classic Home Cinema is a multimedia compact for Microsoft Windows 32 bit and 64 bit. MPC mimics the interface of Windows Media Player 6.4, but provides most options and features available in the modern means. Media Player Classic Home Cinema for free 100% no advertising, so you can directly access content and enjoy media playback without being distracted.
With Media Player Classic Home, you can now change the design a multimedia of the custom toolbar. There is a range to...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDF Annotator 10.0.0.1004</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Dec 2025 16:55:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-annotator-178.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-annotator-178.html
</guid><description>
PDF Annotator software user open any PDF file and add annotations, using the mouse or pen Tablet PC, directly on the Page of the PDF file. PDF Annotator allows users to perform editing operations on PDF files such as: add notes, edit signature, highlight, insert images or text... From the this useful tool, you can completely modify PDF files as you like in order to meet the different work.
PDF Annotator
With the PDF Annotator the document has annotations can then be saved directly back...
</description></item><item><title>Download Black Menu for Google 30.7.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Dec 2025 16:54:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-black-menu-for-google-3231.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-black-menu-for-google-3231.html
</guid><description>
Black Menu for Google (Firefox) gives you fast access to Google services with your favorite drop-down menu conveniently allows you to use Search, Google+ and many other services without leaving the page you are visiting. Click on the menu item to get a preview small window or click the open button to the right to open them in a new tab.
Customize the menu by just entering ‘Add to, and drag / click on the service you want from the list of comprehensive services. To delete a service, drag...
</description></item><item><title>Download Terragen Professional 4.8.64</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Dec 2025 16:53:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-planetside-software-terragen-professional-1203.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-planetside-software-terragen-professional-1203.html
</guid><description>
Planetside Software Terragen Professional is a powerful solution to construction, rendered and animated environment, natural fact. Create entire worlds from your imagination or import the terrain data in the real world and use Terragen to create visually realistic as possible. You control the weather, landscape, rivers, lakes and oceans, the sun, the moon and the stars.
Planetside Software Terragen Professional - Create a realistic environment
With Terragen you have full control over...
</description></item><item><title>Download LosslessCut 3.67.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Dec 2025 16:53:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-losslesscut-1789.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-losslesscut-1789.html
</guid><description>
LosslessCut is the video editor to trim and cut video without loss of quality. Just download the video file and use seal cutter start / stop to only the part you want to cut. Click the crop icon and the highlighted part will be exported to the file new video without any decoding or encoding whatsoever. LosslessCut using ffmpeg (included) to carry all the heavy stuff.
LosslessCut - Cut and edit videos
LosslessCut based on Chromium and uses the video player HTML5, so not all formats are...
</description></item><item><title>Download USB Safely Remove 7.2.1.1330</title><pubDate> Fri, 05 Dec 2025 16:52:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-usb-safely-remove-122.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-usb-safely-remove-122.html
</guid><description>
USB Safely Remove is a great program to automate work with devices your mobile. For example, you can easily specify the launch the program you need when disconnecting or connecting equipment, plus you have access to the command line, you can download USB Safely Remove in the full news. I would like to note an interesting feature of the program is that you can stop the USB device by pressing the hot key and the unique technology of the program will allow you to know why the device you...
</description></item></channel></rss>