<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 13:51:47 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 13:51:47 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Microsoft Activation Scripts 3.5</title><pubDate> Mon, 11 Aug 2025 15:52:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-activation-scripts-5390.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-activation-scripts-5390.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft Activation Scripts is an open source Windows and Office activation tool that features online HWID, Ohook, KMS38 and KMS activation methods, along with advanced troubleshooting functionality.
Activation methods
			Trigger type
			Supported products
			Activation time
			HWID
			Windows 10-11
			Permanent
			Ohook
			Office
			Permanent
			KMS38
			Windows 10-11, Server
			Until 2038
			Online KMS
			Windows / Office
			180 days (with...
</description></item><item><title>Download Unicodia 2.12.6</title><pubDate> Mon, 11 Aug 2025 15:51:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-unicodia-8521.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-unicodia-8521.html
</guid><description>
Unicodia is free, open source software that can be used as an alternative character map for your Windows machine. The interface contains everything you need, allowing you to easily cycle through all the available ASCII symbols and copy them to the clipboard. Uncicodia is a great alternative to your standard Unicode characters and is filled with symbols/characters that make it useful for a number of different uses.
Features of Unicodia
	In Windows 10/11 — all characters of Unicode 15...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Downloader 9.15.5</title><pubDate> Mon, 11 Aug 2025 15:51:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html
</guid><description>
YTD Youtube Downloader is an application that reliable and intuitive, allowing you to quickly download YouTube videos and save them to your computer. You can also convert the media files to the format desired video or extract audio streams and save separately. YTD Youtube Downloader lets you save your favorite clips of yourself from Youtube, Facebook, Vimeo and Dailymotion to your desktop. The software supports URLS from many web site hosting, multimedia and allows you to download desired...
</description></item><item><title>Download 4KSoftware 4K Downloader 5.16.3</title><pubDate> Mon, 11 Aug 2025 15:51:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-downloader-3858.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-downloader-3858.html
</guid><description>
4K Downloader is a Windows application small but powerful to download and convert video in 4K and 8K Ultra HD from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion and thousands of other video-based websites. It speeds up your download by up to 5 times. Consider that most smart phones, TVS, computers, and tablets all support the high definition format, don't be surprised when many users want to enjoy quality content on their device. 4K Downloader is a lightweight software designed to help you grab videos...
</description></item><item><title>Download Agisoft Metashape Professional 2.2.2 Build 20920</title><pubDate> Mon, 11 Aug 2025 15:50:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-agisoft-metashape-professional-1731.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-agisoft-metashape-professional-1731.html
</guid><description>
Agisoft Metashape (formerly PhotoScan) is a software product independently perform image processing and digital data creation, 3D space used in GIS applications, material cultural heritage and the production visual effects as well as the indirect measurement of the different subjects scale. Technical digital photography is deployed wisely is applied with the method of computer vision led to the system processor, smart auto, on the one hand, can be managed by a new person in the field of...
</description></item><item><title>Download TubeDownload Pro 6.28.5</title><pubDate> Mon, 11 Aug 2025 15:50:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubedownload-pro-12035.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubedownload-pro-12035.html
</guid><description>
TubeDownload Pro is a professional Windows application for downloading your favorite videos from YouTube and hundreds of other video sites. TubeDownload Pro can increase download speed up to 500% or even more.
Features of TubeDownload Pro
	Download your favorite videos from YouTube and hundreds of other video sites.
	Increase download speed up to 500% or even more.
	Download 720p, 1080p, 2K, 4K and 8K HD videos from YouTube.
	Download entire playlists in just a few clicks.
	Download...
</description></item><item><title>Download Double Commander 1.1.28</title><pubDate> Mon, 11 Aug 2025 15:49:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-double-commander-7801.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-double-commander-7801.html
</guid><description>
Double Commander is an open source file manager with two panels side by side. The idea is based on Total Commander but with new and different features. Double Commander has multi-rename tool, tabbed interface, custom columns, internal text editor, built-in file viewer, archive support (ZIP, RAR), extensive search functionality, configurable button bar, file activity logging, plug-in support and more.
Features of Double Commander
	Internal text editor (F4) with syntax...
</description></item><item><title>Download RapidRAW 1.3.7</title><pubDate> Mon, 11 Aug 2025 15:49:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rapidraw-13957.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rapidraw-13957.html
</guid><description>
RapidRAW is a modern, high-performance, open-source RAW photo editor, designed to deliver a fast and clean editing experience with a lightweight footprint (under 30MB). Built with performance and usability in mind, the software is aimed at photographers who want a simple, efficient, and fun workflow without compromising performance.
Key Features
	GPU-accelerated processing: Uses a custom WGSL shader to process all image adjustments on the GPU, allowing for smooth, responsive editing...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Video Downloader 11.26.5</title><pubDate> Mon, 11 Aug 2025 15:48:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-video-downloader-9636.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-video-downloader-9636.html
</guid><description>
YT Video Downloader is software used to easily and quickly download any video or audio content from any website in HD quality using video downloader online. Save videos from almost any website supported by a video downloader on your local hard drive. Media search is a convenient way to do this.
Features of YT Video Downloader
	Download videos from hundreds of video sites.
	Really increase your download speed by up to 500% or even more!
	Download 8K, 5K, 4K Ultra HD, 2K Quad HD, 1080p...
</description></item><item><title>Download Thimeo Stereo Tool 10.70</title><pubDate> Mon, 11 Aug 2025 15:48:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stereo-tool-4066.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stereo-tool-4066.html
</guid><description>
Stereo Tool is an audio processor based on software, provide sound quality superior and comes with many unique features. It is used by over 1500 FM stations, from the station of the small local to the station 50 - 100 kW and nationwide network with dozens of generators, thousands of stations online and many radio DAB +, HD, AM and TV. Stereo Tool can make recordings sound equal and consistent in volume and sound color, highlight details and increase the stereo effect is there. It can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Thimeo ST-Enterprise 10.70</title><pubDate> Mon, 11 Aug 2025 15:47:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thimeo-st-enterprise-10422.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thimeo-st-enterprise-10422.html
</guid><description>
Thimeo ST-Enterprise is for larger media groups running multiple stations or channels. It does everything that Stereo Tools does and more! With ST-Enterprise, you can run up to 50(*) FM and/or HD processors on a single computer, with a single interface to control them and an overview screen showing the status of them all. incoming and outgoing signals.
Features of Thimeo ST-Enterprise
	It makes more efficient use of available resources, mainly processing power, and allows you to share...
</description></item><item><title>Download VovSoft Http Requester 6.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 11 Aug 2025 15:47:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-http-requester-6570.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-http-requester-6570.html
</guid><description>
VovSoft Http Requester is a simple tool for asking POST and GET queries. The POST and GET are the two basic requirements in HTTP, each with its own role, but both are based on the demand-feedback protocol. A list of URLs that can be filled in manually or glued to a private school, while the input name and corresponding values also have a reserved area.
The user can add new input data in a manual manner, but there is also an option to import that data from the CSV file. Right next to,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Techsoft MirrorFolder 6.1.523.480 Enterprise Edition</title><pubDate> Mon, 11 Aug 2025 15:43:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-techsoft-mirrorfolder-13158.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-techsoft-mirrorfolder-13158.html
</guid><description>
MirrorFolder is an automatic folder copying and synchronization software for backing up files on Windows desktops, laptops, and servers. You can set up one or more mirroring paths for important folders, or even entire drives, to another local, removable, or network share for automatic synchronization or real-time mirroring. Once mirroring is set up for a folder, file synchronization will be done silently in the background without any additional effort or attention from the user. You can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Starus Photo Recovery 6.9</title><pubDate> Mon, 11 Aug 2025 15:43:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-starus-photo-recovery-3279.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-starus-photo-recovery-3279.html
</guid><description>
Starus Photo Recovery recover digital pictures from disks, memory cards, compact cameras and DSLR cameras in just a few clicks! Starus Photo Recovery helps the amateur photographer and professional photo seasoned can take back the take a photo of them if there is anything wrong with the memory card. Support multiple storage media, Starus Photo Recovery can restore the deleted photos and entire photo collection in just a few simple steps.
Starus Photo Recovery - Recover digital...
</description></item><item><title>Download Social Media Downloader 7.6.5</title><pubDate> Mon, 11 Aug 2025 15:43:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-socialmediaapps-facebook-video-downloader-3742.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-socialmediaapps-facebook-video-downloader-3742.html
</guid><description>
SocialVideo Downloader (formerly SocialMediaApps Facebook Video Downloader) is a Windows application to download and convert your favorite videos from Facebook and hundreds of other video sharing sites. It increases your loading speed by up to 500%, or even more! The application has a simple and intuitive user interface, its main functions and features are quite obvious to anyone. , regardless of prior experience with similar purpose tools.
&amp;nbsp;
SocialVideo Downloader
The main...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tomabo MP4 Downloader Pro 5.6.5</title><pubDate> Mon, 11 Aug 2025 15:42:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tomabo-mp4-downloader-pro-3602.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tomabo-mp4-downloader-pro-3602.html
</guid><description>
Tomabo MP4 Downloader Pro is the app designed exclusively for Windows users to help them download videos from the Internet. In addition, it also increase download speeds by up to 500%, or even more. Tomabo MP4 Downloader Pro, interface design, simple, well-organized, beautifully. Here, users can view a list of videos has download with gravatar, URL, quality, duration and size of them. Software allows download video series at the same time, at the same time, support create a list of clips...
</description></item><item><title>Download Starus File Recovery 7.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 11 Aug 2025 15:42:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-starus-file-recovery-2654.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-starus-file-recovery-2654.html
</guid><description>
Starus File Recovery is a powerful program to restore files after deleting them from the trash can, can works with FAT and NTFS partitions broken, can works with removable disks and flash drives are different, can restore all the documents created in Microsoft Office, works with documents created in Adobe Reader, it can work with photos of most of the graphical format know, it will be easy to find and restore multimedia data in various formats and it will easily fix the logical partition...
</description></item><item><title>Download Database Tour Pro 11.5.1.633</title><pubDate> Mon, 11 Aug 2025 15:41:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-database-tour-pro-5321.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-database-tour-pro-5321.html
</guid><description>
Database Tour Pro application is a comprehensive software that allows you to organize all the database is connected his. It provides support for Borland Database Engine (BDE) and Microsoft ActiveX Data Objects (ADO), SQL scripts, reports, along with conversion and data export, among others.
It contains a browser object for the function, package, triggers, folders, users, roles, profiles, sequences, work, style, Java, exception, link, database, general properties, table, schema, and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Starus Partition Recovery 5.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 11 Aug 2025 15:41:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-starus-partition-recovery-3280.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-starus-partition-recovery-3280.html
</guid><description>
Starus Partition Recovery is the leading product of us to repair the partition broken and restore the information missing. It provides the ability to recover step by step the same for the file deleted and lost as the more simple products of us, at the same time added the option restore partition comprehensive to create a solution all in a perfect.
Starus Partition Recovery - recover hard drive partition
Starus Partition Recovery has the mode analysis quick and comprehensive, allowing...
</description></item><item><title>Download TubeMate Downloader 5.21.5</title><pubDate> Mon, 11 Aug 2025 15:40:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubemate-downloader-4250.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubemate-downloader-4250.html
</guid><description>
TubeMate Downloader is a smart application that lets you download any clip you want from the website hosting the main video and convert them in when download at or then. If you need a simple and effective tool to download videos, you can give it a try. With TubeMate Downloader, you can directly drag and drop video link from your browser into the drop-down box or application window to start downloading. You don't even need to copy and paste the video URL.
TubeMate Downloader - Support...
</description></item><item><title>Download Thimeo Relay 10.70</title><pubDate> Mon, 11 Aug 2025 15:40:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thimeo-relay-10423.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thimeo-relay-10423.html
</guid><description>
Thimeo Relay uses your sound card (internal or external) as a Relay detector and converts on/off signals into RDS commands that can be sent to most devices. RDS encoders, including those in Stereo Engine and STXtreme.
Features of Thimeo Relay
	It minimizes audio latency, ensuring real-time audio processing and synchronization with video content or virtual instruments.
	It offers multiple connection options to meet different audio needs.
	Use your sound card (internal or external) as a...
</description></item><item><title>Download Starus Web Detective 4.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 11 Aug 2025 15:39:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-starus-web-detective-5259.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-starus-web-detective-5259.html
</guid><description>
Starus Web Detective is software that helps you recover history deleted, and the analysis of many types of web browsers. The app will allow you to monitor browsing history, bookmarks, list download and password, even if user has delete this information from your browser. Starus Web Detective will help you find the data even when browsing history is deleted, the entire browser is uninstalled or some files of it is lost, the current user is deleted from the operating system or the hard disk...
</description></item><item><title>Download Syncovery Premium 11.6.6.81</title><pubDate> Mon, 11 Aug 2025 15:39:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncovery-pro-enterprise-232.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncovery-pro-enterprise-232.html
</guid><description>
Syncovery Pro Enterprise is a great application used to back up data and to synchronize personal computers, servers, laptops, notepads and storage online. The software comes with support for FTP and secure FTP servers, SSH, WebDAV, Amazon S3, http, update the part file, ZIP compression, data encryption, and schedule automatic backups.
Syncovery Pro Enterprise have the ability to freely select files and folders across the whole folder hierarchy in tree view and supports email...
</description></item><item><title>Download Internet Video Downloader 7.3.5</title><pubDate> Mon, 11 Aug 2025 15:38:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hdapplications-hd-downloader-6041.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hdapplications-hd-downloader-6041.html
</guid><description>
Internet Video Downloader is a small tool designed to help you download video clips from YouTube, Dailymotion and many other similar sites with high quality that can easily run on smartphones, tablets or the latest Xbox devices. After the quick and simple installation process, you will be welcomed by a user-friendly interface without the ability to cause any problems for you.
Although you can set the app start to download immediately, but you can also create a download list that can be...
</description></item><item><title>Download Starus RAID Restore 2.8</title><pubDate> Mon, 11 Aug 2025 15:38:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-starus-raid-restore-7530.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-starus-raid-restore-7530.html
</guid><description>
Starus RAID Restore is a program to recover data from inactive RAID systems or from disks in those systems. It reads all information about the controller, motherboard or software used to create the disk array. Our product can rebuild failed RAID and it allows you to copy all important information from there.
The built-in build wizard helps you to recover a failed RAID in step-by-step mode. You can use one of the presets or select the required data in the corrupted array and Starus RAID...
</description></item></channel></rss>