<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 15:48:28 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 15:48:28 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Glary Tracks Eraser 6.0.1.32</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 18:08:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-tracks-eraser-1342.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-tracks-eraser-1342.html
</guid><description>
Glary Tracks Eraser is security software privacy when browsing the web, allows you to delete all traces of network access and trace number, including browser cache, cookies, the website is already open, the URL has been entered, the document new mines, temporary files,... Glary Tracks Eraser that helps you free up space in hard disk drives, scan entire junk files in the drive with the speed of processing is extremely fast. Data deleted by Glary Tracks Eraser will not be able to restore,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Glary Disk Cleaner 6.0.1.39</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 18:08:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-disk-cleaner-1341.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-disk-cleaner-1341.html
</guid><description>
Glary Disk Cleaner is the software helps to erase the file system temporarily, cleanup your browser cache, or release the folder. Glary Disk Cleaner show scan results in detail, help you pick exactly each file to delete. The list file is much more wide open, with temporary files, user-generated, or the file system, cache, bug report, log files, data in recycle bin, the shortcut expires.
Glary Disk Cleaner - garbage system
Glary Disk Cleaner is designed to be simple as possible in use....
</description></item><item><title>Download VueScan Pro 9.8.50</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 18:03:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vuescan-pro-75.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vuescan-pro-75.html
</guid><description>
VueScan Pro l  is one of the software  Scan quality pictures  First and appeared quite soon,  VueScan Pro  always asserted its No. 1 position on the technology pages, awards as well as user reviews. Through many versions, VueScan Pro 9 is greatly improved in terms of interface and features. Supporting most popular image formats today, this software will help you scan images quickly, easy to use and high quality output. With the color balance mode, you won't have to worry about blurring the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Nero Burning ROM 27.0.1.4</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 18:02:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nero-burning-rom-2019-155.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nero-burning-rom-2019-155.html
</guid><description>
Nero Burning ROM 2021  efficient data backup and CD burning software burns them to your favorite disc type. Want to keep your data safe and secure? Want to create discs with maximum reliability? No problem with the latest version of Nero Burning ROM, which uses SecurDisc 4.0 and more to ensure the best results.
With Nero, the disc is written fairly quickly and error-free, with many tools integrated into one simple interface. Nero also features mp3 file mixing, video editing, slideshow...
</description></item><item><title>Download IObit Malware Fighter Pro 13.1.0.1617</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 18:02:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iobit-malware-fighter-pro-257.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iobit-malware-fighter-pro-257.html
</guid><description>
IObit Malware Fighter Pro is security software, remove malicious program with many advanced features that help protect safety for your system. IObit Malware Fighter Pro integration inside is the power of technology Dual-Core help quick scan and deep scan the entire system to detect and eliminate concerns about the virus.
IObit Malware Fighter Pro a lot of attention by the ability to detect and remove programs spyware from the system with fast speed and the most accurate. More special is...
</description></item><item><title>Download Yamicsoft Windows 11/10 Manager 2.3</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 17:55:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yamicsoft-windows-11-manager-6779.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yamicsoft-windows-11-manager-6779.html
</guid><description>
Windows 11 Manager is an all-in-one utility for Microsoft Windows 11 specially, it includes over forty different utilities to optimize, tweak, clean up, speed up and repair your Windows 11, helps make your system perform faster, eliminate system fault, increase stability and security, personalize your copy of Windows 11, and meet all of your expectations.
Features of Windows 11 Manager:
Information:
	Creates the system restore point manually;
	Gets detailed information about your...
</description></item><item><title>Download RedNotebook 2.42</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 17:54:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rednotebook-2884.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rednotebook-2884.html
</guid><description>
RedNotebook is a note-taking app for free. It allows you to format, tag and search your entries. You can also add images, links and templates can customize, check the spelling of your notes and export into plain text, HTML or LaTeX. RedNotebook is free software under the GPL.
RedNotebook - Write notes, edit text
Features of RedNotebook
	Use #hashtags
	Format your text bold , italic or underline
	Insert images, files and links to the website
	Links and email addresses are recognized...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tenorshare 4DDiG Email Repair 1.0.1.4</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 17:49:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tenorshare-4ddig-email-repair-11818.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tenorshare-4ddig-email-repair-11818.html
</guid><description>
Tenorshare 4DDiG Email Repair is a powerful software application designed to help Windows users repair damaged or unusable email files. Whether your Outlook, Windows Mail or other email client files are inaccessible or display error messages, this program will provide an effective solution to recover your emails and attachments.
Tenorshare 4DDiG Email Repair is a reliable and effective tool to repair damaged email files on Windows. Whether you're dealing with file corruption, error...
</description></item><item><title>Download O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro 22.1.229 / Server</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 17:40:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-diskimage-pro-218.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-diskimage-pro-218.html
</guid><description>
O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro is software backup data comprehensive and effective is provided to protect the data of the computer system, it creates images for individual drives or the entire system that still does not affect your system.
O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro allows the user to backup the entire computer or drive, the and files whenever you want even while the computer is being used. Or can use O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro to create a copy chinh sac of computer disk drives, can be used instead of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download O&amp;amp;O BlueCon Tech Edition 23.0.14008</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 17:39:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-bluecon-tech-edition-4038.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-bluecon-tech-edition-4038.html
</guid><description>
O&amp;amp;O BlueCon Tech Edition provides a set of powerful tools for users, administrators and service technicians so that the system is broken can be operated back without install ago. The user interface is based on Windows help the use of O&amp;amp;O BlueCon Tech Edition easy to the level required less time for training. It is in the side of administrators in the process of daily as well as whenever disaster happens.
O&amp;amp;O BlueCon Tech Edition - to fix Windows system
BlueCon boot all the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Boris FX CrumplePop Pro 2025.5.3</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 17:38:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-boris-fx-crumplepop-complete-9687.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-boris-fx-crumplepop-complete-9687.html
</guid><description>
Boris FX CrumplePop Complete is a complete set of audio plugin tools to make your sound the best with advanced AI technology. Never before has dealing with common audio problems like background noise, echoes, traffic, wind, and more. as well as enhancing the sound quality to achieve professional results has never been easier. The CrumplePop audio tools are easy to use if you're a beginner, and powerful enough to meet the daily needs of audio professionals.
Features of Boris FX...
</description></item><item><title>Download 10-Strike LANState Pro 10.5</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 17:37:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-10-strike-lanstate-pro-11054.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-10-strike-lanstate-pro-11054.html
</guid><description>
10-Strike LANState Pro is a simple network topology mapping, server monitoring, and management program. Monitor service availability. Manage servers, computers, switches, and other devices more easily with graphical maps. Access device properties, RDP, web UI faster. Restart/shutdown servers and services in just a few clicks!
The program will automatically scan your network for device types and their addresses, and create a network map with vector device icons. If your switches are...
</description></item><item><title>Download Valentina Studio Pro 16.5.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 17:37:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-valentina-studio-pro-2122.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-valentina-studio-pro-2122.html
</guid><description>
Valentina Studio Pro is the best way to transform your data into meaningful information; create, manage, query and explore MySQL, Postgre MariaDB, MS SQL Server and SQLite database.
Valentina Studio Pro
Features of Valentina Studio Pro
SCHEMA EDITING &amp;amp; MAPPING
	Manage multiple databases in tabs and views that can be attached is
	Create / Drop / alter / Browse Tables, fields, index, trigger, constraints, links, views, stored procedures, properties, Sequences, Types, ...
	Edit the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Valentina Server 16.5.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 17:36:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-valentina-server-10771.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-valentina-server-10771.html
</guid><description>
Valentina Server is software that provides reports from all major databases or with its own advanced object-relational database system. It will combine an enterprise reporting server and two database servers into a single solution. You get all the technical features of Valentina Server in terms of usage, more connections and live technical support.
Features of Valentina Server
	Enterprise report server turns data into highly formatted reports in the form of multimedia web pages, text,...
</description></item><item><title>Download ImageMagick 7.1.2-12</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 17:13:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-imagemagick-1319.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-imagemagick-1319.html
</guid><description>
ImageMagick is software image processing command line to create, edit, compose, or convert bitmap images. ImageMagick is completely free for users and you easily download it on taiwebs.com. Typical functions most of software is able to read and write images in many formats (over 100) including DPX, EXR, GIF, JPEG, JPEG-2000, PDF, PhotoCD, PNG, Postcript, SVG, and TIFF.
ImageMagick - image Processing
The Windows version of ImageMagick is installed. Just click on the appropriate version...
</description></item><item><title>Download K-Lite Codec Pack Update 19.3.9</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 17:10:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-update-5145.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-update-5145.html
</guid><description>
K-Lite Codec Pack Update is the update of the set of codecs and related tools. Codec stands for Compressor-decompressor. Codec is necessary to encode and decode (play) audio and video. K-Lite Codec Pack Update is designed as a user-friendly solution with users to play all movie files your. With Codec Pack K-Lite, you can play 99% of all the movies found on your computer. A number of packages codec is not friendly with computers, as they tend to slow down Windows, break down multimedia...
</description></item><item><title>Download Seamless3d 3.038.13</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 17:10:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-seamless3d-10257.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-seamless3d-10257.html
</guid><description>
Seamless3d is one of the easiest 3D modeling and animation programs that offers artistic freedom. It is designed to be a powerful and practical way to create 3D models that will appeal to anyone who wants to create quality 3D animated content for the web. A versatile NURBS-based 3D Modeler/Animator designed for ease of use without compromising artistic freedom, allowing you to create unique models.
Features of Seamless3d
	WYSIWYG
	Undo/Redo
	Export clean, efficient files
	Dedicated...
</description></item><item><title>Download lessmsi 2.11.3</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 17:09:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lessmsi-12392.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lessmsi-12392.html
</guid><description>
Lessmsi (Less MSIerables) is a free and portable application that allows users to view and extract the contents of MSI files.
How does it work? Files with the .msi extension are not as widely used as their .exe cousins, but both contain programs for Windows. The main difference between them is that the latter does not always come with an installer, while it comes standard with the former. However, there will be cases where you just need to view or want to extract specific content from...
</description></item><item><title>Download PingTool 5.0.0.96</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 17:08:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pingtool-11816.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pingtool-11816.html
</guid><description>
PingTool is a powerful utility for administrators. It's more than just a simple ping tool: PingTool can also wake up computers using Wake-on-Lan, to check the availability of TCP ports, scan networks, and more.
PingTool Features
	Permanent display of network device status (red/green)
	Scan IP range - with MAC address and vendor
	Check that the remote device responds on specific TCP ports
	Wake up your computer using Wake-on-Lan
	Direct access to the device via Telnet, SSH and...
</description></item><item><title>Download 3C All-in-One Toolbox 3.1.5b</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 16:45:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-3c-all-in-one-toolbox-8399.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-3c-all-in-one-toolbox-8399.html
</guid><description>
3C All-in-One Toolbox combines many features into one giant toolbox with a modern and easy-to-use interface. All the tools you need to monitor, control and fine-tune all your Android devices. This app uses the Accessibility service to help you stop the app on non-rooted devices but will never collect any information.
Features of 3C All-in-One Toolbox
	Device Manager offers very powerful configurations, task scheduling, and device watchdogs that you can find to optimize performance and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Rosetta Stone: Learn, Practice 8.34.4</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 16:45:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-rosetta-stone-learn-practice-11241.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-rosetta-stone-learn-practice-11241.html
</guid><description>
Interactive and contextual lessons combined with Extended Learning features are truly at your fingertips–anytime, anywhere, on any device; online or offline and completely ad-free. Learn to speak Spanish, French, German, Italian, English, Japanese, Korean, Chinese, Arabic, Portuguese, Russian, Dutch, Filipino, Greek , Hebrew, Hindi, Irish, Persian, Polish, Swedish, Turkish, Vietnamese and more!
Rosetta Stone helps you speak confidently: With many lessons and features focused on...
</description></item><item><title>Download Anti Spy Detector: Anti Hack 48.5.24.12.25</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 16:43:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-anti-spy-detector-firewall-10779.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-anti-spy-detector-firewall-10779.html
</guid><description>
With the powerful built-in firewall in this app, you can monitor every outgoing connection each app makes. If you don't trust the app, you can block it from accessing the internet with a firewall to prevent tracking and analysis. Every outgoing IP or domain will be saved and you can see them, the Firewall will show you the address, organization and information about that IP and if you feel suspicious you can block that domain so that application is no longer accessible. Additionally, you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Any.do - To do list &amp;amp; Calendar 5.18.15.5</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 16:43:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-anydo-to-do-list-calendar-8360.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-anydo-to-do-list-calendar-8360.html
</guid><description>
Any.do is a productivity app that combines the features of a to-do list and a calendar. It allows users to create and organize tasks as well as schedule them according to specific dates and times. The app also includes a feature called "My Day" that helps users focus on the most important tasks of the day.
Some of Any.do's other features include the ability to set reminders, create side and recurring tasks, and collaborate on tasks with others. Additionally, Any.do also has a calendar...
</description></item><item><title>Download Device Info: System &amp;amp; CPU Info 3.4.1.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 16:42:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-device-info-system-cpu-info-8723.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-device-info-system-cpu-info-8723.html
</guid><description>
Device Information: System &amp;amp; CPU Information is a mobile application that provides users with detailed information about the hardware and software specifications of their device. This app is designed to help users better understand their device's capabilities and performance as well as diagnose any potential issues or problems.
With Device Info: System and CPU Info, users can view information about the processor, memory, storage, battery, sensors, and more. of equipment. This app...
</description></item><item><title>Download Memento Database 5.8.4</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 16:42:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-memento-database-11185.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-memento-database-11185.html
</guid><description>
Memento Database is a powerful and user-friendly tool designed to work with any data, helping to store, organize, calculate and visualize information. It is more convenient than spreadsheets, more flexible than dedicated applications. If you are looking for a program to organize personal matters, hobbies or small or medium-sized businesses, Memento is the solution.
Personal use 
Memento can replace dozens of applications, helping you organize your life and increase your...
</description></item></channel></rss>