<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 03:31:03 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 03:31:03 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download HopToDesk 1.44.4</title><pubDate> Mon, 01 Sep 2025 23:40:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hoptodesk-11056.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hoptodesk-11056.html
</guid><description>
HopToDesk is a remote desktop application that allows users to access their remote computer or server from anywhere using a mobile device or browser their website. It provides a secure and convenient way to control and manage computers remotely, making it easier for individuals and teams to work remotely or access their files and applications on the go.
With HopToDesk, users can establish a secure connection to a remote computer or server and perform tasks as if they were sitting in...
</description></item><item><title>Download HttpMaster Pro 6.2.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 01 Sep 2025 23:37:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-httpmaster-pro-1925.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-httpmaster-pro-1925.html
</guid><description>
A useful application for web developers who need to automate the test the web application by requesting multiple resources from a specified site web-based application. The professional version httpMaster in order to meet the requirements of many people when related to the test application. When working with HttpMaster Pro, most of the time you will manage the attributes and properties of the project HttpMaster of the items required in project. Project properties provides the global options...
</description></item><item><title>Download Office Timeline Plus 11.25.00.00 Expert / Pro / Pro+ Edition</title><pubDate> Mon, 01 Sep 2025 23:35:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-timeline-2106.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-timeline-2106.html
</guid><description>
Office Timeline is an add-on very useful and powerful software for Microsoft PowerPoint. With add-ons, you can create PowerPoint documents look more beautiful. With add-ons, you can add the time Line on the project by yourself. Application time for the composition and different segments of the document, your PowerPoint will not only increase the beauty for your work, but also for customers and your manager. The people who created this product is also believe that add-ons this is the only...
</description></item><item><title>Download doPDF 11.9.508</title><pubDate> Mon, 01 Sep 2025 23:34:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dopdf-923.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dopdf-923.html
</guid><description>
doPDF is software that converts any printable document how to PDF format. doPDF acts as a virtual printer for PDF documents. The program installs as a printer driver virtual and can be accessed from any application which supports printing.
doPDF which allows users to create PDF documents by choosing "Print" from any application and with only a single operation, you can convert your document such as Microsoft Excel, Word, PowerPoint or the email and the address of your favorite websites to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Calcpad 7.3.5</title><pubDate> Mon, 01 Sep 2025 23:34:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-calcpad-12576.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-calcpad-12576.html
</guid><description>
Calcpad is free software for mathematical and engineering calculations. It is a flexible and modern programmable calculator with Html report generator. Calcpad uses a simple programming language that is fast and easy to learn. It does not require any special programming skills, which makes it suitable for engineers without any computer programming background. You can create calculation notes simply by writing your formula and text, enclosed in 'quotation marks'.
The program includes...
</description></item><item><title>Download Freemake Video Converter Gold 5.0.0.12</title><pubDate> Mon, 01 Sep 2025 23:33:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-freemake-video-converter-gold-167.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-freemake-video-converter-gold-167.html
</guid><description>
Freemake Video Converter Gold is a software to help convert tail high quality videos with many different formats on many devices. Freemake Video Converter - convert video to AVI, MP4, WMV, MKV, 3GP, DVD, MP3, iPad, iPhone, PSP, Android phone. Video to MP3 just with one click! Rip and burn DVD. Convert YouTube to MP4, AVI, etc. with Freemake! Results guaranteed. Freemake Video Converter has fast conversion speed, guarantee the output quality,support create HTML5 videos have the embed code...
</description></item><item><title>Download Advanced Renamer Commercial 4.16</title><pubDate> Mon, 01 Sep 2025 23:33:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-renamer-2647.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-renamer-2647.html
</guid><description>
Advanced Renamer is a program to rename multiple files and folders at the same time. By configuring the method name change, the name can be manipulated in many different ways. It's easy to set up a batch job using multiple methods on a large number of files. 14 different modes allow you to change the name, attributes and timestamp of the file in once. The file can also be copied or moved to new location based on information in the file.
The program can rename files in many different ways,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Fast Video Cutter Joiner 6.9.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 01 Sep 2025 23:32:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fast-video-cutter-joiner-7542.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fast-video-cutter-joiner-7542.html
</guid><description>
Fast Video Cutter Joiner is a fast video cutter and joiner with an easy to use interface. It allows users to trim parts of a video quickly while maintaining the quality of the original video. It supports various formats like AVI, MPEG, MP4, WMV, 3GP, FLV...
This tool helps you to cut video files into small parts, to keep only the parts you need and remove unwanted parts like trailers and advertisements in a movie. The clips you cut can then be used for other video productions or for a...
</description></item><item><title>Download IsMyLcdOK 6.11</title><pubDate> Mon, 01 Sep 2025 23:32:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ismylcdok-4903.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ismylcdok-4903.html
</guid><description>
IsMyLcdOK is a small program but is effective solution to easily check the pixel dead / paralyzed / stuck on the LCD screen. Many manufacturers offer a policy point of death industrial standard highest. IsMyLcdOK does not have to installed and can be executed easily from the desktop, and can be carried on a small USB or memory device to another. Check the dead pixel is very simple.
Supported operating systems: Windows 10, Windows 10 Pro, Windows 10 Enterprise, Windows 10 Home, Windows...
</description></item><item><title>Download Chaos V-Ray 7.1 Build 7.10.00 for Blender 4.2 - 4.5</title><pubDate> Mon, 01 Sep 2025 23:31:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chaos-v-ray-for-blender-13913.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chaos-v-ray-for-blender-13913.html
</guid><description>
Chaos V-Ray for Blender is a professional, photorealistic rendering engine, now fully integrated into Blender, one of the most popular open source 3D creation tools. This tool brings Chaos' Emmy and Academy Award-winning rendering technology directly to Blender users, allowing for easy and efficient creation of high-quality images and animations.
Key Features:
	Realistic Rendering: Use Chaos' Global Illumination technology to create realistic lighting, reflections, shadows, and...
</description></item><item><title>Download FL Studio Producer Edition 25.1.4 Build 4951 All Plugins</title><pubDate> Mon, 01 Sep 2025 23:19:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-image-line-fl-studio-488.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-image-line-fl-studio-488.html
</guid><description>
Image Line FL Studio is software that provides an environment to produce and create music, open architecture, full-featured for computer. Image Line FL Studio owner, audio workstation digital this has everything you need in one package to compose, arrange, record, edit, mix and master music in professional quality.
With user interface graphics based on the music player FL Studio 20 is the fastest way to create any style of music with a kits and kits studio complete. The plugins, sounds...
</description></item><item><title>Download Atlantis Word Processor 4.4.6.6</title><pubDate> Mon, 01 Sep 2025 23:18:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-atlantis-word-processor-585.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-atlantis-word-processor-585.html
</guid><description>
Atlantis Word Processor is a word processor app with features format, standard text, autocorrect, and spell check.  Atlantis is a word processor in accordance with most of the tasks handled daily text. The interface is very easy to use and offers the toolbars, hotkeys and sound effects thanh can customize (can turn off). It includes a clip library for quick access to the text or images used regular preview, font format and many other features aimed at improving the process of your...
</description></item><item><title>Download AmoyShare BeeConverter Pro 1.7.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 01 Sep 2025 23:18:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-amoyshare-beeconverter-pro-7285.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-amoyshare-beeconverter-pro-7285.html
</guid><description>
BeeConverter Pro is a great application for video converter capable of converting multiple files simultaneously, converting videos for specific devices, handling multiple audio formats and video and most importantly, do all of this with 60x faster conversions. With its help, you can convert video or audio in any popular formats, such as MP4, MKV, AVI, FLV, WEBM and MP3, WMA, WAV, M4A, etc., as well as 4K video.
Features of BeeConverter Pro
	All popular video/audio formats are...
</description></item><item><title>Download CapCut PC 6.9.0.2786 / 7.0.0.2852 Beta 7</title><pubDate> Mon, 01 Sep 2025 23:17:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capcut-pc-9995.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capcut-pc-9995.html
</guid><description>
CapCut PC is a simple video editing tool that you can freely use anywhere. You can create videos on your browser, desktop and laptop, or on your phone. Versatile editing, magical AI tools, team collaboration, and built-in assets. Create videos in a whole new way.
You can edit videos based on editing the timeline, in the process you can add different elements and effects to the video to give the best effect to your work. It is a simple and intuitive set of editing tools and effects that...
</description></item><item><title>Download EverNote 10.153.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 01 Sep 2025 23:17:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-evernote-3261.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-evernote-3261.html
</guid><description>
EverNote is the all in one tool allows you to track notes, todo items, memos, outlines, excerpts, websites, ideas and other things and automatically synchronize them between multiple computers and mobile devices (iPhone, Android, etc.). You can choose to sort their notes into categories, password protect them, export them to XML and more. EverNote supports a number of pattern notes allow you to add to-do list, spreadsheet like Excel to calculate costs (automatic sum), notes, phone, contact...
</description></item><item><title>Download X-Ability Winmostar 11.13.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 01 Sep 2025 23:14:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-x-ability-winmostar-11156.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-x-ability-winmostar-11156.html
</guid><description>
Winmostar is an integrated GUI software designed for simulation programs such as GAMESS, MOPAC, LAMMPS, Gromacs and Quantum ESPRESSO. Winmostar serves as an integrated software solution, using programs (solvers) for MO, DFT and MD calculations as its backend. It provides pre- and post-processing capabilities, as well as file and process management functions. Software supported solvers include GAMESS, MOPAC, LAMMPS, Gromacs and Quantum ESPRESSO. Winmostar is designed to be installed and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Argente Registry Cleaner 4.0.2.7</title><pubDate> Mon, 01 Sep 2025 23:14:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-argente-registry-cleaner-13814.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-argente-registry-cleaner-13814.html
</guid><description>
Argente Registry Cleaner is a free Windows utility designed to scan, clean and repair invalid or obsolete entries in the Windows Registry, helping to improve system stability and performance. This utility quickly analyzes the entire Registry for errors such as invalid entries left by uninstalled programs, missing keys, broken references, and other junk that can cause system crashes.
Key Features:
	Fast and Thorough Scan: Provides multiple scan modes including Safe (fastest), Normal...
</description></item><item><title>Download MusConv 4.10.412 Lifetime</title><pubDate> Mon, 01 Sep 2025 23:13:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html
</guid><description>
MusConv transfers playlists, albums, followed artists and liked songs across a variety of services – Spotify, Apple Music, Amazon Music, YouTube, YouTube Music, iTunes, Deezer, Tidal, SoundCloud, Pandora and more 125 music services!
Features of MusConv Ultimate
	Transfer playlists, albums, followed artists and liked tracks between over 125 music servicesManage playlists (Delete, Merge, Split, Copy...)
	More than 125 music services supported
	Access DAILY updated music charts on...
</description></item><item><title>Download Argente Malware Cleaner 3.0.2.4</title><pubDate> Mon, 01 Sep 2025 23:13:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-argente-malware-cleaner-13494.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-argente-malware-cleaner-13494.html
</guid><description>
Argente Malware Cleaner is a lightweight utility designed to detect and remove a wide range of malware, including spyware, adware, Trojans and other threats that can compromise your privacy and data. It works as a complementary tool alongside your main antivirus software, helping to detect malware that may slip through the cracks.
Key features of Argente Malware Cleaner include:
	Easy-to-use, clean, and user-friendly interface that suits both casual and advanced users.
	Deep scanning...
</description></item><item><title>Download Argente System Repair 1.0.2.3</title><pubDate> Mon, 01 Sep 2025 23:12:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-argente-system-repair-13813.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-argente-system-repair-13813.html
</guid><description>
Argente System Repair is a lightweight utility designed to diagnose and fix common Windows system problems. It scans your system to identify errors in operating system components, file systems, installation files, and other system components, and then applies targeted fixes to resolve these problems. The tool provides different scan modes, including simple scan, recommended scan, and custom scan, allowing users to customize the repair process according to their needs.
System Repair...
</description></item><item><title>Download Franzis FOTO 3D #1 professional 1.12.04285</title><pubDate> Mon, 01 Sep 2025 20:29:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-franzis-foto-3d-professional-14127.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-franzis-foto-3d-professional-14127.html
</guid><description>
Powered by advanced AI, the system offers deep control over space, light, and atmosphere – for images that are not only striking, but also inspiring. The focus is on intelligent use of depth maps, which are automatically generated by advanced AI when photos are uploaded.
A standout feature is spatial exposure, which lets you place light in specific depth areas of an image—for example, a warm light in the foreground or a cool light in the background. Using adjustable radius and color...
</description></item><item><title>Download CMI Selection Manager 2026 v26.0.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 01 Sep 2025 20:16:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cad-masters-selection-manager-12544.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cad-masters-selection-manager-12544.html
</guid><description>
Selection Manager is an Autodesk AutoCAD add-in application that helps you easily save and restore objects that you have selected in your drawings. The selection manager can be used to quickly save and restore selection sets. Selection sets are saved in the drawing and can be used by anyone with the Selection Manager add-in application.
Features:
	Create a selection set from objects in the drawing
	Save selection set to drawing
	Run transparently at the Select Object prompt
	Add...
</description></item><item><title>Download RapidRAW 1.3.11</title><pubDate> Mon, 01 Sep 2025 17:09:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rapidraw-13957.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rapidraw-13957.html
</guid><description>
RapidRAW is a modern, high-performance, open-source RAW photo editor, designed to deliver a fast and clean editing experience with a lightweight footprint (under 30MB). Built with performance and usability in mind, the software is aimed at photographers who want a simple, efficient, and fun workflow without compromising performance.
Key Features
	GPU-accelerated processing: Uses a custom WGSL shader to process all image adjustments on the GPU, allowing for smooth, responsive editing...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sejda PDF Desktop Pro 7.9.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 01 Sep 2025 17:09:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sejda-pdf-desktop-pro-1301.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sejda-pdf-desktop-pro-1301.html
</guid><description>
Sejda PDF Desktop Pro is a professional PDF file action software with full features to help you with PDF tasks. Sejda PDF Desktop is used free of charge in the daily limit. Upgrade of advanced and non-limited features.
Sejda PDF Desktop Pro fully integrate PDF editing features from basic to complex such as document editing, file compression, page removal, inclusion or separation, page publication, PDF conversion. all in the same modern and efficient program.
Features of Sejda PDF...
</description></item><item><title>Download Agisoft Metashape Professional 2.2.2 Build 21069</title><pubDate> Mon, 01 Sep 2025 17:08:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-agisoft-metashape-professional-1731.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-agisoft-metashape-professional-1731.html
</guid><description>
Agisoft Metashape (formerly PhotoScan) is a software product independently perform image processing and digital data creation, 3D space used in GIS applications, material cultural heritage and the production visual effects as well as the indirect measurement of the different subjects scale. Technical digital photography is deployed wisely is applied with the method of computer vision led to the system processor, smart auto, on the one hand, can be managed by a new person in the field of...
</description></item></channel></rss>