<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 01:45:45 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 01:45:45 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Imagine 2.1.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 03 Aug 2025 00:22:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-imagine-7369.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-imagine-7369.html
</guid><description>
Imagine is an application that allows you to view images and animations in a variety of formats, including JPG, BMP, PNG and GIF. With Imagine you can view file properties and EXIF ​​information, copy, move, delete and rename images. Additionally, you can also flip, resize and rotate them, swap colors, set transparency levels, import, export, and edit palettes, and change color depth.
Features of Imagine
	View and save image/animation files at lightning speed
	Multiple...
</description></item><item><title>Download WavePad Sound Editor Master 20.35</title><pubDate> Sun, 03 Aug 2025 00:18:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wavepad-sound-editor-1149.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wavepad-sound-editor-1149.html
</guid><description>
WavePad Sound Editor is editor software and improve the quality of sound create recordings music best quality. WavePad is mootij in the editor software sound good for the computer are configured midrange and low. Because WavePad very compact only about 4MB of space is you already own the software editor sounds good.
WavePad Sound Editor - Side audio quality
WavePad help you edit audio created the Nightcore quality. WavePad Sound Editor there are many options is very impressive as add...
</description></item><item><title>Download PhotoPad Image Editor Pro 14.33</title><pubDate> Sun, 03 Aug 2025 00:18:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photopad-image-editor-572.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photopad-image-editor-572.html
</guid><description>
PhotoPad Image Editor is a software to help edit photos and supports lots of features like edit, cut, rotate, resize and flip digital photos. With PhotoPad Image Editor, you can freely perform the basic editing for their images and also can add some neat effect. It has the option to create a photo collage and mosaic images from your photos, and you can also add text and captions. If you prefer, you can complete your masterpiece by adding the frame or contour is simple.
The main features...
</description></item><item><title>Download Bitsum Process Lasso Pro 16.0.1.16</title><pubDate> Sun, 03 Aug 2025 00:18:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bitsum-process-lasso-pro-289.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bitsum-process-lasso-pro-289.html
</guid><description>
Bitsum Process Lasso Pro is software compact statistics and troubleshoot computer systems, such as crashes by control CPU. Technological process Lassos ProBalance (process balance) adjust the smart priority of running programs so that the process works poorly or too active will not affect the ability to use your computer!
Software Process Lasso to help manage the program or application will be managed and controlled to not have the ability to monopolize the CPU. Process Lasso also...
</description></item><item><title>Download WAU Manager 3.8.4.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 03 Aug 2025 00:17:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wau-manager-2911.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wau-manager-2911.html
</guid><description>
WAU Manager (manager automatic updates of Windows) is an alternative full-featured for interface Windows Updates integrated. The program gives you full control over the Windows Updates, you can decide when and how they are installed and it provides support uninstall and full maintenance for the Windows updates.
WAU Manager - controls Windows update
With WAU Manager you can update Windows manually when want just by a click on the keyboard shortcuts for the desktop, you can update...
</description></item><item><title>Download Switch Sound File Converter Plus 13.18</title><pubDate> Sun, 03 Aug 2025 00:17:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-switch-sound-file-converter-plus-1371.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-switch-sound-file-converter-plus-1371.html
</guid><description>
Switch Sound File Converter Plus is a premium software that helps you easily convert audio, convert audio to various formats for easy use on any device and all the different sounds. Switch Sound File Converter allows to convert between most audio formats as popular as WAV, MP3, MP2, WMA, M4A, OGG, AVI, FLAC, MOV, AMR, AAC, AU, AIFF.... Besides, the software also helps you extract audio directly from DVD and other Videos downloaded from the Internet under various formats such as AVI, MPEG,...
</description></item><item><title>Download ChrisPC Screen Recorder Pro 2.25.0802.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 03 Aug 2025 00:10:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-screen-recorder-pro-3020.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-screen-recorder-pro-3020.html
</guid><description>
ChrisPC Screen Recorder Pro is an application screen shot features and high efficiency allows you to easily record, enhance and share video online. The program can record any application running on your system. You can use a microphone to add words of your own narration to the video of your presentation. You can use this program to present how to use an application or website, to introduce the cursor to your game, to create guide, and more.
ChrisPC Screen Recorder Pro - Rotating, and...
</description></item><item><title>Download WavePad 20.35</title><pubDate> Sun, 03 Aug 2025 00:09:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wavepad-46.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wavepad-46.html
</guid><description>
WavePad is the sound editor allows you to create and edit recordings and audio files, supports a number of file formats including wav, mp3, vox, gsm, real audio, au, aif and more. It allows you to cut, copy and paste parts of recording and optionally apply effects like echo, amplification and noise reduction. In addition, you can insert silence, fade in / out, auto-trim and more.
WavePad supports sample rates from 6000 to 96000Hz, stereo or mono, 8, 16, or 32 bits. The program also...
</description></item><item><title>Download VideoPad Video Editor Pro 17.30</title><pubDate> Sun, 03 Aug 2025 00:09:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-videopad-video-editor-pro-268.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-videopad-video-editor-pro-268.html
</guid><description>
VideoPad Video Editor Pro is software edit video from any camcorder, DV camcorder, VHS player or webcam for best quality. The interface of this utility is divided into several parts (for example: list of multi-media, Effects, transitions, Files, Clips, video track, audio track, overlay), which makes everything seem difficult to operate. You can capture videos from camcorder or other devices like webcam or capture card TV and after you have added files and sequence clips to the queue, you...
</description></item><item><title>Download App Builder 2025.18</title><pubDate> Sun, 03 Aug 2025 00:09:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-app-builder-241.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-app-builder-241.html
</guid><description>
App Builder is a software application developer to help create and design apps, HTML5, web app, web app PWA on both platforms mobile and desktop. App Builder is professional software supports users to create the program HTML5 without writing code. It is very easy to use, suitable with all users who lack of professional knowledge in the field of programming and application design.
App Builder brings to 22 different themes that users can use to design for your app. You can choose 1 or a...
</description></item><item><title>Download ParkControl Pro 5.4.1.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 03 Aug 2025 00:08:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bitsum-parkcontrol-pro-6765.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bitsum-parkcontrol-pro-6765.html
</guid><description>
ParkControl Pro is free software to display and adjust CPU core settings in real time. It also has a bunch of free power automation features. Core Parking automatically disables CPU cores to save power when idle. Disabled cores are re-enabled as CPU load once again increases. This technology is very similar to frequency scaling, in that it seeks to throttle the CPU when idle.
These tweaks are completely safe for any properly configured PC. The only way they seem to be able to cause some...
</description></item><item><title>Download MixPad Masters Edition 13.32</title><pubDate> Sun, 03 Aug 2025 00:08:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mixpad-masters-edition-505.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mixpad-masters-edition-505.html
</guid><description>
MixPad Masters Edition is software mixing many different songs, mix music files available, or the recording is completed and combine them. MixPad Masters Edition is software recording and mixing music is designed to produce sounds easily. Mix music, vocal and audio, adjust the volume, pan, fade and more with MixPad as your digital mixing your.
MixPad Masters Edition will save the sound under the popular formats such as MP3,WAV, AIF, WMA, VOX, M4A, GSM,... user can create, add and remove...
</description></item><item><title>Download Clear Disk Info 4.4.1.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 03 Aug 2025 00:02:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-clear-disk-info-4956.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-clear-disk-info-4956.html
</guid><description>
Clear Disk Info is a utility statistics and health information for the storage devices like SSD, hdd and FLASH. This tool supports SMART monitoring, health diary, NvmE and the device is connected USB. Clear Disk Info will display information in a way user friendly, easy to read. it supports hard drives (HDD), solid state drive (SSD) and is also SSD NvmE latest.
Features of Clear Disk Info
	Lightweight and easy to use
	Get information on hard drive
	Display information user...
</description></item><item><title>Download HTML Compiler 2025.11</title><pubDate> Sun, 03 Aug 2025 00:02:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-html-compiler-2548.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-html-compiler-2548.html
</guid><description>
HTML Compiler is a program for Microsoft Windows (tm) allows you to put an entire HTML application (including HTML, CSS, JavaScript, images, etc.) into a Windows application independent can be executed like any other application window the application. HTML Compiler allows you to customize file real exam results by changing the icon of them and set some other options. For example, you can allow or not allow the ability to print the HTML pages, allow or disallow the text selection and many,...
</description></item><item><title>Download NCH PicoPDF Plus 7.19</title><pubDate> Sun, 03 Aug 2025 00:02:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nch-picopdf-plus-6856.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nch-picopdf-plus-6856.html
</guid><description>
NCH PicoPDF Plus is a simpler and lighter alternative to other popular PDF programs, such as Sumatra PDF and Foxit Reader. More, it can be used completely offline and not based on active internet connectivity to be able to perform some functions such as other similar software.
Features of NCH PicoPDF Plus
	Edit existing text or add new text
	Reorder text and graphics
	Add notes and comments to documents
	Delete or move embedded images
	Add an image to your PDF
	Enter in the space to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Doxillion Document Converter Plus 11.29</title><pubDate> Sun, 03 Aug 2025 00:01:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-doxillion-document-converter-plus-2928.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-doxillion-document-converter-plus-2928.html
</guid><description>
Doxillion Document Converter Plus is a lightweight app and comprehensive, allowing you to convert documents to many different file formats, provides intuitive interface and easy to use. The program also quick, which allows converting documents within minutes, with just a click of the mouse. It also allows you to convert multiple documents at once, saving time and effort.
Doxillion Document Converter Plus supports multiple file formats, including DOC, DOCX, PDF, RTF, TXT, WPS and HTML....
</description></item><item><title>Download DeskFX Audio Enhancer Plus 7.10</title><pubDate> Sun, 03 Aug 2025 00:01:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-deskfx-audio-enhancer-5543.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-deskfx-audio-enhancer-5543.html
</guid><description>
DeskFX Audio Enhancer applies real-time audio effects to play audio on your computer. DeskFX comes with an easy to use interface that allows you to enhance your audio. DeskFX audio enhancement software is designed for you to modify and enhance the music and sound played through your speakers and headphones, to give you the best audio experience possible.
DeskFX Audio Enhancer Features
	Sound effects including equalization, amplification, reverb, chorus, wahwah, vibrate, tremolo and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Crescendo Masters 11.20</title><pubDate> Sun, 03 Aug 2025 00:00:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-crescendo-masters-6038.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-crescendo-masters-6038.html
</guid><description>
Crescendo Masters is a simple and intuitive way to write music notation, Crescendo Masters allows composers to write, save and print their music works on their computers. A wide variety of music, time and sign symbols, along with the free-form layout, allows the composer to optimize the creation of the music for their arrangements.
The features of Crescendo Masters
	The visual interface to work with the music notation
	Set up your own professional quality music
	Composer for the film,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Argente System Repair 1.0.1.8</title><pubDate> Sat, 02 Aug 2025 23:59:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-argente-system-repair-13813.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-argente-system-repair-13813.html
</guid><description>
Argente System Repair is a lightweight utility designed to diagnose and fix common Windows system problems. It scans your system to identify errors in operating system components, file systems, installation files, and other system components, and then applies targeted fixes to resolve these problems. The tool provides different scan modes, including simple scan, recommended scan, and custom scan, allowing users to customize the repair process according to their needs.
System Repair...
</description></item><item><title>Download DiskCopy 1.4.4</title><pubDate> Sat, 02 Aug 2025 23:15:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-diskcopy-8043.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-diskcopy-8043.html
</guid><description>
DiskCopy is a user-friendly disk/partition cloning tool. DiskCopy has really cool features like MBR to GPT and GPT to MBR. You can choose the partition type of the destination disk, it does not have to be the same as the type of the source disk.
Features of DiskCopy
	Copy MBR to GPT and GPT to MBR. You can choose the partition type of the destination disk, it does not have to be the same as the type of the source disk.
	Always bootable. The destination disk can be booted even if the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Flyby11 0.40.64</title><pubDate> Sat, 02 Aug 2025 23:13:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-flyby11-12467.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-flyby11-12467.html
</guid><description>
Flyby11 is a simple patcher that removes annoying restrictions that prevent you from installing Windows 11 (24H2) on unsupported hardware. Do you have an old PC? No TPM, Secure Boot or your processor is not supported? Flyby11 allows you to install Windows 11 24H2. There are no complicated steps. Just run the tool and you'll be running Windows 11 on your outdated machine in no time.
Technical overview
Flyby11 takes advantage of a feature of the Windows 11 setup process that uses the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Blank And Secure 8.18</title><pubDate> Sat, 02 Aug 2025 23:12:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blank-and-secure-2934.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blank-and-secure-2934.html
</guid><description>
Blank And Secure is a application lightweight and portable allows you to completely erase your sensitive data without possibility to restore. This add-on accomplish this by overwriting your files with zeros (0) before you delete them. This method is also called "zeroing data / drives". You should know that once completed, the complete data can't be recovered, so you should only use this tool if you want to permanently delete your files.
Blank And Secure - Delete data permanently
Blank...
</description></item><item><title>Download Telegram for Desktop 6.0.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 02 Aug 2025 23:12:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-telegram-3376.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-telegram-3376.html
</guid><description>
Telegram is an instant messaging service and voice over IP services on the cloud platform. Client application Telegram is available for Android, iOS, Windows Phone, Windows NT, macOS, and Linux. Users can send messages and exchange photos, videos, stickers, audio and files of any kind.
Telegram - Messaging and free phone calls
Telegram seamless sync across all your devices and can be used on desktop, tablet and phone. You can send unlimited amount of messages, photos, videos and files...
</description></item><item><title>Download Argente Malware Cleaner 3.0.1.9</title><pubDate> Sat, 02 Aug 2025 23:06:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-argente-malware-cleaner-13494.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-argente-malware-cleaner-13494.html
</guid><description>
Argente Malware Cleaner is a lightweight utility designed to detect and remove a wide range of malware, including spyware, adware, Trojans and other threats that can compromise your privacy and data. It works as a complementary tool alongside your main antivirus software, helping to detect malware that may slip through the cracks.
Key features of Argente Malware Cleaner include:
	Easy-to-use, clean, and user-friendly interface that suits both casual and advanced users.
	Deep scanning...
</description></item><item><title>Download ExpressVPN 12.104.0.128</title><pubDate> Sat, 02 Aug 2025 23:05:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-expressvpn-422.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-expressvpn-422.html
</guid><description>
ExpressVPN software is the virtual private network for the computer are fast speed, highly secure, ultra-high, easy-to-use, quickly installed. The user-friendly app with our users allows you security connect and access any site just by a click of the mouse. Just log in, install and connect.
VPN network ExpressVPN is protected by encryption best-in-class based on 4096-CA. We continually optimize your network to provide high speeds to you can browse the web constantly, and broadcast and...
</description></item></channel></rss>