<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 13:50:36 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 13:50:36 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Universal Media Server 15.3.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 11 Jan 2026 16:50:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-universal-media-server-2364.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-universal-media-server-2364.html
</guid><description>
Universal Media Server is a media server UPnP compatible multi-platform DLNA. The purpose of this software is to give you a chance to stabilize to make the exchange quick and convenient files necessary. Server the device supports the different output and facilitate the process of exchanging information between a computer and necessary equipment. The development is based on PS3 Media Server, which means you can interact with the Playstation 3, Xbox 360, as well as TV Samsung or...
</description></item><item><title>Download Clean Media Player 2026.1.10.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 11 Jan 2026 16:49:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-clean-media-player-12416.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-clean-media-player-12416.html
</guid><description>
If you've ever been offended by profanity in a movie, chances are you'll want the censored version of the movie. However, until the director decides to release it, you still have the option of muting unwanted scenes or editing the subtitles manually, if you are able to do so. The application mutes and displays subtitles without offensive words and phrases. Customize the profanity filter to your preferences. Skip inappropriate scenes by selecting their start and end times.
Clean Media...
</description></item><item><title>Download Robin YouTube Video Downloader Pro 7.1.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 11 Jan 2026 16:49:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-video-downloader-pro-2828.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-video-downloader-pro-2828.html
</guid><description>
YouTube Video Downloader Pro is a Windows application professional to download and convert videos from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion and thousands of video sharing sites, other. It accelerates your download up to 5 times. YouTube Video Downloader Pro allows you to download multiple videos at the same time. It also allows you to pause, resume and cancel a download at any time.
YouTube Video Downloader Pro - Download online videos on social networks
Features of YouTube Video Downloader...
</description></item><item><title>Download DeskCalc Pro 10.0.6</title><pubDate> Sun, 11 Jan 2026 16:48:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-deskcalc-pro-1874.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-deskcalc-pro-1874.html
</guid><description>
DeskCalc Pro is a math tool can perform a variety of calculations, such as addition, subtraction, multiplication and division, as well as use trigonometric functions like sine, cosine, tangent and other functions. In addition, the program DeskCalc Pro also provides tools currency converter. Software DeskCalc Pro quite easy to perform many math operations, thanks to the support tab of it. Can export data created to Excel.
DeskCalc Pro - mathematical tools
Moreover, DeskCalc Pro allows...
</description></item><item><title>Download LuBan 3D 04.01.2026</title><pubDate> Sun, 11 Jan 2026 16:47:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-luban-3d-10427.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-luban-3d-10427.html
</guid><description>
LuBan 3D is creative design software that helps designers and manufacturers create their innovative products quickly. LuBan automatically creates 3D models in a variety of forms, such as lithophane, stacks, hashes, slabs, reliefs, modules, and wireframes. The resulting model can be fabricated by 3D printing, laser cutting and CNC milling. Model parts can be fabricated using laser cutting and 3D printing. LuBan does not depend on specific fabrication methods; instead, it can communicate...
</description></item><item><title>Download LINQPad Premium 9.5.10</title><pubDate> Sun, 11 Jan 2026 16:46:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-linqpad-premium-7181.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-linqpad-premium-7181.html
</guid><description>
LINQPad is a software utility targeting .NET Framework and .NET Core development. It is used to interactively query SQL databases using LINQ, as well as to write C# code interactively without an IDE. LINQPad will be where C# code can be rapidly prototyped outside of Visual Studio. It can also be used to code in VB.NET, SQL and F#.
With LINQPad, you can interactively query databases using a modern query language: LINQ. LINQPad includes a tool optimized for on-the-fly context creation of...
</description></item><item><title>Download TubeDownload Pro 7.1.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 11 Jan 2026 16:46:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubedownload-pro-12035.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubedownload-pro-12035.html
</guid><description>
TubeDownload Pro is a professional Windows application for downloading your favorite videos from YouTube and hundreds of other video sites. TubeDownload Pro can increase download speed up to 500% or even more.
Features of TubeDownload Pro
	Download your favorite videos from YouTube and hundreds of other video sites.
	Increase download speed up to 500% or even more.
	Download 720p, 1080p, 2K, 4K and 8K HD videos from YouTube.
	Download entire playlists in just a few clicks.
	Download...
</description></item><item><title>Download DesktopOK 12.26</title><pubDate> Sun, 11 Jan 2026 16:37:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopok-1635.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopok-1635.html
</guid><description>
DesktopOK is software save and restore the positions of icons. DesktopOK also offers a solution small but effective for the user to change the screen resolution often. DesktopOK is not installed and can be executed easily from the desktop, and can be carried on a small USB or memory device to another. Start of the program. The first time you use the program, the program will show you screen license. Free program and license info is only displayed the first time (on each PC).
DesktopOK -...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft OneDrive 25.224.1116.0003</title><pubDate> Sun, 11 Jan 2026 16:36:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-onedrive-48.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-onedrive-48.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft OneDrive is a client application file transmission to the service cloud storage of Microsoft. If you are familiar with Dropbox, you will find that OneDrive works in a similar way. It creates a OneDrive folder and any files you copy into the folder will automatically be synced and uploaded to the cloud service OneDrive.
Microsoft OneDrive
You can access your files from the client application other on PC. Mac or mobile devices as well as web interface. OneDrive also allows you...
</description></item><item><title>Download iDefender 5.3.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 10 Jan 2026 22:58:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idefender-13959.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idefender-13959.html
</guid><description>
iDefender is an advanced security solution designed for the home, providing both a High-Performance Intrusion Prevention System (HIPS) and Real-Time Endpoint Detection and Response (EDR). This integrated system protects against potential threats, ensuring the safety and integrity of your devices by proactively monitoring and responding to suspicious activity.
Why iDefender?
Ransomware Prevention
	Detects and blocks ransomware in real time to protect important files from malicious...
</description></item><item><title>Download PrivaZer 4.0.116</title><pubDate> Sat, 10 Jan 2026 22:57:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-privazer-66.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-privazer-66.html
</guid><description>
PrivaZer : the program performs the scan is very thorough not only includes the trace downloads like registration, Internet history, cookies, etc but also find the traces of potential in the field of free disk space of you. PrivaZer can permanently delete all traces by using the method of secure erase and also re-establish the sector disk free to 0 to remove all traces from the delete operation earlier. The process of scanning and cleaning the original can spend less time (20-30 minutes),...
</description></item><item><title>Download pdfFactory Pro 9.20</title><pubDate> Sat, 10 Jan 2026 18:29:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdffactory-pro-277.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdffactory-pro-277.html
</guid><description>
pdfFactory Pro is software to create PDF files according to standards in a simple and secure documents secure. pdfFactory Pro on taiwebs.com that support encryption (40 or 128bit) and control access to the PDF file.
pdfFactory Pro has all the features of pdfFactory and adds bookmarks, job order, title a letter and the email function automatically. Only pdfFactory allows printing to paper or PDF without printing twice. Acrobat is not needed for the printing. Increases the convenience of...
</description></item><item><title>Download reaConverter Pro 8.0.178</title><pubDate> Sat, 10 Jan 2026 18:29:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html
</guid><description>
reaConverter Pro is software image processing feature with batch conversion and image editing periodically becomes simple. eaConverter also provide command line utilities allow you to process images automatically, thus helping you shorten the time for other work.
reaConverter Pro integrated powerful tool of Uber with many great features. It provides advanced solutions to process and adjust images. Management of the conversion process the base image with the latest version of...
</description></item><item><title>Download WYSIWYG Web Builder 20.4.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 10 Jan 2026 18:29:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wysiwyg-web-builder-177.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wysiwyg-web-builder-177.html
</guid><description>
WYSIWYG Web Builder : The construction of the website from scratch using HTML code isn't a pleasant process, even when you know what you are doing. The website can be built using WYSIWYG Web Builder with using the element similar to the package published on the desktop: text and images placed in frames and tables on the page, so very little surprised when most of the efforts to make the web become a experience user-friendly than. the controls do you use to build your pages.
WYSIWYG Web...
</description></item><item><title>Download Corel Painter 2023 v23.0.0.255</title><pubDate> Sat, 10 Jan 2026 18:28:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-corel-painter-1847.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-corel-painter-1847.html
</guid><description>
Corel Painter is the photo editing software comprehensive help quickly change the quality, add effects to the images in a simple way, the tool also supports users to blur, creating a new picture... with the tools available pen color water color pencils... and other colors for users to design, build is a photo comments. Corel Painter will help the artist finishing the limitations are not there in the picture of her by the designer for this include the effects generated material oil...
</description></item><item><title>Download FinePrint 12.20</title><pubDate> Sat, 10 Jan 2026 18:27:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fineprint-276.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fineprint-276.html
</guid><description>
FinePrint is a software support you work in text saves paper and increases the lifespan of your printer. FinePrint is a software connected printer, you can print 4 or 8 pages file on the computer on a page of paper that still ensure the font is clear, easy to read.
With FinePrint works for you, the incidents of printing annoyances will disappear. Below are just some examples of incidents in which FinePrint can fix. Read more part of our Business for the benefit of the FinePrint in the...
</description></item><item><title>Download ManicTime Pro 2025.3.6.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 10 Jan 2026 18:27:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-manictime-18.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-manictime-18.html
</guid><description>
ManicTime is a software automatically collect information about how to use your computer. It records the time of operation of the machine, see the change data in the machine, how much data you share, received on or moved away, what software you use, use at any time
ManicTime allows you to keep up the work of the staff, send progress reports accurately and manage your time better than ever. This type of software can help your business more efficient when it comes to the internal problems...
</description></item><item><title>Download Secret Disk Pro 2026 v317</title><pubDate> Sat, 10 Jan 2026 18:26:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secret-disk-pro-933.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secret-disk-pro-933.html
</guid><description>
Secret Disk Pro 4 is a software to create a virtual disk can be hidden and password protected to keep your data private and safe. You can store any file and folder on the disk. Disc secret works like a hard disk typically, and is compatible with any any other program that you have installed. You can have more than one disk secret, and you can also choose disk letter.
Secret Disk Pro 4 - Create and secure drive
Secret Disk does not encrypt any files, it just limits access to your files...
</description></item><item><title>Download Bigasoft Video Downloader Pro 3.28.8.9497</title><pubDate> Sat, 10 Jan 2026 18:26:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bigasoft-video-downloader-pro-940.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bigasoft-video-downloader-pro-940.html
</guid><description>
Bigasoft Video Downloader Pro  is an online video downloader and converter from YouTube and other online movies to play on personal computers, mobile devices, mobile phones, players MP4 music, TV and easier. Video Downloader can save online video as HD, HQ and 3D movies, then convert to MP4, AVI, WMV, MOV, MKV, FLV, MPG, VOB, etc. for playback on a variety of great digital devices. iPad mini, iPad, iPod, iPhone, Google Nexus, Microsoft Surface, Kindle Fire, BlackBerry, Apple TV, Zune, PSP,...
</description></item><item><title>Download CoolUtils Total Image Converter 8.2.0.290</title><pubDate> Sat, 10 Jan 2026 18:25:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-total-image-converter-848.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-total-image-converter-848.html
</guid><description>
CoolUtils Total Image Converter is software to convert images to other formats, and can edit, cut, resize and rotate them. With Total Image Converter you easy convert TIFFs into JPEGS, make photos suitable for the web or recover old photos in the supported format.
&amp;nbsp;CoolUtils Total Image Converter - convert images to other formats
Features CoolUtils Total Image Converter
	Total Image Converter supports almost all image formats
	Support convert eagle picture series.
	Total Image...
</description></item><item><title>Download Memtest86 Pro 11.6 Build 1000 + ISO</title><pubDate> Sat, 10 Jan 2026 18:25:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-memtest86-pro-725.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-memtest86-pro-725.html
</guid><description>
Memtest86 Pro is software check free RAM memory in your computer to detect the latent fault inside the memory. Anyone know RAM is very important part of the computer. If RAM is error that does not fix soon will greatly affect your computer. Therefore, the Memtest86 Pro is the software necessary for the system of your computer.
Memtest86 Pro - Check memory RAM
Features of Memtest86 Pro
	13 algorithm to check RAM different
	Support RAM DDR4 (and DDR2 &amp;amp; DDR3)
	XMP - configuration...
</description></item><item><title>Download Chaos Intellect 10.7</title><pubDate> Sat, 10 Jan 2026 18:24:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chaos-intellect-4213.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chaos-intellect-4213.html
</guid><description>
Chaos Intellect is the email application and the contact management the next generation of our all in one great program! We will give you five good reasons to switch from app to email your ex and turn Intellect into the email program you choose! If you are looking for a contact manager without email integration, we also made. Chaos Intellect Email client and contact manager. The latest addition to our line, our products have big success since its release and is ready for Vista! Continue...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Video Downloader 12.1.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 10 Jan 2026 18:23:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-video-downloader-9636.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-video-downloader-9636.html
</guid><description>
YT Video Downloader is software used to easily and quickly download any video or audio content from any website in HD quality using video downloader online. Save videos from almost any website supported by a video downloader on your local hard drive. Media search is a convenient way to do this.
Features of YT Video Downloader
	Download videos from hundreds of video sites.
	Really increase your download speed by up to 500% or even more!
	Download 8K, 5K, 4K Ultra HD, 2K Quad HD, 1080p...
</description></item><item><title>Download Bigasoft Audio Converter 5.8.2.9497</title><pubDate> Sat, 10 Jan 2026 18:23:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bigasoft-audio-converter-6059.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bigasoft-audio-converter-6059.html
</guid><description>
Bigasoft Audio Converter is an easy sound conversion tool, which provides a quick way to convert favorites between most formats including MP3, WMA, M4A, AAC, AC3, WAV, OGG, AIFF, ALAC, CAF, etc. The digital conversion to sound can be used as MP3 converge, WMA converge, M4A converge, etc.
Moreover, the MP3 sound converge supports bulk transformation, so you can handle multiple transfers at the same time and place the starting point and time to listen to your great music videos....
</description></item><item><title>Download NTFS Permissions Reporter Enterprise 5.0.628.0 All Editions</title><pubDate> Sat, 10 Jan 2026 18:22:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ntfs-permissions-reporter-enterprise-6370.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ntfs-permissions-reporter-enterprise-6370.html
</guid><description>
System administrators are constantly required to check user rights for specific files and folders. This is often a time-consuming work, with multiple NTFS classes and repetitive adjustments over time creating a security maze. NTFS Permissions Reporter Enterprise allows you to confirm the security status of the entire file system quickly and efficiently. All have multiple export formats, command line support, integration scheduling, advanced filtration, and more.
Features of NTFS...
</description></item></channel></rss>