<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 13:56:24 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 13:56:24 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download 7-Zip 25.01</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 16:25:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-7-zip-446.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-7-zip-446.html
</guid><description>
7Zip is a file storage and open source, provide high compression rate, the most used format f new 7z, bringing compression results are better than 30-50% compared with the ZIP standard. We have tested it with a log file, server is compressed with ZIP had a file size of 18 mb and using 7-Zip was reduced to 8 mb (results may vary, depending on the file type).
In addition, 7Zip also supports the formats 7z, ZIP, CAB, RAR, ARJ, GZIP, BZIP2, TAR, CPIO, RPM and DEB, so it can also be used...
</description></item><item><title>Download DAR - Disk ARchive 2.8.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 16:20:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dar-disk-archive-9009.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dar-disk-archive-9009.html
</guid><description>
DAR is a command line backup and archiving tool that uses selective compression (does not compress compressed files), strong encryption, can split archives into different files of certain size and provide fast hashing, supporting differential backups with or without delta , ftp and sftp binaries for remote cloud storage.
Internal storage directory, allowing very fast recovery of even a single file from a huge archive, finally trimmed, compressed, encrypted finally placed on a cloud...
</description></item><item><title>Download StartAllBack 3.9.13.5291</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 16:18:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-startallback-6857.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-startallback-6857.html
</guid><description>
With the official release of Windows 11, chances are that most of you want to try it out. As the name suggests, StartAllBack is a small, lightweight tool that can help you enjoy the power of the new operating system while keeping the look and feel, especially because main work area, desktop of Windows 7, Windows 10 as taskbars and start menu styles.
StartAllBack is specially designed for Windows 11 and will not work on any older operating systems. If you want to get the start menu back...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mocha Pro for Adobe 2025 v12.5.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 16:17:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mocha-pro-1029.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mocha-pro-1029.html
</guid><description>
Mocha Pro 2019 is the tool for visual effects and postproduction. Tool Tracking and VFX and is plugins for Adobe. Mocha is the artist and editor effects appreciate about the unique ability of his to reduce the time using keyframing related to VFX and premium finishing.
Mocha Pro 2019
Mocha Pro 2019 features track and remove objects that are GPU acceleratedtools, rotoscoping, advanced, stable, solved 3D camera, supports stereo 360 / VR, etc. Using Mocha AE CC in Adobe After Effects? See...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Downloader 9.15.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 16:17:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html
</guid><description>
YTD Youtube Downloader is an application that reliable and intuitive, allowing you to quickly download YouTube videos and save them to your computer. You can also convert the media files to the format desired video or extract audio streams and save separately. YTD Youtube Downloader lets you save your favorite clips of yourself from Youtube, Facebook, Vimeo and Dailymotion to your desktop. The software supports URLS from many web site hosting, multimedia and allows you to download desired...
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 7.0.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 16:15:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-11-7760.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-11-7760.html
</guid><description>
TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 is a program that allows users to discover hidden settings in Windows 11. This application is specially designed for Windows 11, groups many registry settings and distribute them from the easy and secure user interface. With TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 you can move the Windows taskbar to the top and resize the taskbar by editing the registry value. With any application that modifies the registry, we recommend that you have a backup copy...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mocha Pro for OFX 2025 v12.5.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 16:15:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mocha-pro-for-ofx-4303.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mocha-pro-for-ofx-4303.html
</guid><description>
Mocha Pro for OFX is the tracking tool flat the world's most powerful for VFX and postproduction. With the tracking feature and remove objects that are GPU accelerated, mask advanced with snapshot feature edge, stable, corrective lens, the 3D camera, supports stereo 360 / VR, v. v. Mocha Pro for OFX is a plugin for Adobe Premiere Pro &amp;amp; After Effects, servers Avid Media Composer &amp;amp; OFX as Flame, Nuke, Fusion, HitFilm, and VEGAS Pro.
Mocha Pro for OFX 2020
New features in version...
</description></item><item><title>Download DNSQuerySniffer 1.97</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 16:14:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dnsquerysniffer-1762.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dnsquerysniffer-1762.html
</guid><description>
DNSQuerySniffer is a network utility to track all DNS queries are sent from your system in real-time and reports them in a list can sort, along with the port number, IP address, request type, response code and other details. With DNSQuerySniffer you can sort the report by column header, and optionally export the selected items to HTML reports.
DNSQuerySniffer - Monitor DNS queries
DNSQuerySniffer does not require installation, meaning that it can carry is and you just drop the EXE file...
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 7.0.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 16:13:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-10-7759.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-10-7759.html
</guid><description>
TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 is a utility that allows users to discover hidden settings in Windows 10. This application is specially designed for Windows 10, groups many registry settings and provide them from an easy and secure user interface. With TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 you can move the Windows taskbar to the top and resize the taskbar by editing the registry value. With any application that modifies the registry, we recommend that you have a backup copy to...
</description></item><item><title>Download NirLauncher Package 1.30.20</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 16:13:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nirlauncher-152.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nirlauncher-152.html
</guid><description>
NirLauncher is a package of more than 200 freeware utilities developed by Nirsoft, the NirLauncher application is provided free of charge for easy selection, use by feature classification. . Popular Nirsoft Utilities (many of them listed separately on taiwebs.com) NirLauncher includes network tools, password recovery tools, security cleaners, system utilities, programming tools, command line utilities and more.
NirLauncher's Versatile Utility
With this NirLauncher utility, users can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Agisoft Metashape Professional 2.2.2 Build 20889</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 16:12:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-agisoft-metashape-professional-1731.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-agisoft-metashape-professional-1731.html
</guid><description>
Agisoft Metashape (formerly PhotoScan) is a software product independently perform image processing and digital data creation, 3D space used in GIS applications, material cultural heritage and the production visual effects as well as the indirect measurement of the different subjects scale. Technical digital photography is deployed wisely is applied with the method of computer vision led to the system processor, smart auto, on the one hand, can be managed by a new person in the field of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Abelssoft SendMe (Send2Phone) 2025 v1.05</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 16:12:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-abelssoft-send2phone-2198.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-abelssoft-send2phone-2198.html
</guid><description>
Abelssoft Send2Phone is a program that allows you to send files from personal computer to phone your mobile, you can now easily share links, images, any files from PC to mobile or vice versa. Traffic will be encrypted using AES-256, so the authors assure you that you should not worry about blocking data, but I won't believe in a hundred percent. Thanks to the user interface simple, clear and pleasant. you can send the file just by a click of the mouse, the software can be integrated into...
</description></item><item><title>Download dBpoweramp Image Converter Premier R2025-08-01</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 16:11:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbpoweramp-image-converter-7007.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbpoweramp-image-converter-7007.html
</guid><description>
dBpoweramp Image Converter is a simple visual transformation application that aims to make the transition as simple as possible. dBpoweramp Image Converter will switch between all popular formats, Bitmap, PNG, JPEG, TIFF and many other formats. It also has the ability to make mass transformation for multiple files and folders with only one click and filter on the png or other types of files.
dBpoweramp Image Converter is capable of switching high speed by using simultaneously all CPU...
</description></item><item><title>Download FanControl v229</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 16:02:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fancontrol-5749.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fancontrol-5749.html
</guid><description>
FanControl is a highly customizable fan control software for Windows. Stay in control of every aspect of your PC's GPU and CPU fan with the help of this highly customizable fan control app.
Features of FanControl
	Save, edit and load multiple configurations
	Multiple temperature sources (CPU, GPU, motherboard, hard drive, ".sensor" files)
	Custom fan curve
	Fine tune fan control response with steps,% start,% stop, response time and delay
	Mix different curves and sensors...
</description></item><item><title>Download QuadSpinner Gaea 2.2.0.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 16:01:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quadspinner-gaea-3870.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quadspinner-gaea-3870.html
</guid><description>
QuadSpinner Gaea is design software terrain, sophisticated and modern for results the top in moments. The top tools of QuadSpinner Gaea makes realism became the basis. Workflows are streamlined, allowing you to easily gain visibility and work in parallel with your team. Interface is extremely modern and our multitude of gadgets stimulate creativity, not limit it. Working at Gaea very interesting and can help you set a performance standard new.
QuadSpinner Gaea - design software...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sante DICOM Viewer Pro 14.2.4</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 16:00:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sante-dicom-viewer-pro-11761.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sante-dicom-viewer-pro-11761.html
</guid><description>
Sante DICOM Viewer Pro is a professional DICOM viewer, anonymizer, converter, PACS client, mini PACS server, patient CD/DVD burner (with viewer) and more. This is a unique program with unique capabilities, designed and developed by us in-house from the ground up, with the most advanced programming tools and is the result of extensive research and development on DICOM image over the past two decades. Sante DICOM Viewer Pro has been developed since 1999 and is one of the most popular...
</description></item><item><title>Download Robin YouTube Video Downloader Pro 6.15.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 16:00:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-video-downloader-pro-2828.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-video-downloader-pro-2828.html
</guid><description>
YouTube Video Downloader Pro is a Windows application professional to download and convert videos from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion and thousands of video sharing sites, other. It accelerates your download up to 5 times. YouTube Video Downloader Pro allows you to download multiple videos at the same time. It also allows you to pause, resume and cancel a download at any time.
YouTube Video Downloader Pro - Download online videos on social networks
Features of YouTube Video Downloader...
</description></item><item><title>Download Easy Gamer Utility Pro 1.3.78</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 15:53:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easy-gamer-utility-pro-12381.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easy-gamer-utility-pro-12381.html
</guid><description>
Easy Gamer Utility Pro is an easy-to-use program for Windows that can do a lot on your PC to help fix gaming problems, performance problems, and general optimization! The best tool to improve your Windows gaming experience! Is your game laggy and slow? If so, you can use the built-in game accelerator in Easy Gamer Utility, which boosts system performance, makes games run smoother, and increases FPS.
Additionally, this handy utility deletes and cleans unwanted and unnecessary temporary...
</description></item><item><title>Download MPV-EASY Player 0.40.0.3</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 15:53:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mpv-easy-player-3110.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mpv-easy-player-3110.html
</guid><description>
MPV-EASY Player is movies player based on mpv. It comes with easy to use interface, you can quickly adjust many parameters, the default settings are carefully adjusted will be able to stimulate all the performance of the mpv, so use mpv player simple than before a lot.
Basically, MPV-EASY Player is the assembly and combination of MPV, configuring mpv files, the command lua (including all scripts to be shared by other people on github), and the command js with the to read and fully...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tomabo MP4 Downloader Pro 5.6.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 15:52:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tomabo-mp4-downloader-pro-3602.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tomabo-mp4-downloader-pro-3602.html
</guid><description>
Tomabo MP4 Downloader Pro is the app designed exclusively for Windows users to help them download videos from the Internet. In addition, it also increase download speeds by up to 500%, or even more. Tomabo MP4 Downloader Pro, interface design, simple, well-organized, beautifully. Here, users can view a list of videos has download with gravatar, URL, quality, duration and size of them. Software allows download video series at the same time, at the same time, support create a list of clips...
</description></item><item><title>Download Social Media Downloader 7.6.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 15:52:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-socialmediaapps-facebook-video-downloader-3742.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-socialmediaapps-facebook-video-downloader-3742.html
</guid><description>
SocialVideo Downloader (formerly SocialMediaApps Facebook Video Downloader) is a Windows application to download and convert your favorite videos from Facebook and hundreds of other video sharing sites. It increases your loading speed by up to 500%, or even more! The application has a simple and intuitive user interface, its main functions and features are quite obvious to anyone. , regardless of prior experience with similar purpose tools.
&amp;nbsp;
SocialVideo Downloader
The main...
</description></item><item><title>Download 4KSoftware 4K Downloader 5.16.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 15:51:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-downloader-3858.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-downloader-3858.html
</guid><description>
4K Downloader is a Windows application small but powerful to download and convert video in 4K and 8K Ultra HD from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion and thousands of other video-based websites. It speeds up your download by up to 5 times. Consider that most smart phones, TVS, computers, and tablets all support the high definition format, don't be surprised when many users want to enjoy quality content on their device. 4K Downloader is a lightweight software designed to help you grab videos...
</description></item><item><title>Download Automatic Email Processor 3.8.10</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 15:51:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-automatic-email-processor-702.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-automatic-email-processor-702.html
</guid><description>
Automatic Email Processor is a software for managing Email in Outlook efficiency by automatically working with predefined settings. The user interface is divided into two main parts, which is the area allows you to view a list of profiles that you have created and their status and the filters located in the lower part of the interface.
Automatic Email Processor is a comprehensive solution in the archive and print emails and attachments on Outlook fully-automatic. Therefore, you can create...
</description></item><item><title>Download Shutter Encoder 19.3</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 15:51:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-shutter-encoder-6837.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-shutter-encoder-6837.html
</guid><description>
Shutter Encoder is an easy-to-use program to convert, edit and encode images, videos, audio files and more. Shutter Encoder is a video, audio and image converter based on FFmpeg and other great tools. It has been designed by video editors to be as accessible and effective as possible.
Features of Shutter Encoder:
	Cut without re-encoding, Replace Audio, Rewind, Edit, Merge, Extract, Subtitle, Insert Video
	Audio Converter: WAV, AIFF, FLAC, MP3, AAC, AC3, OPUS, OGG
	Edit codecs: DNxHD,...
</description></item><item><title>Download QuickViewer 1.2.5</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 15:50:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quickviewer-3263.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quickviewer-3263.html
</guid><description>
QuickViewer is a image viewer, graphics to browse from the comfort multiple images. The software performs read image data first. And drawing the image data entered on the screen using OpenGL. You can browse picture with response smoother than ever.
QuickViewer - fast picture viewer
The features of the QuickViewer
To display images very quickly (using OpenGL)
Portable (no installation, registration, library, external)
Tablet ready
See page spread 2 pages (two photos, a times, for books...
</description></item></channel></rss>