<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 23:46:18 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 23:46:18 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download XYplorer 28.00.1200</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 00:24:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-533.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-533.html
</guid><description>
XYplorer - File Manager for Windows is software that supports users to manage files on the Window quickly and to arrange the folder tidy. XYplorer features tabbed browsing, search, files, powerful, preview, flexible, highly customizable interface, dual frame options and a variety of unique ways to automate effective tasks often repeat. It's fast, lightweight, and portable.
Features XYplorer
	XYplorer is a file manager mobile. It does not require any settings, store all configuration...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDF Annotator 10.0.0.1003</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 00:23:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-annotator-178.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-annotator-178.html
</guid><description>
PDF Annotator software user open any PDF file and add annotations, using the mouse or pen Tablet PC, directly on the Page of the PDF file. PDF Annotator allows users to perform editing operations on PDF files such as: add notes, edit signature, highlight, insert images or text... From the this useful tool, you can completely modify PDF files as you like in order to meet the different work.
PDF Annotator
With the PDF Annotator the document has annotations can then be saved directly back...
</description></item><item><title>Download OCCT 15.0.9.99</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 00:23:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-occt-perestroika-1680.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-occt-perestroika-1680.html
</guid><description>
OCCT is a free application designed to benchmark and overclock system components. Test tool OverClock includes 4 different tests to assess the stability of your computer. CPU and CPU: Linpack to test the processor, GPU: 3D to check stability of the graphics processor and power supply combination of CPU: Linpack and GPU: 3D to download power of you up to the maximum.
OCCT - Measuring system components
The features of OCCT
	Support is enabled for a maximum of 16 cores.
	All the tests...
</description></item><item><title>Download DVD-Cloner XR Gold 22.10.1492</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 00:22:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dvd-cloner-gold-platinum-270.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dvd-cloner-gold-platinum-270.html
</guid><description>
DVD-Cloner Gold Platinum is a DVD copy software professional with high image quality perfect output, can decrypt and copy DVD to any blank disc with the copy modes varied for playback on many multimedia devices such as PS4, Xbox, Blu-ray, etc. besides, it can also copy a DVD to an ISO file or DVD folder saved on HDD of you.
DVD-Cloner Gold Platinum
With DVD-Cloner 2018, you can backup Blu-ray to BD-R / RE or to your computer and rip DVD movies / Blu-ray content high quality MKV format...
</description></item><item><title>Download GiliSoft Audio Toolbox Suite 13.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 00:22:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-audio-toolbox-suite-856.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-audio-toolbox-suite-856.html
</guid><description>
GiliSoft Audio Toolbox Suite is software that contains 9 program powerful audio like Audio Recorder , Audio Cutter, Audio Joiner, Audio Converter, Video to Mp3,ID3 Tag Editor,Transfer to iTunes,CD Ripper,CD Burner. With GiliSoft Audio Toolbox Suite, you can easily convert and edit any audio file, how to extract, create and copy CD, convert audio files, burn music to CD, rip CD / DVD to the audio file to another, etc.
GiliSoft Audio Toolbox Suite - software sound synthesis
The main...
</description></item><item><title>Download DVD-Cloner XR Platinum 22.10.1492</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 00:22:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dvd-cloner-platinum-6979.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dvd-cloner-platinum-6979.html
</guid><description>
DVD-Cloner Platinum is highly rated professional DVD copying software with perfect output image quality, which can decode and copy DVD to any blank disc with Diverse copy modes for playback on a variety of media devices including PS4, Xbox, Blu-ray players, etc…
Besides, it can also copy DVD disc to ISO file or DVD folder stored on your hard drive. With DVD-Cloner Platinum, you can backup Blu-ray movies to BD-R/RE or your computer and rip high-capacity DVD/Blu-ray movies to MKV format...
</description></item><item><title>Download Astute Graphics Plug-ins Elite Bundle 4.4.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 00:21:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-astute-graphics-plug-ins-elite-bundle-5523.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-astute-graphics-plug-ins-elite-bundle-5523.html
</guid><description>
Astute Graphics Plug-ins Elite Bundle is a set of graphics editing tools for Adobe Illustrator. It includes many unique tools like Phantasm, VectorScribe, WidthScribe and many others. Get the complete set of plug-ins and transform your workflow in Illustrator. Add speed, ease, and precision with all our plug-ins and become the Astute Graphics Plug-in Elite Package!
Astute Graphics Plug-ins Elite Bundle Features:
	Correct alignment + selection
	Sketching visual vector
	Instantly...
</description></item><item><title>Download SoftPerfect RAM Disk 25.12</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 00:20:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-softperfect-ram-disk-4359.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-softperfect-ram-disk-4359.html
</guid><description>
SoftPerfect RAM Disk is a program disk, RAM performance is designed to help you have a disk on the computer is stored completely in memory. Because memory is much faster than physical hard disk, should store temporary data on disk in fast memory to achieve higher performance. Whether your job is what, keep reading to find out if a RAM disk can offer you what. The program creates a virtual disk located in the computer RAM accessible in Windows Explorer and other applications, allowing you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Pazu StreamGet All-In-One Video Downloader 2.8.9</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 00:20:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pazu-streamget-all-in-one-video-downloader-12037.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pazu-streamget-all-in-one-video-downloader-12037.html
</guid><description>
StreamGet All-In-One Video Downloader is the ultimate downloading solution for you. It supports downloading any movies and shows from the most popular streaming sites including Netflix, Prime Video, Disney Plus, Max, Hulu, and Apple TV Plus. The downloader is continuously updated to support more platforms in the future.
Download movies and shows from various streaming platforms to MP4/MKV on your Windows device and enjoy them anywhere you want.
Features of Pazu StreamGet All-In-One...
</description></item><item><title>Download Abelssoft WashAndGo 29.03.67755</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 00:19:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-abelssoft-washandgo-3246.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-abelssoft-washandgo-3246.html
</guid><description>
Abelssoft WashAndGo is an application lightweight but strong, allowing you to quickly and easily remove all unnecessary files from your hard drive. The program will clean up your system and will increase the speed and performance of your computer. Abelssoft WashAndGo can access and remove a variety of unnecessary items, including files, junk files, dump and log files, and temporary folder, the backup files not in use, the file buffer is not needed and many other things. The program will...
</description></item><item><title>Download DVD-Cloner XR 22.10.0.1492</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 00:19:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dvd-cloner-10743.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dvd-cloner-10743.html
</guid><description>
DVD Cloner is your comprehensive solution for copying and ripping DVD, Blu-ray and UHD, now including "Rip UHD to MKV (HDR 10+)" feature advanced. Easily convert UHD discs to MKV (HDR10+) format, store them on an external hard drive, and enjoy playback on any 4K UHD Player. Experience the same Dolby HD Audio and HDR Video quality as the original disc. With ultra-fast performance, intuitive interface and flexible copy modes, DVD-Cloner 2024 ensures seamless, loss-free output. Fully...
</description></item><item><title>Download eDrawings Pro 2025</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 00:18:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-edrawings-pro-suite-4941.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-edrawings-pro-suite-4941.html
</guid><description>
eDrawings Pro Suite is the right tool to share files CAD in compressed format and get feedback from users. The program code form the environment of the plug-in, such as AutoCAD, Pro Engineering and Salydvrk added and you can export project output as e-mail compression formats and other ways to connect with others to share their opinion about the product design. This product can work as a group to the convention to cooperate on product design.
It also can compress, view other members in...
</description></item><item><title>Download MaxCut Business Edition 2.9.6.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 00:18:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-maxcut-business-edition-3912.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-maxcut-business-edition-3912.html
</guid><description>
MaxCut Business Edition is a software to create cutting diagrams, accurate, and cost estimate for the wood industry, cabinets and metal,.. You enter the size and material, MaxCut will do the rest! Produce optimized cutting diagrams, create estimates, orders, and labels - it's just a click. Run the application MaxCut Business Edition brings a pretty clean interface and slick quickly get you up and running. Most space represents the editing area, with the main function are stored cleverly in...
</description></item><item><title>Download ToonTrack EZdrummer 3.1.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 00:17:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-toontrack-ezdrummer-13426.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-toontrack-ezdrummer-13426.html
</guid><description>
EZdrummer 3 reinvents the role that drum production software can play in the music composition scene. It gives you creative freedom with a comprehensive set of easy-to-use features that allow you to create complete drum tracks without ever leaving the software. A solid beat is the heartbeat of any great song. EZdrummer 3 is packed with features designed to help you easily create the right rhythm for your music.
Key features of EZdrummer 3 include:
	Seven high-quality drum kits and six...
</description></item><item><title>Download Syncovery Premium 11.11.3.133</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 00:17:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncovery-pro-enterprise-232.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncovery-pro-enterprise-232.html
</guid><description>
Syncovery Pro Enterprise is a great application used to back up data and to synchronize personal computers, servers, laptops, notepads and storage online. The software comes with support for FTP and secure FTP servers, SSH, WebDAV, Amazon S3, http, update the part file, ZIP compression, data encryption, and schedule automatic backups.
Syncovery Pro Enterprise have the ability to freely select files and folders across the whole folder hierarchy in tree view and supports email...
</description></item><item><title>Download PanFone WhatsApp Transfer 2.4.9</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 00:16:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-panfone-whatsapp-transfer-5580.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-panfone-whatsapp-transfer-5580.html
</guid><description>
PanFone WhatsApp Transfer is the best solution to backup, restore and transfer WhatsApp iOS / Android messages as well as export WhatsApp messages to HTML and CSV files. This PanFone WhatsApp Transfer easily and securely transferred iOS to Android WhatsApp can be a useful tool to help you backup and restore WhatsApp data. It will not overwrite or delete previous backups. You can restore WhatsApp backups to your phone any time you want.
Seamlessly transfer all WhatsApp chat history,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cash Register Pro 4.0.6</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 00:16:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cash-register-pro-3853.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cash-register-pro-3853.html
</guid><description>
Cash Register Pro a software cash register full of features and creative for a Windows computer, it will help you to better handle all the activities of the computer money. The application comes with the user interface logical and user friendly allows you to work quickly and do not commit the common error. The program can be used on a number of computers and offers a wide range of authorization secure and reliable. Cash Register Pro will help you track products and goods remain...
</description></item><item><title>Download Syncios WhatsApp Transfer 2.4.9</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 00:15:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncios-whatsapp-transfer-5944.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncios-whatsapp-transfer-5944.html
</guid><description>
Syncios WhatsApp Transfer helps to backup your WhatsApp history more easily than ever before. It allows you to backup and restore your WhatsApp iPhone/iPad/Android data in just one click. Syncios WhatsApp Transfer can meet all your needs for publishing WhatsApp conversations.
You can export and print the WhatsaS conversations; publish WhatsApp messages, photos, videos and audio files selectively or by a click.
The features of Syncios WhatsApp Transfer
	Why saves all WhatsApp content...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sante DICOM Viewer Pro 14.2.8</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 00:15:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sante-dicom-viewer-pro-11761.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sante-dicom-viewer-pro-11761.html
</guid><description>
Sante DICOM Viewer Pro is a professional DICOM viewer, anonymizer, converter, PACS client, mini PACS server, patient CD/DVD burner (with viewer) and more. This is a unique program with unique capabilities, designed and developed by us in-house from the ground up, with the most advanced programming tools and is the result of extensive research and development on DICOM image over the past two decades. Sante DICOM Viewer Pro has been developed since 1999 and is one of the most popular...
</description></item><item><title>Download Quicken WillMaker &amp;amp; Trust 26.1.3127</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 00:06:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quicken-willmaker-trust-4277.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quicken-willmaker-trust-4277.html
</guid><description>
Quicken WillMaker &amp;amp; Trust is the easiest way to create a package of your estate, whether you beginner or you want to update the sort earlier. This powerful software guides you throughout the process from beginning to end, provide you with practical information and legal that you need to take the best decision for you and your family. Quicken WillMaker &amp;amp; Trust is software write wills original, created and regularly updated by the experts of Nolo. Updates free legal will continue the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sante DICOM Editor 10.2.8</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 00:05:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sante-dicom-editor-11760.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sante-dicom-editor-11760.html
</guid><description>
Sante DICOM Editor is a professional DICOM editor, viewer, anonymizer, converter, dicomizer, PACS client, mini PACS server, patient CD/DVD burner (with viewer) and more that too.
Sante DICOM Editor is the industry's leading post-processing application for editing, converting and processing DICOM files, it is used by most major corporations and medical device manufacturers and is DICOM drafting is chosen by the largest universities and colleges. hospitals around the world. Among other...
</description></item><item><title>Download Playnite 10.45</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 00:02:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-playnite-6972.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-playnite-6972.html
</guid><description>
Playnite is an open-source video game library manager and manager with support for third-party libraries such as Steam, GOG, Origin, Battle.net and Uplay. Includes supporting the game, providing a unified interface for your game. With Playnite, you can comfortably enter the game from Steam, Battle.net, Origin, GOG and Uplay services, including uninstalled games.
You have three options to view when using Playnite. You also have the custom game option or add any game or program with...
</description></item><item><title>Download QontrolPanel (QuickSoundSwitcher) 1.10.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 00:01:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quicksoundswitcher-14033.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quicksoundswitcher-14033.html
</guid><description>
QuickSoundSwitcher is a lightweight, open-source Windows utility designed to quickly and easily manage audio input and output devices. It allows users to switch between multiple audio devices (e.g. speakers, headphones, microphones) and control the volume directly from the system tray without navigating to complex Windows settings.
The program also provides an application volume mixer, allowing for volume adjustment and muting for individual programs. This tool is especially useful for...
</description></item><item><title>Download ChessBase Catalan Powerbook 2025</title><pubDate> Mon, 01 Dec 2025 21:13:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chessbase-catalan-powerbook-14314.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chessbase-catalan-powerbook-14314.html
</guid><description>
ChessBase Catalan Powerbook is a specialized Catalan opening book, designed to be used with ChessBase and Fritz to provide very deep move trees, based on statistics rather than a traditional game database. The games on which the Catalan Powerbook is based have an average elo rating of at least 2300. Over 415,000 engine games and 55,000 games from the Mega 2025 + 2024 Letters Database exceed this elo threshold and form the basis for the Catalan Powerbook 2025.
From White's point of view,...
</description></item><item><title>Download ImageMagick 7.1.2-9</title><pubDate> Mon, 01 Dec 2025 17:17:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-imagemagick-1319.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-imagemagick-1319.html
</guid><description>
ImageMagick is software image processing command line to create, edit, compose, or convert bitmap images. ImageMagick is completely free for users and you easily download it on taiwebs.com. Typical functions most of software is able to read and write images in many formats (over 100) including DPX, EXR, GIF, JPEG, JPEG-2000, PDF, PhotoCD, PNG, Postcript, SVG, and TIFF.
ImageMagick - image Processing
The Windows version of ImageMagick is installed. Just click on the appropriate version...
</description></item></channel></rss>