<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 05:31:28 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 05:31:28 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download HFS: HTTP File Server (version 3) 0.57.15</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 00:39:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hfs-http-file-server-11851.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hfs-http-file-server-11851.html
</guid><description>
HFS is a web file server to run on your computer. Share a folder or even a file thanks to the virtual file system. Essentially, this application turns your computer into an HTTP server and all users who want to connect and download files can do so by loading a simple website in their browser. HFS includes many configuration settings, so you can basically change each part of the application, starting with how users download files and ending with the appearance of the created website.
HFS...
</description></item><item><title>Download SoftMaker Office Professional 2024 Rev S1228.0906</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 00:37:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-softmaker-office-professional-819.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-softmaker-office-professional-819.html
</guid><description>
SoftMaker Office Professional version, professional office support in terms of writing, calculation, presentation, E-mail, tasks,.. When using SoftMaker Office documents, calculations and presentations are handled as fast as e-mail or appointment and task planning. From the simple work daily to these documents, the most demanding, SoftMaker Office 2018 is the indispensable help of you.
SoftMaker Office is compatible with all the Microsoft Office. It edit Microsoft Office documents true to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Soda PDF Desktop Pro 14.0.516.23080</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 00:37:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-soda-pdf-home-808.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-soda-pdf-home-808.html
</guid><description>
Soda PDF Pro  is intuitive PDF software that helps you to easily process and create PDF files from more than 300 different formats. Soda PDF is built to help you power through any PDF task. Convert to a wide range of file types. Edit the content of your document. Create custom forms. Annotate your files. Send and track contracts for electronic signatures.
Soda PDF Pro: Create PDF file
Features of Soda PDF Pro
	Read your PDFs and digital publications in 3D with unique page-turning...
</description></item><item><title>Download SwapVoice 1.0.13</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 00:36:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-swapvoice-14126.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-swapvoice-14126.html
</guid><description>
Convert your voice into instant, actionable text with SwapVoice's intelligent trigger recognition system, for just a one-time subscription fee instead of the monthly licensing fees of other similar tools. Perfect for professionals, content creators, and anyone who wants to work faster and smarter.
SwapVoice Features
	Offline Speech Recognition - Cloud-Independent, Absolutely Secure
	Multilingual Support - 15 languages ​​including English, Dutch, German, French, Spanish, Italian,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Free Video Editor 1.4.64.903 Premium</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 00:36:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-video-editor-2573.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-video-editor-2573.html
</guid><description>
Free Video Editor is an application that converts video formats to other video formats. And there are a lot of video formats. But we can say that MP4 is the video format most popular today. Free Video Editor by DVDVideoSoft aims to convert video files to any format compatible with the multimedia device popular. So, if you encounter a rare case, not the iPad or the Xbox One of you get out, let's convert it into common use. Transition this video to create video files for any modern device,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Hasleo Backup Suite 5.4.2.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 00:32:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hasleo-backup-suite-6588.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hasleo-backup-suite-6588.html
</guid><description>
Hasleo Backup Suite is a free backup and free Windows recovery, integration of backup features, recovery, and replication, it is designed for Windows operating system users and can be used on both Windows PC and Windows Server. The backup and recovery feature of Hasleo Backup Suite can help you backup and restore your Windows, disk and partition operating system to protect your Windows operating system and your personal data. The replication feature of Hasleo Backup Suite can help you...
</description></item><item><title>Download FL Studio Producer Edition 25.1.5 Build 4976</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 00:32:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-image-line-fl-studio-488.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-image-line-fl-studio-488.html
</guid><description>
Image Line FL Studio is software that provides an environment to produce and create music, open architecture, full-featured for computer. Image Line FL Studio owner, audio workstation digital this has everything you need in one package to compose, arrange, record, edit, mix and master music in professional quality.
With user interface graphics based on the music player FL Studio 20 is the fastest way to create any style of music with a kits and kits studio complete. The plugins, sounds...
</description></item><item><title>Download Zero Install 2.28.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 00:31:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zero-install-1632.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zero-install-1632.html
</guid><description>
Zero Install is a system, install the software distribution cross africa focus. Other features include full support for shared libraries (with the SAT for resolution dependent), share between users, and integration with the package manager original foundation. Zero Install supports both binary packages and source and works on Linux systems , OS X , Unix and Windows. It is completely open source.
Zero Install - System software installation
Zero Install also has a number of interesting...
</description></item><item><title>Download Resolume Arena 7.23.2 rev 51094</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 00:30:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-arena-760.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-arena-760.html
</guid><description>
Resolume Arena is software Visual Jockey for DJ help adjust, mix and match image combination screen displayed directly. Software control it from the lighting and synchronize with the DJ via SMPTE time code. Adjust the ratio and position of the clip to suit your needs. Apply effects to change the powerful interface of the video. Everything running on the card screen so you get fast performance and good image quality as possible.
Resolume Arena - software Visual Jockey for DJ
Features of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sandboxie 5.71.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 00:29:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sandboxie-818.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sandboxie-818.html
</guid><description>
Sandboxie software to browse the Web securely while still keeping all the functionality your browser for content works against harmful agents such as sanbox up your computer. You may not know, when you browse the Web, the change will occur with the system of your computer. When you use Sandboxie, the software will protect the web browser of their own.
Sandboxie - web protection, safe browsing
The main features of Sandboxie
Stay safe on the Internet with Sandboxie
	Run the program in...
</description></item><item><title>Download Auslogics Anti-Malware 1.23.0.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 00:29:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-auslogics-anti-malware-788.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-auslogics-anti-malware-788.html
</guid><description>
Auslogics Anti-Malware is software antivirus, top protection against the threat of data security and malware. Auslogics Anti-Malware is the product of Auslogics, certified Microsoft® Gold Application Developer. The software is Microsoft appreciated in developing quality software to meet the increasing demand of the users.
Auslogics Anti-Malware - viruses and malware
Features of Auslogics Anti-Malware
	Detection of the toxic
	Schedule automatic scans flexible
	Keep your computer safe...
</description></item><item><title>Download Remo Outlook Backup &amp;amp; Migrate 2.0.1.100</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 00:29:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-remo-outlook-backup-migrate-7838.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-remo-outlook-backup-migrate-7838.html
</guid><description>
Remo Outlook Backup &amp;amp; Migrate is a safe and simple Utility to restore, backup and migrate your Outlook data without any limitations. Use this tool to automatically back up and migrate specific Outlook properties including settings, notes, attachments, and more.
Features of Remo Outlook Backup &amp;amp; Migrate
	Migrate Outlook data quickly and securely
	Unlimited Outlook Backup and Migration
	Backup Outlook data securely in the cloud
	Complete Outlook backup with just one...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sandboxie Plus 1.16.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 00:28:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sandboxie-plus-4962.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sandboxie-plus-4962.html
</guid><description>
Sandboxie Plus is an application version of the open source project on Github, equipped with software to protect your information while browsing the web or running valuable software. doubt. Web browsing, downloading or running software can affect system security. To prevent this from happening, a high user experience and strong layers of protection are needed to prevent malware from spreading to the system. For example, by opening an unknown application, malware in flash memory can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Syncthing 2.0.8</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 00:27:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncthing-2115.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncthing-2115.html
</guid><description>
Syncthing is synchronization service, cloud and open and non-focus allows you to share and sync files with other computers and gives you full control how to share your data and who can access it. Syncthing does not store your data in any other place, there is no server side Tuesday how to join. In addition, all the communication is secured by TLS and every button is determined by the certificate the strength of the encryption. Only computers that have explicitly allowed can connect with...
</description></item><item><title>Download Abelssoft HackCheck 2026 v8.01.64992</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 00:26:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-abelssoft-hackcheck-686.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-abelssoft-hackcheck-686.html
</guid><description>
Abelssoft HackCheck is software to monitor the online account of you to detect the hacker attacks and alert you when attacks occur! If the data of the your account online, you have the risk of being stolen by criminals, the program will emit alarm sound. Scan and monitor all the user accounts constantly against the attacks of hacker. Who is notified can act with purpose! Hacks guides, news and basic information.
Features of Abelssoft HackCheck
	Protecting background for your account:...
</description></item><item><title>Download NxFilter 4.7.3.5</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 00:26:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nxfilter-50.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nxfilter-50.html
</guid><description>
NxFilter is a server filter DNS have the ability to filter Internet traffic based on domain names and content types. In addition, it can use check package DNS to protect your network from malware and botnet activity.
NxFilter is installed on a single computer, where it acts as a proxy server, DNS. To route Internet traffic through NxFilter, you will need to change the DNS settings on all the machines that you want to protect to use the IP address of the individual NxFilter (instead of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download tinyMediaManager 5.2.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 00:26:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tinymediamanager-1819.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tinymediamanager-1819.html
</guid><description>
tinyMediaManager is a media manager full-featured to arrange and cleanup your media library your. Just choose (s) the folder containing your movies and the program can automatically get all meta data required for movies and program your TV from TheMovieDB.org, Imdb.com, OFDb.de and other online sources. tinyMediaManager download at artwork, film, cast, plot and details of other communication. Each film or program is presented with a unique art background, category, and appropriate...
</description></item><item><title>Download VRGeoscience Virtual Reality Geological Studio 3.02 Build 33</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 00:25:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vrgeoscience-virtual-reality-geological-studio-12732.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vrgeoscience-virtual-reality-geological-studio-12732.html
</guid><description>
VRGS (Virtual Reality Geological Studio) provides an integrated software solution for visualizing, interpreting and analyzing 3D geological datasets of virtual rock outcrops. It allows users to import large datasets from Lidar and Structure from Motion (SfM)/photogrammetry, create and visualize ultra-high-resolution models in 3D in VR or desktop mode, and deploy a comprehensive set of analytical tools to describe and interpret key geological features such as layers, faults, and...
</description></item><item><title>Download EMCO Network Inventory Enterprise 5.8.27.11201</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 00:25:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-emco-network-inventory-enterprise-2817.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-emco-network-inventory-enterprise-2817.html
</guid><description>
EMCO Network Inventory Enterprise is a software audit information network. In fact, with the help of this software, you can obtain information within few seconds as the type of operating system, peripherals, etc. Benefits from a reporting tool very powerful in this program make the information provided in the form of reports is very accurate.
In addition, scanning technology, modern software this so that you will not need any special configuration and difficult to work with this product...
</description></item><item><title>Download HomeBank 5.9.5</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 00:20:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-homebank-1160.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-homebank-1160.html
</guid><description>
HomeBank is a software personal accounting helps you manage finances, track expenses and manage your budget. HomeBank can nerd the interface is quite simple but the program back offers all the features that most people need to manage personal finance their.
HomeBank - Manage personal finance
In addition, you can import your bank statements from the file OFX / QFX, customize the type of spending and income, set a limit personal budget and create a custom report (with chart) to know you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sante PACS Server 4.2.4</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 00:19:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sante-pacs-server-7541.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sante-pacs-server-7541.html
</guid><description>
Sante PACS Server is an HTTP (web) server for DICOM files and a CD/DVD Burn and Print server that offers high performance and reliability at an affordable price. It provides connectivity to all DICOM methods (CT, MR, US, CR, NM, XA, MG, DX, etc.). Reviewing of DICOM images can be done using the Sante PACS Viewer (the system's built-in, full-featured DICOM Viewer). The built-in web server can be used as a free cloud server for DICOM files!
Tools of Sante PACS Server
	The Migration Tool...
</description></item><item><title>Download Flyby11 1.10.340</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 00:19:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-flyby11-12467.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-flyby11-12467.html
</guid><description>
Flyby11 is a simple patcher that removes annoying restrictions that prevent you from installing Windows 11 (24H2) on unsupported hardware. Do you have an old PC? No TPM, Secure Boot or your processor is not supported? Flyby11 allows you to install Windows 11 24H2. There are no complicated steps. Just run the tool and you'll be running Windows 11 on your outdated machine in no time.
Technical overview
Flyby11 takes advantage of a feature of the Windows 11 setup process that uses the...
</description></item><item><title>Download ECam Pro 5.0.432</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 00:19:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ecam-1615.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ecam-1615.html
</guid><description>
ECam is a reliable tool that allows you to create the design and simulation process, cut by lathe computer programming. The software allows you to create the cutting, drilling, face, chisel, or sanding the workpiece. You cansetup each step of the desired process in a graphical environment, where you can view and edit the 3D elements on the ECam.
ECam - design and simulation of the cutting process 3D
The features and functions of ECam
3D modeling
	Understanding 3D is effective...
</description></item><item><title>Download PACETEQ OneTiming 1.10.177</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 00:18:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-paceteq-onetiming-12731.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-paceteq-onetiming-12731.html
</guid><description>
OneTiming integrates all important data sources, including all major timing protocols, GPS feeds, Race Control Messages, weather data and video feeds. The optimal balance of performance and durability is designed to be the benchmark for dynamic and complex racing environments.
Key Features of OneTiming
	Data Integration: OneTiming seamlessly combines information from multiple channels, including timekeeping, telemetry, weather data, and audio/video feeds. This integration supports all...
</description></item><item><title>Download Red Button 6.6</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 00:18:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-red-button-3355.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-red-button-3355.html
</guid><description>
Red Button is a powerful tool for optimization and cleaning your Windows PC. It will delete the junk files and unnecessary components of Windows, free up disk space, delete the Internet activity traces and fingerprint digital, protect your privacy, clean and optimize registry, activate hundreds of Windows installations offline, allowing your computer to run faster and speed up computer performance overall. You will get everything needed for maintaining Windows in a perfect condition....
</description></item></channel></rss>