<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 03:33:41 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 03:33:41 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download EaseUS Todo PCTrans Pro 14.2.2 + Technician</title><pubDate> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 23:40:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-todo-pctrans-pro-1291.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-todo-pctrans-pro-1291.html
</guid><description>
EaseUS Todo PCTrans Professional is powerful software helps transfer data, apps and settings of your account from one computer to another easily. EasUS Todo PCTrans put everything into a new PC and ready to use . Transfer tool PC this easy move safe files, folder files, program and account your existing to a new computer. In just a click of the mouse, making PC your new is loaded with everything you need. Instead of copy and paste, you can transfer to new PC in a seamless way.
EaseUS...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wise Registry Cleaner Pro 11.2.4.729</title><pubDate> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 23:39:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wise-registry-cleaner-pro-468.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wise-registry-cleaner-pro-468.html
</guid><description>
Wise Registry Cleaner Pro software is dọp registry cleaner, defragment the hard drive to help optimize system and speed up computer. The advantage is, before cleanup registry software will allow users to create a backup safety. Therefore the cleanup, speed up pc back up safe and does not encounter the bug, what I wanted.
Wise Registry Cleaner is used as a tool to manage the program and lets you search for and delete obsolete files, folders, register, temporary hot key combination and...
</description></item><item><title>Download PassFab 4EasyPartition 3.8.1.11</title><pubDate> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 23:38:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-passfab-4easypartition-7983.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-passfab-4easypartition-7983.html
</guid><description>
After using your PC for many years, there are bound to be many files you want to transfer to your new PC. PassFab 4EasyPartition can perform a one-click migration saving you hours of reinstalling operating systems and applications. It has an intuitive interface and step-by-step wizard that makes migrating the system in just a few steps. PassFab 4EasyPartition will effectively solve the problem of low disk space, speed up your computer and make it run faster.
Features of PassFab...
</description></item><item><title>Download ProfiCAD 13.2.8</title><pubDate> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 23:38:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-proficad-1546.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-proficad-1546.html
</guid><description>
ProfiCAD is a software Program to draw diagram and circuit diagram of the electrical circuit and electronics with many features to support users. ProfiCAD will search the control circuit is different then help, you can design a variety of diagram techniques, such as diagrams, pneumatic and hydraulic. One of the obvious features of this product is the simplicity of it. Simple in the tool bar and the icons represent the parts. Simply arrange the menu, just put the items on the screen and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mullvad Browser 15.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 23:37:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mullvad-browser-12254.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mullvad-browser-12254.html
</guid><description>
Mullvad Browser is a privacy-focused web browser developed through a partnership between Mullvad VPN and Tor Project. This browser is designed to minimize tracking and fingerprinting. You can say that this is the Tor browser to use without the Tor Network. Instead, you can use this browser with a reliable VPN. The idea is to provide one more alternative – besides the Tor Network – to browse the internet with more privacy. To get as many people as possible together against today's big...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ashampoo WinOptimizer 28.00.20</title><pubDate> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 23:36:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-winoptimizer-870.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-winoptimizer-870.html
</guid><description>
Ashampoo WinOptimizer is a software cleanup, optimize and protect your PC. It frees up disk space, fix errors on computer. WinOptimizer has overcome the shortcomings of Windows and give you a system faster, leaner and leaner. Many features automated features make setting it up a problem is only a few clicks of the mouse most simple.
Ashampoo WinOptimizer - Clean optimize PC
Ashampoo WinOptimizer provides instant access to your system, you can look and feel the way that best suits you....
</description></item><item><title>Download PC Internals Pro 2.003</title><pubDate> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 23:35:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pc-internals-pro-13002.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pc-internals-pro-13002.html
</guid><description>
PC Internals Pro is a new solution that allows Windows users to comprehensively analyze the system components and reliable monitoring of the hard drive. This software is aimed at individual users as well as IT experts and retail agents attach importance to transparency, early detection and data security. PC Internals provides detailed information about the processor, RAM, graphics card, drive and other system components. The chart directly displays the current load, while the specific...
</description></item><item><title>Download EaseUS Disk Copy Pro WinPE 6.9.0 Build 20251011</title><pubDate> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 23:35:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-disk-copy-pro-winpe-9088.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-disk-copy-pro-winpe-9088.html
</guid><description>
EaseUS Disk Copy Pro WinPE is a software program used to clone hard drives, SSDs and other storage devices. It allows users to create an exact copy of their storage device, including the operating system, applications, and data, and transfer it to another storage device.
EaseUS Disk Copy Pro WinPE can easily upgrade your hard drive from old disk to new one or clone MBR disk to GPT or GPT disk to MBR. Also, it allows you to clone HDD to SSD for better performance.
Features of EaseUS...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cleaning Suite Professional 4.021</title><pubDate> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 23:34:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cleaning-suite-professional-4623.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cleaning-suite-professional-4623.html
</guid><description>
Cleaning Suite Professional is software support you clean the system from unnecessary data with a total of six effective tool. If the system boots increasingly slow and hard drive is full, then it is high time to clean the system thoroughly. With software Cleaning Suite Professional this, you can delete temporary files, delete browser history, cache and cookies from all the popular Internet browsers and security applications and tools are installed automatically start when the system...
</description></item><item><title>Download Executor 2.1.4</title><pubDate> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 23:34:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-executor-271.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-executor-271.html
</guid><description>
Executor for windows is a software alternative premium customization features for the Windows "Run" and "Search Programs". When you press WIN + Z and provides the search results instant, as-you-type for any keywords you enter. By default, Executor will index all the Desktop and Start Menu and you can easily expand the search range by adding the folder location additional.
Executor for windows
The program comes with a list of commands built in which you can use to quickly access many...
</description></item><item><title>Download TubeDownload Pro 6.30.5</title><pubDate> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 23:34:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubedownload-pro-12035.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubedownload-pro-12035.html
</guid><description>
TubeDownload Pro is a professional Windows application for downloading your favorite videos from YouTube and hundreds of other video sites. TubeDownload Pro can increase download speed up to 500% or even more.
Features of TubeDownload Pro
	Download your favorite videos from YouTube and hundreds of other video sites.
	Increase download speed up to 500% or even more.
	Download 720p, 1080p, 2K, 4K and 8K HD videos from YouTube.
	Download entire playlists in just a few clicks.
	Download...
</description></item><item><title>Download Softwarenetz Invoice Rechnung 11.25</title><pubDate> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 23:33:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-softwarenetz-invoice-5588.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-softwarenetz-invoice-5588.html
</guid><description>
Softwarenetz Invoice is a useful program for self-employed, freelancers and small companies who are in need of a simple and user-friendly program for invoicing. The invoice program contains the complete address / customer database. You can see at a glance all invoices, payments and reminders for a particular customer. The memo field gives you the opportunity to enter customer specific information. Importing existing client from csv file is also included.
You can print your invoice on your...
</description></item><item><title>Download 4DDiG Partition Manager 3.8.1.11</title><pubDate> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 23:33:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4ddig-partition-manager-2024-9781.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4ddig-partition-manager-2024-9781.html
</guid><description>
4DDiG Partition Manager is a powerful Windows disk partition software expert in system migration, disk cloning and disk partition management. It can effectively clone your entire disk or partition, providing a reliable solution for data backup.
This is Windows 10 fast system and data transfer solution &amp;amp; 11. 4DDiG Partition Manager can move the system and large files or folders from one disk partition to a larger one with just one click. Or you can use it to move the system and large...
</description></item><item><title>Download Screencapt Professional 2.006</title><pubDate> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 23:32:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-screencapt-professional-12260.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-screencapt-professional-12260.html
</guid><description>
Screencapt Professional is powerful Windows software for screen recording that allows you to accurately and easily record any on-screen activity. Whether you want to create tutorials, record webinars, or simply record your favorite games, Screencapt gives you all the tools you need.
With Screencapt, you can record the entire screen, a selected area, or a specific window. This flexibility makes Screencapt the perfect screen recorder for any type of application. Thanks to the built-in...
</description></item><item><title>Download Internet Video Downloader 7.9.6</title><pubDate> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 23:32:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hdapplications-hd-downloader-6041.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hdapplications-hd-downloader-6041.html
</guid><description>
Internet Video Downloader is a small tool designed to help you download video clips from YouTube, Dailymotion and many other similar sites with high quality that can easily run on smartphones, tablets or the latest Xbox devices. After the quick and simple installation process, you will be welcomed by a user-friendly interface without the ability to cause any problems for you.
Although you can set the app start to download immediately, but you can also create a download list that can be...
</description></item><item><title>Download Monkfish XML Software XML Blueprint 22.2025.10.30</title><pubDate> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 23:32:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-monkfish-xml-software-xml-blueprint-12529.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-monkfish-xml-software-xml-blueprint-12529.html
</guid><description>
The intelligent XML editor in XMLBlueprint fully supports DTD, Relax NG, Schematron, XSD, XSLT (1.0, 2.0, 3.0) and XPath (1.0, 2.0, 3.1). The unique combination of relevant features and an affordable price for both professional and home users makes this a smart choice for all your XML-related work. With XMLBlueprint you can edit and validate very large XML files (1GByte or more). With an intuitive user interface, XMLBlueprint makes XML editing quick and easy. XMLBlueprint is the best...
</description></item><item><title>Download TSplus Advanced Security Ultimate 7.4.10.28</title><pubDate> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 23:31:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tsplus-security-7308.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tsplus-security-7308.html
</guid><description>
Unique cybersecurity software TSplus Security provides the basic protections every remote server administrator needs and more. Enable up to seven measures and set the right level of security for your network. When you use remote desktop to allow your employees to work from home, reduce your risk of attack and increase your peace of mind with the powerful features of TSplus Security.
Features of TSplus Security
	Using a country-based whitelist, TSplus Security allows administrators to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Monkeys Audio 11.71</title><pubDate> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 23:31:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-monkeys-audio-949.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-monkeys-audio-949.html
</guid><description>
Monkey\'s Audio is software that compresses digital music without loss of quality. Supports high quality WAV files and CD ripping. Monkeys Audio will compress .wav tracks into .ape files to reduce their size without loss of sound quality, decompress .ape, convert files, check file integrity and manage tags.
Unlike traditional methods like MP3 and OGG, which permanently remove quality to save space, Monkey\'s Audio only creates perfect copies with the same sound quality as the originals....
</description></item><item><title>Download Psiphon 186.20251029</title><pubDate> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 23:30:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-psiphon-7347.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-psiphon-7347.html
</guid><description>
Psiphon is a firewall bypass tool by Psiphon Inc. Uses VPN, SSH and HTTP Proxy technology to give you uncensored access to Internet content. Your Psiphon app automatically learns about new hotspots to maximize your chances of bypassing censorship.
The way the software works is that Psiphon constantly changes the proxy, so the user's IP address is also constantly changing, the server will not detect the user's real address, so you can feel free. roof. access to websites and software...
</description></item><item><title>Download RDS Advanced Security Ultimate 7.4.10.28</title><pubDate> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 23:30:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rds-advanced-security-ultimate-13846.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rds-advanced-security-ultimate-13846.html
</guid><description>
RDS Advanced Security Ultimate is comprehensive cybersecurity software designed to protect Remote Desktop Services (RDS) infrastructure from a wide range of cyber threats, including brute force attacks, ransomware, unauthorized logins, and malicious IP addresses. This software provides advanced, multi-layered security features to protect RDS servers and ensure secure remote access.
Key Features:
	Hacker IP Protection: Blocks millions of malicious IP addresses daily with a...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Lightroom Classic 2026 v15.0 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 20:39:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-photoshop-lightroom-classic-0004-734.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-photoshop-lightroom-classic-0004-734.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Photoshop Lightroom Classic is a desktop-optimized photo editing and organizing software. Lightroom Classic gives you powerful one-click tools and advanced controls to make your photos look great. Easily organize all your photos on your desktop and share them in a variety of ways.
In addition, Lightroom Classic has a powerful import process that allows users to preview images before importing. It supports many camera raw formats and includes a database system for efficient photo...
</description></item><item><title>Download Advanced SystemCare Pro 19.0.1.160</title><pubDate> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 18:36:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-systemcare-pro-368.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-systemcare-pro-368.html
</guid><description>
Advanced SystemCare Pro is software that provides features to optimize a PC system professional cleanup, repair, speed up and protect PC.  Advanced SystemCare Pro tab Protect new is added, is designed to provide quick access to protect browsing from being tracked by automatically delete traces of privacy when browser closed and detect and resist the attack of the plugin / malicious toolbar by Browser Anti -Backing and Plugin / toolbar cleaner.
Program speed up pc top
Advanced SystemCare...
</description></item><item><title>Download Topaz Video AI Pro 7.1.6 / 1.0.4</title><pubDate> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 18:36:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-video-enhance-ai-3733.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-video-enhance-ai-3733.html
</guid><description>
Topaz Video Enhance AI is a tool to increase video quality with this great technology ONE. Topaz Video Enhance WHO wide open your video to resolutions up to 8K with the details and consistency of motion. Until the present, there is no way to re-create a perfect high resolution video from the footage is low resolution. From the family film to SD low quality to DVD quality and more than that, Video Enhance WHO will convert your video into the footage is upgrade clear with resolutions up to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Directory Opus Pro 13.19.2 Beta</title><pubDate> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 18:35:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-opus-pro-779.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-opus-pro-779.html
</guid><description>
Directory Opus Pro is a software replacement for Explorer with traditional strength and function more than any manager other files. Directory Opus Pro full support for high DPI screen (for example 4K and 5K) with the rename dialog is redesigned, with new features. Besides being a recording macro only allows you to perform mass renaming complex that don't need regular expressions. In addition, Directory Opus Pro also enhances the ability to script.Better handling of renaming recursive and...
</description></item><item><title>Download 4K Video Downloader Plus 25.4.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 18:35:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-video-downloader-617.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-video-downloader-617.html
</guid><description>
4K Video Downloader Plus is software support downloads video, audio and subtitles from YouTube with high quality up to 4K. Download process video is very simple: just copy the video link from your browser and click Paste Url. Done! If you want that video on your iPad, iPhone or other device, we have protected you.
The feature on 4K Video Downloader Plus
	Download entire playlists and channels from YouTube and save them in MP4, MKV, M4A, MP3, FLV, 3G, create a file .m3u for...
</description></item></channel></rss>