<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 13:52:29 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 13:52:29 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Monkeys Audio 11.30</title><pubDate> Thu, 07 Aug 2025 16:45:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-monkeys-audio-949.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-monkeys-audio-949.html
</guid><description>
Monkey\'s Audio is software that compresses digital music without loss of quality. Supports high quality WAV files and CD ripping. Monkeys Audio will compress .wav tracks into .ape files to reduce their size without loss of sound quality, decompress .ape, convert files, check file integrity and manage tags.
Unlike traditional methods like MP3 and OGG, which permanently remove quality to save space, Monkey\'s Audio only creates perfect copies with the same sound quality as the originals....
</description></item><item><title>Download Wagnardsoft Tools (WTools) 1.0.5.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 07 Aug 2025 16:44:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wagnardsoft-tools-8092.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wagnardsoft-tools-8092.html
</guid><description>
Wagnardsoft Tools (or WTools) is a lightweight utility that contains many tools to clean your system from temporary and error files Other times take up space and can be dangerous for your PC. It is developed by the author of the program Display Driver Uninstaller has been trusted and used by many people.&amp;lt; /p&amp;gt;
Wagnardsoft Tools gives you the essentials to clean up targeted areas of your machine and thus free up space. It's important to note that don't delete important registry keys...
</description></item><item><title>Download Flameshot 13.0.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 07 Aug 2025 16:34:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-flameshot-11451.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-flameshot-11451.html
</guid><description>
Flameshot is a powerful and user-friendly screenshot tool for Windows that makes it easy to take, edit, and share screenshots. It offers a wide range of features and customization options, making it suitable for both casual and expert users.
It has an interactive GUI (graphical user interface) with controls to select the desired capture area, move and resize the capture window, perform editing with popular drawing tools ( pencil, line, rectangle, circle, blur, undo/redo) and select the...
</description></item><item><title>Download RainbowTaskbar 3.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 07 Aug 2025 16:34:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rainbowtaskbar-6740.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rainbowtaskbar-6740.html
</guid><description>
RainbowTaskbar is an open source, customizable Windows taskbar that includes colors and transitions. Add some color to your taskbar by changing the color shift on the spectrum, you can like it visually. The program allows you to customize the colors; Instructions can be found on the author's website.
</description></item><item><title>Download Brave Browser 1.81.131</title><pubDate> Thu, 07 Aug 2025 16:33:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-brave-browser-2874.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-brave-browser-2874.html
</guid><description>
Brave Browser is a browser based on Chromium, the basic principle is that operation fast and privacy of users. The program can block pop-up windows and other ads, plus it blocked the mechanism for monitoring the online activities of your. Therefore, you can purchase and safely browse the website you are interested in without having to worry about the fact that your activity will be monitored and then you will be shown the necessary advertising or service provider of parties...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Substance 3D Painter 11.0.3.4609 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Thu, 07 Aug 2025 16:33:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-substance-painter-1279.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-substance-painter-1279.html
</guid><description>
Substance Painter is a drawing application 3D completely new with the possibility of unprecedented and workflow is optimized, help in creating graphics easier than ever. To create sprites or 3D characters, no need to have knowledge about a painters professional animation, now it has become easy and accessible for the average user . The program is recognized in the world is creative tool and the most convenient to draw 3D create character models.
Substance Painter - App 3D drawing
The...
</description></item><item><title>Download 3DCoat 2025.10</title><pubDate> Thu, 07 Aug 2025 16:32:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-3d-coat-1269.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-3d-coat-1269.html
</guid><description>
3D Coat is a computer program that trade for modeling objects of different organic and 3D models low-poly. The app provides a variety of tools allow users to create sculptures, adding topology, create UV maps, texture surface interactions of the model, showing the static and animated round of the pattern.
3D Coat - 3D modeling
The content in the software 3D Coat:
Texture simple and PBR:
	Support drawing drawings top en model, draw the pixel and Ptex
	Rendered physics-based (PBR)...
</description></item><item><title>Download LibreWolf 141.0.2-1</title><pubDate> Thu, 07 Aug 2025 16:31:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-librewolf-11967.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-librewolf-11967.html
</guid><description>
LibreWolf is a customized and independent version of Firefox, with the main goals being user privacy, security and freedom. LibreWolf is designed to provide increased protection against tracking and fingerprinting techniques and includes a number of security enhancements. This is achieved through our security and privacy oriented settings and patches. LibreWolf also aims to remove all telemetry, data collection and annoyances, as well as disable anti-free features like DRM.
LibreWolf...
</description></item><item><title>Download TeamTalk 5.19</title><pubDate> Thu, 07 Aug 2025 16:30:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-teamtalk-7663.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-teamtalk-7663.html
</guid><description>
TeamTalk is an application that allows users to have full control over their communication channel, it allows access to publicly available rooms (hosted on the machine). owner of TeamTalk) or create a fully customized, standalone server. TeamTalk is a cross-platform utility that supports connection to Windows OS, macOS and Linux distributions. That way, you can connect remotely with people from anywhere and from all backgrounds, and you can have the added benefit of flexibility.
With...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tablacus Explorer 25.8.6</title><pubDate> Thu, 07 Aug 2025 16:30:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tablacus-explorer-3674.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tablacus-explorer-3674.html
</guid><description>
Tablacus Explorer is a file manager open-source is designed to help you arrange the contents of your folders. Tablacus Explorer has a user interface very simple and you will be familiar with working with this program immediately. Folders and files can be sorted or grouped by name, type, size and date when they were last modified. App can automatically remember to set your tab if you close it and allows you to copy or move items to different positions and save the settings to format an XML...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft Teams 1.8.00.21151</title><pubDate> Thu, 07 Aug 2025 16:29:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-teams-6904.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-teams-6904.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft Teams is a system that provides chat, meetings, notes and attachments. Whether you're working with teammates on a project or planning a weekend away with loved ones, Microsoft Teams helps bring people together so they can get things done. It's the only app that has chats, meetings, files, tasks, and calendars in one place, so you can easily connect with people and make plans come true.
Features of Microsoft Teams:
	Meeting safely with teammates, family, and friends.
	Live...
</description></item><item><title>Download AutoPowerOptionsOK 6.16</title><pubDate> Thu, 07 Aug 2025 16:29:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-autopoweroptionsok-1820.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-autopoweroptionsok-1820.html
</guid><description>
AutoPowerOptionsOK is a small program that can automatically turn off your screen, put your computer in sleep mode or switch between the power options. Each action can be triggered based on the absence of events keyboard and / or mouse for a specified time interval. For example, you can automatically turn off the screen if the mouse or keyboard has not been used in 10 minutes.
AutoPowerOptionsOK - power Management automatically
AutoPowerOptionsOK is a compact tool designed to help you...
</description></item><item><title>Download DriverStore Explorer 0.12.100</title><pubDate> Thu, 07 Aug 2025 16:28:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-driverstore-explorer-2892.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-driverstore-explorer-2892.html
</guid><description>
DriverStore Explorer RAPR is software for dealing with drivers Windows more easily. The supported operations include enumeration, adding driver package (stage), add and install, delete and delete force from the store drivers.
DriverStore Explorer - drivers
The features of the DriverStore Explorer
	Listed / Listed all the packages are held in the store current drivers.
	Export the list as CSV.
	Added package drivers catalog drivers (called staging)
	Install &amp;amp; Add driver package...
</description></item><item><title>Download Python 3.13.6</title><pubDate> Thu, 07 Aug 2025 16:28:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-python-4355.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-python-4355.html
</guid><description>
Python is a programming language high-level for the purpose of programming multi-function, due to Guido van Rossum created and first launched in 1991. Python is designed with strong advantages is easy to read, easy to learn and easy to remember. Python is a language can form very bright, clear structure, convenient for new people to learn programming. Python fully create a dynamic and user mechanisms to allocate the memory automatically; so it is similar to Perl, Ruby, Scheme, Smalltalk,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tixati 3.36</title><pubDate> Thu, 07 Aug 2025 16:27:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tixati-2355.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tixati-2355.html
</guid><description>
A Bittorrent free, good have been updated, are designed for operating systems Microsoft Windows and Linux (for the OS Monday, you can download a version from the official website of the developer). The difference between a client and a large number of others is that users are provided a wide opportunity to control the torrent of them, they also write on your program that it consumes less memory than uTorrent and Halite famous.
Tixati - App download torrent
Tixati is also ready to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Darktable 5.2.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 07 Aug 2025 16:26:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-darktable-3959.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-darktable-3959.html
</guid><description>
Darktable is an application process work, photography, open source and developer rough. A lighttable virtual and Darktable for the photographer. It manages the negative of your digital in the database, lets you view them through a lamp can zoom and allows you to develop raw images and enhance them. Original image of you never be modified! Features color management professional to ensure fidelity in all the way in and handle GPU acceleration means you can speed up the process of his work by...
</description></item><item><title>Download Psiphon 186.202500805</title><pubDate> Thu, 07 Aug 2025 16:26:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-psiphon-7347.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-psiphon-7347.html
</guid><description>
Psiphon is a firewall bypass tool by Psiphon Inc. Uses VPN, SSH and HTTP Proxy technology to give you uncensored access to Internet content. Your Psiphon app automatically learns about new hotspots to maximize your chances of bypassing censorship.
The way the software works is that Psiphon constantly changes the proxy, so the user's IP address is also constantly changing, the server will not detect the user's real address, so you can feel free. roof. access to websites and software...
</description></item><item><title>Download FreeCAD 1.0.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 07 Aug 2025 16:25:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-freecad-7546.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-freecad-7546.html
</guid><description>
FreeCAD is a parameter 3D model, based on a general purpose feature for CAD, MCAD, CAx, CAE and PLM, directly targeting mechanical engineering and product design but also in line with more use of use in engineering, such as architecture or other engineering majors. It is 100% open source code and extremely modular, allowing very advanced expansion and custom.
FreeCAD is based on OpenCasCade, a powerful figure, with a 3D scene representation model compatible with Open Inventor provided...
</description></item><item><title>Download MatchWare MindView 9.0.50806</title><pubDate> Thu, 07 Aug 2025 16:24:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mindview-5965.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mindview-5965.html
</guid><description>
MindView is a professional thinking mapping software that allows you to brainpower, organize and present an intuitive idea. Known for the integration of the MS Office that once won the award, the software mapping software allows you to work more efficiently, turning the idea into action faster than ever! With six interchangable viewing modes, unique project management features and strong collaboration options; MindView has become a leading company in the software mapping software...
</description></item><item><title>Download Google Chrome 139.0.7258.67</title><pubDate> Thu, 07 Aug 2025 16:24:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-chrome-1012.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-chrome-1012.html
</guid><description>
Google Chrome web browser is the most used today. Support surf the web, listen to music, watch movies, play web game effective no jerky lag with the internet connection stable. When you are surfing the web or performing an important task, whether it is operation big or small, work or entertainment, then Chrome has the smart features and the speed you need to make, create and explore on the net.
The latest version of Google Chrome is the third 114. But we are providing for users Google...
</description></item><item><title>Download CapCut PC 6.7.0.2661 / 6.8.0.2722 Beta 7</title><pubDate> Thu, 07 Aug 2025 16:23:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capcut-pc-9995.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capcut-pc-9995.html
</guid><description>
CapCut PC is a simple video editing tool that you can freely use anywhere. You can create videos on your browser, desktop and laptop, or on your phone. Versatile editing, magical AI tools, team collaboration, and built-in assets. Create videos in a whole new way.
You can edit videos based on editing the timeline, in the process you can add different elements and effects to the video to give the best effect to your work. It is a simple and intuitive set of editing tools and effects that...
</description></item><item><title>Download Photo Supreme 2025.3.1.7987</title><pubDate> Thu, 07 Aug 2025 16:22:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photo-supreme-430.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photo-supreme-430.html
</guid><description>
Photo Supreme is a software product management professional pictures of idimager. With Photo Supreme you can arrange, manage back stock photo archive of yourself and share them with you here and relatives easily via Email or Facebook. Photo Supreme provides users method to sort images effective, logical, as well as edit and share your photos with friends and relatives in the family. Especially the Photo Supreme allows to work with multiple image formats and support mounting support,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Abelssoft AntiBrowserSpy Pro 2026 v9.02.64191</title><pubDate> Thu, 07 Aug 2025 16:22:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-abelssoft-antibrowserspy-347.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-abelssoft-antibrowserspy-347.html
</guid><description>
Abelssoft AntiBrowserSpy is software that functions off function spy hidden of the browser of you to clean the traces of web surfing activities such as : Browser-Cache, History and Cookies. Abelssoft AntiBrowserSpy help remove Internet Traces allows you to remove Internet traces easily. This includes the deletion of the history entries and web cache. List download and the URL entered can also be cleaned. Additionaly AntiBrowserSpy contains the cookie management allows you to view and...
</description></item><item><title>Download CalendarTask (formerly DesktopCal) 3.25.252.7603</title><pubDate> Thu, 07 Aug 2025 16:21:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopcal-1831.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopcal-1831.html
</guid><description>
CalendarTask (formerly DesktopCal) is a simple desktop calendar that blends into your desktop without blocking access to your desktop icons. You can double-click on a date to quickly add notes and also jump to specific dates in the past or future.
CalendarTask - Computer calendar
CalendarTask can use your current wallpaper or loop through images from your folder and update your desktop every few minutes. The program helps you make appointments, make plans... Not only that, the Screen...
</description></item><item><title>Download RapidRAW 1.3.4</title><pubDate> Thu, 07 Aug 2025 16:21:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rapidraw-13957.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rapidraw-13957.html
</guid><description>
RapidRAW is a modern, high-performance, open-source RAW photo editor, designed to deliver a fast and clean editing experience with a lightweight footprint (under 30MB). Built with performance and usability in mind, the software is aimed at photographers who want a simple, efficient, and fun workflow without compromising performance.
Key Features
	GPU-accelerated processing: Uses a custom WGSL shader to process all image adjustments on the GPU, allowing for smooth, responsive editing...
</description></item></channel></rss>