<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 21:35:49 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 21:35:49 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download WinScript 1.4.3</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 23:23:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winscript-12800.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winscript-12800.html
</guid><description>
WinScript is an open source tool built to help you build custom scripts for Windows 10 and 11. It includes scripts for debugging, privacy, performance, and more, along with the ability to install all your favorite apps with just one click.
Features
	Debloat: Remove Windows bloatware, CoPilot, Edge, OneDrive, and other pre-installed features preset.
	Privacy: Disable Windows and 3rd party data collection, tracking, app access, and telemetry.
	Performance: Set background services to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Opera GX (Gaming Browser) 124.0.5705.61</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 23:22:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-gx-3170.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-gx-3170.html
</guid><description>
Opera GX is a special version of the Opera browser is built to complement gamers avid. Browser this game comes with the unique features to help users make maximum use of both the game and their browser. Opera GX is built specifically to support the game. This browser includes the unique features to help users have the best experience when gaming and surfing the web.
Opera GX - special browser for gamers
GX Control allows you to set a limit on the level of use RAM, CPU and network where...
</description></item><item><title>Download R-Wipe &amp;amp; Clean 20.0 Build 2537</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 23:21:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-wipe-clean-891.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-wipe-clean-891.html
</guid><description>
R-Wipe &amp;amp; Clean is software to delete junk files, unnecessary files from your computer to release the storage space and speed up your computer. In addition, R-Wipe &amp;amp; Clean also unleash the capacity of your drive and delete information invasion of privacy on different operations online and offline including your internet history and cookies, the list of downloaded files and documents were open, buffer different data, temporary files and many other items, created by the operating...
</description></item><item><title>Download XYplorer 28.00.0900 Beta</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 23:15:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-533.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-533.html
</guid><description>
XYplorer - File Manager for Windows is software that supports users to manage files on the Window quickly and to arrange the folder tidy. XYplorer features tabbed browsing, search, files, powerful, preview, flexible, highly customizable interface, dual frame options and a variety of unique ways to automate effective tasks often repeat. It's fast, lightweight, and portable.
Features XYplorer
	XYplorer is a file manager mobile. It does not require any settings, store all configuration...
</description></item><item><title>Download System Info 18.42</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 23:14:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-system-info-11391.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-system-info-11391.html
</guid><description>
System Info is a simple piece of software that displays various information about your system, including its hardware, operating system, and more. Having everything presented in a single interface, where you can copy and share that data elsewhere, can finally become convenient for regular users. That's what System Information does: it gives you various data about your system, including hardware specifications, operating system, network, and more. without installation.
This application...
</description></item><item><title>Download OCCT 15.0.8.99</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 23:14:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-occt-perestroika-1680.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-occt-perestroika-1680.html
</guid><description>
OCCT is a free application designed to benchmark and overclock system components. Test tool OverClock includes 4 different tests to assess the stability of your computer. CPU and CPU: Linpack to test the processor, GPU: 3D to check stability of the graphics processor and power supply combination of CPU: Linpack and GPU: 3D to download power of you up to the maximum.
OCCT - Measuring system components
The features of OCCT
	Support is enabled for a maximum of 16 cores.
	All the tests...
</description></item><item><title>Download uTorrent Pro 3.6.0 Build 47228</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 23:13:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-utorrent-pro-79.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-utorrent-pro-79.html
</guid><description>
uTorrent - Download the torrent file
uTorrent Pro is an application BitTorrent efficient for Windows. Most of the features in the BitTorrent client and others have in uTorrent, including priority bandwidth, scheduling, automatic download at RSS and Mainline DHT. Additionally, uTorrent supports specification joint protocol encryption and peer exchange of goods. Unlike many torrent clients, it does not hog system resources have value - typically using less than 6MB of memory, allowing you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tenorshare 4DDiG Windows Backup 1.1.1.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 23:13:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tenorshare-4ddig-windows-backup-14219.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tenorshare-4ddig-windows-backup-14219.html
</guid><description>
Backup files, partitions, or computers to computers or external devices. Full system backup to keep your system safe. Restore a specific partition from a full backup to save time. Task management console for easy backup.
Backup data with just one click
	PC backup: Delete, overwrite, corruption, or sudden crash can cause data loss. To keep your data safe, easily create a backup of your files, partitions, drives, or system with 4DDiG Windows Backup. Create a backup task, choose what you...
</description></item><item><title>Download ffMediaMaster (formerly myFFmpeg) 1.1.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 23:13:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-myffmpeg-2894.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-myffmpeg-2894.html
</guid><description>
ffMediaMaster is a communication tool designed with simple ideas, which will bring in a creative way to use FFmpeg. You can use this app to easily create high quality videos without having to write code. The utility will help you handle and convert a range of media files with just a few simple steps. ffMediaMaster supports a wide variety of multimedia formats, such as H264, Matroska, DNxHD, MPEG TS, XAVS, Theora, OGG, Animated GIF, VP9, MXF, MPEG-4, H265 HEVC, PRORES, DVVideo, MPEG FLV,...
</description></item><item><title>Download CalendarTask (formerly DesktopCal) 3.26.259.8213</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 23:12:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopcal-1831.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopcal-1831.html
</guid><description>
CalendarTask (formerly DesktopCal) is a simple desktop calendar that blends into your desktop without blocking access to your desktop icons. You can double-click on a date to quickly add notes and also jump to specific dates in the past or future.
CalendarTask - Computer calendar
CalendarTask can use your current wallpaper or loop through images from your folder and update your desktop every few minutes. The program helps you make appointments, make plans... Not only that, the Screen...
</description></item><item><title>Download GibbsCAM 2026 v26.0.51</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 23:12:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gibbscam-001-732.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gibbscam-001-732.html
</guid><description>
GibbsCAM is a full-featured CAM system that provides powerful CNC programming capabilities to optimize manufacturing production.GibbsCAM 12 introduces a modern, updated system Updated interface designed to increase efficiency and improve overall user experience.
GibbsCAM
GibbsCAM updates with a new interface that gives users the ability to customize, along with the ease-of-use features users expect, while still maintaining character, personality and traditional workflows. by...
</description></item><item><title>Download Pixel Composer 1.20.0.8</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 23:07:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pixel-composer-13321.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pixel-composer-13321.html
</guid><description>
Pixel Composer is a Node-based visual effects (VFX) software designed specifically for pixel art. It allows users to create, edit, and composite pixel art effects in a non-destructive and procedural way. The software features a powerful node and graph system that allows users to mix, stack, and combine multiple effects without altering the original file.
It supports animation of any parameter using keyframes, curves, and expressions, and includes simulation capabilities such as rigid...
</description></item><item><title>Download Vovsoft PDF Reader 5.7</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 23:07:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-pdf-reader-6226.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-pdf-reader-6226.html
</guid><description>
Vovsoft PDF Reader is a simple, lightweight PDF viewing application. There is no complex configuration to view your PDF files from the desktop. The minimus interface provides all the necessary elements. The unique design PDF reader does not tax the system resources of your computer.
Features of Vovsoft PDF Reader
	The interaction is PDF document
	Lightweight and easy to use
	Simple interface.
System requirements:
	The operating system was supported: Windows 10 /8.1/8/7/Vista/XP...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mountain Duck 5.1.0.28309</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 23:06:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mountain-duck-4115.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mountain-duck-4115.html
</guid><description>
Mountain Duck allows you to mount servers and cloud storage as the disk on the computer to your desk. Open the file remotely with any application and act as on a local disk without the need to synchronize the file. Based on the platform open source solid of Cyberduck, all of the main protocols are supported to connect to any server you want, including FTP, SFTP, WebDAV, Azure Cloud Storage, Amazon S3, Google Cloud Storage, Google Drive, Dropbox, Backblaze B2 &amp;amp; OpenStack Swift. Transfer...
</description></item><item><title>Download Lansweeper 12.6.0.12</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 23:00:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lansweeper-2011.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lansweeper-2011.html
</guid><description>
Lansweeper is an application to manage IT assets and the scanning device is connected to the network. This software can scan and identify all network devices have workstation IP and Windows, Linux and Mac and indexing for them. Deep Scan Engine this software uses a set of protocols to detect and receive data from any device connected to the network. All data received can be stored in database SQL Compact or SQL Server.
Lansweeper - Scan system Internet
Software Lansweeper design open...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinMerge 2.16.52.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 22:37:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winmerge-2028.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winmerge-2028.html
</guid><description>
WinMerge is a tool to merge and distinguish open source for Windows. WinMerge can compare and folders and files, presenting differences in a visual text easy to understand or manipulate. WinMerge is very useful for determining what has changed between the version of the project and merge the changes between the versions. WinMerge can be used as a tool to compare / merge, external or as a standalone application.
In addition, Winmerge has many helpful features helps to compare, synchronize...
</description></item><item><title>Download VideoByte BD-DVD Ripper 2.2.22</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 20:19:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-videobyte-bd-dvd-ripper-14311.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-videobyte-bd-dvd-ripper-14311.html
</guid><description>
VideoByte BD-DVD Ripper is a versatile program to convert Blu-ray and DVD discs (including ISO and VIDEO_TS folders) to digital video and audio files on Windows and macOS. The software is designed to handle both homemade discs and most copyright-protected commercial discs, so users can backup and watch movies on computers, phones, TVs, and media servers instead of having to use physical discs every time.
Features of VideoByte BD-DVD Ripper
	Supports Blu-ray and DVD discs, folders, and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Moneyspire 26.0.4</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 20:10:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-moneyspire-14310.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-moneyspire-14310.html
</guid><description>
Moneyspire is a personal and small business finance management program that lets you track your basic accounts, budgets, bills, loans, and investments. Categorize your spending and income into customizable categories. Track bills so you never forget to pay and avoid late fees. Set budgets to track spending and avoid overspending in specific categories like eating out. Forecast account balances to avoid overdrafts and cash shortages. Balance your checkbook and compare it to your bank...
</description></item><item><title>Download RealCADD 5.70</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 20:05:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-realcadd-14309.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-realcadd-14309.html
</guid><description>
RealCADD is a vector-based 2D computer-aided drawing (CAD) program used for drawing technical drawings, plans, and diagrams on desktop operating systems. The software is positioned as a lighter and more intuitive alternative to large CAD suites like AutoCAD, for users who primarily need 2D drawing.
Features of RealCADD
	Supports precise 2D drawing with straight lines, arcs, splines, dimensions, crosshatching, and text, suitable for architectural, mechanical, and general engineering...
</description></item><item><title>Download AcaStat 11.1.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 19:59:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-acastat-14308.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-acastat-14308.html
</guid><description>
Enter data in the data tab, import and export delimited files, copy and paste or drag and drop data directly from spreadsheets. AcaStat creates frequency tables, cross-tabs, descriptive statistics, correlations, OLS and logistic regressions, t-tests, non-parametric tests, etc. Format variable labels and values, set missing values, use controls and recode variables. Includes 31 summary statistics procedures and five helper modules.
Core Statistics Procedures
	Frequency tables and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Razer Cortex 11.4.10.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 17:03:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-razer-cortex-5468.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-razer-cortex-5468.html
</guid><description>
Razer Cortex is one of the first game enhancement apps released on the market and as the name suggests, it can help you tweak the performance of your PC and game at the same time. If you're playing video games on a regular basis, then we don't need to tell you more about how FPS or a split-second delay can cost you with a round, ranked arena or a single hit. impressive headshot. The advanced graphics not only make the game more interesting, but they can sometimes determine if you can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Find.Same.Images.OK 5.84</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 17:02:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-find-same-images-ok-113.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-find-same-images-ok-113.html
</guid><description>
Find.Same.Images.OK lets find the images identical or similar in the folder of you, even if they were to rotate, change size or change.
Just select one or more folders that you want the program to scan and it will return a list of all the duplicate images or very similar, as indicated by the percent the same and the preview is built.Then, you can select images from the list and then copy, move or delete them.
Find.Same.Images.OK
In addition, there are other options smart option allows...
</description></item><item><title>Download WSCC Windows System Control Center 10.0.1.4 Commercial</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 17:01:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wscc-windows-system-control-center-1599.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wscc-windows-system-control-center-1599.html
</guid><description>
WSCC Windows System Control Center can automatically install and update the add-ons are supported. Alternatively, WSCC can use the http protocol to download and run the program. WSCC is portable device, no installation required. Extract content of zip archive downloaded into any folder on your computer.
The interface is very simple and intuitive, thus allowing any type of user how to find his way, regardless of the experience of their previous with the IT world. Besides, it includes a...
</description></item><item><title>Download Gilisoft Total Repair 11.2.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 17:00:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-total-repair-12836.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-total-repair-12836.html
</guid><description>
Total Repair Toolkit is an all-in-one system maintenance tool that integrates smart diagnosis, in-depth repair, and performance optimization. It has a one-click smart repair engine that can automatically resolve over 500 common problems such as system lag, game crashes, and file corruption. Meanwhile, it provides a professional manual repair module to meet advanced requirements.
Gilisoft Total Repair Features
	Application error repair based on a large DLL library
	In-depth diagnosis...
</description></item><item><title>Download Zoom Player Max 22.0 RC2</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 17:00:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zoom-player-max-104.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zoom-player-max-104.html
</guid><description>
Zoom Player MAX help you to see the film on DVD, Blu-ray, Flash movies and HD format with high quality and the ability to display subtitles in English very well. The advantage of software is that takes up very little system resources to play the movie with quick speed, change the wallpaper options while viewing movies.
Zoom Player MAX is the movies, browse high-quality photos on the computer with the advantages such as compact size, quick start, built-in codec. The application supports...
</description></item></channel></rss>