<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 13:44:35 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 13:44:35 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download KILHO AutoClick 1.4.4</title><pubDate> Tue, 21 Oct 2025 16:16:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kilho-autoclick-12515.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kilho-autoclick-12515.html
</guid><description>
AutoClick is a software or script designed to automate mouse clicking tasks, especially useful for repetitive actions in a variety of applications, including gaming and data entry. It allows users to define specific click points and automatically click at those locations. This tool is user-friendly and supports recording click sequences for repeated use.
AutoClick allows users to set precise time intervals and geographic coordinates for various click patterns. Additionally, AutoClick...
</description></item><item><title>Download ExtraMAME 25.10</title><pubDate> Tue, 21 Oct 2025 16:13:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-extramame-2608.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-extramame-2608.html
</guid><description>
ExtraMAME is a simple tool that allows simulation of the arcade game from the most popular platform but is long forgotten, thanks to which the game industry has reached the current level. After launch, you will get 11 games pre-installed, among which are: Super Mario Bros, Pac-Man Plus, Space Invaders II and other games.
The simulation of multiple machine arcade is authored by Nicola Salmoria and team MAME. MAME lets you play thousands of arcade game old school on your computer. ExtraMAME...
</description></item><item><title>Download ON1 Photo RAW 2026 v20.0.5.17637</title><pubDate> Tue, 21 Oct 2025 16:12:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-on1-photo-raw-1791.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-on1-photo-raw-1791.html
</guid><description>
ON1 Photo RAW 2023  includes the essential tools and features every photographer needs in their workflow. Our state-of-the-art, super-fast, non-destructive processing engine gives you an extremely smooth and efficient editing experience.
ON1 Photo RAW focuses on letting you get the most out of every photo. Photographers now have a quick photo management engine, hundreds of customizable photo effects, fast and beautiful HDR, masking and selection tools, layers and more in one app. Quickly...
</description></item><item><title>Download 4DDiG Disk Copy 1.1.0.29</title><pubDate> Tue, 21 Oct 2025 16:12:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4ddig-disk-copy-12660.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4ddig-disk-copy-12660.html
</guid><description>
4DDiG Disk Copy is user-friendly disk cloning software that allows you to completely and safely clone one hard drive or partition to another. With this disk cloning feature, you can clone HDD to SSD for device upgrade, clone SSD or HDD for data backup, clone disk for data transfer. Here's how to clone a drive.
Main features
	Efficient disk cloning to upgrade your hard drive or computer
	Easily transfer data to another hard drive
	Create secure local backups of specific partitions or...
</description></item><item><title>Download Automatic Email Processor 3.8.16</title><pubDate> Tue, 21 Oct 2025 16:12:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-automatic-email-processor-702.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-automatic-email-processor-702.html
</guid><description>
Automatic Email Processor is a software for managing Email in Outlook efficiency by automatically working with predefined settings. The user interface is divided into two main parts, which is the area allows you to view a list of profiles that you have created and their status and the filters located in the lower part of the interface.
Automatic Email Processor is a comprehensive solution in the archive and print emails and attachments on Outlook fully-automatic. Therefore, you can create...
</description></item><item><title>Download Synchredible Professional 9.003</title><pubDate> Tue, 21 Oct 2025 16:11:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-synchredible-professional-1923.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-synchredible-professional-1923.html
</guid><description>
Synchredible Professional is the most advanced version help synchronize the folder and your drive quickly and easily. Whether it is a single file or an entire drive - Synchredible Professional will synchronize, copy and save them for you. The software guide will assist you to identify the work that is scheduled in advance or be done through the USB connection. This way, you can keep your files in sync - automatically.
In the past years, the advanced technology of the us in Synchredible...
</description></item><item><title>Download ON1 Photo RAW MAX 2026 v20.0.5.17637</title><pubDate> Tue, 21 Oct 2025 16:11:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-on1-photo-raw-max-10717.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-on1-photo-raw-max-10717.html
</guid><description>
ON1 Photo RAW MAX 2024 is powerful photo editing software that provides photographers with many tools and features to enhance and edit their images. With a user-friendly interface, it offers advanced editing capabilities, including non-destructive editing, AI-powered adjustments, and precise control over color and tone. It also supports raw files from over 800 cameras and works with JPEG, TIF, PSD, PSB, PNG and DNG files. Additionally, it also includes photo organization tools to manage...
</description></item><item><title>Download Diffchecker 6.6.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 21 Oct 2025 16:10:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-diffchecker-5025.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-diffchecker-5025.html
</guid><description>
Diffchecker is a application compare text, images and powerful file to desktop of your. Available for Windows, macOS. Compare text files, documents, PDF. Compare photos, graphics. Because Diffchecker Desktop running entirely on your computer, so it does not have to communicate with our servers to create your difference. This means that there is no other way in addition you can view your sensitive data, you.
Diffchecker Desktop run offline, that means you can use it anytime, anywhere and...
</description></item><item><title>Download UltraSearch Professional 4.8.3.1183</title><pubDate> Tue, 21 Oct 2025 16:10:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ultrasearch-professional-10252.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ultrasearch-professional-10252.html
</guid><description>
UltraSearch Professional is the professional version that helps you find your files and documents on all connected hard drives and network drives. Search by file type, document content, or file properties. Take back your valuable time and let UltraSearch do the searching for you.
UltraSearch Professional does not maintain an index stored on your hard disk. It achieves speed by working directly on the Master File Table (MFT) of NTFS partitions. So it even identifies NTFS hardlinks. That...
</description></item><item><title>Download MiniMeters 1.0.20.1950</title><pubDate> Tue, 21 Oct 2025 16:09:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minimeters-9410.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minimeters-9410.html
</guid><description>
MiniMeters is a simple standalone sound meter application for Windows. Monitor your System Audio*, Any Input, or insert the MiniMeter Server Plug-in (VST3/AU/CLAP) at the end of your main channel in the DAW of your choice. Customize the layout in a horizontal bar (perfect for above or below the audio engine of your choice) or pop out into modules to create custom layouts.
Features of MiniMeters
	6 modules to choose from to build your perfect metering setup: Spectrogram, Waveform,...
</description></item><item><title>Download O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro 21.2.200 / Server</title><pubDate> Tue, 21 Oct 2025 16:09:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-diskimage-pro-218.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-diskimage-pro-218.html
</guid><description>
O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro is software backup data comprehensive and effective is provided to protect the data of the computer system, it creates images for individual drives or the entire system that still does not affect your system.
O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro allows the user to backup the entire computer or drive, the and files whenever you want even while the computer is being used. Or can use O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro to create a copy chinh sac of computer disk drives, can be used instead of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Synchredible 9.003</title><pubDate> Tue, 21 Oct 2025 16:08:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-synchredible-53.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-synchredible-53.html
</guid><description>
Synchredible is an easy to use tool to synchronize folders and files. It provides a wizard interface lets you set up the sync job, select files to exclude, schedule the job to execute automatically, and more.Additional features include support for network and external drives, check CRC32, and more.
Synchredible - synchronization of folders and files
Among other things, you can use the filter for the file type specific data synchronization according to the time or routine deletion of...
</description></item><item><title>Download MyLanViewer Enterprise 6.6.2 / Business</title><pubDate> Tue, 21 Oct 2025 16:08:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mylanviewer-enterprise-1274.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mylanviewer-enterprise-1274.html
</guid><description>
MyLanViewer is a program for scanning IP address, Netbios and LAN / Network powerful for Windows tool whois and traceroute, remote shutdown and process management Wake On LAN (WOL), scan and monitor wireless networks. This app will help you find all IP addresses, MAC addresses and shared folders of computers on the network wired or wireless (Wi-Fi).
MyLanViewer Enterprise - Scan IP address LAN/Network
The program scans network and displays the computer network in your window, friends...
</description></item><item><title>Download Syncovery Premium 11.9.3.113</title><pubDate> Tue, 21 Oct 2025 16:08:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncovery-pro-enterprise-232.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncovery-pro-enterprise-232.html
</guid><description>
Syncovery Pro Enterprise is a great application used to back up data and to synchronize personal computers, servers, laptops, notepads and storage online. The software comes with support for FTP and secure FTP servers, SSH, WebDAV, Amazon S3, http, update the part file, ZIP compression, data encryption, and schedule automatic backups.
Syncovery Pro Enterprise have the ability to freely select files and folders across the whole folder hierarchy in tree view and supports email...
</description></item><item><title>Download RAM Saver Professional 25.10.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 21 Oct 2025 16:07:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ram-saver-pro-565.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ram-saver-pro-565.html
</guid><description>
RAM Saver Pro is a professional software optimize RAM is for system stable operation with high performance. RAM Saver Pro aims to provide all the tools necessary to increase the amount of free memory, at any time, also monitor and check the RAM.
When using RAM Saver Pro, you will be allowed to access its main menu by right-clicking on the tray icon. Also, if you want to display the main panel of the program you just double-click the icon. In addition, from the main interface of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download VovSoft Tree Notes 2.5</title><pubDate> Tue, 21 Oct 2025 16:06:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-tree-notes-11294.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-tree-notes-11294.html
</guid><description>
Vovsoft Tree Notes is a decentralized note-taking application designed to improve your organizational efficiency and streamline your information management process. This powerful software provides users with a user-friendly platform to create, organize and access their notes with ease.
Tree Notes for Windows is a flexible and powerful note-taking solution that meets the needs of individuals, students, professionals, and creative minds alike. Boost your productivity, stay organized, and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Grub2Win 3.0.0.7</title><pubDate> Tue, 21 Oct 2025 16:06:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-grub2win-3177.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-grub2win-3177.html
</guid><description>
Grub2Win is a open source program to dual boot Windows and Linux safely. Grub2Win boot code the GNU Grub version 2.04. Everything is in a folder of 20 MB on Windows drive C: On the EFI system, a few small modules to be installed into the EFI partition of your.
Grub2Win - Boot system, Windows
Using GUI Windows and simple instructions you can install Grub2Win quickly and safely. Notice the boot time and help can be displayed in multiple languages. After installing interface, it's easy to...
</description></item><item><title>Download O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Professional WinPE 21.2.200</title><pubDate> Tue, 21 Oct 2025 16:06:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-diskimage-workstation-4548.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-diskimage-workstation-4548.html
</guid><description>
O&amp;amp;O DiskImage WinPE is a program user friendly designed to help users create images of partitions and hard disk to keep them safe for their data in case disaster strikes. O&amp;amp;O DiskImage WinPE includes a set the ability to backup files and drives strong, helping users to easily keep data they want to secure. Users can create images of partitions or entire computer with just a few mouse clicks and they can also create the disk can boot if necessary.
Features of O&amp;amp;O DiskImage...
</description></item><item><title>Download Notepad++ 8.8.7 + Portable</title><pubDate> Tue, 21 Oct 2025 16:05:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-notepad-1062.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-notepad-1062.html
</guid><description>
Notepad++ is software editor programming editor and edit source code support on Windows platform, working with many other programming languages like ASP, PHP, Java, C#, Python, Jsp... Notepad++ is a source code editor is many programmers choice with many functions than men of it is Notepad.
Notepad++ - tool editor programming
Notepad++ has many features, simple interface, and can combine with many programming languages different. Notepad++ supports you to automatically perform various...
</description></item><item><title>Download Vovsoft Auto Change Screensavers 2.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 21 Oct 2025 16:04:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-auto-change-screensavers-2784.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-auto-change-screensavers-2784.html
</guid><description>
Vovsoft Auto Change Screensavers is a tool to the desktop mini will change the screen saver of you. App Auto Change Screensavers allows you to automatically change the screen saver of his. Have you installed more screensavers interesting? Sometimes people spend a lot of time trying to choose which one to make default. Manager this screensaver solves that problem.
Now you can have all your savers run on your screen and this does not need to adjust the Windows settings every time you want...
</description></item><item><title>Download TickTick Premium 6.4.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 21 Oct 2025 16:04:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ticktick-premium-7770.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ticktick-premium-7770.html
</guid><description>
TickTick Premium is a task management application that helps users stay organized, it is very suitable for educators and students with many incentives. TickTick turns your Windows PC device into a flexible, easy-to-use and highly efficient office platform. Join millions of people to capture ideas, organize their lives, and do something creative every day.
Whether there are work related tasks or personal goals, TickTick is here to help you manage all your to-dos. With five different...
</description></item><item><title>Download Imagiro Piano 2.2.308</title><pubDate> Tue, 21 Oct 2025 16:03:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-imagiro-piano-9987.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-imagiro-piano-9987.html
</guid><description>
Imagiro Piano is a virtual piano instrument packed with lofi character. combines gentle, intimate piano recordings with creative processing. Recorded in the bedroom and pulled from extensive internet repositories, the imagiro's piano delivers piano sounds with flawless beauty. Use loops and inversions to create lush frozen piano sounds, or use the ADSR controls to turn a celeste into an EDM strum.
Features of Imagiro Piano
	loop mode for infinite intimacy
	reverse mode for mellower...
</description></item><item><title>Download FileCenter Professional Suite 12.0.30</title><pubDate> Tue, 21 Oct 2025 16:02:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-filecenter-professional-suite-3407.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-filecenter-professional-suite-3407.html
</guid><description>
FileCenter Professional Suite is a set of tools, file manager and powerful document. FileCenter Professional Suite is a management solution document full and effective designed for small businesses. The program blends organize files and scan easily with the ability to edit and create PDF advanced. In addition, the program also comes with a number of functions and features, such as Search, OCR, restore files, etc. Integrated with cloud services such as OneDrive, Google Drive and Dropbox,...
</description></item><item><title>Download UltraSearch 4.8.3.1183</title><pubDate> Tue, 21 Oct 2025 16:02:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ultrasearch-5751.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ultrasearch-5751.html
</guid><description>
UltraSearch finds files and folders on local NTFS drives and provides results in seconds. UltraSearch does not maintain an index stored on your hard disk, but achieves its speed by working directly on the Main File Table (MFT) of an NTFS partition. UltraSearch even identifies NTFS hard links. Just enter a filename or template like * .exe and see the first result while you're still typing.
Features of UltraSearch
	Additional information such as file size and file date (last changed,...
</description></item><item><title>Download EstlCAM 12.153</title><pubDate> Tue, 21 Oct 2025 16:02:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-estlcam-13476.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-estlcam-13476.html
</guid><description>
EstlCAM is a user-friendly CNC and CAM (Computer-Aided Manufacturing) control software, designed to generate toolpaths and G-code for CNC machines, especially suitable for 2D, 2.5D and 3D milling operations. The software supports importing a variety of design file formats, including 2D drawings (.dxf, .svg, .png, .jpg) and 3D models (.stl), allowing users to position, scale, and rotate designs before generating toolpaths.
The software is especially popular among enthusiasts and...
</description></item></channel></rss>