<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 17:41:16 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 17:41:16 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download AB Download Manager 1.6.10</title><pubDate> Thu, 14 Aug 2025 19:46:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ab-download-manager-12399.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ab-download-manager-12399.html
</guid><description>
With this application, you can easily download files from anywhere. Enjoy fast, free downloads with seamless browser extension support. It is built to be a desktop application that allows you to manage and organize your downloads better than before.
AB Download Manager features
	Simple and modern UI: Simple UI and dark mode by default
	Faster download speeds: Download files using multiple connections to increase your download speed by up to 500%
	Download Queue: Create and manage your...
</description></item><item><title>Download Brave Browser 1.81.135</title><pubDate> Thu, 14 Aug 2025 19:38:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-brave-browser-2874.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-brave-browser-2874.html
</guid><description>
Brave Browser is a browser based on Chromium, the basic principle is that operation fast and privacy of users. The program can block pop-up windows and other ads, plus it blocked the mechanism for monitoring the online activities of your. Therefore, you can purchase and safely browse the website you are interested in without having to worry about the fact that your activity will be monitored and then you will be shown the necessary advertising or service provider of parties...
</description></item><item><title>Download EaseUS Todo PCTrans Pro 14.2 Build 20250811 + Technician</title><pubDate> Thu, 14 Aug 2025 19:36:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-todo-pctrans-pro-1291.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-todo-pctrans-pro-1291.html
</guid><description>
EaseUS Todo PCTrans Professional is powerful software helps transfer data, apps and settings of your account from one computer to another easily. EasUS Todo PCTrans put everything into a new PC and ready to use . Transfer tool PC this easy move safe files, folder files, program and account your existing to a new computer. In just a click of the mouse, making PC your new is loaded with everything you need. Instead of copy and paste, you can transfer to new PC in a seamless way.
EaseUS...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Lightroom Classic 2025 v14.5.0 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Thu, 14 Aug 2025 19:36:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-photoshop-lightroom-classic-0004-734.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-photoshop-lightroom-classic-0004-734.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Photoshop Lightroom Classic is a desktop-optimized photo editing and organizing software. Lightroom Classic gives you powerful one-click tools and advanced controls to make your photos look great. Easily organize all your photos on your desktop and share them in a variety of ways.
In addition, Lightroom Classic has a powerful import process that allows users to preview images before importing. It supports many camera raw formats and includes a database system for efficient photo...
</description></item><item><title>Download Syncthing 2.0.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 14 Aug 2025 19:34:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncthing-2115.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncthing-2115.html
</guid><description>
Syncthing is synchronization service, cloud and open and non-focus allows you to share and sync files with other computers and gives you full control how to share your data and who can access it. Syncthing does not store your data in any other place, there is no server side Tuesday how to join. In addition, all the communication is secured by TLS and every button is determined by the certificate the strength of the encryption. Only computers that have explicitly allowed can connect with...
</description></item><item><title>Download Free YouTube Download 4.4.35.812 Premium</title><pubDate> Thu, 14 Aug 2025 19:34:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-download-1177.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-download-1177.html
</guid><description>
Free YouTube Download Premium is the most popular application to download videos from YouTube. The program was released in 2006 and regularly updated since then. Use the program to download and convert YouTube videos to view offline anytime.
Free YouTube Download - added Support to download youtube
Download more videos! Save whole playlists and YouTube channels, videos from a playlist individually (history, video be favorite, favourites, Watch later), videos from many different...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Dimension 4.1.4.4533 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Thu, 14 Aug 2025 19:33:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-dimension-cc-254.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-dimension-cc-254.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Dimension CC 2019 is software for designing 2D and 3D to easily create 3D images are of high quality, made to combine the resources intuitive 2D and 3D in one product the actual environment. Purpose introduction of Adobe Dimension is to provide to developers the tools necessary to integrate assets in 2D and 3D without having to study the application complex and specialized. In other words, the program allows you to quickly and simple and creative image other combined 2D and 3D...
</description></item><item><title>Download Pano2VR Pro 7.1.11</title><pubDate> Thu, 14 Aug 2025 19:33:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pano2vr-pro-999.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pano2vr-pro-999.html
</guid><description>
Pano2VR Pro is software to help you create the images travel. Pano2VR quickly publish panoramic images to travel in a snap. Pano2VR will help you to quickly get the project up and running and on the desktop as well as mobile devices. Pano2VR offers an easy way to add and edit panoramas and sightseeing trips available on Google Street View. When you have connected your account, you will see all the excursions and panoramic picture that you've uploaded to Google Street View. You can continue...
</description></item><item><title>Download Argente Registry Cleaner 4.0.2.4</title><pubDate> Thu, 14 Aug 2025 19:32:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-argente-registry-cleaner-13814.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-argente-registry-cleaner-13814.html
</guid><description>
Argente Registry Cleaner is a free Windows utility designed to scan, clean and repair invalid or obsolete entries in the Windows Registry, helping to improve system stability and performance. This utility quickly analyzes the entire Registry for errors such as invalid entries left by uninstalled programs, missing keys, broken references, and other junk that can cause system crashes.
Key Features:
	Fast and Thorough Scan: Provides multiple scan modes including Safe (fastest), Normal...
</description></item><item><title>Download Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium 4.4.35.812</title><pubDate> Thu, 14 Aug 2025 19:32:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-to-mp3-converter-premium-844.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-to-mp3-converter-premium-844.html
</guid><description>
Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium version is a software used to convert YouTube to MP3, extract audio from playlists YouTube, show listings, charts, video responses, channels, favorites of the user. With Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium, you can download and convert playlists, channels, stream original tv series and get them into iTunes at the same time.
Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium - convert YouTube to MP3
Features Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium from the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Argente Malware Cleaner 3.0.2.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 14 Aug 2025 19:31:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-argente-malware-cleaner-13494.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-argente-malware-cleaner-13494.html
</guid><description>
Argente Malware Cleaner is a lightweight utility designed to detect and remove a wide range of malware, including spyware, adware, Trojans and other threats that can compromise your privacy and data. It works as a complementary tool alongside your main antivirus software, helping to detect malware that may slip through the cracks.
Key features of Argente Malware Cleaner include:
	Easy-to-use, clean, and user-friendly interface that suits both casual and advanced users.
	Deep scanning...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Substance 3D Stager 3.1.4.6273 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Thu, 14 Aug 2025 19:31:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-substance-3d-stager-6624.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-substance-3d-stager-6624.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Substance 3D Stager is a professional staging tool for designing and rendering scenes. Import content, arrange your scene, apply materials and textures, adjust both image-based and physical lighting, save the camera with different resolutions, and render realistic images , all in Stager!
Substance 3D Stager allows you to make creative decisions in context. Tweak and adjust your compositions in real time. Build your realistic 3D scenes with smart tools quickly and efficiently. With...
</description></item><item><title>Download MusConv Ultimate 4.10.407</title><pubDate> Thu, 14 Aug 2025 19:30:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html
</guid><description>
MusConv transfers playlists, albums, followed artists and liked songs across a variety of services – Spotify, Apple Music, Amazon Music, YouTube, YouTube Music, iTunes, Deezer, Tidal, SoundCloud, Pandora and more 125 music services!
Features of MusConv Ultimate
	Transfer playlists, albums, followed artists and liked tracks between over 125 music servicesManage playlists (Delete, Merge, Split, Copy...)
	More than 125 music services supported
	Access DAILY updated music charts on...
</description></item><item><title>Download Argente System Repair 1.0.2.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 14 Aug 2025 19:29:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-argente-system-repair-13813.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-argente-system-repair-13813.html
</guid><description>
Argente System Repair is a lightweight utility designed to diagnose and fix common Windows system problems. It scans your system to identify errors in operating system components, file systems, installation files, and other system components, and then applies targeted fixes to resolve these problems. The tool provides different scan modes, including simple scan, recommended scan, and custom scan, allowing users to customize the repair process according to their needs.
System Repair...
</description></item><item><title>Download Plagiarism Checker X Business 9.0.6</title><pubDate> Thu, 14 Aug 2025 19:29:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-plagiarism-checker-x-enterprise-2981.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-plagiarism-checker-x-enterprise-2981.html
</guid><description>
Plagiarism Checker X Enterprise is a professional software helps to check text on a web page. It's for teachers, students, publishers. Plagiarism is constant headache for students, teachers, web content writers, website administrators and online publishers. With the availability of online resources, the trend to copy / paste has been growing. This is not only against professional ethics but also violates copyrights, which may lead to lawsuits. Therefore, everyone tries to avoid trouble....
</description></item><item><title>Download Agelong Tree 6.0.5</title><pubDate> Thu, 14 Aug 2025 16:28:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-agelong-tree-14050.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-agelong-tree-14050.html
</guid><description>
Agelong Tree is genealogy software that helps users build and print family trees, store and display information about relatives and important events in life. The software supports multiple languages and offers features such as Unicode GEDCOM support, integration with Google Maps, and the ability to define custom fields.
Agelong Tree is convenient for both beginners and professionals, and is packed with features
	Build a family tree using photos.
	Calculate and display the degrees of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Visual Studio Code 1.103.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 14 Aug 2025 16:10:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-visual-studio-code-3182.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-visual-studio-code-3182.html
</guid><description>
Visual Studio Code is the encryption tool of Microsoft has met most of the needs of the developer. Environment this encoding was introduced to compete with other products such as Sublime and Nodepad ++ . Microsoft, in its new product, has not been released in many years, has provided many features in a simple environment. In addition to the familiar with a dozen programming languages, the syntax and get to know coding language as soon as be encrypted and allows for syntax highlighting, it...
</description></item><item><title>Download ImageMagick 7.1.2-1</title><pubDate> Thu, 14 Aug 2025 16:09:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-imagemagick-1319.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-imagemagick-1319.html
</guid><description>
ImageMagick is software image processing command line to create, edit, compose, or convert bitmap images. ImageMagick is completely free for users and you easily download it on taiwebs.com. Typical functions most of software is able to read and write images in many formats (over 100) including DPX, EXR, GIF, JPEG, JPEG-2000, PDF, PhotoCD, PNG, Postcript, SVG, and TIFF.
ImageMagick - image Processing
The Windows version of ImageMagick is installed. Just click on the appropriate version...
</description></item><item><title>Download Office Timeline Plus 11.19.00.00 Expert / Pro / Pro+ Edition</title><pubDate> Thu, 14 Aug 2025 16:08:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-timeline-2106.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-timeline-2106.html
</guid><description>
Office Timeline is an add-on very useful and powerful software for Microsoft PowerPoint. With add-ons, you can create PowerPoint documents look more beautiful. With add-ons, you can add the time Line on the project by yourself. Application time for the composition and different segments of the document, your PowerPoint will not only increase the beauty for your work, but also for customers and your manager. The people who created this product is also believe that add-ons this is the only...
</description></item><item><title>Download GPU-Z 2.68</title><pubDate> Thu, 14 Aug 2025 16:07:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gpu-z-1144.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gpu-z-1144.html
</guid><description>
GPU-Z is a compact utility, simple help display parameters GPU and video Card the computer. GPU-Z to display information adapter details, Bios version, memory details, overclock, default clock, 3D clock, and much more. Besides, the program also includes check download GPU to verify configuration lane PCI-Express, as well as monitoring sensors in real time.
GPU-Z - information Display, GPU and display Card
Features of GPU-Z
	Small utility that displays the parameters of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cockos REAPER 7.43</title><pubDate> Thu, 14 Aug 2025 16:07:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cockos-reaper-889.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cockos-reaper-889.html
</guid><description>
Cockos REAPER is a powerful software for for windows, chp lets you record, arrange, edit, and display the audio waveform multi-track. Cockos REAPER offers an extensive feature set includes many effects and a sample project. REAPER supports ASIO, Kernel Streaming, WaveOut, and DirectSound for playback and recording. It reads the files in WAV, OGG and MP3 files and records WAV files. You can arrange any number of items in any number of tracks and use plug-in sound processing (DirectX and...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinUAE 6.0.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 14 Aug 2025 16:06:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winuae-4960.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winuae-4960.html
</guid><description>
WinUAE is a port to Windows of emulator Amiga UAE are designed to simulate cargo Amore 500, 1000 and 2000. WinUAE is easily one of the emulator most complex that we have seen with more options than you can use. You will need to know where to find the resources to use it properly. It also supports multi-CPU simulation, drive, etc.
The characteristics of WinUAE
	The chips original (OCS), The chip enhanced (ECS) and architecture, advanced graphics (AGA)
	Device I / O: ( floppy drive ,...
</description></item><item><title>Download R-Drive Image 7.3 Build 7308</title><pubDate> Thu, 14 Aug 2025 16:05:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-drive-image-1971.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-drive-image-1971.html
</guid><description>
R-Drive Image is a powerful utility provides create a file disk image for backup purposes, or copy. File disk image contains the exact copy each and every byte of hard drive, partition or logical disk and can be created with various levels compression without stopping Windows os and therefore without interrupting your work. The image file this drive can then be stored in many places, including various removable media as different as a CD-R (W) / DVD, Iomega Zip or Jazz, etc.
R-Drive...
</description></item><item><title>Download CpuFrequenz 4.48 + Portable</title><pubDate> Thu, 14 Aug 2025 16:05:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cpufrequenz-2900.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cpufrequenz-2900.html
</guid><description>
About the hardware, amount of RAM good, faster hard drives or solid state drives and multi-core processor is required to have better performance for your computer. About the software, you are not cluttered with the installed operating system to make it use the hardware with the highest performance.
If you feel the processor of the computer does not operate at full capacity even when you have good hardware, then it can be due to install the operating system, BIOS settings, error thermal...
</description></item><item><title>Download QOwnNotes 25.8.3</title><pubDate> Thu, 14 Aug 2025 16:04:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qownnotes-3178.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qownnotes-3178.html
</guid><description>
QOwnNotes is notes bookmark file simple text (GPL) open source application for GNU / Linux , Mac OS X and Windows of Patrizio Bekerle ( pbek on GitHub and IRC) (optional) activity along with the notes application of ownCloud or Nextcloud. QOwnNote store your notes as plain text files and can be synchronized with synchronization function file of ownCloud / Nextcloud. You can also use other apps like Syncthing or Dropbox . Just write out your thoughts as they appear, and edit them if...
</description></item></channel></rss>