<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 10:20:46 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 10:20:46 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download IObit Driver Booster Pro 13.1.0.171</title><pubDate> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 00:00:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iobit-driver-booster-102.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iobit-driver-booster-102.html
</guid><description>
IObit Driver Booster Pro is the starting step to avoid hardware errors, the loss of the system and hidden security vulneruses. To update the regular driver is also an effective way to enhance your overall computer performance and maximize your gaming experience. While this process can be dangerous and frustrating if done manually. IObit Driver Booster Pro is introduced to download and update the driver for you automatically with only one click. Based on the cloud library, IObit Driver...
</description></item><item><title>Download HWiNFO 8.34 Build 5870</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 23:59:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hwinfo-1828.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hwinfo-1828.html
</guid><description>
HWiNFO (HWiNFO32) is a diagnostic tool and hardware information, recognizes and displays detailed information about all the hardware components of you. HWiNFO will hold the component in the tree view and provide the report easy to read for each category.
HWiNFO - Hardware Diagnostics
HWiNFO is especially useful so you don't have to install it on each computer and completely for free. Just run the direct program and you will have full information of the computer that you need. The...
</description></item><item><title>Download HEU KMS Activator 63.3.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 23:59:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-heu-kms-activator-7529.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-heu-kms-activator-7529.html
</guid><description>
HEU KMS Activator is a quick Windows and Office activator with multiple methods like Digital License, KMS38, OEM and KMS. This tool takes advantage of building a KMS server inside your system, so it can easily activate both Windows and Office.
In addition, it also supports Windows backup and restore, Change MS Office Edition, Key setting manually in case you purchased the original Key and more.
Features of HEU KMS Activator
	Digital Trigger &amp;amp; KMS
	Office uninstallation...
</description></item><item><title>Download BluffTitler Ultimate 16.8.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 23:58:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bluffTitler-ultimate-39.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bluffTitler-ultimate-39.html
</guid><description>
Create 3D titles brilliant for your video with BluffTitler Ultimate. You want to impress your friends and clients with 3D titles interesting? But don't want to spend a fortune on 3D animation, as well as professional software video titling?
BluffTitler is the easiest way to add animated text, 3D spectacular for photos and videos of you! Other 3D programs always seemed too hard to learn and too expensive to justify. But thanks to BluffTitler, I can finally create all the wonderful...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tor Browser 15.0.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 23:58:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tor-browser-1833.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tor-browser-1833.html
</guid><description>
Tor Browser also has full name is Tor Browser Bundle is a web browser give you ability to access the internet safety and security your personal information as well as sensitive documents absolutely. By Tor Browser Bundle will automatically change the IP address on the machine to hide the identity when surfing the web. Tor Browser is free web browser full-featured basic and advanced allows you to leverage the Tor network anonymously without need to make any configuration changes or install...
</description></item><item><title>Download Yamicsoft Windows 11/10 Manager 2.2.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 23:57:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yamicsoft-windows-11-manager-6779.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yamicsoft-windows-11-manager-6779.html
</guid><description>
Windows 11 Manager is an all-in-one utility for Microsoft Windows 11 specially, it includes over forty different utilities to optimize, tweak, clean up, speed up and repair your Windows 11, helps make your system perform faster, eliminate system fault, increase stability and security, personalize your copy of Windows 11, and meet all of your expectations.
Features of Windows 11 Manager:
Information:
	Creates the system restore point manually;
	Gets detailed information about your...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wise Disk Cleaner 11.2.8.848</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 23:57:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wise-disk-cleaner-392.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wise-disk-cleaner-392.html
</guid><description>
Wise Disk Cleaner software to clean hard drive by finding and deleting junk files downloads accumulate over time. Wise Disk Cleaner is pre-configured with about 50 types of extension files can usually be considered disposable, and you can extend the range by adding the file types of their own.
Wise Disk Cleaner to use the advanced algorithm with the ability to quick scan and comprehensive scan of hard drive space. Users can delete browsing history as well as the personal data important...
</description></item><item><title>Download HWiNFO Portable 8.34.5870</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 23:56:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hwinfo-portable-11340.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hwinfo-portable-11340.html
</guid><description>
HWiNFO Portable is a professional hardware information and diagnostic tool that supports the latest components, technologies and industry standards. These tools are designed to collect and present the maximum amount of information possible about computer hardware, making them suitable for users looking for driver updates, computer manufacturers, system integrators as well as technical experts. Retrieved information is presented in a logical, easy-to-understand format and can be exported...
</description></item><item><title>Download Executor 2.1.7</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 23:55:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-executor-271.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-executor-271.html
</guid><description>
Executor for windows is a software alternative premium customization features for the Windows "Run" and "Search Programs". When you press WIN + Z and provides the search results instant, as-you-type for any keywords you enter. By default, Executor will index all the Desktop and Start Menu and you can easily expand the search range by adding the folder location additional.
Executor for windows
The program comes with a list of commands built in which you can use to quickly access many...
</description></item><item><title>Download MSAct++ 2.10</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 23:55:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-msact-plus-plus-258.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-msact-plus-plus-258.html
</guid><description>
MSAct++ is compact software with features activate windows and office license quickly with click simple. Program for install key and activate Windows 7-10 and Office 2010-2016. If the key installed allows the activation through the network, through the Internet, product will be activated automatically, if this does not happen and the lock is not key - code is issued to transfer the M $ Activation Center to activate by phone. Unlike MSAct in the program MSAct Plus has the ability to create...
</description></item><item><title>Download Systweak PDF Editor 1.0.0.8300</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 23:54:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-systweak-pdf-editor-11484.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-systweak-pdf-editor-11484.html
</guid><description>
Systweak PDF Editor is a fast and simple solution to edit, convert, sign, protect, compress PDF files and make scanned PDF files searchable and can choose. With Systweak PDF Editor, quickly convert your PDF files into a variety of editable formats. Converting PDF files to and from any MS Office files, images, ebooks, web pages, and other formats just got easier.
For working and editing PDF files, Systweak PDF editor offers many features and tools. Using them, you can mark text for...
</description></item><item><title>Download Avast Premium Security 25.11.10580</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 23:53:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avast-premier-antivirus-security-1359.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avast-premier-antivirus-security-1359.html
</guid><description>
Avast! Premier Antivirus is antivirus software famous by combining all the technologies and methods virus advanced. The developer software this anti-virus have invested in all their knowledge about fighting viruses to create one of the software anti-virus best. Program anti-virus this combines all the technology and advanced methods to get the level of computer security highest. This product is ideal for all the Windows operating system.
Avast! Premier Antivirus - antivirus...
</description></item><item><title>Download DiskBoss Ultimate 16.1.18 + Pro + Enterprise</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 23:53:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-diskboss-ultimate-1289.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-diskboss-ultimate-1289.html
</guid><description>
DiskBoss Ultimate is a software application professional, built to help you analyze disks, directories and network shares, arrange files and folders, perform the operation the advanced search and delete duplicate items, as well as perform management activities file automatically based on user-defined rules and policies.
DiskBoss Ultimate - analyzing disk and file manager
This tool also can synchronize disks, directories and network shares, perform the task delete data securely in batch...
</description></item><item><title>Download EverNote 10.162.3.38898</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 23:52:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-evernote-3261.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-evernote-3261.html
</guid><description>
EverNote is the all in one tool allows you to track notes, todo items, memos, outlines, excerpts, websites, ideas and other things and automatically synchronize them between multiple computers and mobile devices (iPhone, Android, etc.). You can choose to sort their notes into categories, password protect them, export them to XML and more. EverNote supports a number of pattern notes allow you to add to-do list, spreadsheet like Excel to calculate costs (automatic sum), notes, phone, contact...
</description></item><item><title>Download Prime95 31.01 Build 1</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 23:52:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-prime95-6149.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-prime95-6149.html
</guid><description>
Prime95 is a tool used on the windows operating system of 64-bit platforms, which allows users to calculate the math, implementation of the formula for complex computing expressions, Prime95 64 bits also supporting you to integrate into redaction software such as microsoft. Another thing is that the Prime95 64 bit allows for the standard deviation and other difficult expressions.
Prime95 is known to be a small and easy-to-use app that allows you to find the Mersenne Prime number...
</description></item><item><title>Download Coolmuster Data Recovery 3.0.55</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 23:51:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-data-recovery-6165.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-data-recovery-6165.html
</guid><description>
Coolmuster Data Recovery is a data recovery software on a computer hard drive with a quick search engine that finds out all the data of the deleted user on the computer, performing the recovery of all the data such as email, images, videos, audio files, and text files.
Coolmuster Data Recovery restored more than 550 different file formats including images, office files, videos, audio files, emails, compressed files ... the deleted data, partition format, or unaccessed file was restored...
</description></item><item><title>Download DiskBoss 16.1.18</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 23:51:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-diskboss-19.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-diskboss-19.html
</guid><description>
DiskBoss Free scan drives or folders and view a report of how the amount of your storage used by the file type. It automatically categorizes your files by general types (e.g. multimedia files, executables, documents, etc.) and allows you to see more details to see the results for each file type and last is a list of all the files in the group.
Other features include creating signatures the MD5, SHA1 or SHA256 for the file and text to HTML, Excel CSV and ACSII.
The free version is limited...
</description></item><item><title>Download Perfinity dotNET Runtime Analyzer 9.0.12</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 23:50:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfinity-dotnet-runtime-analyzer-10650.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfinity-dotnet-runtime-analyzer-10650.html
</guid><description>
Perfinity dotNET Runtime Analyzer is a powerful line-level pattern analyzer that provides functionality to identify performance bottlenecks in applications. In contrast to the classic .NET profiler, it allows users to analyze processes using native code. Therefore, performance issues caused by native code can be identified, for example, from 3rd party libraries like the .NET runtime.
In addition, the tool supports event tracking to maximize user experience. File I/O activity, network...
</description></item><item><title>Download DBF Viewer 2000 v8.89.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 23:49:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbf-viewer-2000-7869.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbf-viewer-2000-7869.html
</guid><description>
DBF Viewer 2000 is a fast, efficient solution for viewing and editing all types of DBF files. It can handle files from dBase, Visual dBase, Foxpro, Visual FoxPro and Clipper, just to name a few, with performance that easily rivals expensive professional database utilities. DBF Viewer 2000 is extremely fast, does any task, just one simple query and cleanup copy to export data at lightning speed.
With DBF Editor's simple, dynamically generated visual dialogs, you can easily view the...
</description></item><item><title>Download nTopology 5.34.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 23:49:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ntopology-7887.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ntopology-7887.html
</guid><description>
nTopology is software that enables engineers and designers to create any geometry no matter how complex and meet the requirements of high performance products . Our software is used from research through production to create breakthrough products and processes for the aerospace, automotive, medical and consumer industries. Our customers depend on the general design capabilities of the nTopology to get the most out of new hardware, optimize components where performance is important,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Inno Setup Unpacker 2.1.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 23:49:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-inno-setup-unpacker-12546.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-inno-setup-unpacker-12546.html
</guid><description>
Inno Setup is a popular and reliable application that creates program installers by helping you create scripts. Extracting the installation files from their container, resulting from compiling code with Inno Setup, can only be done through self-extracting files. In other words, you need to create a self-extracting executable to shell the installation documents.
Inno Setup Unpacker can help you avoid such actions, which is especially useful because some system security protocols block...
</description></item><item><title>Download TheSage 7.72.2824</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 23:48:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thesage-2794.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thesage-2794.html
</guid><description>
TheSage has full name is TheSage English Dictionary and Thesaurus is a complete dictionary and thesaurus of the English language. It runs locally and does not use your Internet connection. The program provides a screen that has unique structure, as well as searching wildcard, anagram search and much more.
TheSage - English dictionary
During the installation process, you selected install dictionary English TheSage and dictionary in the usual way, or create a mobile version. Create...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDF Annotator 10.0.0.1000</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 20:54:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-annotator-178.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-annotator-178.html
</guid><description>
PDF Annotator software user open any PDF file and add annotations, using the mouse or pen Tablet PC, directly on the Page of the PDF file. PDF Annotator allows users to perform editing operations on PDF files such as: add notes, edit signature, highlight, insert images or text... From the this useful tool, you can completely modify PDF files as you like in order to meet the different work.
PDF Annotator
With the PDF Annotator the document has annotations can then be saved directly back...
</description></item><item><title>Download Apache OpenOffice 4.1.16</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 17:32:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-openoffice-4220.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-openoffice-4220.html
</guid><description>
OpenOffice is a replacement tool for free and mobile for productivity tools Office provides many utilities, such as text processing, spreadsheet, presentation, graphics, editor, recipe and program management database. OpenOffice can be installed and used on all popular platforms and provides support for many different languages. The app will store your data in ODF format, but also can read and write files in many other formats. The file formats used by the software most popular Office...
</description></item><item><title>Download StartAllBack 3.9.17.5334</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 17:30:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-startallback-6857.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-startallback-6857.html
</guid><description>
With the official release of Windows 11, chances are that most of you want to try it out. As the name suggests, StartAllBack is a small, lightweight tool that can help you enjoy the power of the new operating system while keeping the look and feel, especially because main work area, desktop of Windows 7, Windows 10 as taskbars and start menu styles.
StartAllBack is specially designed for Windows 11 and will not work on any older operating systems. If you want to get the start menu back...
</description></item></channel></rss>