<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 01:50:33 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 01:50:33 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Audacity 3.7.5</title><pubDate> Fri, 08 Aug 2025 01:49:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-audacity-1648.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-audacity-1648.html
</guid><description>
Audacity software to record audio along with editing features such as noise filtering, distortion noise, insert unique effects. The latest version of Audacity include the improvement of effects, interface, updates Nyquist and libflac. A number of bugs have also been fixed to help the software operate more smoothly. Audacity accompanied by the link to various sources, assist you learn how to use all the features of the program. These sources include Quick Help Guide (quick help), a guide,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Office Timeline Plus 11.18.00.00 Expert / Pro / Pro+ Edition</title><pubDate> Fri, 08 Aug 2025 01:48:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-timeline-2106.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-timeline-2106.html
</guid><description>
Office Timeline is an add-on very useful and powerful software for Microsoft PowerPoint. With add-ons, you can create PowerPoint documents look more beautiful. With add-ons, you can add the time Line on the project by yourself. Application time for the composition and different segments of the document, your PowerPoint will not only increase the beauty for your work, but also for customers and your manager. The people who created this product is also believe that add-ons this is the only...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Camera Raw 17.4.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 08 Aug 2025 01:47:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-camera-raw-02en-785.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-camera-raw-02en-785.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Camera Raw is Plugin edit photo on photoshop with the ability to handle the raw photos after the shoot to create beautiful photos and quality than the input image initially, this program helps support the photographers in editing and photography, make the photo beautiful.
Adobe Camera Raw - edit Raw images Photoshop
Adobe Camera Raw is a plugin which is integrated accompanied by a number of software photo editing such as Photoshop, Photoshop Elements, After Effects and...
</description></item><item><title>Download VideoProc Converter AI 8.3</title><pubDate> Fri, 08 Aug 2025 01:47:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-videoproc-2473.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-videoproc-2473.html
</guid><description>
VideoProc (an improved version of WinX HD Video Converter Deluxe) - processing software the most powerful video designed to edit, cut, crop, merge, adjust, convert and compress (4K) video with full Hardware Acceleration. Is the heir to be improved a lot, VideoProc integrated conversion / compression video UHD, the download at videos (YouTube) with the video editor, gives you the power to control optimal for every video file much music, SD, HD and 4K on your PC. With technology hardware...
</description></item><item><title>Download Capture One Pro 16.6.4.3044 + Enterprise</title><pubDate> Fri, 08 Aug 2025 01:46:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capture-one-pro-624.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capture-one-pro-624.html
</guid><description>
Capture One Pro is the software solution complete photo editing. With powerful tools to organize, color grading, editing grades, and more, you have full control over the images and process his work. Capture One has been developed with quality images and easy to use. Every tool is designed to give you full control over all aspects of the process editing - preserve, restore and optimize all information from the file RAW of you. Full the tool provides the ability to expand to always achieve...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft Office 2021-2024 Professional Plus VL (64-bit) 2507 Build 19029.20156</title><pubDate> Fri, 08 Aug 2025 01:46:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-office-2021-6670.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-office-2021-6670.html
</guid><description>
Since the end of February 2021, Microsoft has announced two new versions of Office 2021 including: Office 2021 and Office LTSC. Reportedly, Office 2021 is the next version of Office 2019, promising to bring users a better experience in the new Word, Excel or PowerPoint tools.
With each office user, the Microsoft Office toolkit is essential and indispensable software in the job. Microsoft Office has undergone numerous editions from Office 2010, 2013, 2016, 2019 to Microsoft 365 developed...
</description></item><item><title>Download Macrium Reflect Workstation / Server / Server Plus 8.1.8631</title><pubDate> Fri, 08 Aug 2025 01:44:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-macrium-reflect-1444.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-macrium-reflect-1444.html
</guid><description>
Macrium Reflect is software backup and recovery files, image files, with big improvements in speed, simplicity and strength. The software we provide taiwebs.com 've included 3 version is Macrium Reflect Workstation / Server / Server Plus. Whole our focus is to help organizations protect critical data and business systems, without fuss and budget breaking.
Macrium Reflect - backup and restore files
The function of Macrium Reflect
	Backup tool new: image gradually increases and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Media Player Classic Black Edition 1.8.6</title><pubDate> Fri, 08 Aug 2025 01:44:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-media-player-classic-black-edition-3351.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-media-player-classic-black-edition-3351.html
</guid><description>
Media Player Classic Black Edition is abbreviated as MPC-BE is a free program that can interface black support users to watch movies, listen to music on the computer with the new interface. Media Player Classic - BE is based on the project "Media Player Classic" original (Gabest) and the project "Media Player Classic Home Cinema" (Casimir666), contains additional features and bug fixes.
Both programs are quite similar, because they are based on Media Player Classic original. In fact, MPC...
</description></item><item><title>Download Intel Graphics Driver for Windows 10 / 11 32.0.101.6987</title><pubDate> Fri, 08 Aug 2025 01:44:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intel-graphics-driver-for-windows-10-5954.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intel-graphics-driver-for-windows-10-5954.html
</guid><description>
Intel Graphics Driver for Windows 10 supports Intel ' s latest 8th-generation Core processor, introducing the Intel ® UHD graphics, with the ability to immerve in the top 4K UHD entertainment from your laptop for a maximum of 10 hours. Along with some security fixes, this driver also optimised the system's inactivity to reduce power consumption.
Look at the complete new interface of gameplay.intel.com, where you will find the proposed game settings for many of your favorite PC games....
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe DNG Converter 17.4.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 08 Aug 2025 01:43:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-dng-converter-2452.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-dng-converter-2452.html
</guid><description>
Adobe DNG Converter, a free utility that converts files from more than 350 cameras to DNG, enables you to easily convert the files raw exclusively for camera file raw DNG more universal. A program strong enough which allows you to convert the source files RAW to DNG format popular and more convenient with a few clicks of the mouse.
DNG allows photographers to archive files, raw images of them in a single format for easy cataloging and access in the future. With specification formats are...
</description></item><item><title>Download DaVinci Resolve Studio 20.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 08 Aug 2025 01:43:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-davinci-resolve-studio-1072.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-davinci-resolve-studio-1072.html
</guid><description>
DaVinci Resolve Studio is professional video editing and color grading software developed by Blackmagic Design. This is an enhanced version of the free DaVinci Resolve software, providing additional features and capabilities for professional video editing, color correction, and post-production.
One of the outstanding features of DaVinci Resolve Studio is its powerful color correction capabilities. It provides a comprehensive set of tools and features for advanced color correction,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ashampoo WinOptimizer 28.00.13</title><pubDate> Fri, 08 Aug 2025 01:42:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-winoptimizer-870.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-winoptimizer-870.html
</guid><description>
Ashampoo WinOptimizer is a software cleanup, optimize and protect your PC. It frees up disk space, fix errors on computer. WinOptimizer has overcome the shortcomings of Windows and give you a system faster, leaner and leaner. Many features automated features make setting it up a problem is only a few clicks of the mouse most simple.
Ashampoo WinOptimizer - Clean optimize PC
Ashampoo WinOptimizer provides instant access to your system, you can look and feel the way that best suits you....
</description></item><item><title>Download AIMP 5.40 Build 2690 + Portable</title><pubDate> Fri, 08 Aug 2025 01:41:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aimp-1302.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aimp-1302.html
</guid><description>
AIMP is a free audio with support for large number of formats and playlists. It works with multiple playlists immediately, allows creation of bookmarks and also has the playback queue.
AIMP - audio player
Features of AIMP
	Clear sound, technology of re-creating fundamentally different from Winamp and WMP
	The balance sensitivity
	Maximum functions from minimal resource
	Minimum consumption of system resources
	Multi-language support
	Support the audio format
	Adjust the hot keys for...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Camera Raw for macOS 17.4.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 08 Aug 2025 01:40:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/mac/download-adobe-camera-raw-for-mac-786.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/mac/download-adobe-camera-raw-for-mac-786.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Camera Raw launches a version dedicated to Mac OS. This is a photo editing plugin on photoshop with the ability to process raw photos after taking them to create more beautiful and quality photos than the original input image. This program helps photographers in editing and taking photos, creating beautiful photos.
Adobe Camera Raw For Mac - Photoshop Raw photo editing plugin for Mac
Features of Adobe Camera Raw
	As a Photoshop Plugins.
	Quick Raw image editing...
</description></item><item><title>Download AfterCodecs 1.12.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 08 Aug 2025 01:39:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aftercodecs-905.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aftercodecs-905.html
</guid><description>
AfterCodecs (Autocroma AfterCodecs) is a set of Adobe CC brings you the best codec and to export more quickly. AfterCodecs regularly updated with codecs, features or speed improvements new. Send email to us, we listen to your needs! Autokroma have a fork ffmpeg private call is ffkroma. The last work of us is to improve the encoder HAP.
AfterCodecs - The plugin Adobe CC
The features of Autocroma AfterCodecs
	Fill in the gaps codec
	AfterCodecs brings you consistency all the codecs and...
</description></item><item><title>Download InfoTouch Professional 2.5.6</title><pubDate> Fri, 08 Aug 2025 01:38:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-infotouch-professional-5518.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-infotouch-professional-5518.html
</guid><description>
InfoTouch Professional is an innovative and reliable solution for public showcases and self-service kiosks. The software protects public computers against any kind of undesirable end-user actions, monitors kiosk, generates usage statistics, and enables easy and secure display of various types of information in public spaces such as libraries, schools, universities, museums, etc.
InfoTouch Features
	Display web pages in a secure Web browser
	Creates a personalized start page and...
</description></item><item><title>Download KORG Modwave Native 1.3.6</title><pubDate> Fri, 08 Aug 2025 01:38:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-korg-modwave-native-10310.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-korg-modwave-native-10310.html
</guid><description>
Modwave, released in 2021, builds on the DW legacy and transforms it into a modern monster synth, featuring incredibly deep wavetable oscillators, stunning filters , extremely flexible modulation, complex sample sequencing, and macro controls for unique, powerful, and easy-to-customize sounds and phrases.
The software is fully compatible with hardware modwave synthesizers. KORG Modwave Native is available in VST3, AAX, and standalone formats on both macOS and Windows, as well as AU on...
</description></item><item><title>Download KORG Wavestate Native 1.4.6</title><pubDate> Fri, 08 Aug 2025 01:38:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-korg-wavestate-native-10309.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-korg-wavestate-native-10309.html
</guid><description>
KORG Wavestate Native is designed from the ground up for a new generation of musicians, producers and composers, taking cues from sources as diverse as modular synths, groove boxes and layouts algorithm. It is available in VST3, AAX, and standalone formats on both macOS and Windows, as well as AU on macOS. You can seamlessly exchange audio between hardware and software. Produce in your DAW with the original wave state, then play the same sounds on stage using the wave state...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe DNG Converter for macOS 17.4.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 08 Aug 2025 01:33:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/mac/download-adobe-dng-converter-for-mac-3708.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/mac/download-adobe-dng-converter-for-mac-3708.html
</guid><description>
Adobe DNG Converter for Mac (DNG) is a publicly available storage format for raw files created by various digital cameras. This addresses the lack of an open standard for raw files created by individual camera models and ensures that photographers have easy access to their files. Hundreds of software manufacturers such as Apple and Google have developed support for DNG. And venerable camera manufacturers like Leica, Casio, Ricoh, Samsung, and Pentax have introduced cameras that offer...
</description></item><item><title>Download TSplus Advanced Security Ultimate 7.3.8.4</title><pubDate> Fri, 08 Aug 2025 01:33:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tsplus-security-7308.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tsplus-security-7308.html
</guid><description>
Unique cybersecurity software TSplus Security provides the basic protections every remote server administrator needs and more. Enable up to seven measures and set the right level of security for your network. When you use remote desktop to allow your employees to work from home, reduce your risk of attack and increase your peace of mind with the powerful features of TSplus Security.
Features of TSplus Security
	Using a country-based whitelist, TSplus Security allows administrators to...
</description></item><item><title>Download ISM BazzISM 2.5.5</title><pubDate> Thu, 07 Aug 2025 22:37:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ism-bazzism-14018.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ism-bazzism-14018.html
</guid><description>
ISM BazzISM is a drum synthesizer plugin specifically designed to create bass kick drum sounds using the sinus sweep method. It allows users to interactively create and customize deep bass kick sounds, making it popular in dance music production. BazzISM was one of the first kick synth plugins on the market and remains a standard thanks to its ease of use and efficiency in quickly creating custom kick drum sounds with adjustable sweep parameters.
More about BazzISM:
	It is available...
</description></item><item><title>Download EaseUS Data Recovery Wizard Professional WinPE 19.6.5 Build 20250721</title><pubDate> Thu, 07 Aug 2025 18:05:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-data-recovery-wizard-winpe-4379.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-data-recovery-wizard-winpe-4379.html
</guid><description>
EaseUS Data Recovery Wizard WinPE - recovery software best data to restore data deleted, formatted or lost from PC, laptop or mobile device easily and quickly. Help get back the lost files or deleted photos, music, sounds, emails, etc. from hard drive, memory card, USB, digital cameras, mobile devices, and other storage media. Program recover data this recover files lost or deleted 100% safe from losing cases different data on different devices without overwriting original data.
EaseUS...
</description></item><item><title>Download Screenpresso Pro 2.1.38</title><pubDate> Thu, 07 Aug 2025 18:04:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-screenpresso-pro-1362.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-screenpresso-pro-1362.html
</guid><description>
Screenpresso Pro is a program easy to take great photos on your screen! Screenpresso blocked Print Screen key and screen capture the best in a few seconds. Allows you to capture windows and screen area, roll the part of the screen, edit the images obtained, add effects, resize a group of images, send screenshots by email and post them to Web resources.
Screenpresso Pro - Shooting the computer screen
Features of Screenpresso Pro
	Take the window and screen area. Take a partial screen...
</description></item><item><title>Download Final Draft 13.2.5 Build 94</title><pubDate> Thu, 07 Aug 2025 18:04:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-final-draft-1241.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-final-draft-1241.html
</guid><description>
Final Draft is a professional program to write scripts for movies, tv shows and performances. This program is a word processor text window with a lot of ability to script specialized. To use the program, you absolutely do not need to know the rules to design the scenario - draft ultimate will automatically convert scripts you write by world standards.
Final Draft - script Writing professional
The features of Final Draft
	Send a copy of the index cards with the summary directly to...
</description></item><item><title>Download XYplorer 27.10.0400</title><pubDate> Thu, 07 Aug 2025 18:03:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-533.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-533.html
</guid><description>
XYplorer - File Manager for Windows is software that supports users to manage files on the Window quickly and to arrange the folder tidy. XYplorer features tabbed browsing, search, files, powerful, preview, flexible, highly customizable interface, dual frame options and a variety of unique ways to automate effective tasks often repeat. It's fast, lightweight, and portable.
Features XYplorer
	XYplorer is a file manager mobile. It does not require any settings, store all configuration...
</description></item></channel></rss>