<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 11:59:24 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 11:59:24 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Flameshot 13.0.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 23:26:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-flameshot-11451.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-flameshot-11451.html
</guid><description>
Flameshot is a powerful and user-friendly screenshot tool for Windows that makes it easy to take, edit, and share screenshots. It offers a wide range of features and customization options, making it suitable for both casual and expert users.
It has an interactive GUI (graphical user interface) with controls to select the desired capture area, move and resize the capture window, perform editing with popular drawing tools ( pencil, line, rectangle, circle, blur, undo/redo) and select the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Advanced SystemCare Ultimate 17.5.0.133</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 23:23:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-systemcare-ultimate-132.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-systemcare-ultimate-132.html
</guid><description>
Advanced SystemCare Ultimate 17: Antivirus software that also helps protect, repair, clean and optimize your PC. Based on BitDefender antivirus technology and IObit anti-malware engine, it is part of IObit antivirus project devoted to providing better and value-added services to our users.
With real-time protection against viruses, spyware and phishing attacks, powerful tuning and cleaning functions, Advanced SystemCare Ultimate provides always-on protection, Automatic and all-in-one...
</description></item><item><title>Download ProfiCAD 13.1.5</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 23:23:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-proficad-1546.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-proficad-1546.html
</guid><description>
ProfiCAD is a software Program to draw diagram and circuit diagram of the electrical circuit and electronics with many features to support users. ProfiCAD will search the control circuit is different then help, you can design a variety of diagram techniques, such as diagrams, pneumatic and hydraulic. One of the obvious features of this product is the simplicity of it. Simple in the tool bar and the icons represent the parts. Simply arrange the menu, just put the items on the screen and...
</description></item><item><title>Download SoftwareNetz Mailing 1.61</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 23:22:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-softwarenetz-mailing-6711.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-softwarenetz-mailing-6711.html
</guid><description>
Mailing is the software that creates the newsletter and professional mail and sends a letter with only one click to your client and your contact address. With an integrated e-mail editor, you can create a career e-mail in HTML format. To create an attractive letter, you can use graphics files, colors, different fonts, links, tables, and you can use the default design template with integrated e-mail editor, you can create a career e-mail in HTML format. To create an attractive letter, you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Disk Drill Enterprise 6.0.1053.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 23:22:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-disk-drill-enterprise-6875.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-disk-drill-enterprise-6875.html
</guid><description>
Disk Drill Enterprise is software that allows you to recover files from hard drives and USB devices, external hard drives, memory cards, iPhone and iPad, drive formats like NTFS, FAT, exFAT, HFS + Mac drive, EXT2/3/4. The software provides fast scan and deep scan mode, depending on the user's needs, to save time and achieve the highest efficiency.
Features of Disk Drill Enterprise
	Users simply need one click to activate Disk Drill.
	Support to scan the entire drive and rejoin lost...
</description></item><item><title>Download Pale Moon 33.8.1.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 23:16:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pale-moon-1883.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pale-moon-1883.html
</guid><description>
Pale Moon is a copy of Firefox has been optimized for the Windows operating System with the processor performance, high current. It looks identical to Firefox browser standard, and supports the extensions, themes and identities of Firefox. All extensions, bookmarks and settings of your existing be entered during the installation process, so except for the logo, you won't notice any difference on function.
Pale Moon - secure web browser
However, what you may notice is the difference in...
</description></item><item><title>Download Unicodia 2.12.5</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 23:16:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-unicodia-8521.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-unicodia-8521.html
</guid><description>
Unicodia is free, open source software that can be used as an alternative character map for your Windows machine. The interface contains everything you need, allowing you to easily cycle through all the available ASCII symbols and copy them to the clipboard. Uncicodia is a great alternative to your standard Unicode characters and is filled with symbols/characters that make it useful for a number of different uses.
Features of Unicodia
	In Windows 10/11 — all characters of Unicode 15...
</description></item><item><title>Download Atlantis Word Processor 4.4.6.3</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 23:15:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-atlantis-word-processor-585.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-atlantis-word-processor-585.html
</guid><description>
Atlantis Word Processor is a word processor app with features format, standard text, autocorrect, and spell check.  Atlantis is a word processor in accordance with most of the tasks handled daily text. The interface is very easy to use and offers the toolbars, hotkeys and sound effects thanh can customize (can turn off). It includes a clip library for quick access to the text or images used regular preview, font format and many other features aimed at improving the process of your...
</description></item><item><title>Download Xara Photo &amp;amp; Graphic Designer+ 25.0.0.71855</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 23:15:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xara-photo-graphic-designer-1051.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xara-photo-graphic-designer-1051.html
</guid><description>
Xara Photo &amp;amp; Graphic Designer is photo editing software detail, drawing, creative and professional design. To materialize all the ideas as cut paste photos to print documents and works of art, digital: Get impressive results quickly! Combine text with graphics and images to create your own design for invitations, posters, or post on social media. Design your projects in an elegant way with the text function new in Xara Photo &amp;amp; Graphic Designer.
Xara Photo &amp;amp; Graphic Designer...
</description></item><item><title>Download Zoom Player Max 21.5.1.2151</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 23:14:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zoom-player-max-104.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zoom-player-max-104.html
</guid><description>
Zoom Player MAX help you to see the film on DVD, Blu-ray, Flash movies and HD format with high quality and the ability to display subtitles in English very well. The advantage of software is that takes up very little system resources to play the movie with quick speed, change the wallpaper options while viewing movies.
Zoom Player MAX is the movies, browse high-quality photos on the computer with the advantages such as compact size, quick start, built-in codec. The application supports...
</description></item><item><title>Download Xara Web Designer+ 25.0.0.71855</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 23:14:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xara-web-designer-premium-1035.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xara-web-designer-premium-1035.html
</guid><description>
Xara Web Designer Premium is software that creates professional websites using a variety of templates are professionally designed are available. Xara Web Designer Premium allows you to create multiple versions of your website, for example, the version for desktop, tablet and mobile devices which you can export as an HTML file individually. Accurately display your website on every terminal, from PC to smartphones and tablets. It's easy and does not require programming knowledge.
Xara Web...
</description></item><item><title>Download HttpMaster Pro 6.2.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 23:13:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-httpmaster-pro-1925.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-httpmaster-pro-1925.html
</guid><description>
A useful application for web developers who need to automate the test the web application by requesting multiple resources from a specified site web-based application. The professional version httpMaster in order to meet the requirements of many people when related to the test application. When working with HttpMaster Pro, most of the time you will manage the attributes and properties of the project HttpMaster of the items required in project. Project properties provides the global options...
</description></item><item><title>Download BDtoAVCHD 3.1.8</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 23:13:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bdtoavchd-2570.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bdtoavchd-2570.html
</guid><description>
BDtoAVCHD is a free tool to create disc AVCHD from files Blu-Ray or HD MKV. When beginning out, we have the folder structure ready to burn to DVD5 or DVD9. AVCHD format allows playback the same type of content as Blu-Ray and holding high definition (1080p) but on media DVD5 or DVD9. It is ideal to backup Blu-Ray with much smaller size and maintaining high quality. The recorded disc is obtained compatible with most Blu-Ray players and PS3. Also can convert Blu-Ray to MKV and Blu-Ray 3D to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Devart Excel Add-ins 2.10.1404.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 23:11:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-devart-excel-add-ins-5320.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-devart-excel-add-ins-5320.html
</guid><description>
Devart Excel Add-ins lets you work with databases and cloud data in Microsoft Excel as with regular Excel spreadsheets. With the Devart Excel Add-in, you can get exactly the data you need with the Visual Query Builder or with SQL, and refresh the queried external data in your workbook at any time with just one click. The external data can be edited as you normally would in Excel, and then saved back to the data source.
The Devart Excel Add-ins is integrated with Microsoft Excel 2007,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Xara Designer Pro+ 25.0.0.71855</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 23:11:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xara-designer-pro-plus-5361.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xara-designer-pro-plus-5361.html
</guid><description>
Xara Designer Pro Plus is professional software for graphic design, web design, image editing, illustration and DTP. Xara Designer Pro X Optimized packages for your designs. Xara Designer Pro Plus combines graphics and web design, illustration, photo editing, and desktop publishing - all in one compact workspace.
Powerful drawing tools let you draw lines, shapes and curves using vectors and adjust the proportions without losing quality. Your images look sharp to the smallest detail. This...
</description></item><item><title>Download OpenVPN 2.6.14</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 23:10:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-openvpn-4245.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-openvpn-4245.html
</guid><description>
OpenVPN provides the VPN solution flexible to secure communication of your data, whether it is the right to privacy on the Internet, remote access for employees, security, IoT, or for the data center cloud. Solution VPN software, our Server can be deployed in place by standard server or virtual device or on the cloud.
OpenVPN - VPN Solution flexible
Though built with the open source OpenVPN, the solution of our additional functionality to meet the needs of business customers, the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Lansweeper 12.5.4</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 23:10:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lansweeper-2011.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lansweeper-2011.html
</guid><description>
Lansweeper is an application to manage IT assets and the scanning device is connected to the network. This software can scan and identify all network devices have workstation IP and Windows, Linux and Mac and indexing for them. Deep Scan Engine this software uses a set of protocols to detect and receive data from any device connected to the network. All data received can be stored in database SQL Compact or SQL Server.
Lansweeper - Scan system Internet
Software Lansweeper design open...
</description></item><item><title>Download Fast Video Cutter Joiner 6.8.7</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 23:08:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fast-video-cutter-joiner-7542.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fast-video-cutter-joiner-7542.html
</guid><description>
Fast Video Cutter Joiner is a fast video cutter and joiner with an easy to use interface. It allows users to trim parts of a video quickly while maintaining the quality of the original video. It supports various formats like AVI, MPEG, MP4, WMV, 3GP, FLV...
This tool helps you to cut video files into small parts, to keep only the parts you need and remove unwanted parts like trailers and advertisements in a movie. The clips you cut can then be used for other video productions or for a...
</description></item><item><title>Download Muziza YouTube Downloader Converter 8.11.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 23:08:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-muziza-youtube-downloader-converter-3972.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-muziza-youtube-downloader-converter-3972.html
</guid><description>
Muziza YouTube Downloader Converter is a tool to create conditions for an attractive interface and many features to help you to download video clips from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion, Instagram and other sites. Muziza YouTube Downloader Converter can also download the video UHD 8K, 5K, 4K, QHD 2K, HD 1080p and 720p from YouTube. The app allows you download only audio stream from YouTube and save as MP3. You don't need to download the entire video file.
Muziza YouTube Downloader...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT-DL 11.3.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 23:07:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-dl-5876.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-dl-5876.html
</guid><description>
YT-DL is a small program to download videos from YouTube and other video sites. Our goal is to make the program as simple as its name.
The features of YT-DL
	Download the video from YouTube and other video sites
	Increase download speed up to 400%
	Download multiple videos at the same time
	Pause and continue to download at any time
	Preview video content while downloading
</description></item><item><title>Download Internet Video Downloader 7.3.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 23:03:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hdapplications-hd-downloader-6041.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hdapplications-hd-downloader-6041.html
</guid><description>
Internet Video Downloader is a small tool designed to help you download video clips from YouTube, Dailymotion and many other similar sites with high quality that can easily run on smartphones, tablets or the latest Xbox devices. After the quick and simple installation process, you will be welcomed by a user-friendly interface without the ability to cause any problems for you.
Although you can set the app start to download immediately, but you can also create a download list that can be...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Geek YTDL Pro 11.3.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 23:03:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-geek-ytdl-pro-9895.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-geek-ytdl-pro-9895.html
</guid><description>
YT Geek YTDL Pro is software that helps users easily download videos from YouTube and hundreds of other video sites. It is very easy to use, just paste the video URL and you can download the video while keeping the original quality. Not only videos on Youtube, users can download any video from social networking sites like Facebook, Vimeo, Myspace video,...
Features of YT Geek YTDL Pro
	Download videos from YouTube and other video sites.
	Increase download speed up to 400%.
	Download...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tribler 8.2.3</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 23:02:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tribler-4761.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tribler-4761.html
</guid><description>
Tribler is free software comes with a set of neat features not only to download faster, but also more security. application retains the fashion style with modern interface, the layout is well-organized and intuitive features. The side panel provides quick access to most of the areas you will visit, such as home, search results loader, channel list downloads, as well as the video player is deployed. No need to say that all of the corresponding options pop up in the rest of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Free Download Manager 6.29.1 Build 6392</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 21:34:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-download-manager-3105.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-download-manager-3105.html
</guid><description>
Free Download Manager is free application download manager, Free Download Manager will significantly increase downloads by splitting the files into several smaller parts and then downloads at the same time. Speed your download will be significantly increased. Manager download free can also continue to download at broken or not responding, so you don't need start downloading from the beginning after occasionally interrupted.
Free Download Manager - Manage and speed up downloads
You can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ashampoo Photo Converter 3.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 04 Aug 2025 20:19:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-photo-converter-14004.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-photo-converter-14004.html
</guid><description>
Ashampoo Photo Converter is a Windows software tool designed for efficient image conversion and editing. The software supports more than 18 image formats and includes popular formats such as BMP, GIF, JPG, PNG, PDF and many more. The software can process individual photos or entire folders in batch mode, suitable for processing large photo collections.
Ashampoo Photo Converter Features
	Extensive format support allows conversion between multiple file types.
	Batch processing for...
</description></item></channel></rss>