<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 13:44:29 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 13:44:29 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download FE File Explorer Pro 4.7.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:43:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-fe-file-explorer-pro-9504.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-fe-file-explorer-pro-9504.html
</guid><description>
FE File Explorer Pro ( Paid version) is a powerful File Manager app on Android and iOS. It can access not only local files but also files on your computer, NAS and Cloud. Transfer files from any location to any location. Stream movies and music to your Android phone and tablet. Directly view and manage documents, photos and files without downloading.
Fe File Explorer Pro Features
	Access network shares on MacOS, Windows, Linux, NAS via SMB/CIFS Protocol.
	Access WebDav Server, FTP...
</description></item><item><title>Download ibis Paint X 13.1.10</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:42:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ibis-paint-x-13615.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ibis-paint-x-13615.html
</guid><description>
ibis Paint X is a popular and versatile drawing application downloaded over 400 million times in total as a series, providing over 47000 brushes, over 21000 materials, over 2100 fonts, 84 filters, 46 screentones, 27 blending modes, recording of drawing process, stroke stabilization feature, various ruler features such as radial ruler or symmetry ruler, and clipping mask features.
Features
	Expansive Brush Library: Over 300 customizable brushes including pencil, pen, spray, oil paint,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Construction Calc Pro 6.99</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:42:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-construction-calc-pro-9627.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-construction-calc-pro-9627.html
</guid><description>
Save money with quick material estimates. Save time by calculating angles, measurements and quantities. The ideal handy companion for anyone in the construction industry. Construction Calc Pro took 12 months and 21,500 lines of code to develop and is the easiest-to-use construction calculation and estimating app available on any mobile platform. There are no complicated instructions to master or instructions to follow – just enter data and get accurate results.
Calculator and...
</description></item><item><title>Download CamScanner- scanner, PDF maker 7.2.0.2509070000</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:41:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-camscanner-pdf-scanner-app-9065.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-camscanner-pdf-scanner-app-9065.html
</guid><description>
CamScanner is the best scanning app that will turn your phone into a PDF scanner. CamScanner helps you scan, store, sync, and collaborate on a variety of content across smartphones, iPads, tablets, and computers. The app uses the device's camera to take high-quality photos of documents, which are then processed and converted into PDF files that can be stored and shared electronically.
CamScanner is designed to be an easy-to-use and flexible tool for scanning and managing documents on...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDFelement-PDF Editor &amp;amp; Reader 5.3.8</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:41:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pdfelement-pdf-editor-reader-13491.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pdfelement-pdf-editor-reader-13491.html
</guid><description>
Discover the intelligent PDF solution with PDFelement AI PDF Editor, Reader, Scanner and Converter. A seamless AI experience for PDFs that lets you chat, translate, proofread, summarize PDFs and more. It offers a comprehensive set of features to create, edit, convert, annotate, sign, and secure PDF documents, suitable for individuals, students, educators, and small businesses.
Key features include:
	PDF Editing: Intuitive ribbon menus allow easy editing of text, images, hyperlinks,...
</description></item><item><title>Download English Verb Conjugator Pro 3.7.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:41:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-english-verb-conjugator-pro-9965.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-english-verb-conjugator-pro-9965.html
</guid><description>
View nearly 2000 English verbs in 20 tenses. With simple navigation and integrated search, you can find the verb you need in seconds.
Now with audio!! Not sure how to pronounce a verb? Now you can hear how every verb is pronounced. Just tap the button next to the conjugation. Verbs with audio have a speaker icon next to them.
Note: This feature requires an Internet connection.
Includes copy, email, and SMS verb conjugation capabilities.
</description></item><item><title>Download TeraBox: 1TB Cloud &amp;amp; AI Space 4.5.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:40:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-terabox-cloud-storage-space-13078.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-terabox-cloud-storage-space-13078.html
</guid><description>
Sign up to get 1024GB of free cloud storage for life! Automatically back up your photos and videos. Support online photo preview and video playback. Using TeraBox, you can store about 300,000 photos, more than 2500 movies or 6.5 million documents. We provide a secure storage space for all your files, while protecting them from the risk of theft. You can securely back up, sync, access, and share your important content.
Get free cloud storage now and back up your data to avoid loss!...
</description></item><item><title>Download YouCam Makeup - Selfie Editor 6.36.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:40:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-youcam-makeup-selfie-editor-11693.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-youcam-makeup-selfie-editor-11693.html
</guid><description>
YouCam Makeup is a popular selfie photo editing app that allows users to enhance their selfies and experiment with different makeup looks. With many features and tools, YouCam Makeup is designed to help users achieve a perfect and professional look in their photos.
One of the main features of YouCam Makeup is the ability to apply virtual makeup in real time. The app uses augmented reality technology to detect facial features and apply makeup effects, allowing users to try on a variety...
</description></item><item><title>Download AppBlock - Block Apps &amp;amp; Sites 7.9.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:39:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-appblock-block-apps-sites-8371.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-appblock-block-apps-sites-8371.html
</guid><description>
AppBlock - Block websites &amp;amp; Apps: Productivity App is a mobile device tracking manager that helps you block annoying apps and websites, track phone usage time, and set personal reminders to manage your productivity. you and focus on the important things.
Set timers or specific day reminders to block apps and websites, track screen time, or customize your profile to enable connection-based app and website blockers Your specific Wi-Fi or location. This way, you can automatically block...
</description></item><item><title>Download Programming Hub: Learn to code 5.2.48</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:39:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-programming-hub-learn-to-code-13115.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-programming-hub-learn-to-code-13115.html
</guid><description>
Learn to code in HTML, Javascript, C, C++, C#, Swift, Python, R Programming, Java, Artificial Intelligence, CSS, etc. with just one app Programming Hub: Learn to code is a coding learning app created through research and collaboration with Google experts to provide the perfect programming learning path. You will learn to code like a pro, and enjoy it like a game. Easy, fast and fun!
With a huge collection of 5000+ programs (code examples), 20+ courses and the world's fastest compiler,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Rotation Control Pro 5.4.4</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:39:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-rotation-control-pro-10794.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-rotation-control-pro-10794.html
</guid><description>
Specific rotation mode may be applied on application -oriented applications. Simple design with easy -to -understand and easy -to -use functions. Recommended for those:
	Want to use the main screen of smartphones in horizontal mode
	Want to use the game in horizontal mode or video application in vertical mode
	Want to always use tablets in horizontal mode
	Want to switch between fixed directions by only one touch through the status bar
The features of Rotation Control Pro
Rotate...
</description></item><item><title>Download myTuner Radio App: FM stations 9.6.8</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:39:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-mytuner-radio-app-fm-stations-11072.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-mytuner-radio-app-fm-stations-11072.html
</guid><description>
Now available for Samsung TVs, LG TVs AND Roku! With the myTuner Radio app, you can listen to live radio from around the world on your Android phone or tablet. With a modern, beautiful and easy-to-use interface, myTuner gives you the best experience when listening to online radio, internet radio, AM and FM radio.
myTuner Radio App Features: FM Radio
	listen to more than 50,000 radio stations from more than 200 countries and territories;
	follow your favorite shows and over 1 million...
</description></item><item><title>Download pixiv 6.154.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:38:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pixiv-13352.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pixiv-13352.html
</guid><description>
Pixiv is a large online community platform primarily focused on illustration, where artists and enthusiasts can post, share, and enjoy creative works such as illustrations, manga, novels, and animation illustrations (ugoira). This is an official pixiv app that makes it easier for you to search and view illustrations, manga and novels.
Improvements in the update:
	Ratings and bookmarks will be combined as "Like!".
	Bookmarks are now titled "collections".
	There is a home page where...
</description></item><item><title>Download Blend Photos - Photo Blender 5.7.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:38:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-blend-photos-photo-blender-11203.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-blend-photos-photo-blender-11203.html
</guid><description>
With Blend Photos, you can access full photo blender and photo overlay features. Quickly and easily upgrade your photo mixer. Discover the power of image overlays and unleash your artistry with Blend Photos. It offers a wide range of photo blending features at your fingertips from the basics like cropping and rotating to more complex tools like creating double exposures or photo blenders and photo overlays. With a selection of highly customizable photo blending effects, you can create...
</description></item><item><title>Download KineMaster - Video Editor 7.8.5.35422.GP</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:38:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-kinemaster-video-editor-13174.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-kinemaster-video-editor-13174.html
</guid><description>
KineMaster is the best video editor and video maker for mobile videographers, with powerful video editing features: Just a few taps to trim videos, merge videos, add effects, add images, add music and add text to create amazing videos quickly. KineMaster makes creating vlogs, slideshows, video collages and green screen videos easier than ever. KineMaster's Asset Store provides video editors with a huge library of royalty-free music, sound effects, stickers, and video templates, helping...
</description></item><item><title>Download VN - Video Editor &amp;amp; Maker 2.9.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:37:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-vn-video-editor-maker-13686.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-vn-video-editor-maker-13686.html
</guid><description>
VN is a free and easy-to-use video editing application without watermark. The intuitive interface makes video editing simple without prior knowledge. It provides all the necessary features to create professional and high-quality videos, meeting the needs of both professional and amateur video editors.
Intuitive video editor
	Quick Rough Cut: The track editing design feature for PC versions is built into the VN application. This makes it easy to zoom in/out on any material and select...
</description></item><item><title>Download Auto Move To SD Card 3.0.7</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:37:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-auto-move-to-sd-card-14029.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-auto-move-to-sd-card-14029.html
</guid><description>
Automatically move from internal memory to external memory (SD card): With this feature, auto-move helps automatically transfer files from internal memory to external memory, avoiding the situation where internal memory is full. This feature supports all types of image, video, audio, document, apk and other file types.
Auto transfer will automatically transfer files from selected folders whenever new files are added to selected folders without opening the app.
You can select specific...
</description></item><item><title>Download Eye Exercises: VisionUp 3.3.68</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:37:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-eye-exercises-visionup-13304.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-eye-exercises-visionup-13304.html
</guid><description>
Take your eye care to the next level with VisionUp, the ultimate eye care app for the modern millennial. We know you're glued to your phone (no judgement!), but too much screen time can be damaging to your eyes. That's where VisionUp comes in!
Why you need VisionUp:
	Say goodbye to blurry vision: Say goodbye to eye strain, headaches, and eye fatigue. VisionUp's scientifically proven exercises will help you see clearly in no time!
	Train your focus like a boss: Do you feel like your...
</description></item><item><title>Download MacroFactor - Macro Tracker 5.4.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:36:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-macrofactor-macro-tracker-13209.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-macrofactor-macro-tracker-13209.html
</guid><description>
MacroFactor combines innovative coaching algorithms with proven behavioral and nutritional science to help you achieve your diet goals and achieve powerful, sustainable results. MacroFactor uses a dynamic algorithm to adapt to changes in your metabolism and personalize your macro plan to keep you on track.
Key Features
Nutrition Coach
	Get a science-based macro plan tailored to your goals and preferences
	Set goals for weight loss, maintenance, or gain
	The AI-powered nutrition coach...
</description></item><item><title>Download Endel: Focus, Relax &amp;amp; Sleep 3.125.958</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:36:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-endel-focus-relax-sleep-13542.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-endel-focus-relax-sleep-13542.html
</guid><description>
Focus, relax, and sleep through the power of sound. Endel creates AI-powered sounds designed to support your daily life. Backed by science and loved by millions worldwide.
Endel is powered by patented core AI technology. It uses inputs such as location, environment, and heart rate to create the ultimate personalized soundscape. This happens quickly and allows Endel to reconnect your state to your circadian rhythm.
Features
	Relax: calm your mind to create a sense of comfort and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Facemoji AI Emoji Keyboard 3.5.8.6</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:36:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-facemoji-ai-emoji-keyboard-13124.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-facemoji-ai-emoji-keyboard-13124.html
</guid><description>
Facemoji AI Emoji Keyboard is a free AI smart chatgpt app Awesome Custom Keyboard Fonts. With 5000+ emojis, WhatsApp stickers, Kaomoji, GIFs, cool fonts, TikTok emojis, stylish themes on this emoji keyboard.
Create stickers based on your inputs and share them with your friends via Whatsapp, Facebook and TikTok. Just type the phrase you want and create personalized stickers to add a unique touch to your chat. Try it and share your ideas with your friends, make every chat full of...
</description></item><item><title>Download AI Logo Generator, Logo Maker 112.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:35:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ai-logo-generator-logo-maker-13211.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ai-logo-generator-logo-maker-13211.html
</guid><description>
Create a logo in minutes with the AI ​​logo generator. No logo design skills required. Fast and easy to use. Just enter your business name and select your industry - it only takes 2 minutes. Our logo maker app offers customizable logo designs for any type of business.
Features
	Corporate Logo Maker: Design a professional logo that suits your business.
	Business Logo Maker: Perfect for startups, entrepreneurs, and established brands.
	Gaming Logo Maker: Build eye-catching and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Vyapar - Billing App GST Invoice Maker 20.8.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:35:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-vyapar-billing-app-gst-invoice-maker-13240.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-vyapar-billing-app-gst-invoice-maker-13240.html
</guid><description>
Vyapar App is the best-rated online invoicing and invoice creation app. With its user-friendly interface and powerful features, Vyapar App stands out as the top-rated invoicing software for mobile devices.
One of the key values ​​that Vyapar App offers is its ability to simplify the invoicing process for businesses of all sizes. Whether you run a small retail store, a service business, or a large enterprise, Vyapar Invoicing Software provides the tools you need to create...
</description></item><item><title>Download My Recipe Box: My Cookbook 8.6.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:35:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-my-recipe-box-my-cookbook-13138.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-my-recipe-box-my-cookbook-13138.html
</guid><description>
Want a free recipe manager and organizer that also has tools like a grocery list maker and meal planner? Look no further than My Cookbook, the all-in-one recipe book app designed to make your cooking journey seamless and fun. With powerful features, My Recipe Box is like a digital cooking table that puts you in control of your recipes, streamlines meal planning, and unleashes your inner chef.
Key Features
	Add your own recipes
	Import recipes from most cooking sites.
	Edit your...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mo: Meditation &amp;amp; Sleep 1.47.5</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:34:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-mo-meditation-sleep-13670.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-mo-meditation-sleep-13670.html
</guid><description>
Mo is perfect for beginners, with lessons starting at just four minutes. We believe in the importance of establishing a daily meditation routine, even if it's short. And with consistent practice, you'll gradually be able to lengthen your meditation sessions and progress to more advanced meditations.
Think bedtime stories are just for kids? Think again! At Mo, we believe that everyone can enjoy the soothing power of a good bedtime story. Our professional storytellers will guide you into...
</description></item></channel></rss>