<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 01:49:20 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 01:49:20 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Multi Commander 15.7.0 Build 3132</title><pubDate> Thu, 08 Jan 2026 23:12:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-multi-commander-2038.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-multi-commander-2038.html
</guid><description>
Multi Commander is a file manager, multi tab and is an alternative to the Windows Explorer standard. It uses the table layout control dual very popular and effective. Multi Commander has everything you need in daily work with files to increase speed and efficiency.
Multi Commander - file Manager
Multi Commander has all the standard features that any manager files would have, such as copy, move, rename, view. But the strong point of Multi Command is the special feature allows you to...
</description></item><item><title>Download MEmu Android Emulator 9.3.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 08 Jan 2026 23:09:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-memu-2975.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-memu-2975.html
</guid><description>
MEmu or also known as Android Emulator is the Android emulator light and free, allowing Windows users to enjoy Android experience the original on the computer and device Microsoft their. This app provides outstanding performance, allowing you to play on PC a series of games designed to run on Android devices. This app allows you to play the game favorite Android on larger screens, to bring you a better gaming experience.
MEmu - Android emulator, lightweight and free
Software MEmu also...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ashampoo Burning Studio 2026 1.27</title><pubDate> Thu, 08 Jan 2026 23:08:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-burning-studio-free-7691.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-burning-studio-free-7691.html
</guid><description>
Ashampoo Burning Studio Free is a reliable and feature-rich recording software with everything you need to burn and backup data, rip music discs, create audio discs or burn existing videos, such as MP4 files, photos to Blu-ray and more! With an intuitive interface, the program is also ideal for beginners who will achieve great results quickly.
Features of Ashampoo Burning Studio Free
	100% free to use.
	Easily burn data in a variety of formats, including CD, DVD and Blu-ray...
</description></item><item><title>Download WindowManager 10.24</title><pubDate> Thu, 08 Jan 2026 23:07:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desksoft-windowmanager-573.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desksoft-windowmanager-573.html
</guid><description>
WindowManager is a software by DeskSoft dedicated to providing software utilities for windows. DeskSoft WindowManager is the window manager window to ensure your windows are placed exactly where you want. Software will help you to help you improve your work flow by remembering and restoring the position and size of the program and your window. The processing window can completely customize and you can set the special rules for the windows favorite or used most often.
WindowManager send...
</description></item><item><title>Download iTop Data Recovery Pro 6.0.0.926</title><pubDate> Thu, 08 Jan 2026 23:06:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-itop-data-recovery-pro-7139.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-itop-data-recovery-pro-7139.html
</guid><description>
iTop Data Recovery Pro is a powerful data recovery tool that speeds up scanning and data recovery processes due to iTop's unique recovery algorithm. In just a few minutes, you can get your deleted files back perfectly as expected. Besides, Scan options are diverse for different needs. You can quickly find your lost data by Location and File Type.
iTop Data Recovery allows you to easily perform file recovery without limitations. More than 1000 file formats are supported. Meanwhile, this...
</description></item><item><title>Download Steinberg VST Connect Pro 5.6.10</title><pubDate> Thu, 08 Jan 2026 23:06:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-steinberg-vst-connect-pro-9939.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-steinberg-vst-connect-pro-9939.html
</guid><description>
Steinberg VST Connect Pro is a full-featured, remote recording solution that allows anyone to capture voice talent, musicians or other performers in professional quality. , no matter where they are on the planet.
In addition, VST Connect Pro allows you to expand your studio from your physical location to cover the whole world. It allows any musician with a computer, an internet connection, and the free VST Connect Performer app to record directly on your studio DAW, even if they're on...
</description></item><item><title>Download NTFS Permissions Reporter Enterprise 5.0.609.0 All Editions</title><pubDate> Thu, 08 Jan 2026 23:06:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ntfs-permissions-reporter-enterprise-6370.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ntfs-permissions-reporter-enterprise-6370.html
</guid><description>
System administrators are constantly required to check user rights for specific files and folders. This is often a time-consuming work, with multiple NTFS classes and repetitive adjustments over time creating a security maze. NTFS Permissions Reporter Enterprise allows you to confirm the security status of the entire file system quickly and efficiently. All have multiple export formats, command line support, integration scheduling, advanced filtration, and more.
Features of NTFS...
</description></item><item><title>Download Abelssoft YouTube Song Downloader Plus 2026 v26.04</title><pubDate> Thu, 08 Jan 2026 23:05:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-abelssoft-youtube-song-downloader-plus-111.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-abelssoft-youtube-song-downloader-plus-111.html
</guid><description>
Abelssoft YouTube Song Downloader Plus 2018.18.17 Program YouTube Song Downloader Plus will help you search the music and video files from YouTube, after you can download them at. To search for music you just need to enter song name in the required field and you will get results, then you can download all videos and audio files. The program can search the entire album, this function will help to find individual songs from separate albums, because of this we specify the name of the artist...
</description></item><item><title>Download CoolUtils Total Image Converter 8.2.0.289</title><pubDate> Thu, 08 Jan 2026 23:05:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-total-image-converter-848.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-total-image-converter-848.html
</guid><description>
CoolUtils Total Image Converter is software to convert images to other formats, and can edit, cut, resize and rotate them. With Total Image Converter you easy convert TIFFs into JPEGS, make photos suitable for the web or recover old photos in the supported format.
&amp;nbsp;CoolUtils Total Image Converter - convert images to other formats
Features CoolUtils Total Image Converter
	Total Image Converter supports almost all image formats
	Support convert eagle picture series.
	Total Image...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinContig 5.0.3.3</title><pubDate> Thu, 08 Jan 2026 23:04:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wincontig-3299.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wincontig-3299.html
</guid><description>
WinContig is a defragmentation utility is easy to use, does not create any folder settings or registry files on your PC. The meaning of it is fast defragmentation documents without the need to defrag the whole disk. In addition, WinContig allows you to group the documents into the record and it also welcomes a number of the button command line can you can use to change the way the application works. The interface of the app is very instinctive, and so it will be very simple to use it,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Abelssoft KeyDepot 2026 v12.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 08 Jan 2026 23:04:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-abelssoft-keydepot-14052.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-abelssoft-keydepot-14052.html
</guid><description>
Abelssoft KeyDepot is a password manager software designed to securely store and manage passwords, logins, and other sensitive data. The software uses advanced encryption technology, specifically AES-256 encryption, to protect user data from unauthorized access. KeyDepot allows users to create a master password to secure access to their password vault, and this master password will never be stored on Abelssoft servers for added security.
Features of Abelssoft KeyDepot
	Secure password...
</description></item><item><title>Download VSave 2.4.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 08 Jan 2026 23:03:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vsave-14404.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vsave-14404.html
</guid><description>
VSave is a video saving and editing app that lets you download videos from cloud storage services, import videos from your camera or library, and convert or edit video formats and attributes. It's compatible with major platforms including YouTube, NicoNico, Apple Music, Spotify, TikTok, Twitter, and other video, audio, and social media websites. It supports downloading playlists, shows, channels, individual songs, and entire albums. Save content permanently in high quality without data...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tenorshare 4DDiG File Repair 4.3.7.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 08 Jan 2026 23:03:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tenorshare-4ddig-file-repair-5630.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tenorshare-4ddig-file-repair-5630.html
</guid><description>
Tenorshare 4DDiG File Repair is AI-powered software to repair damaged or damaged videos, photos, files and audios, improve their quality and add color to black media white. 4DDiG photo editing solves all photo problems like blurry photos, overexposed photos, etc. Powered by AI, it can dramatically improve image resolution and colorize black and white photos in seconds, not hours.
Features of Tenorshare 4DDiG File Repair
	Easily repair any blurry, overexposed and damaged videos, photos...
</description></item><item><title>Download Libre Hardware Monitor 0.9.5</title><pubDate> Thu, 08 Jan 2026 23:02:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-libre-hardware-monitor-7447.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-libre-hardware-monitor-7447.html
</guid><description>
Libre Hardware Monitor, a fork of Open Hardware Monitor, is free software that can monitor your temperature, fan speed, voltage, load, and clock speed sensors. your computer. With the help of LibreHardwareMonitor you can read information from devices like:
	Motherboard
	Intel and AMD processors
	NVIDIA and AMD Graphics Card
	HDD, SSD, and NVMe
	Network cards.
</description></item><item><title>Download SpinFire Insight 2025.3.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 08 Jan 2026 23:01:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-spinfire-utimate-10726.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-spinfire-utimate-10726.html
</guid><description>
SpinFire Utimate provides your entire organization with a unified way to view, interrogate, and translate CAD files. SpinFire Enterprise is best in class software for CAD visualization, allowing you to open all types of extensions, all types of CAD data very quickly and allowing you to easily read CAD data imported and working with it.
Features of SpinFire Utimate
	With an intuitive interface available in more than 10 languages, SpinFire Enterprise allows anyone to leave feedback,...
</description></item><item><title>Download SmartGit 25.1.104</title><pubDate> Thu, 08 Jan 2026 23:01:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-smartgit-13978.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-smartgit-13978.html
</guid><description>
SmartGit is a cross-platform, graphical Git application designed for professional users to simplify and enhance Git version control workflows. SmartGit supports major Git hosting services like GitHub, Bitbucket, GitLab, and Azure DevOps with built-in features to handle pull requests, comments, and code reviews directly in the app.
Why choose SmartGit as your Git Client?
	One for all.
	SmartGit helps new Git users as well as helps experienced developers work more efficiently.
	SmartGit...
</description></item><item><title>Download Google Chrome 143.0.7499.193</title><pubDate> Thu, 08 Jan 2026 18:13:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-chrome-1012.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-chrome-1012.html
</guid><description>
Google Chrome web browser is the most used today. Support surf the web, listen to music, watch movies, play web game effective no jerky lag with the internet connection stable. When you are surfing the web or performing an important task, whether it is operation big or small, work or entertainment, then Chrome has the smart features and the speed you need to make, create and explore on the net.
The latest version of Google Chrome is the third 114. But we are providing for users Google...
</description></item><item><title>Download CPU-Z 2.18</title><pubDate> Thu, 08 Jan 2026 18:10:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cpu-z-2240.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cpu-z-2240.html
</guid><description>
A wonderful development has been updated, in a simple way, can display technical information about the computer, your personal nature it will operate in Windows operating systems from version 98 to latest version 7. After starting, you can see the specifications of different sets of processing center, you can find out full data on the video card and motherboard, I forgot to add about RAM, download CPU-Z from our project in full news.
CPU-Z - Check CPU hardware
After installing, launch...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDF-XChange Pro 10.8.2.407</title><pubDate> Thu, 08 Jan 2026 18:07:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-xchange-editor-pro-3422.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-xchange-editor-pro-3422.html
</guid><description>
PDF-XChange Editor Pro is an application to manipulate and create PDF versatile, offering a wide range of useful features and powerful will help you to easily work with PDF files. This application is very flexible and allows you to easily create and modify PDF files. PDF-XChange Editor Pro provides a powerful set of tools and flexibility to work with PDF files, such as editor PDF-XChange new, utilities series, OFFice2PDF and the Addin tool Bar allows you to easily convert multiple file...
</description></item><item><title>Download IObit Driver Booster Pro 13.2.0.184</title><pubDate> Thu, 08 Jan 2026 18:06:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iobit-driver-booster-102.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iobit-driver-booster-102.html
</guid><description>
IObit Driver Booster Pro is the starting step to avoid hardware errors, the loss of the system and hidden security vulneruses. To update the regular driver is also an effective way to enhance your overall computer performance and maximize your gaming experience. While this process can be dangerous and frustrating if done manually. IObit Driver Booster Pro is introduced to download and update the driver for you automatically with only one click. Based on the cloud library, IObit Driver...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDF-XChange Editor Plus 10.8.2.407</title><pubDate> Thu, 08 Jan 2026 18:06:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-xchange-editor-plus-645.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-xchange-editor-plus-645.html
</guid><description>
PDF-XChange Editor Plus is the editor, PDF viewer, compact, fast with many features, add-ons, professional. When using the PDF-XChange Editor Plus, easy for users to create, view, edit, annotate, OCR and digital signing PDF files, plus much more.
PDF-XChange Editor is a PDF editing full-featured. With the help of it, you can edit, fix, add, or delete text easily. Graphics can also be moved, resized or removed.
Features PDF-XChange Editor Plus
Edit documents
	Use a variety of editing...
</description></item><item><title>Download Media Player Classic Home Cinema 2.6.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 08 Jan 2026 18:05:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-media-player-classic-home-cinema-2839.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-media-player-classic-home-cinema-2839.html
</guid><description>
Media Player Classic Home Cinema is a multimedia compact for Microsoft Windows 32 bit and 64 bit. MPC mimics the interface of Windows Media Player 6.4, but provides most options and features available in the modern means. Media Player Classic Home Cinema for free 100% no advertising, so you can directly access content and enjoy media playback without being distracted.
With Media Player Classic Home, you can now change the design a multimedia of the custom toolbar. There is a range to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Aperty 1.5.0 (1438)</title><pubDate> Thu, 08 Jan 2026 18:04:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aperty-12574.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aperty-12574.html
</guid><description>
Aperty is a dedicated portrait editing software developed by Skylum, designed to simplify the editing process for professional photographers. It offers a wide range of features to enhance portrait photography while reducing post-processing time.
Why Aperty?
Aperty is a photo editing tool for professional portrait photographers who want to reduce post-processing time without sacrificing quality and client satisfaction.
Features of Aperty
	Automatic Editing: Optimize your editing...
</description></item><item><title>Download XYplorer (32 Bit) 27.20.0900</title><pubDate> Thu, 08 Jan 2026 18:04:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-portable-12066.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-portable-12066.html
</guid><description>
XYplorer Portable is a file management software application that provides a comprehensive set of features for organizing and managing files and folders on your computer. This is a portable version of XYplorer that you can run directly from a portable storage device, such as a USB drive, without installation.
XYplorer Portable Features
	File Management: XYplorer Portable provides a two-window interface, allowing you to view and work with two folders at the same time. It provides easy...
</description></item><item><title>Download XRECODE3 1.177</title><pubDate> Thu, 08 Jan 2026 18:03:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xrecode-iii-2915.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xrecode-iii-2915.html
</guid><description>
"Xrecode II" is the switch and grab the audio allows you to convert from mp2, mp3, ac3, aiff, wma, amr, ogg, ape, flac, cue, mpc, wv, tak, mid, cue, m4b, tta, wav, dts , wav (rf64), m4a, mp4, ra, shn, rm, avi, aac, mpg, vob, mka, mkv, flv, Mov, swf, ofr, divx, wmv, spx, mp3, m4v, 3gp, m2v, 3g2, m4v, m2ts, ts, adts, tak, xm, mod, it, s3m, alac, umx, mtm, mlp to m4a, ape, flac, mp4 (using NeroAAC), raw, ogg, wav, wav (rf64) , wma, mpc, WavPack, mp2, ofr, Speex, ac3, tak, aiff, snd, Shorten...
</description></item></channel></rss>