<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 15:43:59 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 15:43:59 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download ON1 Effects 2026.2 v20.2.1.17958</title><pubDate> Sat, 17 Jan 2026 17:53:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-on1-effects-1430.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-on1-effects-1430.html
</guid><description>
ON1 Effects is a collection of photo effects includes hundreds of effects, photo filters, LUT, borders, textures and presets and all can be fully customized according to your style. The ability to create endless Effects with ON1. Most popular our included HDR Look, B &amp;amp; W, Lens Blur (tilt-shift), Glows, Color Enhancer, Tone Enhancer, Textures, B Border, Film Look, Split Tone,...
ON1 Effects 2019 - The visual effects
ON1 Effects 2019 includes everything you need to create any style...
</description></item><item><title>Download Aeon Timeline 3.5.36</title><pubDate> Sat, 17 Jan 2026 17:52:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aeon-timeline-4952.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aeon-timeline-4952.html
</guid><description>
Aeon Timeline is a tool line-time for creative thinking. Most of the application time line traditional designed to suit a single need: to create attractive screen on time one way. They are present, static, and perfectly aligned with the slide and overhead projector.
With Aeon Timeline, you can split your timeline into logical groups, projects or arcs at the same time. You can model the relationships between events and people, places, and ideas. Aeon calculate ages of people for you. And...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mozilla Firefox 147.0.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 17 Jan 2026 17:52:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-firefox-quantum-501.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-firefox-quantum-501.html
</guid><description>
Firefox Quantum is a web browser independently provide the tabbed browsing combined with numerous handy features like pop-up blocker, Bookmarks, direct (integrated RSS), password manager, and more. Functionality can be extended with dozens of plugins available for free (extensions).
Firefox Quantum are interface completely new, beautiful, neat, minimalistic and delicate, eats less RAM to 30% compared with the old version and solve the condition consuming capacity
Firefox can import all...
</description></item><item><title>Download StartAllBack 3.9.21.5350</title><pubDate> Sat, 17 Jan 2026 17:51:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-startallback-6857.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-startallback-6857.html
</guid><description>
With the official release of Windows 11, chances are that most of you want to try it out. As the name suggests, StartAllBack is a small, lightweight tool that can help you enjoy the power of the new operating system while keeping the look and feel, especially because main work area, desktop of Windows 7, Windows 10 as taskbars and start menu styles.
StartAllBack is specially designed for Windows 11 and will not work on any older operating systems. If you want to get the start menu back...
</description></item><item><title>Download 4K Video Downloader Plus 26.0.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 17 Jan 2026 17:51:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-video-downloader-617.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-video-downloader-617.html
</guid><description>
4K Video Downloader Plus is software support downloads video, audio and subtitles from YouTube with high quality up to 4K. Download process video is very simple: just copy the video link from your browser and click Paste Url. Done! If you want that video on your iPad, iPhone or other device, we have protected you.
The feature on 4K Video Downloader Plus
	Download entire playlists and channels from YouTube and save them in MP4, MKV, M4A, MP3, FLV, 3G, create a file .m3u for...
</description></item><item><title>Download Perfectly Clear WorkBench 5.0.1.3049</title><pubDate> Sat, 17 Jan 2026 17:50:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfectly-clear-workbench-6892.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfectly-clear-workbench-6892.html
</guid><description>
Perfectly Clear Workbench is an application that uses image editing libraries Perfectly Clear by Athentech and is provided to demonstrate the capabilities of the Perfectly Clear processing libraries, which recognize faces and allow quick export of processing settings for use.
One of the key features in Workbench is the ability to "export to API" when saving a Preset. This allows you to make image edits in Workbench and adjust the settings to suit your editing style and needs. You can...
</description></item><item><title>Download 4K YouTube to MP3 26.0.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 17 Jan 2026 17:50:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-youtube-to-mp3-622.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-youtube-to-mp3-622.html
</guid><description>
4K YouTube to MP3 is a software to convert video youtube to mp3 quickly and easily by the manipulation drag-and-drop simple. With 4K YouTube to MP3 you just drag and drop the link to the favorite songs of you and get the MP3 files to your computer, as easy as that. Transfer songs directly to iPod, iPhone and iPad everywhere you go. No install annoying and complex to solve, just a clean interface, user friendly and functional.
When using 4K YouTube to MP3, users will get the playlists,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare Recoverit 14.0.14.5</title><pubDate> Sat, 17 Jan 2026 17:49:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-recoverits-374.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-recoverits-374.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare Recoverit is a data recovery software that is easily lost at a rapid rate and is used by many people. You will do what happens if one day your data is suddenly lost due to the virus or deleted it, .. Wondershare Recoverit will provide you with an environment to protect important data.
Wondershare Recoverit has all the scanning processes that are divided into multiple types, from the typical recovery of the deleted files that are deleted to the recovery of missing files due...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cloanto Amiga Forever Plus Edition 11.2.4</title><pubDate> Sat, 17 Jan 2026 17:49:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cloanto-amiga-forever-plus-edition-4743.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cloanto-amiga-forever-plus-edition-4743.html
</guid><description>
Cloanto Amiga Forever Plus Edition is the emulator, preservation and support of official Amiga of Cloanto, a software developer Commodore / Amiga brought to you from the 1980s. The different editions of Amiga Forever blend high-quality software and original content with the video great top to record the time and let you experience firsthand the history, culture, challenges and passion behind the Amiga.
The features of Cloanto Amiga Forever Plus Edition
	Interface player revolutionary...
</description></item><item><title>Download ProfiCAD 13.4.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 17 Jan 2026 17:45:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-proficad-1546.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-proficad-1546.html
</guid><description>
ProfiCAD is a software Program to draw diagram and circuit diagram of the electrical circuit and electronics with many features to support users. ProfiCAD will search the control circuit is different then help, you can design a variety of diagram techniques, such as diagrams, pneumatic and hydraulic. One of the obvious features of this product is the simplicity of it. Simple in the tool bar and the icons represent the parts. Simply arrange the menu, just put the items on the screen and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Valentina Studio Pro 16.5.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 17 Jan 2026 17:37:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-valentina-studio-pro-2122.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-valentina-studio-pro-2122.html
</guid><description>
Valentina Studio Pro is the best way to transform your data into meaningful information; create, manage, query and explore MySQL, Postgre MariaDB, MS SQL Server and SQLite database.
Valentina Studio Pro
Features of Valentina Studio Pro
SCHEMA EDITING &amp;amp; MAPPING
	Manage multiple databases in tabs and views that can be attached is
	Create / Drop / alter / Browse Tables, fields, index, trigger, constraints, links, views, stored procedures, properties, Sequences, Types, ...
	Edit the...
</description></item><item><title>Download NTFS Permissions Reporter Enterprise 5.0.636</title><pubDate> Sat, 17 Jan 2026 17:37:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ntfs-permissions-reporter-enterprise-6370.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ntfs-permissions-reporter-enterprise-6370.html
</guid><description>
System administrators are constantly required to check user rights for specific files and folders. This is often a time-consuming work, with multiple NTFS classes and repetitive adjustments over time creating a security maze. NTFS Permissions Reporter Enterprise allows you to confirm the security status of the entire file system quickly and efficiently. All have multiple export formats, command line support, integration scheduling, advanced filtration, and more.
Features of NTFS...
</description></item><item><title>Download Syncovery Premium 11.12.1.151</title><pubDate> Sat, 17 Jan 2026 17:36:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncovery-pro-enterprise-232.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncovery-pro-enterprise-232.html
</guid><description>
Syncovery Pro Enterprise is a great application used to back up data and to synchronize personal computers, servers, laptops, notepads and storage online. The software comes with support for FTP and secure FTP servers, SSH, WebDAV, Amazon S3, http, update the part file, ZIP compression, data encryption, and schedule automatic backups.
Syncovery Pro Enterprise have the ability to freely select files and folders across the whole folder hierarchy in tree view and supports email...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft Edge 144.0.3719.82</title><pubDate> Sat, 17 Jan 2026 17:36:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-edge-3940.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-edge-3940.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft Edge is web browser developed specifically for Windows operating system 10 alternatives to Internet Explorer is the default browser on Windows. Browser Microsoft Edge built-in assistant Cortana brings content and website based on the user's preferences, there are also system utilities quite extensive help you to customize according to individual. Microsoft Edge has the similarity with Google Chrome quite large, except the target is marked more of the interface and the rounded...
</description></item><item><title>Download Photo Reducer 6.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 17 Jan 2026 17:23:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photo-reducer-10218.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photo-reducer-10218.html
</guid><description>
Photo Reducer is free software that supports image size reduction in various formats by choosing from countless presets or defining values yourself, then sending via email or save locally. In terms of optimization, the app comes with a lot of preset configurations. These are found in a drop-down menu, with options for ideal print size, digital frames, screens for HD TVs and 4K TVs, ideal sizes for the web, as well as customization options. The second choice allows you to adjust quality...
</description></item><item><title>Download Active Partition Recovery Ultimate 26.0.2.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 17 Jan 2026 17:01:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-active-partition-recovery-ultimate-611.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-active-partition-recovery-ultimate-611.html
</guid><description>
Active@ Partition Recovery Ultimate is a data recovery tool in the end. In addition to the Professional features, it also contains an ISO image that can boot (based on WinPE Active @ Boot Disk Lite) that you can burn to CD-ROM or write to a USB Flash drive and boot Windows from CD-ROM / USB to recover partitions (including the system) as well as to restore files and special folder from within the Windows environment familiar.
The final version includes Active@ LiveCD (recovery...
</description></item><item><title>Download MasterCook 24.0.3.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 17 Jan 2026 17:00:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mastercook-6541.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mastercook-6541.html
</guid><description>
Arrange your recipes, make cookbooks and manage the diet and nutrition with the MasterCook 2020, which is ranked 9.8 out of 10 by TopTenReviews. The flexible tools for the family chef and professional chef to organize all of your kitchen activities and your cooking.
Features of MasterCook
	The flexible tools for family chef and professional chefs arrange all your kitchen and cooking activities.
	Set up a daily or weekly food budget for each ration, formula or menu.
	Change the rations...
</description></item><item><title>Download Diamond Cut Audio Restoration Tools 11.09</title><pubDate> Sat, 17 Jan 2026 17:00:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-diamond-cut-audio-restoration-tools-5851.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-diamond-cut-audio-restoration-tools-5851.html
</guid><description>
Diamond Cut Audio Restoration Tools is the next step in the process of sound processing. With DCart10, we have added and enhanced the existing tools that you know and loved, at the same time that we have made the search and use much easier. In addition, we greatly discounted both the new and upgraded version!
The features of Diamond Cut Audio Restoration Tools
	Recovery and Improved Sound
	Create MP3 into your favorite music
	Clean up the records and old tapes
	Create a CD of your...
</description></item><item><title>Download Family Tree Heritage Gold 16.0.16</title><pubDate> Sat, 17 Jan 2026 16:59:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-family-tree-heritage-gold-5596.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-family-tree-heritage-gold-5596.html
</guid><description>
Build your Family Tree and share your Family Story with Family Tree Heritage Gold. This new gold edition offers exciting, easy-to-use new features, including a new descendant View, print background images on multiple charts, improved synchronization with FamilySearch ™ Family Tree, and record non-traditional marital relationships, along with more efficient ways to enter important genealogical data.
TreeTips ™ is an advanced technology built into the Family Tree Heritage to display...
</description></item><item><title>Download PowerShell HelpWriter 2026 v3.0.72</title><pubDate> Sat, 17 Jan 2026 16:59:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sapien-powershell-helpwriter-7224.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sapien-powershell-helpwriter-7224.html
</guid><description>
PowerShell HelpWriter is the premier editor for Windows PowerShell XML help files. Create and edit help files for all command types, including cmdlets, functions, workflows, and CIM commands. PowerShell HelpWriter parses your module and generates startup help files that match the cmdlets and convert the help based on existing comments.
Features of PowerShell HelpWriter
	Create help files for modules.
	Create and edit themes.
	Check spelling in real time.
	Create and design modular...
</description></item><item><title>Download Print.Test.Page.OK 3.48</title><pubDate> Sat, 17 Jan 2026 16:58:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-printtestpageok-4501.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-printtestpageok-4501.html
</guid><description>
Print.Test.Page.OK is a tool to print a test page allows you to check your printer to find errors and effective. Print.Test.Page.OK is equipped with two test pages, and slope color, allowing you to check the color printer at any time, regardless of whether it is color laser printer or modern inkjet printers. You can quickly start the print test page via the Print button. One thing essential is the color and the way it is displayed for your printer. Steaks, teen, color,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Picture Window Pro 8.0.544</title><pubDate> Sat, 17 Jan 2026 16:56:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-picture-window-pro-7452.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-picture-window-pro-7452.html
</guid><description>
Picture Window Pro is a powerful image editing tool designed for serious photographers with strict creative and quality standards. Its comprehensive set of photo editing and editing tools let you control and shape every aspect of your images.
Picture Window Pro 8 is a complete rewrite of Picture Window Pro 7. It features non-destructive image editing through a novel interface based on an image tree. It also fully supports large, high-resolution displays and can be used in dual monitor...
</description></item><item><title>Download SAPIEN VersionRecall 2026 v1.8.177</title><pubDate> Sat, 17 Jan 2026 16:56:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sapien-versionrecall-8198.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sapien-versionrecall-8198.html
</guid><description>
VersionRecall automates the most widely used manual process for creating backups and maintaining multiple versions of your files. It removed the complexity of APIs, database backends, developer tools, and foreign file formats. Your versioned files are stored as files in their original format, not in a database or some proprietary, modified format. With the ability to automatically submit custom scheduled changes, you don't even have to worry about manually "checking in" your code;...
</description></item><item><title>Download SAPIEN PowerShell Studio 2026 v5.10.263</title><pubDate> Sat, 17 Jan 2026 16:55:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sapien-powershell-studio-7201.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sapien-powershell-studio-7201.html
</guid><description>
PowerShell Studio is the premier editing and tooling environment for PowerShell. Create graphical tools using PowerShell with an easy-to-use GUI designer. Eliminates the need to manually write hundreds of lines of code. Use PowerShell Studio's built-in templates and wired controls to create advanced GUIs quickly. Create a PowerShell script module in minutes with PowerShell Studio. Easily convert your existing functions into a deliverable module. PowerShell Studio has a powerful editor...
</description></item><item><title>Download Database Workbench Pro 6.9.2.873</title><pubDate> Sat, 17 Jan 2026 16:55:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-database-workbench-pro-12498.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-database-workbench-pro-12498.html
</guid><description>
Database Workbench Pro is a comprehensive integrated development environment (IDE) designed for developers and database administrators. It supports multiple database systems, including InterBase, SQL Server, Firebird, MySQL, Oracle, NexusDB, MSDE, and Sybase SQL Anywhere, making it a versatile tool for cross-database development.
It provides both database-specific and database-independent visual design tools. Users can create new databases or create visual diagrams from existing...
</description></item></channel></rss>