<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 15:46:30 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 15:46:30 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download RDS Advanced Security Ultimate 7.4.8.4</title><pubDate> Fri, 08 Aug 2025 18:46:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rds-advanced-security-ultimate-13846.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rds-advanced-security-ultimate-13846.html
</guid><description>
RDS Advanced Security Ultimate is comprehensive cybersecurity software designed to protect Remote Desktop Services (RDS) infrastructure from a wide range of cyber threats, including brute force attacks, ransomware, unauthorized logins, and malicious IP addresses. This software provides advanced, multi-layered security features to protect RDS servers and ensure secure remote access.
Key Features:
	Hacker IP Protection: Blocks millions of malicious IP addresses daily with a...
</description></item><item><title>Download Dragonrise Games YoloX 1.4.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 08 Aug 2025 18:45:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dragonrise-games-yolox-11598.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dragonrise-games-yolox-11598.html
</guid><description>
Use YoloX to change your game crosshair.Including color inversion, sound sensor, motion sensor, heat safety and other features never seen before.Development your target with the next revolution in crosshair technology!
YoloX Features
	Effect: Invert colors and other effects.
	Animation: Separate animations for primary fire, secondary fire, and jump.
	Sound sensor: Animated response to game sounds. Now you can listen to your own music without missing any key sounds.
	Motion sensor:...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft Edge 139.0.3405.86</title><pubDate> Fri, 08 Aug 2025 18:41:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-edge-3940.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-edge-3940.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft Edge is web browser developed specifically for Windows operating system 10 alternatives to Internet Explorer is the default browser on Windows. Browser Microsoft Edge built-in assistant Cortana brings content and website based on the user's preferences, there are also system utilities quite extensive help you to customize according to individual. Microsoft Edge has the similarity with Google Chrome quite large, except the target is marked more of the interface and the rounded...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaPortal 2.5 / 1.38.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 08 Aug 2025 18:40:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediaportal-2627.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediaportal-2627.html
</guid><description>
MediaPortal is a media player and open source software project, digital video recorders, are often considered as an alternative solution for Windows Media Center. MediaPortal is a media center, it is open source after launch, not only can view the different video formats, but also view photos in a convenient form.
MediaPortal is written on the website of the developer, as a Microsoft Windows application, this program can be called safely is a project quite unique on the network, because...
</description></item><item><title>Download FileVoyager 25.8.7.0 Full</title><pubDate> Fri, 08 Aug 2025 18:39:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-filevoyager-3322.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-filevoyager-3322.html
</guid><description>
FileVoyager is a OFM free and efficient (The file manager main system) is designed for the computer MS Windows. OFM is a file manager use two separate tab of browser drive. Tabbed interface, this simplifies the operation, file transfer, and ensure speed and efficiency. FileVoyager provide increased functionality and includes a set of rich tools. Using this tool, you will be able to easily browse the disk, archive, folder, FTP and FTPS of quickly and efficiently. You can browse your files...
</description></item><item><title>Download Opera GX (Gaming Browser) 120.0.5543.160</title><pubDate> Fri, 08 Aug 2025 18:39:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-gx-3170.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-gx-3170.html
</guid><description>
Opera GX is a special version of the Opera browser is built to complement gamers avid. Browser this game comes with the unique features to help users make maximum use of both the game and their browser. Opera GX is built specifically to support the game. This browser includes the unique features to help users have the best experience when gaming and surfing the web.
Opera GX - special browser for gamers
GX Control allows you to set a limit on the level of use RAM, CPU and network where...
</description></item><item><title>Download APFX Audio PRIMO 1.4.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 08 Aug 2025 15:44:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-apfx-audio-primo-14019.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-apfx-audio-primo-14019.html
</guid><description>
APFX Audio PRIMO is a versatile guitar amp simulation plugin and iPad app designed to deliver high-quality sound using AI modeling based on high-end Italian tube amps. It features two independent channels: Channel 1 covers the sound from clean to clipped, and Channel 2 provides crisp and leading sound. PRIMO includes a 3-band EQ, compressor, noise gate, amplifier, effects such as tri-chorus, phaser, digital and analog delay, reverb and IR loader with studio-grade speaker cabinet...
</description></item><item><title>Download Audacity 3.7.5</title><pubDate> Fri, 08 Aug 2025 01:49:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-audacity-1648.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-audacity-1648.html
</guid><description>
Audacity software to record audio along with editing features such as noise filtering, distortion noise, insert unique effects. The latest version of Audacity include the improvement of effects, interface, updates Nyquist and libflac. A number of bugs have also been fixed to help the software operate more smoothly. Audacity accompanied by the link to various sources, assist you learn how to use all the features of the program. These sources include Quick Help Guide (quick help), a guide,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Office Timeline Plus 11.18.00.00 Expert / Pro / Pro+ Edition</title><pubDate> Fri, 08 Aug 2025 01:48:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-timeline-2106.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-timeline-2106.html
</guid><description>
Office Timeline is an add-on very useful and powerful software for Microsoft PowerPoint. With add-ons, you can create PowerPoint documents look more beautiful. With add-ons, you can add the time Line on the project by yourself. Application time for the composition and different segments of the document, your PowerPoint will not only increase the beauty for your work, but also for customers and your manager. The people who created this product is also believe that add-ons this is the only...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Camera Raw 17.4.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 08 Aug 2025 01:47:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-camera-raw-02en-785.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-camera-raw-02en-785.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Camera Raw is Plugin edit photo on photoshop with the ability to handle the raw photos after the shoot to create beautiful photos and quality than the input image initially, this program helps support the photographers in editing and photography, make the photo beautiful.
Adobe Camera Raw - edit Raw images Photoshop
Adobe Camera Raw is a plugin which is integrated accompanied by a number of software photo editing such as Photoshop, Photoshop Elements, After Effects and...
</description></item><item><title>Download VideoProc Converter AI 8.3</title><pubDate> Fri, 08 Aug 2025 01:47:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-videoproc-2473.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-videoproc-2473.html
</guid><description>
VideoProc (an improved version of WinX HD Video Converter Deluxe) - processing software the most powerful video designed to edit, cut, crop, merge, adjust, convert and compress (4K) video with full Hardware Acceleration. Is the heir to be improved a lot, VideoProc integrated conversion / compression video UHD, the download at videos (YouTube) with the video editor, gives you the power to control optimal for every video file much music, SD, HD and 4K on your PC. With technology hardware...
</description></item><item><title>Download Capture One Pro 16.6.4.3044 + Enterprise</title><pubDate> Fri, 08 Aug 2025 01:46:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capture-one-pro-624.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capture-one-pro-624.html
</guid><description>
Capture One Pro is the software solution complete photo editing. With powerful tools to organize, color grading, editing grades, and more, you have full control over the images and process his work. Capture One has been developed with quality images and easy to use. Every tool is designed to give you full control over all aspects of the process editing - preserve, restore and optimize all information from the file RAW of you. Full the tool provides the ability to expand to always achieve...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft Office 2021-2024 Professional Plus VL (64-bit) 2507 Build 19029.20156</title><pubDate> Fri, 08 Aug 2025 01:46:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-office-2021-6670.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-office-2021-6670.html
</guid><description>
Since the end of February 2021, Microsoft has announced two new versions of Office 2021 including: Office 2021 and Office LTSC. Reportedly, Office 2021 is the next version of Office 2019, promising to bring users a better experience in the new Word, Excel or PowerPoint tools.
With each office user, the Microsoft Office toolkit is essential and indispensable software in the job. Microsoft Office has undergone numerous editions from Office 2010, 2013, 2016, 2019 to Microsoft 365 developed...
</description></item><item><title>Download Macrium Reflect Workstation / Server / Server Plus 8.1.8631</title><pubDate> Fri, 08 Aug 2025 01:44:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-macrium-reflect-1444.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-macrium-reflect-1444.html
</guid><description>
Macrium Reflect is software backup and recovery files, image files, with big improvements in speed, simplicity and strength. The software we provide taiwebs.com 've included 3 version is Macrium Reflect Workstation / Server / Server Plus. Whole our focus is to help organizations protect critical data and business systems, without fuss and budget breaking.
Macrium Reflect - backup and restore files
The function of Macrium Reflect
	Backup tool new: image gradually increases and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Media Player Classic Black Edition 1.8.6</title><pubDate> Fri, 08 Aug 2025 01:44:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-media-player-classic-black-edition-3351.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-media-player-classic-black-edition-3351.html
</guid><description>
Media Player Classic Black Edition is abbreviated as MPC-BE is a free program that can interface black support users to watch movies, listen to music on the computer with the new interface. Media Player Classic - BE is based on the project "Media Player Classic" original (Gabest) and the project "Media Player Classic Home Cinema" (Casimir666), contains additional features and bug fixes.
Both programs are quite similar, because they are based on Media Player Classic original. In fact, MPC...
</description></item><item><title>Download Intel Graphics Driver for Windows 10 / 11 32.0.101.6987</title><pubDate> Fri, 08 Aug 2025 01:44:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intel-graphics-driver-for-windows-10-5954.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intel-graphics-driver-for-windows-10-5954.html
</guid><description>
Intel Graphics Driver for Windows 10 supports Intel ' s latest 8th-generation Core processor, introducing the Intel ® UHD graphics, with the ability to immerve in the top 4K UHD entertainment from your laptop for a maximum of 10 hours. Along with some security fixes, this driver also optimised the system's inactivity to reduce power consumption.
Look at the complete new interface of gameplay.intel.com, where you will find the proposed game settings for many of your favorite PC games....
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe DNG Converter 17.4.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 08 Aug 2025 01:43:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-dng-converter-2452.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-dng-converter-2452.html
</guid><description>
Adobe DNG Converter, a free utility that converts files from more than 350 cameras to DNG, enables you to easily convert the files raw exclusively for camera file raw DNG more universal. A program strong enough which allows you to convert the source files RAW to DNG format popular and more convenient with a few clicks of the mouse.
DNG allows photographers to archive files, raw images of them in a single format for easy cataloging and access in the future. With specification formats are...
</description></item><item><title>Download DaVinci Resolve Studio 20.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 08 Aug 2025 01:43:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-davinci-resolve-studio-1072.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-davinci-resolve-studio-1072.html
</guid><description>
DaVinci Resolve Studio is professional video editing and color grading software developed by Blackmagic Design. This is an enhanced version of the free DaVinci Resolve software, providing additional features and capabilities for professional video editing, color correction, and post-production.
One of the outstanding features of DaVinci Resolve Studio is its powerful color correction capabilities. It provides a comprehensive set of tools and features for advanced color correction,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ashampoo WinOptimizer 28.00.13</title><pubDate> Fri, 08 Aug 2025 01:42:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-winoptimizer-870.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-winoptimizer-870.html
</guid><description>
Ashampoo WinOptimizer is a software cleanup, optimize and protect your PC. It frees up disk space, fix errors on computer. WinOptimizer has overcome the shortcomings of Windows and give you a system faster, leaner and leaner. Many features automated features make setting it up a problem is only a few clicks of the mouse most simple.
Ashampoo WinOptimizer - Clean optimize PC
Ashampoo WinOptimizer provides instant access to your system, you can look and feel the way that best suits you....
</description></item><item><title>Download AIMP 5.40 Build 2690 + Portable</title><pubDate> Fri, 08 Aug 2025 01:41:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aimp-1302.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aimp-1302.html
</guid><description>
AIMP is a free audio with support for large number of formats and playlists. It works with multiple playlists immediately, allows creation of bookmarks and also has the playback queue.
AIMP - audio player
Features of AIMP
	Clear sound, technology of re-creating fundamentally different from Winamp and WMP
	The balance sensitivity
	Maximum functions from minimal resource
	Minimum consumption of system resources
	Multi-language support
	Support the audio format
	Adjust the hot keys for...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Camera Raw for macOS 17.4.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 08 Aug 2025 01:40:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/mac/download-adobe-camera-raw-for-mac-786.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/mac/download-adobe-camera-raw-for-mac-786.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Camera Raw launches a version dedicated to Mac OS. This is a photo editing plugin on photoshop with the ability to process raw photos after taking them to create more beautiful and quality photos than the original input image. This program helps photographers in editing and taking photos, creating beautiful photos.
Adobe Camera Raw For Mac - Photoshop Raw photo editing plugin for Mac
Features of Adobe Camera Raw
	As a Photoshop Plugins.
	Quick Raw image editing...
</description></item><item><title>Download AfterCodecs 1.12.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 08 Aug 2025 01:39:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aftercodecs-905.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aftercodecs-905.html
</guid><description>
AfterCodecs (Autocroma AfterCodecs) is a set of Adobe CC brings you the best codec and to export more quickly. AfterCodecs regularly updated with codecs, features or speed improvements new. Send email to us, we listen to your needs! Autokroma have a fork ffmpeg private call is ffkroma. The last work of us is to improve the encoder HAP.
AfterCodecs - The plugin Adobe CC
The features of Autocroma AfterCodecs
	Fill in the gaps codec
	AfterCodecs brings you consistency all the codecs and...
</description></item><item><title>Download InfoTouch Professional 2.5.6</title><pubDate> Fri, 08 Aug 2025 01:38:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-infotouch-professional-5518.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-infotouch-professional-5518.html
</guid><description>
InfoTouch Professional is an innovative and reliable solution for public showcases and self-service kiosks. The software protects public computers against any kind of undesirable end-user actions, monitors kiosk, generates usage statistics, and enables easy and secure display of various types of information in public spaces such as libraries, schools, universities, museums, etc.
InfoTouch Features
	Display web pages in a secure Web browser
	Creates a personalized start page and...
</description></item><item><title>Download KORG Modwave Native 1.3.6</title><pubDate> Fri, 08 Aug 2025 01:38:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-korg-modwave-native-10310.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-korg-modwave-native-10310.html
</guid><description>
Modwave, released in 2021, builds on the DW legacy and transforms it into a modern monster synth, featuring incredibly deep wavetable oscillators, stunning filters , extremely flexible modulation, complex sample sequencing, and macro controls for unique, powerful, and easy-to-customize sounds and phrases.
The software is fully compatible with hardware modwave synthesizers. KORG Modwave Native is available in VST3, AAX, and standalone formats on both macOS and Windows, as well as AU on...
</description></item><item><title>Download KORG Wavestate Native 1.4.6</title><pubDate> Fri, 08 Aug 2025 01:38:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-korg-wavestate-native-10309.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-korg-wavestate-native-10309.html
</guid><description>
KORG Wavestate Native is designed from the ground up for a new generation of musicians, producers and composers, taking cues from sources as diverse as modular synths, groove boxes and layouts algorithm. It is available in VST3, AAX, and standalone formats on both macOS and Windows, as well as AU on macOS. You can seamlessly exchange audio between hardware and software. Produce in your DAW with the original wave state, then play the same sounds on stage using the wave state...
</description></item></channel></rss>