<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 01:44:54 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 01:44:54 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download PrivaZer Pro Donors 4.0.114</title><pubDate> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 00:16:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-privazer-donors-198.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-privazer-donors-198.html
</guid><description>
PrivaZer Donors  cleans and removes filth traces from the system. Intensive cleaning of unwanted traces of what you've done, viewed, downloaded, deleted, etc. Take ownership of your security and freedom - Free up disk space. Keep your PC snug and secure !!!
With one click, PrivaZer can safely clean: Internet browsers, Index.dat, Cookies, Tor Cookies, Flash Cookies, Silverlight Cookies, DOM Storing, IndexedDB, AppCache Registry, RAM, Pagefile.sys and Hiberfil.sys files.  PrivaZer  can...
</description></item><item><title>Download CyberLink AudioDirector Ultra 2026 v16.0.5822.10</title><pubDate> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 00:16:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-audiodirector-ultra-288.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-audiodirector-ultra-288.html
</guid><description>
Sound is half the movie experience and improving the audio in the project video will greatly enhance the final result. AudioDirector contains advanced tools help edit and edit the audio quickly and simply. With the audio feature and seamless integration with PowerDirector.
We provide CyberLink AudioDirector Ultra editor software, mix, and adjust the soundtrack, effects, audio for video, and all the passages spoken in the video. CyberLink AudioDirector Ultra is the upgrade version of...
</description></item><item><title>Download VideoProc Converter AI 8.5</title><pubDate> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 00:15:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-videoproc-2473.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-videoproc-2473.html
</guid><description>
VideoProc (an improved version of WinX HD Video Converter Deluxe) - processing software the most powerful video designed to edit, cut, crop, merge, adjust, convert and compress (4K) video with full Hardware Acceleration. Is the heir to be improved a lot, VideoProc integrated conversion / compression video UHD, the download at videos (YouTube) with the video editor, gives you the power to control optimal for every video file much music, SD, HD and 4K on your PC. With technology hardware...
</description></item><item><title>Download Capture One Pro 16.7.0.3201 + Enterprise</title><pubDate> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 00:07:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capture-one-pro-624.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capture-one-pro-624.html
</guid><description>
Capture One Pro is the software solution complete photo editing. With powerful tools to organize, color grading, editing grades, and more, you have full control over the images and process his work. Capture One has been developed with quality images and easy to use. Every tool is designed to give you full control over all aspects of the process editing - preserve, restore and optimize all information from the file RAW of you. Full the tool provides the ability to expand to always achieve...
</description></item><item><title>Download Gilisoft Total Repair 11.0.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 00:06:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-total-repair-12836.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-total-repair-12836.html
</guid><description>
Total Repair Toolkit is an all-in-one system maintenance tool that integrates smart diagnosis, in-depth repair, and performance optimization. It has a one-click smart repair engine that can automatically resolve over 500 common problems such as system lag, game crashes, and file corruption. Meanwhile, it provides a professional manual repair module to meet advanced requirements.
Gilisoft Total Repair Features
	Application error repair based on a large DLL library
	In-depth diagnosis...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cisdem Video Compressor 2.4.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 00:06:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cisdem-video-compressor-12046.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cisdem-video-compressor-12046.html
</guid><description>
Cisdem Video Compressor is a software program designed to reduce video file size without losing quality. It provides a user-friendly interface and various compression settings to help users optimize their video files for different purposes, such as sharing online, saving storage space or improve video streaming performance.
Cisdem Video Compressor supports many input video formats, including MP4, MOV, AVI, MKV, etc. It allows users to choose different compression methods, such as...
</description></item><item><title>Download Viber for PC 26.5.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 00:05:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-viber-2406.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-viber-2406.html
</guid><description>
Viber is a software of instant messaging, based on VoIP protocols, multi-platform due to the Viber Media development for smart phones used to send sms and make calls over the internet. Along with text messaging, users can exchange images, video and audio.
Viber - software news message, chat online
This is a program that is quite popular is mainly designed for mobile phones, but now we are talking about the version for Windows, so immediately. It will allow you to send messages to other...
</description></item><item><title>Download PrivaZer 4.0.114</title><pubDate> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 00:05:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-privazer-66.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-privazer-66.html
</guid><description>
PrivaZer : the program performs the scan is very thorough not only includes the trace downloads like registration, Internet history, cookies, etc but also find the traces of potential in the field of free disk space of you. PrivaZer can permanently delete all traces by using the method of secure erase and also re-establish the sector disk free to 0 to remove all traces from the delete operation earlier. The process of scanning and cleaning the original can spend less time (20-30 minutes),...
</description></item><item><title>Download foobar2000 2.25.3</title><pubDate> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 00:04:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-foobar2000-1812.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-foobar2000-1812.html
</guid><description>
foobar2000 is the media player for media formats MP3, WAV, OGG and other formats multimedia other. It has no bells and whistles, however, under the hood, the program offers quite many features, including format, title and layout of the interface can be customized, convert WAV, Equalizer, Resampler, note cards, MP3, playlists, music album, CD, drag / drop and more. It also includes all the standard features like shuffle, random play, etc.
foobar2000 - The media player
foobar2000 running...
</description></item><item><title>Download Olympia Graphic Design 1.7.7.55</title><pubDate> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 00:04:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-olympia-graphic-design-9607.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-olympia-graphic-design-9607.html
</guid><description>
Olympia Graphic Design is an intuitive yet powerful illustration and design software application. With Olympia Graphic Design, you'll have access to advanced tools, filters, effects, and more, giving you the arsenal you need to take your projects to the next level.
Olympia Graphic Design comes with 2000 royalty-free vector graphics and images to complete your work. You can even access over 100 professional design ideas to inspire and motivate you! It allows users to create flyers,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wing FTP Server Corporate 8.0.6</title><pubDate> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 00:02:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wing-ftp-server-corporate-2752.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wing-ftp-server-corporate-2752.html
</guid><description>
Wing FTP Server Corporate is a highly functional, easy and safe can be used in the operating system Windows, Linux, Mac and Solaris are used. The software supports a number of file transfer protocol such as FTP, HTTP, FTPS, HTTPS and SFTP. Wing FTP Server provides web-based interface to manage the server at any time. You can also get performance server and the online and even send email notifications about various events happening on the server.
Management server multi-function
Wing FTP...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cypheros TS-Doctor 4.2.16</title><pubDate> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 00:01:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cypheros-ts-doctor-9146.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cypheros-ts-doctor-9146.html
</guid><description>
Cypheros TS-Doctor is a software tool designed to edit and repair MPEG2 and H.264 transport streams. Easily create your own movie library, easy, fast and without loss of picture and sound quality. TS-Doctor is the perfect tool for editing and repairing recordings from Sat, Cable and DVB-T Receivers. This software is specifically designed for use with digital TV recordings and can process recordings from a variety of digital TV sources, including satellite, cable and terrestrial...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cisdem Video Converter 4.1.3</title><pubDate> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 00:01:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cisdem-video-converter-9557.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cisdem-video-converter-9557.html
</guid><description>
Cisdem Video Converter is an all-in-one solution for converting video and audio files of any format, ripping DVD movies and converting online videos. The converter provides support for more than 150 audio and video file formats, and helps you download or share content with others. Cisdem Video Converter gives you the ability to make audio or video content compatible with almost any device.
Save videos and music from 1000+ hosting sites for offline viewing, including YouTube, Facebook,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wagnardsoft Tools (WTools) 1.0.6.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 00:00:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wagnardsoft-tools-8092.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wagnardsoft-tools-8092.html
</guid><description>
Wagnardsoft Tools (or WTools) is a lightweight utility that contains many tools to clean your system from temporary and error files Other times take up space and can be dangerous for your PC. It is developed by the author of the program Display Driver Uninstaller has been trusted and used by many people.&amp;lt; /p&amp;gt;
Wagnardsoft Tools gives you the essentials to clean up targeted areas of your machine and thus free up space. It's important to note that don't delete important registry keys...
</description></item><item><title>Download Hasleo Backup Suite 5.5.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 00:00:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hasleo-backup-suite-6588.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hasleo-backup-suite-6588.html
</guid><description>
Hasleo Backup Suite is a free backup and free Windows recovery, integration of backup features, recovery, and replication, it is designed for Windows operating system users and can be used on both Windows PC and Windows Server. The backup and recovery feature of Hasleo Backup Suite can help you backup and restore your Windows, disk and partition operating system to protect your Windows operating system and your personal data. The replication feature of Hasleo Backup Suite can help you...
</description></item><item><title>Download dbForge Studio for MySQL Enterprise 2025.2.91</title><pubDate> Thu, 30 Oct 2025 00:00:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbforge-studio-for-mysql-enterprise-edition-7743.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbforge-studio-for-mysql-enterprise-edition-7743.html
</guid><description>
dbForge Studio for MySQL is a popular GUI tool for developing, managing, and administering MySQL and MariaDB databases. The IDE allows you to create and execute queries, develop and debug stored procedures, automate database object management, and analyze table data through an intuitive interface. The MySQL client provides data and schema comparison and synchronization tools, database reporting tools, backup options with scheduling, and much more.
Features of dbForge Studio for...
</description></item><item><title>Download ClrMamePro 4.050</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 23:59:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-clrmamepro-3195.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-clrmamepro-3195.html
</guid><description>
ClrMamePro is a ROM manager for MAME emulator. It will help you update your ROM collections of his. The project began in 1997 and is a application MS-DOS based command line, but quickly added GUI (user interface graphics). Gone through many different versions and it has perfected with the unique features below.
ClrMamePro - manager, ROM for emulator
The features of ClrMamePro
	Search for the lost games, roms, samples
	Find and rename wrong named roms, samples
	Find and resize wrong...
</description></item><item><title>Download Coder Technologies Coder 2.26.3</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 23:56:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coder-oss-enterprise-8726.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coder-oss-enterprise-8726.html
</guid><description>
Coder OSS Enterprise is a development platform that provides a complete cloud-based solution for software development, testing and deployment. It is designed to simplify the software development process by providing developers with a collaborative and streamlined environment.
Coder offloads development from local workstations to your on-premises infrastructure and public cloud. Boost developer productivity with powerful server resources and instant integration. Keep the code and data...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adlice Protect (formerly RogueKiller) 16.5.0.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 23:56:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rogueKiller-171.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rogueKiller-171.html
</guid><description>
RogueKiller is a tool anti-malware independent can assist advanced users with the removal of a number of difficulties in the removal of malware, in security software rogue special.
The program can terminate processes, malware has to know to you can delete them manually or use the tool clear of the Tuesday to complete the work. RogueKiller can also restore HOSTS file as well as your DNS settings and Proxy, which is often modified by rogue applications.
RogueKiller
When you run...
</description></item><item><title>Download GSoft4U Music Collection 3.9.4.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 23:55:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gsoft4u-music-collection-2437.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gsoft4u-music-collection-2437.html
</guid><description>
GSoft4U Music Collection is a free software to help you fully organized music collection of an archive can search quality. Archiving process is very simple; put on details related to format, genre, release date, record label, as well as rating the 'why' of it. The artists will be divided up alphabetically for easy access.
GSoft4U Music Collection - Manage music collection
The app will allow you to add additional information into its music, as this of course you must have an Internet...
</description></item><item><title>Download AI Image Watermark Remover Pro 1.0.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 21:12:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ai-image-watermark-remover-pro-14263.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ai-image-watermark-remover-pro-14263.html
</guid><description>
Are you tired of unwanted watermarks, logos, texts or objects cluttering up your photos? AI Image Watermark Remover Pro is the ultimate solution to help you create perfect, clean and professional photos. Powered by advanced AI inpainting technology, the app intelligently removes any unwanted elements and recreates the background with incredible precision, as if it never existed.
Whether you're a photographer cleaning up your portfolio, a designer preparing assets, or simply someone...
</description></item><item><title>Download CyberLink PhotoDirector Ultra 2026 v17.0.1027.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 21:08:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-photodirector-ultra-129.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-photodirector-ultra-129.html
</guid><description>
Cyberlink PhotoDirector Ultra is known to be photo editing tools and videos with the effect is extremely rich, help you to change the style for the individual images or the videos of his favorite. This software integrated the 3D engine helps to speed up Video processing, which allows accessing the repository effect online and extract the Videos into the movies 3D Bru-ray, 3D AVCHD.
Cyberlink PhotoDirector Ultra to offer users a more professional tool to handle their images, remove...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinRAR 7.20 Beta 1 / 7.13 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 20:32:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winrar-127.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winrar-127.html
</guid><description>
WinRAR is a compression utility data advanced supports multiple formats including RAR, ZIP, CAB, ARJ, LZH, ACE, TAR, GZip, UUE, ISO, BZIP2, Z and 7-Zip. It allows you to create, organize and manage archives in a comfortable way and quickly. WinRAR naturally are is a leading software currently in the compression and decompression of data. With the enhanced algorithm is applied, the software allows users to compress bulk files in different formats into synthetic 1 single file to facilitate...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare PDFelement Pro 12.0.8.3784</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 20:30:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-pdfelement-pro-105.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-pdfelement-pro-105.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare PDFelement Pro support users to convert PDF to office documents for easier use, modify in every situation. Is one of the software conversion material is rated best today, integrated with many features. We recommend that you should use experience software many useful features this.
Wondershare PDFelement Pro - conversion Fie PDF more features, multi-language
Wondershare PDFelement Pro what?
Convert PDF into Word, Excel, PowerPoint...
• Convert PDF and protected PDF into...
</description></item><item><title>Download Winxvideo AI 4.5.0.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 29 Oct 2025 20:29:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winxvideo-ai-10981.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winxvideo-ai-10981.html
</guid><description>
Winxvideo AI is an innovative video editing app that leverages the power of artificial intelligence to provide users with advanced video editing capabilities. With advanced features and a user-friendly interface, Winxvideo AI is designed to streamline the video editing process and empower creators to create professional-quality videos.
Winxvideo AI meets all your audio/video conversion needs and compresses your 4K/8K footage from GB to MB without compromising on quality, powered by...
</description></item></channel></rss>