<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 15:38:15 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 15:38:15 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download PDF-XChange Editor Plus 10.7.3.401.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:55:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-xchange-editor-plus-645.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-xchange-editor-plus-645.html
</guid><description>
PDF-XChange Editor Plus is the editor, PDF viewer, compact, fast with many features, add-ons, professional. When using the PDF-XChange Editor Plus, easy for users to create, view, edit, annotate, OCR and digital signing PDF files, plus much more.
PDF-XChange Editor is a PDF editing full-featured. With the help of it, you can edit, fix, add, or delete text easily. Graphics can also be moved, resized or removed.
Features PDF-XChange Editor Plus
Edit documents
	Use a variety of editing...
</description></item><item><title>Download Screenpresso Pro 2.1.39</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:55:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-screenpresso-pro-1362.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-screenpresso-pro-1362.html
</guid><description>
Screenpresso Pro is a program easy to take great photos on your screen! Screenpresso blocked Print Screen key and screen capture the best in a few seconds. Allows you to capture windows and screen area, roll the part of the screen, edit the images obtained, add effects, resize a group of images, send screenshots by email and post them to Web resources.
Screenpresso Pro - Shooting the computer screen
Features of Screenpresso Pro
	Take the window and screen area. Take a partial screen...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDF-XChange Pro 10.7.3.401.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:54:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-xchange-editor-pro-3422.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-xchange-editor-pro-3422.html
</guid><description>
PDF-XChange Editor Pro is an application to manipulate and create PDF versatile, offering a wide range of useful features and powerful will help you to easily work with PDF files. This application is very flexible and allows you to easily create and modify PDF files. PDF-XChange Editor Pro provides a powerful set of tools and flexibility to work with PDF files, such as editor PDF-XChange new, utilities series, OFFice2PDF and the Addin tool Bar allows you to easily convert multiple file...
</description></item><item><title>Download Helium Music Manager Premium 17.4.528</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:54:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-helium-music-manager-premium-164.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-helium-music-manager-premium-164.html
</guid><description>
Helium Music Manager is a music manager that can rip, tag, play, browse, search, rename, burn and synchronize your music with the mobile. You can control your music collection with Helium Music Manager. Stop using time looking for the file on your computer or looking through CDS, vinyl records and tapes - instead, simply enjoy and explore your music! Helium Music Manager can replace the ripper, the player, tag editor and related software to audio your other.
Helium Music Manager...
</description></item><item><title>Download Abelssoft HappyCard 4.05</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:53:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-abelssoft-happycard-3128.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-abelssoft-happycard-3128.html
</guid><description>
Abelssoft HappyCard allows you to create cards, business cards only in few clicks. HappyCard help users to have simple interface to use to create invitation cards in just a few clicks. The card is made creative, without any previous knowledge. No matter if you want to make a invitation card, greeting card or a gift card: HappyCard comes with 50 card templates professional for events such as birthday party, wedding, etc.
Abelssoft HappyCard - Create invitations, business cards
Features...
</description></item><item><title>Download Gilisoft Image Converter 8.2.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:53:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-image-converter-13869.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-image-converter-13869.html
</guid><description>
Gilisoft Image Converter is a software tool designed to quickly convert images between various formats, including JPG, PNG, HEIC, etc. This tool supports batch image conversion, allowing users to process multiple images at once, efficient for large-scale tasks. Additional features often include image compression and image conversion to PDF format for easier sharing and printing.
Fast image conversion
For users who need to process large numbers of images, this converter provides batch...
</description></item><item><title>Download WindowManager 10.23.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:52:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desksoft-windowmanager-573.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desksoft-windowmanager-573.html
</guid><description>
WindowManager is a software by DeskSoft dedicated to providing software utilities for windows. DeskSoft WindowManager is the window manager window to ensure your windows are placed exactly where you want. Software will help you to help you improve your work flow by remembering and restoring the position and size of the program and your window. The processing window can completely customize and you can set the special rules for the windows favorite or used most often.
WindowManager send...
</description></item><item><title>Download reaConverter Pro 7.854</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:52:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html
</guid><description>
reaConverter Pro is software image processing feature with batch conversion and image editing periodically becomes simple. eaConverter also provide command line utilities allow you to process images automatically, thus helping you shorten the time for other work.
reaConverter Pro integrated powerful tool of Uber with many great features. It provides advanced solutions to process and adjust images. Management of the conversion process the base image with the latest version of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Reveal Sound Spire 1.5.19</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:51:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reveal-sound-spire-3455.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reveal-sound-spire-3455.html
</guid><description>
Reveal Sound Spire is a virtual synthesizers there are four sets of oscillating modes with support polymorphism, nine-voice unison, and on each of the oscillators. You can re-create the wave as ultrasound and ultrasound respectively. Have the effect integrated. Reveal Sound was founded by musicians and programmers in 2009 for creating a plug-in sound class. Our goal - to prove that the synthesis of audio software can be of high quality. We are constantly improving the algorithm of their...
</description></item><item><title>Download O&amp;amp;O Defrag Pro 30.0.1056</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:51:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-o-o-defrag-pro-149.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-o-o-defrag-pro-149.html
</guid><description>
O&amp;amp;O Defrag Pro is the professional software has the ability to defragment the hard disk and can work with the file system different from FAT / 32 to NTFS / 5, and support for the different arrays Volume / Stripe Sets. You can also set the schedule which O &amp;amp; O Defrag will be booted and perform a number of manipulation certain. Regular defragmentation of the disk partition optimized performance of your computer. The user interface is very easy to use. It has a ribbon bar displays all...
</description></item><item><title>Download O&amp;amp;O Defrag Server 30.0.1056</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:51:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-defrag-server-2521.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-defrag-server-2521.html
</guid><description>
O&amp;amp;O Defrag Server professional software has the ability to defragment the hard disk and can work with the file system different from FAT / 32 to NTFS / 5, and support for the different arrays Volume / Stripe Sets. You can also set the schedule which O &amp;amp; O Defrag will be booted and perform a number of manipulation certain. Regular defragmentation of the disk partition optimized performance of your computer. The user interface is very easy to use. It has a ribbon bar displays all the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Grub2Win 3.0.0.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:49:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-grub2win-3177.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-grub2win-3177.html
</guid><description>
Grub2Win is a open source program to dual boot Windows and Linux safely. Grub2Win boot code the GNU Grub version 2.04. Everything is in a folder of 20 MB on Windows drive C: On the EFI system, a few small modules to be installed into the EFI partition of your.
Grub2Win - Boot system, Windows
Using GUI Windows and simple instructions you can install Grub2Win quickly and safely. Notice the boot time and help can be displayed in multiple languages. After installing interface, it's easy to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Materialise Magics 29.0.1.30</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:49:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-materialise-magics-1477.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-materialise-magics-1477.html
</guid><description>
Materialize Magics is the name of the specialized software and 3D printing techniques. Of course, in recent years, you've read articles about 3D printing. The software you're looking for is a powerful tool and is a provider editor software STL top. With this software, you will be able to turn your files into STL and identified and corrected after the error. You will also be able to edit your layout and provide the background you need to 3D print.
Materialise Magics - software engineer,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Awesome Miner Ultimate 11.2.4</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:49:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-awesome-miner-9041.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-awesome-miner-9041.html
</guid><description>
Awesome Miner is a software application designed to manage and monitor cryptocurrency mining operations. It supports a wide variety of mining hardware, including ASICs and GPUs, and can be used to manage mining for a variety of cryptocurrencies, including Bitcoin, Ethereum, and Litecoin.
Powerful tool to manage and monitor cryptocurrency mining activities. With support for a wide variety of mining hardware and cryptocurrencies, mobile apps, and customizable alerting and performance...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cash Register Pro 4.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:48:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cash-register-pro-3853.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cash-register-pro-3853.html
</guid><description>
Cash Register Pro a software cash register full of features and creative for a Windows computer, it will help you to better handle all the activities of the computer money. The application comes with the user interface logical and user friendly allows you to work quickly and do not commit the common error. The program can be used on a number of computers and offers a wide range of authorization secure and reliable. Cash Register Pro will help you track products and goods remain...
</description></item><item><title>Download iDefender 5.1.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:34:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idefender-13959.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idefender-13959.html
</guid><description>
iDefender is an advanced security solution designed for the home, providing both a High-Performance Intrusion Prevention System (HIPS) and Real-Time Endpoint Detection and Response (EDR). This integrated system protects against potential threats, ensuring the safety and integrity of your devices by proactively monitoring and responding to suspicious activity.
Why iDefender?
Ransomware Prevention
	Detects and blocks ransomware in real time to protect important files from malicious...
</description></item><item><title>Download Imagine 2.2.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:34:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-imagine-7369.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-imagine-7369.html
</guid><description>
Imagine is an application that allows you to view images and animations in a variety of formats, including JPG, BMP, PNG and GIF. With Imagine you can view file properties and EXIF ​​information, copy, move, delete and rename images. Additionally, you can also flip, resize and rotate them, swap colors, set transparency levels, import, export, and edit palettes, and change color depth.
Features of Imagine
	View and save image/animation files at lightning speed
	Multiple...
</description></item><item><title>Download GOM Player Free 2.3.112 Build 5382</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:33:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gom-player-994.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gom-player-994.html
</guid><description>
GOM Player is a program to listen to music for free with the ability to play all format music and video now without the need to install additional codec. GOM Media Player brings all video codecs needed to play multiple video formats and various audio. Simple interface, light volume but powerful function is the factor which makes GOM Player famous in the music software.
GOM Media Player according to the reviews is considered the listen to music, watch video best. The user can control GOM...
</description></item><item><title>Download DesktopOK 12.13</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:33:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopok-1635.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopok-1635.html
</guid><description>
DesktopOK is software save and restore the positions of icons. DesktopOK also offers a solution small but effective for the user to change the screen resolution often. DesktopOK is not installed and can be executed easily from the desktop, and can be carried on a small USB or memory device to another. Start of the program. The first time you use the program, the program will show you screen license. Free program and license info is only displayed the first time (on each PC).
DesktopOK -...
</description></item><item><title>Download ExifTool 13.37</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:32:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-exiftool-1685.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-exiftool-1685.html
</guid><description>
ExifTool is a library of Perl platform-independent plus a command line application for reading, writing, and editing meta information in various file types. ExifTool supports many metadata formats including EXIF , GPS , IPTC , XMP , JFIF , GeoTIFF , ICC Profile , Photoshop IRB , FlashPix , AFCP and ID3 , as well as notes of the manufacturer of many digital cameras by Canon , Casio , DJI , FLIR , FujiFilm , GE , GoPro , HP , JVC / Victor , Kodak , Leaf , Minolta / Konica-Minolta , Motorola...
</description></item><item><title>Download OpenVPN 2.6.15</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:31:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-openvpn-4245.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-openvpn-4245.html
</guid><description>
OpenVPN provides the VPN solution flexible to secure communication of your data, whether it is the right to privacy on the Internet, remote access for employees, security, IoT, or for the data center cloud. Solution VPN software, our Server can be deployed in place by standard server or virtual device or on the cloud.
OpenVPN - VPN Solution flexible
Though built with the open source OpenVPN, the solution of our additional functionality to meet the needs of business customers, the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Portable WiFi - Mobile Hotspot 3.9.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:20:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-portable-wifi-mobile-hotspot-13650.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-portable-wifi-mobile-hotspot-13650.html
</guid><description>
Portable WiFi Hotspot helps you share Internet with other mobile devices and create a free hotspot. This is a simple and free WiFi hotspot app for Android that you can use to share Internet with other devices. Personal hotspot app provides everything you need to share free WiFi with friends and family!
Turn your phone into a mobile hotspot instantly with this free WiFi hotspot app without root. Simple to use and easy to set up, this hotspot app will turn your phone into a powerful...
</description></item><item><title>Download UVX Player Pro: Ultimate VideoX 3.7.6</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:20:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-uvx-player-pro-8627.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-uvx-player-pro-8627.html
</guid><description>
UVX Player Pro is a video player application available on Android devices. It provides a way to play videos on your device, including high definition (HD) and Ultra High Definition (UHD) videos. This app supports many video formats, including AVI, MP4, MKV, FLV, and more. Some of its features include gesture control, playback speed control, and subtitle support. UVX Player Pro also includes an integrated video converter, allowing users to convert video files to other formats. It also has...
</description></item><item><title>Download Barbell Workout at Home &amp;amp; Gym 4.12</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:20:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-barbell-home-workout-8674.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-barbell-home-workout-8674.html
</guid><description>
Build muscle and increase strength with weight training.
Download the app and get everything you need
	Pre-set training plan
	Illustration of exercises for each muscle group
	Voice feedback
	Detailed history
	Beautiful, well-proportioned body and toned muscles
Tips
	Choose a weight that you feel comfortable with.
	Only increase the weight when you start to feel like the set is no longer challenging you.
</description></item><item><title>Download Weather &amp;amp; Widget - Weawow 7.0.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:19:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-weather-widget-weawow-8870.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-weather-widget-weawow-8870.html
</guid><description>
Weawow is a beautiful and highly accurate weather forecast application. You can also sell your photos at the Weawow marketplace. Weawow is a comprehensive and user-friendly weather app and widget that provides users with accurate and reliable weather information and forecasts as well as a host of other features and functions. This is a useful tool for those who want to stay up to date with the latest forecasts and weather conditions, whether for personal or professional purposes.
Weawow...
</description></item></channel></rss>