<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 20:02:12 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 20:02:12 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download R-Wipe &amp;amp; Clean 20.0 Build 2535</title><pubDate> Mon, 10 Nov 2025 16:40:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-wipe-clean-891.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-wipe-clean-891.html
</guid><description>
R-Wipe &amp;amp; Clean is software to delete junk files, unnecessary files from your computer to release the storage space and speed up your computer. In addition, R-Wipe &amp;amp; Clean also unleash the capacity of your drive and delete information invasion of privacy on different operations online and offline including your internet history and cookies, the list of downloaded files and documents were open, buffer different data, temporary files and many other items, created by the operating...
</description></item><item><title>Download StartAllBack 3.9.17.5333</title><pubDate> Mon, 10 Nov 2025 16:39:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-startallback-6857.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-startallback-6857.html
</guid><description>
With the official release of Windows 11, chances are that most of you want to try it out. As the name suggests, StartAllBack is a small, lightweight tool that can help you enjoy the power of the new operating system while keeping the look and feel, especially because main work area, desktop of Windows 7, Windows 10 as taskbars and start menu styles.
StartAllBack is specially designed for Windows 11 and will not work on any older operating systems. If you want to get the start menu back...
</description></item><item><title>Download Windows Password Recovery Tool Ultimate 8.5.0.5</title><pubDate> Mon, 10 Nov 2025 16:38:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-password-recovery-tool-ultimate-4190.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-password-recovery-tool-ultimate-4190.html
</guid><description>
Windows Password Recovery Tool Ultimate is software recover Windows password first in the world to reset login password forgotten of Windows. Just need 3 simple steps to recover Windows password without system reinstallation and without need to restore data. Tool password recovery could reset or remove Windows password, delete the administrator account and create new accounts for all computer users. This software is also very secure, no vulnerability to steal the password while you are...
</description></item><item><title>Download UniFab 3.0.3.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 10 Nov 2025 16:38:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-unifab-10377.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-unifab-10377.html
</guid><description>
UniFab is software to efficiently convert, compress and edit more than 1000 video formats for playback on any device without losing quality. Enlarge video/audio to 1080p/DTS 7.1 and upgrade video to HDR10 or Dolby Vision with AI Enhancer. UniFab Pro provides the best AI-powered zoom tool that allows you to enlarge videos from low resolutions, such as 360p, 480p and 720p, to 1080p without losing any quality. Clearer and sharper image details will bring you an exceptional viewing...
</description></item><item><title>Download Windows 11 Pro + Office 2024 25H2 v26200.7019 NoTPM Multilingual Preactivated</title><pubDate> Mon, 10 Nov 2025 16:37:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-11-pro-incl-office-7292.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-11-pro-incl-office-7292.html
</guid><description>
Windows 11 Pro is a Microsoft operating system announced in 2021, part of the Windows NT family of operating systems. Windows 11 was released to the general public on October 5, 2021 as a free upgrade through Windows Update for eligible Windows 10 devices.
This Windows 11 Pro Premium is created from the original Microsoft installer and is integrated with the latest update in 2022. By skipping TPM 2.0 for computers Windows 11 cannot be installed and it is also Comes with the office...
</description></item><item><title>Download GoodSync Enterprise 12.9.14.4</title><pubDate> Mon, 10 Nov 2025 16:36:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-goodsync-enterprise-163.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-goodsync-enterprise-163.html
</guid><description>
GoodSync Enterprise is a software that saves files and files easily and is reliable. It automatically analyts, synchronize and backup your email, family photos, contacts, MP3, financial documentation and other important files-between desktop computers, laptops, servers, external drives and Windows Mobile devices as well as remotely via FTP , SFTP, WebDAV and more. The GoodSync synchronized software combines bulletproof reliability with an extremely easy interface to compare, synchronize...
</description></item><item><title>Download PCUnlocker Enterprise Edition 6.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 10 Nov 2025 16:36:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pcunlocker-enterprise-edition-6940.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pcunlocker-enterprise-edition-6940.html
</guid><description>
PCUnlocker is a utility that can boot to ignore/reset the forgotten administrator password or other user on Windows 11/10/8/7/XP/XP/2019/2016/2012/2003/2003/2003/2000 and Active Directory server (AD). Unlock your system immediately if you forget the Windows password or the user account is locked or disabled. PCUnlocker is designed to enable users to populate the forgotten Windows password by recording a CD/DVD or USB flash drive capable of starting.
Features of PCUnlocker:
	Simple and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Global Mapper Pro 26.2.1 Build 110625</title><pubDate> Mon, 10 Nov 2025 16:36:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-global-mapper-professional-3563.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-global-mapper-professional-3563.html
</guid><description>
Global Mapper is a GIS application affordable and easy-to-use application that provides access to a great variety of spatial data sets and provides just the right level functionality to satisfy both GIS experts and experience users started. Also similar to a tool management data space independently and as an integral component of a GIS system enterprise-wide, Global Mapper is the tool mandatory for anyone working with maps or spatial data.
Global Mapper - GIS application
Global Mapper...
</description></item><item><title>Download PassFab 4WinKey Ultimate 8.5.0.5</title><pubDate> Mon, 10 Nov 2025 16:35:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-passfab-4winkey-5491.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-passfab-4winkey-5491.html
</guid><description>
PassFab 4WinKey is the leading tool that helps you recover Windowsm passwords, delete or reset local and admin passwords, delete or create Windows accounts in minutes. One click to create Windows password reset disc (USB / CD / DVD). Compatible with Windows 10 / 8.1 / 8/7 / Vista / XP and Server 2019.
Except for a factory reset for Windows systems, you can also get your password back using this Windows password lock software and then access your PC again. No need to reinstall your...
</description></item><item><title>Download ProfiCAD 13.3.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 10 Nov 2025 16:34:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-proficad-1546.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-proficad-1546.html
</guid><description>
ProfiCAD is a software Program to draw diagram and circuit diagram of the electrical circuit and electronics with many features to support users. ProfiCAD will search the control circuit is different then help, you can design a variety of diagram techniques, such as diagrams, pneumatic and hydraulic. One of the obvious features of this product is the simplicity of it. Simple in the tool bar and the icons represent the parts. Simply arrange the menu, just put the items on the screen and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Directory Opus Pro 13.19.6 Beta</title><pubDate> Mon, 10 Nov 2025 16:34:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-opus-pro-779.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-opus-pro-779.html
</guid><description>
Directory Opus Pro is a software replacement for Explorer with traditional strength and function more than any manager other files. Directory Opus Pro full support for high DPI screen (for example 4K and 5K) with the rename dialog is redesigned, with new features. Besides being a recording macro only allows you to perform mass renaming complex that don't need regular expressions. In addition, Directory Opus Pro also enhances the ability to script.Better handling of renaming recursive and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Any Video Downloader Pro 9.7.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 10 Nov 2025 16:33:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-video-downloader-pro-3731.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-video-downloader-pro-3731.html
</guid><description>
Any Video Downloader Pro is software support you can download video HD 720p, 1080p, 2K, 4K and 8K from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion, Vimeo, Metacafe and thousands of video sharing sites, other. It is a tool to speed up multi-threading can speed up your download faster up to 5 times. This helpful program support download at the same time. Any Video Downloader Pro lets you download multiple videos at the same time. Moreover, it allows you to pause and resume downloads if you need more...
</description></item><item><title>Download 4KSoftware 4K Downloader 5.19.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 10 Nov 2025 16:32:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-downloader-3858.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-downloader-3858.html
</guid><description>
4K Downloader is a Windows application small but powerful to download and convert video in 4K and 8K Ultra HD from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion and thousands of other video-based websites. It speeds up your download by up to 5 times. Consider that most smart phones, TVS, computers, and tablets all support the high definition format, don't be surprised when many users want to enjoy quality content on their device. 4K Downloader is a lightweight software designed to help you grab videos...
</description></item><item><title>Download ChessOK Aquarium Pro 2025 v25.0.0.981</title><pubDate> Mon, 10 Nov 2025 16:32:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chessok-aquarium-pro-1504.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chessok-aquarium-pro-1504.html
</guid><description>
ChessOK Aquarium Pro 2019 is software that provides the functions advanced analysis, review games, search chess playing strong, playing, databases and much more. If you've owned engine Houdini 6 UCI and are looking for an appropriate interface, ChessOK Aquarium 2019 is the best you can find.
ChessOK Aquarium is an analysis tool, database and publishing chess revolutionary, fully compatible with the chess playing engines, the most powerful in the world, including Houdini 6 and Stockfish....
</description></item><item><title>Download Syncovery Premium 11.10.2.122</title><pubDate> Mon, 10 Nov 2025 16:31:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncovery-pro-enterprise-232.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncovery-pro-enterprise-232.html
</guid><description>
Syncovery Pro Enterprise is a great application used to back up data and to synchronize personal computers, servers, laptops, notepads and storage online. The software comes with support for FTP and secure FTP servers, SSH, WebDAV, Amazon S3, http, update the part file, ZIP compression, data encryption, and schedule automatic backups.
Syncovery Pro Enterprise have the ability to freely select files and folders across the whole folder hierarchy in tree view and supports email...
</description></item><item><title>Download AllMapSoft Google Maps Downloader 8.884</title><pubDate> Mon, 10 Nov 2025 16:30:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-google-maps-downloader-2796.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-google-maps-downloader-2796.html
</guid><description>
AllMapSoft Google Maps Downloader is a reliable application aimed at downloading maps from Google at high speed. The result is a set of small images can be combined in a larger map. This can serve in a large variety of projects, from creating a tile map to presentations and tutorials.
Google Maps Downloader successfully fulfills both of those conditions, providing simple means to quickly grab maps at the resolution satisfactory. In addition, it is extremely easy to use and integrated a...
</description></item><item><title>Download DoYourData Super Eraser 8.1 Business</title><pubDate> Mon, 10 Nov 2025 16:30:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-doyourdata-super-eraser-business-1210.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-doyourdata-super-eraser-business-1210.html
</guid><description>
DoYourData Super Eraser offers a simple solution and safe to delete the data from PC, hard drive, RAID arrays, servers, USB drive, memory card, digital camera, SD card, external hard drive. It will permanently cancel and delete the selected data, leaving no chance of recovery, which does not affect the lifespan of the device.
DoYourData Super Eraser Business - Delete data securely
Features of DoYourData Super Eraser Business
	Support delete data from many different devices, including...
</description></item><item><title>Download ZD Soft Screen Recorder 12.0.7</title><pubDate> Mon, 10 Nov 2025 16:29:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zd-soft-screen-recorder-136.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zd-soft-screen-recorder-136.html
</guid><description>
ZD Soft Screen Recorder supports user taping the game in 2D or 3D, film screen, the content is screened in the multimedia. The Videos are saved in a list and popular formats with best quality.
ZD Soft Screen Recorder is a program recording software screen high performance. It works just like a camera really. A camcorder can record many things in the real world including computer screen, while ZD Soft Screen Recorder can only record computer screen but can do much better than a camcorder...
</description></item><item><title>Download AmoyShare BeeConverter Pro 3.3.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 10 Nov 2025 16:29:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-amoyshare-beeconverter-pro-7285.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-amoyshare-beeconverter-pro-7285.html
</guid><description>
BeeConverter Pro is a great application for video converter capable of converting multiple files simultaneously, converting videos for specific devices, handling multiple audio formats and video and most importantly, do all of this with 60x faster conversions. With its help, you can convert video or audio in any popular formats, such as MP4, MKV, AVI, FLV, WEBM and MP3, WMA, WAV, M4A, etc., as well as 4K video.
Features of BeeConverter Pro
	All popular video/audio formats are...
</description></item><item><title>Download Agisoft Metashape Professional 2.3.0 Build 21576</title><pubDate> Mon, 10 Nov 2025 16:28:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-agisoft-metashape-professional-1731.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-agisoft-metashape-professional-1731.html
</guid><description>
Agisoft Metashape (formerly PhotoScan) is a software product independently perform image processing and digital data creation, 3D space used in GIS applications, material cultural heritage and the production visual effects as well as the indirect measurement of the different subjects scale. Technical digital photography is deployed wisely is applied with the method of computer vision led to the system processor, smart auto, on the one hand, can be managed by a new person in the field of...
</description></item><item><title>Download AllmapSoft Google Satellite Maps Downloader 8.413</title><pubDate> Mon, 10 Nov 2025 16:28:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-google-satellite-maps-downloader-687.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-google-satellite-maps-downloader-687.html
</guid><description>
AllmapSoft Google Satellite Maps Downloader is software help download map images from google maps on computer for you to get the satellite images from google map. All the downloaded photos will be saved on disk. You can see the map is downloaded by viewer Or you can combine them into the map BMP, big. It supports proxy server. And you can easily get the longitude and latitude of each image tile small download.
You can use offline maps in GIS software such as Global Mapper, QGIS,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Chess Assistant Pro 25 v12.00 Build 1</title><pubDate> Mon, 10 Nov 2025 16:27:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chess-assistant-pro-1506.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chess-assistant-pro-1506.html
</guid><description>
Chess Assistant Pro is a unique tool to manage the game and database, chess, playing chess through the Internet, analyzing games or playing chess against the computer. Chess Assistant 19 includes the program, the martial play, the flag mode, the opening Encyclopedia, a system powerful search mode, Tree unique database of about 7.077.000 games in total.
Chess Assistant Pro - help play chess
Houdini 6 PRO, chess program strongest in the world, continue to surge the impression created by...
</description></item><item><title>Download Softwarenetz Text editor 1.38</title><pubDate> Mon, 10 Nov 2025 16:26:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-softwarenetz-text-editor-6692.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-softwarenetz-text-editor-6692.html
</guid><description>
Softwarenetz Text editor is a simple and friendly program with users for your private and business letters. Create your personal writing or work in the text editor.
Features of Softwarenetz Text editor
	Insert an image and image into your text. The text editor supports all the popular formats (jpg, gif, bmp, png).
	Includes the interactive description in five languages, which will test your documents to find the correct errors.
	The catalog will arrange all the documents into...
</description></item><item><title>Download Evaer for Teams 1.25.11.9</title><pubDate> Mon, 10 Nov 2025 16:26:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-evaer-for-teams-7459.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-evaer-for-teams-7459.html
</guid><description>
Evaer for Teams is a software that provides a powerful Microsoft Teams recording solution to help you record and archive Teams calls and meetings. Evaer for Teams is designed to work with the Microsoft Teams desktop application. This is the best recording software for Microsoft Teams.
Evaer directly records and stores it on your hard drive. You can freely dispose of the recorded video without worrying about the security of the recorded file. Evaer captures Team original video data for...
</description></item><item><title>Download AllMapSoft Universal Maps Downloader 10.231</title><pubDate> Mon, 10 Nov 2025 16:25:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-universal-maps-downloader-736.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-universal-maps-downloader-736.html
</guid><description>
AllMapSoft Universal Maps Downloader is software download map images on the computer for offline viewing support many types such as Google Maps, Yahoo maps, Bing maps, OpenStreet Maps, Yandex Maps, Ovi Maps, MapQuest Maps. All the downloaded photos will be saved on disk. You can view downloaded maps by Maps Viewer Or you can combine them into one big bmp, or jpg file tif by Maps Combiner, and also you can export all the tiles into a database format MBTiles.
AllMapSoft Universal Maps...
</description></item></channel></rss>