<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 10:16:22 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 10:16:22 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download OneCommander Pro 3.99.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 21 Aug 2025 20:58:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-one-commander-4232.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-one-commander-4232.html
</guid><description>
One Commander is a file manager for Microsoft Windows with function improved user interface and navigation experience, system file and manipulating the files. Utilities use the tree view to sort the folder, subfolders, and files your, make sure that the current location of you always clear. It supports multiple tabs, allowing you to easily switch between them and access the folder you need.
One Commander - a filemanager for Windows
Depending on the format of the files, some files can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Alfa eBooks Manager Pro / Web 9.3.5.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 21 Aug 2025 20:58:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-alfa-ebooks-manager-web-981.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-alfa-ebooks-manager-web-981.html
</guid><description>
Alfa eBooks Manager Web is a program that enables to arrange the electronic books and paper of you in a single electronic library. eBooks Manager Website will host the electronic books and print in an electronic library. Group, filter and sort books by multiple parameters. Find any book in just a second by title, author or ISBN.
Alfa eBooks Manager Web - ebook library
Alfa eBooks Manager Web provides comprehensive set of fields, including the author, category, publisher, series, ISBN,...
</description></item><item><title>Download WYSIWYG Web Builder 20.2.4</title><pubDate> Thu, 21 Aug 2025 20:57:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wysiwyg-web-builder-177.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wysiwyg-web-builder-177.html
</guid><description>
WYSIWYG Web Builder : The construction of the website from scratch using HTML code isn't a pleasant process, even when you know what you are doing. The website can be built using WYSIWYG Web Builder with using the element similar to the package published on the desktop: text and images placed in frames and tables on the page, so very little surprised when most of the efforts to make the web become a experience user-friendly than. the controls do you use to build your pages.
WYSIWYG Web...
</description></item><item><title>Download Room Arranger 10.2.0.731</title><pubDate> Thu, 21 Aug 2025 20:56:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-room-arranger-3779.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-room-arranger-3779.html
</guid><description>
Room Arranger is a 3D application lets you easily plan for the room, office or his apartment just a few mouse clicks. The application comes with a simple interface will significantly simplify your work. You can draw many kinds of objects and items to create furniture of your own. This app also includes a library of object rich.
Software Room Arranger enables you to view your project in 3D form. You can also upload the 3D scene interact on your blog or your website. The application uses...
</description></item><item><title>Download Capture One Pro 16.6.5.3072 + Enterprise</title><pubDate> Thu, 21 Aug 2025 20:56:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capture-one-pro-624.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capture-one-pro-624.html
</guid><description>
Capture One Pro is the software solution complete photo editing. With powerful tools to organize, color grading, editing grades, and more, you have full control over the images and process his work. Capture One has been developed with quality images and easy to use. Every tool is designed to give you full control over all aspects of the process editing - preserve, restore and optimize all information from the file RAW of you. Full the tool provides the ability to expand to always achieve...
</description></item><item><title>Download Steinberg VST Live Pro 2.2.60</title><pubDate> Thu, 21 Aug 2025 20:55:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-steinberg-vst-live-pro-7557.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-steinberg-vst-live-pro-7557.html
</guid><description>
Steinberg VST Live Pro is a unique, stable software solution designed for musicians who want to deliver a great performance, including sound, light and video, wherever they are. VST Live comes with a wide range of virtual instruments, sync features for music, text and chord symbols showing on other devices, video, Cubase import, MIDI tracks for lighting control Live DMX and more.
Features of Steinberg VST Live Pro
The core of your live production.
Has all the functionality needed to...
</description></item><item><title>Download O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro 21.1.184 / Server</title><pubDate> Thu, 21 Aug 2025 20:54:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-diskimage-pro-218.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-diskimage-pro-218.html
</guid><description>
O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro is software backup data comprehensive and effective is provided to protect the data of the computer system, it creates images for individual drives or the entire system that still does not affect your system.
O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro allows the user to backup the entire computer or drive, the and files whenever you want even while the computer is being used. Or can use O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro to create a copy chinh sac of computer disk drives, can be used instead of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Folder Player Pro 5.35 build 352</title><pubDate> Thu, 21 Aug 2025 20:29:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-folder-player-pro-8330.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-folder-player-pro-8330.html
</guid><description>
Folder Player Pro is a mobile music player application available for Android devices. It allows users to play and organize their music files by folders, instead of just by artist or album. This app is perfect for users who have a lot of music files on their device and want to listen to them in a more organized way.
Features of Folder Player Pro APK
	Ability to play music files by folder, making it easy to find and listen to specific songs or albums
	Supports many audio file formats,...
</description></item><item><title>Download TickTick:To Do List &amp;amp; Calendar 7.6.7.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 21 Aug 2025 20:29:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ticktick-to-do-list-tasks-8702.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ticktick-to-do-list-tasks-8702.html
</guid><description>
TickTick is a simple and effective task management and to-do list application that helps you schedule, manage time, remind about deadlines and organize your life at work, at home. home and everywhere else. TickTick is here to help you make the most of your day and get things done (gtd). Whether there's an idea you want to capture, a personal goal to achieve, a job to complete, or collaborating with other colleagues, even create a shopping list (with the help of a list creator). book)....
</description></item><item><title>Download CamScanner- scanner, PDF maker 6.94.0.2508080000</title><pubDate> Thu, 21 Aug 2025 20:29:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-camscanner-pdf-scanner-app-9065.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-camscanner-pdf-scanner-app-9065.html
</guid><description>
CamScanner is the best scanning app that will turn your phone into a PDF scanner. CamScanner helps you scan, store, sync, and collaborate on a variety of content across smartphones, iPads, tablets, and computers. The app uses the device's camera to take high-quality photos of documents, which are then processed and converted into PDF files that can be stored and shared electronically.
CamScanner is designed to be an easy-to-use and flexible tool for scanning and managing documents on...
</description></item><item><title>Download AI Video Editor - VideoShow AI 11.0.0.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 21 Aug 2025 20:28:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-video-editor-maker-videoshow-8149.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-video-editor-maker-videoshow-8149.html
</guid><description>
Video Editor &amp;amp; Maker VideoShow is a video editing and movie making app that allows you to create and edit videos on your mobile device. With this movie maker, creating memes, creating videos or slideshows with photos, images, music, stickers and sound effects is easy and fun. Providing the latest Halloween materials! Young filmmakers can even beautify videos with text, FX, effects, GIFs, trendy filters, transitions or live dubbing in a creative and personalized way.
All-in-one...
</description></item><item><title>Download Digital Compass 16.5 Build 157</title><pubDate> Thu, 21 Aug 2025 20:27:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-digital-compass-13590.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-digital-compass-13590.html
</guid><description>
This app is a smart compass with high accuracy and a great tool for outdoor activities. This compass app allows you to easily determine the direction you are facing. This app is built using the device's gyroscope, accelerometer, magnetometer, gravity sensor to determine the direction. Make sure your device has an accelerometer and magnetometer sensor or it will not work.
Features
	Show current location (longitude, latitude, address)
	Show altitude
	Show magnetic field strength
	Show...
</description></item><item><title>Download AI Keyboard: Chatbot, Grammar v144</title><pubDate> Thu, 21 Aug 2025 20:27:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ai-keyboard-chatbot-grammar-13363.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ai-keyboard-chatbot-grammar-13363.html
</guid><description>
AI Keyboard: Chatbot, Grammar is a revolutionary app designed to transform your typing experience with AI keyboard technology and GPT API, powered by GPT GPT-4o mini and GPT-4o. Designed to be used seamlessly across multiple writing applications, it provides powerful grammar checking support for multiple languages. Rewrite complete sentences or adapt to different tones depending on the context of your message.
Check grammar, complete sentences, and explain each error for a deeper...
</description></item><item><title>Download Folder in Folder 1.4.3</title><pubDate> Thu, 21 Aug 2025 20:26:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-folder-in-folder-11528.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-folder-in-folder-11528.html
</guid><description>
Having trouble organizing your apps into folders? Here is the solution! With this app, you can now organize your apps into subfolders. Just create a folder and add it to your home screen.
Main features
	Create a folder with applications or subfolders.
	Auto folder (predefined folder, cannot be edited).
	Add various widgets for folders to your home.
</description></item><item><title>Download Speak &amp;amp; Learn English: Learna 2.1.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 21 Aug 2025 20:26:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-speak-learn-english-learna-13414.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-speak-learn-english-learna-13414.html
</guid><description>
This is the complete solution to help you master English! Learn English with grammar, speaking, reading, pronunciation and vocabulary exercises designed to improve your proficiency in every aspect of the language.
With Learna AI, you can speak English confidently and effectively through interactive conversations. Our app takes your language learning journey beyond traditional methods. Whether you are a beginner or an advanced learner, Learna AI is here to help you learn and speak...
</description></item><item><title>Download Maple Calculator: Math Solver 4.2.7</title><pubDate> Thu, 21 Aug 2025 20:26:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-maple-calculator-math-solver-13489.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-maple-calculator-math-solver-13489.html
</guid><description>
Powered by Maple, the world's most powerful math engine, this all-in-one calculator solves math problems, creates 2-D and 3-D visualizations, and provides step-by-step solutions to a wide variety of math homework problems encountered in high school and college.
This app is a graphing calculator, scientific calculator, algebra calculator, integral calculator, and calculator integration all rolled into one! Take a picture of your problem with your phone's camera or type it in through the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Deezer Music for Android TV 4.3.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 21 Aug 2025 20:26:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-deezer-for-android-tv-11212.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-deezer-for-android-tv-11212.html
</guid><description>
Music lover? Stream and listen to top radio hits or discover new songs with Deezer music player on your Android TV. Access the best music, hear your favorite live tunes and more when you turn your TV into a jukebox. Are you looking to discover new music? Browse channels with your remote or listen to Deezer Flow.
	Access to millions of songs
	Stream - the best music experience around
	Stream songs, artists, radio hits and Audio Channels
	Listen to playlists curated by top music...
</description></item><item><title>Download AVG Cleaner - Storage Cleaner 25.15.0 build 800011220</title><pubDate> Thu, 21 Aug 2025 20:25:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-avg-cleaner-storage-cleaner-9005.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-avg-cleaner-storage-cleaner-9005.html
</guid><description>
AVG Cleaner is a memory cleaning and optimization application developed by AVG Technologies. It is designed to help users reclaim space on their Android devices by deleting unnecessary files and optimizing system performance.
The app can scan your device for junk files, including temporary files, cache files, and outdated APK files, and help you delete them safely. Additionally, AVG Cleaner can analyze your device's battery consumption and provide suggestions on how to improve your...
</description></item><item><title>Download Smart Transfer: Copy My Data 2.9.6</title><pubDate> Thu, 21 Aug 2025 20:25:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-smart-transfer-copy-my-data-13691.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-smart-transfer-copy-my-data-13691.html
</guid><description>
Looking for an easier way to move your files? Smart Switch offers a seamless and efficient solution. You can easily transfer contacts, photos, videos, and more with just a few taps. Our user-friendly interface and secure data transfer ensure a smooth transition.
File transfer is often necessary when moving data from an old mobile device to a new one. If you just bought a new phone and want to keep all your files, use our Smart Switch app!
Key Features:
	Easy Data Transfer: Easily...
</description></item><item><title>Download Barbell Workout at Home &amp;amp; Gym 4.10</title><pubDate> Thu, 21 Aug 2025 20:24:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-barbell-home-workout-8674.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-barbell-home-workout-8674.html
</guid><description>
Build muscle and increase strength with weight training.
Download the app and get everything you need
	Pre-set training plan
	Illustration of exercises for each muscle group
	Voice feedback
	Detailed history
	Beautiful, well-proportioned body and toned muscles
Tips
	Choose a weight that you feel comfortable with.
	Only increase the weight when you start to feel like the set is no longer challenging you.
</description></item><item><title>Download Weather &amp;amp; Radar USA - Pro 2025.17</title><pubDate> Thu, 21 Aug 2025 20:24:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-weather-radar-usa-pro-8391.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-weather-radar-usa-pro-8391.html
</guid><description>
Weather &amp;amp; Radar USA is a mobile application that provides users with real-time weather information and forecasts for locations in the United States. The app includes many features such as current weather conditions, hourly and daily forecasts, radar and satellite images, and severe weather alerts. It also includes many customizable settings, such as the ability to set up multiple locations and receive notifications about specific weather conditions.
Features of Weather &amp;amp; Radar...
</description></item><item><title>Download Penly: Digital Planner &amp;amp; Notes 1.23.8</title><pubDate> Thu, 21 Aug 2025 20:24:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-penly-digital-planner-notes-13595.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-penly-digital-planner-notes-13595.html
</guid><description>
Unleash your creativity and increase your productivity with Penly — the all-in-one digital planner, journal, and note-taking app. Includes reusable, undated digital planners with hyperlinked monthly, weekly, and daily pages for easy navigation. Users can write their own dates and choose from a variety of planner styles and colors (rainbow pink or minimalist black).
Features
	Simple, intuitive interface
	Smooth handwriting and smart eraser
	Text, image, and shape tools
	Create...
</description></item><item><title>Download Face Swap - AI Photo Editor 1.5.4_19082025</title><pubDate> Thu, 21 Aug 2025 20:24:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-face-swap-ai-photo-editor-13079.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-face-swap-ai-photo-editor-13079.html
</guid><description>
Turn your imagination into reality with Face Swap - AI Photo Editor, the ultimate app for swapping faces in photos and videos. Whether you want to explore different looks, step into another era, or just have fun with unique face transformations, this app is your gateway to a world of endless possibilities. If you are looking for the best face swap video editing app, you have come to the right place!
Face Swap with Photos
Explore a huge collection of categories, from vintage fashion to...
</description></item><item><title>Download SnapTube for Android 7.45.0.74550110</title><pubDate> Thu, 21 Aug 2025 20:23:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-snaptube-youtube-downloader-hd-video-8351.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-snaptube-youtube-downloader-hd-video-8351.html
</guid><description>
SnapTube is a mobile application that allows users to download videos from various platforms, such as YouTube, Vimeo, and Dailymotion. It provides video resolution in multiple formats 144p, 720p, 1080p HD, 2K HD, 4K HD and audio formats MP3 and M4A. With Snaptube, users can search for content across all their platforms without using multiple apps.
Features of SnapTube for Android
Download in multiple resolutions
	MP4 videos are available in resolutions: choose small 360 pixels or...
</description></item><item><title>Download SpeedChecker Speed Test 2.8.3</title><pubDate> Thu, 21 Aug 2025 20:23:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-speedchecker-speed-test-8162.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-speedchecker-speed-test-8162.html
</guid><description>
SpeedChecker Speed ​​Test is a mobile application that allows users to test the speed of their internet connection. To use the app, users simply download and install the app on their Android device, open the app, and then follow the on-screen instructions to run a speed test. The application will measure the download and upload speed of the user's internet connection and display the results in a clear and easy-to-read format.
It can also provide additional information such as...
</description></item></channel></rss>