<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 11:33:29 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 11:33:29 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download PrivaZer Donors 4.0.110</title><pubDate> Sat, 30 Aug 2025 03:27:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-privazer-donors-198.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-privazer-donors-198.html
</guid><description>
PrivaZer Donors  cleans and removes filth traces from the system. Intensive cleaning of unwanted traces of what you've done, viewed, downloaded, deleted, etc. Take ownership of your security and freedom - Free up disk space. Keep your PC snug and secure !!!
With one click, PrivaZer can safely clean: Internet browsers, Index.dat, Cookies, Tor Cookies, Flash Cookies, Silverlight Cookies, DOM Storing, IndexedDB, AppCache Registry, RAM, Pagefile.sys and Hiberfil.sys files.  PrivaZer  can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Advanced Installer Architect 23.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 30 Aug 2025 03:26:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-installer-128.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-installer-128.html
</guid><description>
Advanced Installer is a Windows utility designed to help you build the package Windows Installer in a working environment clean and intuitive.
Although it has many parameters dedicated but the user interface is very simple and gives users the ability to create new projects by selecting the type, namely installer (for example: application Visual Studio or .NET, pack 32/64-bit mixture), Java , updates, support, mobile devices, and other things.
Advanced Installer - An environment for...
</description></item><item><title>Download CorelDRAW Graphics Suite 2025 v26.2.0.170</title><pubDate> Sat, 30 Aug 2025 03:26:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coreldraw-graphics-suites-01en-1429.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coreldraw-graphics-suites-01en-1429.html
</guid><description>
CorelDRAW Graphics Suite is the software graphic designers with all the tools vector illustration, layout, photo editing and professional design. This is a comprehensive tool to help you work faster, smarter and in more places with software graphics design superiority this.
You will achieve superior productivity with new features are high-calibre program in graphic design this versatile. You will appreciate the process work smoother with support for PDF / X-4 standard and industrial...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cockos REAPER 7.45</title><pubDate> Sat, 30 Aug 2025 03:25:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cockos-reaper-889.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cockos-reaper-889.html
</guid><description>
Cockos REAPER is a powerful software for for windows, chp lets you record, arrange, edit, and display the audio waveform multi-track. Cockos REAPER offers an extensive feature set includes many effects and a sample project. REAPER supports ASIO, Kernel Streaming, WaveOut, and DirectSound for playback and recording. It reads the files in WAV, OGG and MP3 files and records WAV files. You can arrange any number of items in any number of tracks and use plug-in sound processing (DirectX and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Monkeys Audio 11.40</title><pubDate> Sat, 30 Aug 2025 03:25:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-monkeys-audio-949.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-monkeys-audio-949.html
</guid><description>
Monkey\'s Audio is software that compresses digital music without loss of quality. Supports high quality WAV files and CD ripping. Monkeys Audio will compress .wav tracks into .ape files to reduce their size without loss of sound quality, decompress .ape, convert files, check file integrity and manage tags.
Unlike traditional methods like MP3 and OGG, which permanently remove quality to save space, Monkey\'s Audio only creates perfect copies with the same sound quality as the originals....
</description></item><item><title>Download MusConv Ultimate 4.10.411</title><pubDate> Sat, 30 Aug 2025 03:24:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html
</guid><description>
MusConv transfers playlists, albums, followed artists and liked songs across a variety of services – Spotify, Apple Music, Amazon Music, YouTube, YouTube Music, iTunes, Deezer, Tidal, SoundCloud, Pandora and more 125 music services!
Features of MusConv Ultimate
	Transfer playlists, albums, followed artists and liked tracks between over 125 music servicesManage playlists (Delete, Merge, Split, Copy...)
	More than 125 music services supported
	Access DAILY updated music charts on...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Premiere Pro 2025 v25.4.1.003 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Sat, 30 Aug 2025 03:24:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-premiere-pro-0021-1361.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-premiere-pro-0021-1361.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Premiere Pro is the leading video editing software for film, TV, and the web. Creative tools, integration with other Adobe apps and services, and the power of Adobe Sensei help you turn footage into finished movies and videos in a seamless workflow. It offers high-quality video editing at 4K x 4K resolution and beyond, with 32-bit color, in both RGB and YUV color spaces. Edit audio samples, support for VST audio plug-ins (plug-ins), and 5.1 surround sound tracks. The Premiere Pro...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Lightroom Classic 2025 v14.5.1 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Sat, 30 Aug 2025 03:23:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-photoshop-lightroom-classic-0004-734.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-photoshop-lightroom-classic-0004-734.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Photoshop Lightroom Classic is a desktop-optimized photo editing and organizing software. Lightroom Classic gives you powerful one-click tools and advanced controls to make your photos look great. Easily organize all your photos on your desktop and share them in a variety of ways.
In addition, Lightroom Classic has a powerful import process that allows users to preview images before importing. It supports many camera raw formats and includes a database system for efficient photo...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Media Encoder 2025 v25.4.1.001 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Sat, 30 Aug 2025 03:23:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-0010-adobe-media-encoder-1360.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-0010-adobe-media-encoder-1360.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Media Encoder 2024 is a professional audio and video converter that allows you to encode audio and video files into various distribution formats for applications different uses and audiences. Such video and audio formats are characterized by a high degree of compression. By downloading this program on taiwebs.com, you can export videos in formats supported by various devices, from DVD players and websites to mobile phones, portable media players and High Definition and High...
</description></item><item><title>Download LibreWolf 142.0.1-1</title><pubDate> Sat, 30 Aug 2025 03:22:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-librewolf-11967.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-librewolf-11967.html
</guid><description>
LibreWolf is a customized and independent version of Firefox, with the main goals being user privacy, security and freedom. LibreWolf is designed to provide increased protection against tracking and fingerprinting techniques and includes a number of security enhancements. This is achieved through our security and privacy oriented settings and patches. LibreWolf also aims to remove all telemetry, data collection and annoyances, as well as disable anti-free features like DRM.
LibreWolf...
</description></item><item><title>Download QueueExplorer Professional 5.0.54</title><pubDate> Sat, 30 Aug 2025 03:21:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-queueexplorer-professional-4823.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-queueexplorer-professional-4823.html
</guid><description>
QueueExplorer is a tool indispensable to work with queues and messages: understand and manage your system, find the error and fix it. Or you can use QueueExplorer to sort them by any field available. Because of the sort display the messages in another order with them will be handled, QueueExplorer more columns of Ms Ms # # so you can still see what is processed first.
The features of QueueExplorer
Move, copy or delete messages
	Messages can be handled the same as in process explorer,...
</description></item><item><title>Download HTML Compiler 2025.17</title><pubDate> Sat, 30 Aug 2025 03:21:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-html-compiler-2548.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-html-compiler-2548.html
</guid><description>
HTML Compiler is a program for Microsoft Windows (tm) allows you to put an entire HTML application (including HTML, CSS, JavaScript, images, etc.) into a Windows application independent can be executed like any other application window the application. HTML Compiler allows you to customize file real exam results by changing the icon of them and set some other options. For example, you can allow or not allow the ability to print the HTML pages, allow or disallow the text selection and many,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Flyby11 1.6.246</title><pubDate> Sat, 30 Aug 2025 03:16:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-flyby11-12467.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-flyby11-12467.html
</guid><description>
Flyby11 is a simple patcher that removes annoying restrictions that prevent you from installing Windows 11 (24H2) on unsupported hardware. Do you have an old PC? No TPM, Secure Boot or your processor is not supported? Flyby11 allows you to install Windows 11 24H2. There are no complicated steps. Just run the tool and you'll be running Windows 11 on your outdated machine in no time.
Technical overview
Flyby11 takes advantage of a feature of the Windows 11 setup process that uses the...
</description></item><item><title>Download PrivaZer 4.0.110</title><pubDate> Sat, 30 Aug 2025 03:16:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-privazer-66.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-privazer-66.html
</guid><description>
PrivaZer : the program performs the scan is very thorough not only includes the trace downloads like registration, Internet history, cookies, etc but also find the traces of potential in the field of free disk space of you. PrivaZer can permanently delete all traces by using the method of secure erase and also re-establish the sector disk free to 0 to remove all traces from the delete operation earlier. The process of scanning and cleaning the original can spend less time (20-30 minutes),...
</description></item><item><title>Download Flyoobe 1.6.246</title><pubDate> Sat, 30 Aug 2025 03:16:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oobelux-13956.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oobelux-13956.html
</guid><description>
Flyoobe was born out of the frustration many users felt with the Windows 11 setup experience. Whether it was the mandatory online account, the endless "Next, next, next..." screens, or the incomplete configuration options when you finally reached the desktop, the current setup lacked focus on what users really wanted.
Why choose Flyoobe?
	Simplifies the Windows 11 setup process right out of the box.
	Allows easy local account creation without need to hunt for hidden options.
	Includes...
</description></item><item><title>Download Manifold System 9.0.182</title><pubDate> Sat, 30 Aug 2025 03:15:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-manifold-system-7612.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-manifold-system-7612.html
</guid><description>
Manifold System is a geographic information system (GIS) software package developed by Manifold Software Limited, running on Microsoft Windows. Manifold System handles both vector and raster data, including spatial SQL, a built-in Internet Map Server (IMS) and other general GIS features.
Manifold System combines the visual and spatial power of GIS with the massive data science power of a built-in parallel DBMS: Easily do what GIS alone or DBMS tools transmit system can't do...
</description></item><item><title>Download Download Master 7.1.3.1735</title><pubDate> Fri, 29 Aug 2025 22:51:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-download-master-2005.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-download-master-2005.html
</guid><description>
Download Master is a software to improve the speed of file download from the Internet. Download Master replace the standard module of the load in the popular browsers such as Google Chrome, Firefox, Safari, Yandex.Browser, Opera, Internet Explorer etc. The software support download the file from the current position after the break of the network connection. Download Master lets you download videos or music from various services and have the priority function of the load. The software...
</description></item><item><title>Download Broot 1.48.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 29 Aug 2025 22:48:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-broot-8588.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-broot-8588.html
</guid><description>
Broot is an open source command line tool for browsing and navigating file systems. Broot provides a fast and intuitive way to navigate the file system with a tree-like interactive interface. It provides various features like searching for files, opening files and folders, copying file paths to clipboard, etc. It also supports customizing keys and color themes.
Features of Broot
	Fast file browsing: Lets you quickly navigate through large directory structures with a tree-like...
</description></item><item><title>Download Realtek High Definition Audio Drivers 6.0.9865.1 WHQL</title><pubDate> Fri, 29 Aug 2025 22:44:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-realtek-high-definition-audio-drivers-r282-32bit-64bit-442.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-realtek-high-definition-audio-drivers-r282-32bit-64bit-442.html
</guid><description>
Realtek High Definition Audio Drivers is audio drivers Realtek high-quality latest for windows operating systems, virgin audio controller is based on Realtek for Windows 7/8/8.1/10. When the window is integrated this Driver will make the sound of computer, laptop, your back up crisp, and the sound output for the highest quality possible.
Realtek High Definition Audio Drivers and devices are supported :
ALC880, ALC882, ALC883, ALC885, ALC888, ALC889, ALC861VC, ALC861VD, ALC892, ALC663,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare UniConverter 16.7.0.368</title><pubDate> Fri, 29 Aug 2025 22:44:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-uniconverter-4808.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-uniconverter-4808.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare UniConverter ( old name is Wondershare Video Converter Ultimate) which allows you to convert the video format. You can cut, splice, move, or add effects, subtitles a easy way. When using software you easily cut, splice, move, as well as add the effects, the subtitles to the video.... Or can switch the clods SD, HD video to any format popular for use with iPod (Classic, Nano and Touch), iPhone, Apple TV, Zune, PSP, Pocket PC...
Wondershare UniConverter helps convert formats...
</description></item><item><title>Download iTubeGo YouTube Downloader 10.8.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 29 Aug 2025 22:43:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-itubego-youtube-downloader-3681.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-itubego-youtube-downloader-3681.html
</guid><description>
iTubeGo YouTube Downloader  is the best way to download live video from 1000+ streaming sites. iTubeGo YouTube Downloader is a powerful download tool that allows you to save video and audio for free. The output format of high speed converter is high quality MP4, MP3. Fully compatible with iPhone, iPad, iTunes, iMovie, Android Phone and more.
iTubeGo YouTube Downloader - Solution for downloading high quality Youtube video 
Features of iTubeGo YouTube Downloader
	Download videos from...
</description></item><item><title>Download XYplorer 27.10.0700</title><pubDate> Fri, 29 Aug 2025 22:43:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-533.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-533.html
</guid><description>
XYplorer - File Manager for Windows is software that supports users to manage files on the Window quickly and to arrange the folder tidy. XYplorer features tabbed browsing, search, files, powerful, preview, flexible, highly customizable interface, dual frame options and a variety of unique ways to automate effective tasks often repeat. It's fast, lightweight, and portable.
Features XYplorer
	XYplorer is a file manager mobile. It does not require any settings, store all configuration...
</description></item><item><title>Download HFS: HTTP File Server (version 3) 0.57.14</title><pubDate> Fri, 29 Aug 2025 22:42:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hfs-http-file-server-11851.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hfs-http-file-server-11851.html
</guid><description>
HFS is a web file server to run on your computer. Share a folder or even a file thanks to the virtual file system. Essentially, this application turns your computer into an HTTP server and all users who want to connect and download files can do so by loading a simple website in their browser. HFS includes many configuration settings, so you can basically change each part of the application, starting with how users download files and ending with the appearance of the created website.
HFS...
</description></item><item><title>Download HE - Hardware Read and Write Utility 1.25.08.29</title><pubDate> Fri, 29 Aug 2025 22:42:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-he-hardware-read-and-write-utility-4287.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-he-hardware-read-and-write-utility-4287.html
</guid><description>
HE - Hardware Read and Write Utility is a powerful utility intended for hardware engineer, engineer, BIOS developer, driver, engineer, QA engineers, performance test engineers, diagnostic, etc., this utility access almost all the computer hardware, including PCI (PCI Express), index / Data, PCI, memory, index memory / Data space I / O, Index I / O / Data, Super I / O, DIMM SPD, CPU The registers MSR, screen, SMART, physical area of the hard drive identification data, ATA, dump tables ACPI...
</description></item><item><title>Download LibreOffice 25.8.1 / 7.6.7</title><pubDate> Fri, 29 Aug 2025 22:41:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-libreoffice-391.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-libreoffice-391.html
</guid><description>
LibreOffice is editor free for office similar to MS Office and OpenOffice includes word processor, spreadsheet application, presentation tool, database and design diagrams. Here is the app code open source, multi-feature, to offer users many tools to draft documents and handle the office documents efficiently.
The program can open or import most Microsoft Office formats popular, including .doc .ppt and .csv as well as many document formats other. LibreOffice is a tool to be more user...
</description></item></channel></rss>