<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 15:41:42 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 15:41:42 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download PDF-XChange Pro 10.7.0.398.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 18:27:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-xchange-editor-pro-3422.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-xchange-editor-pro-3422.html
</guid><description>
PDF-XChange Editor Pro is an application to manipulate and create PDF versatile, offering a wide range of useful features and powerful will help you to easily work with PDF files. This application is very flexible and allows you to easily create and modify PDF files. PDF-XChange Editor Pro provides a powerful set of tools and flexibility to work with PDF files, such as editor PDF-XChange new, utilities series, OFFice2PDF and the Addin tool Bar allows you to easily convert multiple file...
</description></item><item><title>Download Balabolka 2.15.0.902</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 18:26:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-balaboka-142.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-balaboka-142.html
</guid><description>
Balabolka is a text-to-speech (TTS) program. It can read text on your screen in a human-like voice. You can use Balabolka to listen to text from a variety of file formats, convert text to spoken audio files, and adjust speech parameters such as speed and pitch. It is often used for accessibility purposes, helping people who have difficulty reading or multi-tasking by listening to text while doing other activities. Balabolka supports multiple languages and uses different TTS engines,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Digiarty Aiarty Video Enhancer 2.5</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 18:26:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-digiarty-aiarty-video-enhancer-13862.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-digiarty-aiarty-video-enhancer-13862.html
</guid><description>
Digiarty Aiarty Video Enhancer is an AI-powered desktop software designed to upscale, denoise, deblur, and enhance videos up to 4K resolution with professional quality and speed. It uses advanced AI models optimized for GPU acceleration and Turbo mode, enabling real-time or near-real-time video processing, including frame interpolation for smooth motion up to 90fps, 120fps, or higher. This tool is effective in restoring low-resolution, old, blurry, jerky or underexposed footage,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Acrobat Pro DC 2025.001.20630 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 18:26:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-001en-adobe-acrobat-pro-458.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-001en-adobe-acrobat-pro-458.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Acrobat Pro DC is a comprehensive software that helps you create and edit the PDF&amp;nbsp;document, or create form, sign, protect PDF, connect, split PDF, export PDF to various formats. The Acrobat Pro DC is the latest version of Adobe with improvements in the interface with the polished ribbon bar and the ability to create and handle pdf files as well as its male versions.
The highlight of the Acrobat Pro DC is probably the ability to connect, store documents on the cloud, you can...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDF-XChange Editor Plus 10.7.0.398.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 18:24:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-xchange-editor-plus-645.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-xchange-editor-plus-645.html
</guid><description>
PDF-XChange Editor Plus is the editor, PDF viewer, compact, fast with many features, add-ons, professional. When using the PDF-XChange Editor Plus, easy for users to create, view, edit, annotate, OCR and digital signing PDF files, plus much more.
PDF-XChange Editor is a PDF editing full-featured. With the help of it, you can edit, fix, add, or delete text easily. Graphics can also be moved, resized or removed.
Features PDF-XChange Editor Plus
Edit documents
	Use a variety of editing...
</description></item><item><title>Download GOM Player Free 2.3.111 Build 5381</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 18:24:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gom-player-994.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gom-player-994.html
</guid><description>
GOM Player is a program to listen to music for free with the ability to play all format music and video now without the need to install additional codec. GOM Media Player brings all video codecs needed to play multiple video formats and various audio. Simple interface, light volume but powerful function is the factor which makes GOM Player famous in the music software.
GOM Media Player according to the reviews is considered the listen to music, watch video best. The user can control GOM...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Downloader 9.16</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 18:23:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html
</guid><description>
YTD Youtube Downloader is an application that reliable and intuitive, allowing you to quickly download YouTube videos and save them to your computer. You can also convert the media files to the format desired video or extract audio streams and save separately. YTD Youtube Downloader lets you save your favorite clips of yourself from Youtube, Facebook, Vimeo and Dailymotion to your desktop. The software supports URLS from many web site hosting, multimedia and allows you to download desired...
</description></item><item><title>Download Muziza YouTube Downloader Converter 8.12</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 18:22:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-muziza-youtube-downloader-converter-3972.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-muziza-youtube-downloader-converter-3972.html
</guid><description>
Muziza YouTube Downloader Converter is a tool to create conditions for an attractive interface and many features to help you to download video clips from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion, Instagram and other sites. Muziza YouTube Downloader Converter can also download the video UHD 8K, 5K, 4K, QHD 2K, HD 1080p and 720p from YouTube. The app allows you download only audio stream from YouTube and save as MP3. You don't need to download the entire video file.
Muziza YouTube Downloader...
</description></item><item><title>Download Clementine Music Player 1.4.1-50</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 18:22:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-clementine-4762.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-clementine-4762.html
</guid><description>
Clementine is a tools multi-platform software which allows you to listen to music from hard drive, library, audio CDS or the Internet, as well as manage it, edit the card and see the lyrics. Clementine is inspired by Amarok 1.4, focusing on a easy to use interface for searching and playing your music.
Clementine also allows you can view track information such as length, bit rate, sample rate, size, file type, number of times played and your ranking, as well as complete the card...
</description></item><item><title>Download TubeMate Downloader 5.22</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 18:22:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubemate-downloader-4250.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubemate-downloader-4250.html
</guid><description>
TubeMate Downloader is a smart application that lets you download any clip you want from the website hosting the main video and convert them in when download at or then. If you need a simple and effective tool to download videos, you can give it a try. With TubeMate Downloader, you can directly drag and drop video link from your browser into the drop-down box or application window to start downloading. You don't even need to copy and paste the video URL.
TubeMate Downloader - Support...
</description></item><item><title>Download Disk Sorter Ultimate 17.2.14 + Server + Pro</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 18:21:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-disk-sorter-ultimate-1464.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-disk-sorter-ultimate-1464.html
</guid><description>
Disk Sorter Ultimate is the utility classification file lightweight and simple helps people detect files on most types of drives, as well as manage them according to many different criteria to create more capacity on the disc. This app allows you to search through the 500,000 files, have storage capacity of 2TB. To start sorting, all what you have to do is select a directory, drive or server and click the button "Classification". You should know that you can search for the type specific...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tomabo MP4 Downloader Pro 5.7</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 18:21:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tomabo-mp4-downloader-pro-3602.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tomabo-mp4-downloader-pro-3602.html
</guid><description>
Tomabo MP4 Downloader Pro is the app designed exclusively for Windows users to help them download videos from the Internet. In addition, it also increase download speeds by up to 500%, or even more. Tomabo MP4 Downloader Pro, interface design, simple, well-organized, beautifully. Here, users can view a list of videos has download with gravatar, URL, quality, duration and size of them. Software allows download video series at the same time, at the same time, support create a list of clips...
</description></item><item><title>Download Exacoustics GHOST 1.1.8</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 18:20:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-exacoustics-ghost-13879.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-exacoustics-ghost-13879.html
</guid><description>
Exacoustics GHOST is a powerful and innovative synthesis plugin that uniquely combines Wavetable synthesis and Frequency Modulation (FM) synthesis into one integrated instrument. Released in August 2024 by Brisbane-based developer Exacoustics, the plugin quickly gained attention for its fresh approach and deep sound design capabilities.
Key Features:
	Hybrid Synthesis Engine: Combines the flexibility of wavetable oscillators with the complexity and richness of FM synthesis.
	Six...
</description></item><item><title>Download Vidiot 2.1.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 16:45:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vidiot-2987.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vidiot-2987.html
</guid><description>
Vidiot is a video editing program that allows users to quickly combine clips and movies family. It provides support for the video MOV, AVI and MP4, image GIF or JPG format, along with audio files WAV and MP3. The set task is done quickly and with minimal effort. For the user interface, although the main window has layout clear, but it seems complicated right from the start.
Vidiot - video editor easy to use
Program Vidiot has the ability to preview the clip in the media player...
</description></item><item><title>Download Total Commander 11.56 Final</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 16:40:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-total-commander-1148.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-total-commander-1148.html
</guid><description>
Total Commander is a file manager popular allows you to perform various actions with any files on the hard drive, work with archives, data, multimedia... Open top is Total Commander has a new user interface is updated with the button in Windows XP, new icons of files, store, button, drive, etc.
Total Commander - file Manager program
Besides, Total Commander has the ability to set different colors for the files and folder background. A editable mode and sync manually when you compare...
</description></item><item><title>Download Light Image Resizer 7.3.0.120</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 16:31:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-light-image-resizer-945.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-light-image-resizer-945.html
</guid><description>
Light Image Resizer or also known as VSO Image Resizer. This is a software support thumbnail resolution images or move images in your hard drive. Light Image Resizer helps people store photos and digital images on their PC and who want to resize, compress, convert, create copies, import or organize photos. Light Image Resizer is integrated into Windows Explorer, right-click on your pictures and start working on your photos.
Light Image Resizer - miniature high-resolution photos and sort...
</description></item><item><title>Download Obsidian 1.9.10</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 16:30:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-obsidian-10386.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-obsidian-10386.html
</guid><description>
Obsidian is a powerful knowledge base that operates on a local folder containing plain text Markdown files. It allows users to create internal links for notes and then display the connections as a graph. Additionally users can also organize and structure their thoughts and knowledge in a flexible, non-linear way.
Features of Obsidian
Personal notes:
	Links: Create connections between your notes.
	Graph: Visualize the relationships between your notes.
	Plugins: Build your ideal...
</description></item><item><title>Download iliumsoft eWallet 8.12.1.38089</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 16:30:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iliumsoft-ewallet-2569.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iliumsoft-ewallet-2569.html
</guid><description>
iliumsoft eWallet is a digital wallet in which you can store bank card details in a secure way, you only need to record the password from the account and website, then access them from anywhere in the world by personal computer or mobile phone, since developer interested in this If you read the official website, as the authors assure us, your information will be protected as much as possible, if anyone knows, then AES 256-bit will be used for this, you think it is safe? I don't judge, but...
</description></item><item><title>Download Intel Graphics Driver for Windows 10 / 11 32.0.101.6989</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 16:29:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intel-graphics-driver-for-windows-10-5954.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intel-graphics-driver-for-windows-10-5954.html
</guid><description>
Intel Graphics Driver for Windows 10 supports Intel ' s latest 8th-generation Core processor, introducing the Intel ® UHD graphics, with the ability to immerve in the top 4K UHD entertainment from your laptop for a maximum of 10 hours. Along with some security fixes, this driver also optimised the system's inactivity to reduce power consumption.
Look at the complete new interface of gameplay.intel.com, where you will find the proposed game settings for many of your favorite PC games....
</description></item><item><title>Download 7thShare Card Data Recovery 7.0.0.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 16:29:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-7thshare-card-data-recovery-1904.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-7thshare-card-data-recovery-1904.html
</guid><description>
7thShare Card Data Recovery is recovery tool SD Card, is designed to recover deleted, formatted, corrupted or lost photos, music files, documents, videos, etc from any memory card SD, CF, MMC, XD, SDHC and many more. 7thShare Card Data Recovery will recover photos, videos, documents, music, and more from SD memory Card, USB DRIVE, external hard DRIVE, digital camera, phone, music player recovery card the world's best efficient recovery documents deleted, lost, corrupted or formatted,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Android Studio 2025.1.2.12</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 16:29:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-android-studio-3890.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-android-studio-3890.html
</guid><description>
Android Studio is an Android development environment, completely new, provides many improvements and new features compared to Eclipse ADT. This software solution will is IDE the official Android when is finishing. This tool provides many tools and features such as editing, layout, rich set of tools to capture usability, compatibility version, performance and other issues, create a lot APK, build system based on Gradle flexibility, extended support for Google Services, integrated support...
</description></item><item><title>Download SweetScape 010 Editor 16.0.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 16:28:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sweetscape-010-editor-1492.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sweetscape-010-editor-1492.html
</guid><description>
SweetScape 010 Editor is a text editor and hex editor professional is designed to quickly and easily edit any file or drive on your computer. Combine the easy to use interface with a complete set of editing tools, 010 Editor is a valuable tool for anyone working with text files or binary files. One of the most powerful features of 010 Editor is the ability to analyze virtually any file binary how to change binary form.
Instead of browsing through a bunch of bytes hex as the hex editor...
</description></item><item><title>Download KiCad 9.0.4</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 16:28:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kicad-10384.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kicad-10384.html
</guid><description>
KiCad is a unique software product that allows you to open, create and develop electronic circuits for subsequent visualization of printed circuit board designs in interactive views . It allows you to develop complex circuit diagrams using an electronic components database and test signal integrity. It includes free applications, facilities, templates, and open libraries.
Using KiCad, users will be able to create truly professional printed circuit board layouts, beautifully designed...
</description></item><item><title>Download MiniMeters 1.0.15.1906</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 16:27:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minimeters-9410.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minimeters-9410.html
</guid><description>
MiniMeters is a simple standalone sound meter application for Windows. Monitor your System Audio*, Any Input, or insert the MiniMeter Server Plug-in (VST3/AU/CLAP) at the end of your main channel in the DAW of your choice. Customize the layout in a horizontal bar (perfect for above or below the audio engine of your choice) or pop out into modules to create custom layouts.
Features of MiniMeters
	6 modules to choose from to build your perfect metering setup: Spectrogram, Waveform,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Youtube Downloader HD 5.9.8.7</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 16:27:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-downloader-hd-3122.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-downloader-hd-3122.html
</guid><description>
Youtube Downloader HD is the best application to download and save Youtube videos. And it's completely free :) You can also convert the downloaded video into various formats easily. Youtube Downloader HD is the download at video free. Download at your videos easily and convert to AVI video format or into MP4 video format (compatible with iPad, iPhone). You can download high quality videos, high definition videos and Full HD from YouTube.
Youtube Downloader HD - Download Youtube videos...
</description></item></channel></rss>