<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 13:46:23 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 13:46:23 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Lansweeper 12.6.0.11</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 16:45:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lansweeper-2011.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lansweeper-2011.html
</guid><description>
Lansweeper is an application to manage IT assets and the scanning device is connected to the network. This software can scan and identify all network devices have workstation IP and Windows, Linux and Mac and indexing for them. Deep Scan Engine this software uses a set of protocols to detect and receive data from any device connected to the network. All data received can be stored in database SQL Compact or SQL Server.
Lansweeper - Scan system Internet
Software Lansweeper design open...
</description></item><item><title>Download 510k PEACH 1.0.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 16:44:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-510k-peach-14199.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-510k-peach-14199.html
</guid><description>
PEACH 510k is a next-generation polyphonic MIDI plugin designed to create rhythmically-bending, variable polyphonic arpeggiator sequences in digital audio workstations (DAWs). Unlike traditional arpeggiators that follow fixed up/down cycle patterns, PEACH allows each lane of the arpeggiator to run at an independent step length. This feature turns simple chords into complex, variable polyphonic patterns, full of rhythm and variation.
Key Features
Polymetric Lanes — Each lane (Gate,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Audio Damage AD055 Quanta 2 v2.1.4</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 16:44:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-audio-damage-ad055-quanta-9492.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-audio-damage-ad055-quanta-9492.html
</guid><description>
Quanta is a full-featured, easy-to-use detail synthesizer for AAX, AudioUnits, VST and VST3 servers. The user interface has been cleaned, modernized and offers clear and consistent controls with the new controls.
Features of Audio Damage AD055 Quanta
	Multi-format Template Loader
	Grain Engine
	Two virtual analog oscillators
	Noise Source
	Dual Multi-Mode Filter
	Flexible Envelope Generator (FEG) x 4
	Flexible Low Frequency Oscillator (FLFO) x 2
	Sampling and holding
	Modulation...
</description></item><item><title>Download TubeDownload Pro 6.31.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 16:43:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubedownload-pro-12035.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubedownload-pro-12035.html
</guid><description>
TubeDownload Pro is a professional Windows application for downloading your favorite videos from YouTube and hundreds of other video sites. TubeDownload Pro can increase download speed up to 500% or even more.
Features of TubeDownload Pro
	Download your favorite videos from YouTube and hundreds of other video sites.
	Increase download speed up to 500% or even more.
	Download 720p, 1080p, 2K, 4K and 8K HD videos from YouTube.
	Download entire playlists in just a few clicks.
	Download...
</description></item><item><title>Download Coolmuster PDF Password Remover 2.3.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 16:43:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-pdf-password-remover-4203.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-pdf-password-remover-4203.html
</guid><description>
Coolmuster PDF Password Remover is software password unlock PDF files protected Click people like to use password to protect copyright PDF of their work out of copying, printing, editing or stealing by others. So, sometimes you need to delete password from PDF to edit, copy, or share. Under this situation, Coolmuster PDF Password Remover can be an ideal assistant to you can remove password as you like.
Coolmuster PDF Password Remover - Remove password protected PDF
Forget the PDF...
</description></item><item><title>Download Algonaut Atlas 2.6.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 16:40:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-algonaut-atlas-7328.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-algonaut-atlas-7328.html
</guid><description>
Algonaut Atlas is an Artificial Intelligence-powered sampler that will change the way you find sounds and create rhythms. See all of your own templates curated in one place with style and feature-based maps. Find inspiration by creating an instant drum kit using your own templates. Speed ​​up your workflow by dragging and dropping into any application.
Features of Algonaut Atlas
	Export to MIDI and Audio Loops.
	Built for drums, fast and flexible. The best parts of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cairo Desktop 0.4.434</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 16:40:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cairo-desktop-12316.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cairo-desktop-12316.html
</guid><description>
Cairo is a desktop environment for Windows. Its goal is to develop desktop experiences that increase productivity and improve current technology standards. Focusing on stability, performance and productivity, Cairo aims to provide an interface that exceeds expectations and is easier to use.
Cairo features
	Taskbar: The Cairo taskbar keeps the desktop area intact for your wallpaper and apps. Additionally, windows are arranged the same way you choose to organize your program list,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft OneNote 16.0.19328.20190</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 16:39:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-onenote-4756.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-onenote-4756.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft OneNote is a note-taking app advanced, feature-rich aims to take information organization to a whole new level. Its purpose is to provide a laptop, digital reliable and reasonably likely alternative notes traditional paper and encourage collaboration of multiple users.
Microsoft OneNote comes with a variety of tools to collect and manage information easily. The main advantage of it is related to the ability to organize, allows users to collect text, multimedia content (images,...
</description></item><item><title>Download HE - Hardware Read and Write Utility 1.25.11.12</title><pubDate> Thu, 13 Nov 2025 16:39:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-he-hardware-read-and-write-utility-4287.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-he-hardware-read-and-write-utility-4287.html
</guid><description>
HE - Hardware Read and Write Utility is a powerful utility intended for hardware engineer, engineer, BIOS developer, driver, engineer, QA engineers, performance test engineers, diagnostic, etc., this utility access almost all the computer hardware, including PCI (PCI Express), index / Data, PCI, memory, index memory / Data space I / O, Index I / O / Data, Super I / O, DIMM SPD, CPU The registers MSR, screen, SMART, physical area of the hard drive identification data, ATA, dump tables ACPI...
</description></item><item><title>Download Office Tool Plus 10.28.29.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 18:03:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-tool-plus-3664.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-tool-plus-3664.html
</guid><description>
Office Tool Plus based on the Office deployment tool from Microsoft. You can customize configuration files installation and install Office of to install Office without Internet. Configure install Office, as well as customize the product C2R have installed, such as add and remove components, language packs, etc.
Office Tool Plus - Download and install Office
The characteristics of Office Tool Plus
	1. Configure install Office, as well as customize the product C2R have installed, such...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft Activation Scripts 3.8</title><pubDate> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 18:01:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-activation-scripts-5390.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-activation-scripts-5390.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft Activation Scripts is an open source Windows and Office activation tool that features online HWID, Ohook, KMS38 and KMS activation methods, along with advanced troubleshooting functionality.
Activation methods
			Trigger type
			Supported products
			Activation time
			HWID
			Windows 10-11
			Permanent
			Ohook
			Office
			Permanent
			KMS38
			Windows 10-11, Server
			Until 2038
			Online KMS
			Windows / Office
			180 days (with...
</description></item><item><title>Download PIDKey Lite 1.64.4 b51</title><pubDate> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 18:00:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pidkey-lite-2693.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pidkey-lite-2693.html
</guid><description>
PIDKey Lite is a program intended to show the renovation and preservation in the database of the product information to check "validity" of the key Microsoft from the famous program we or is Ratiborus and VAMT. Program PIDKey LiteIt is the successor of the PIDKey. and I got out of it the idea the best program (allows you To add new keyboard with two methods additional mode key).
The program has a number of configuration integration, but you can also create custom profiles by themselves....
</description></item><item><title>Download GoodSync Enterprise 12.9.15.5</title><pubDate> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 18:00:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-goodsync-enterprise-163.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-goodsync-enterprise-163.html
</guid><description>
GoodSync Enterprise is a software that saves files and files easily and is reliable. It automatically analyts, synchronize and backup your email, family photos, contacts, MP3, financial documentation and other important files-between desktop computers, laptops, servers, external drives and Windows Mobile devices as well as remotely via FTP , SFTP, WebDAV and more. The GoodSync synchronized software combines bulletproof reliability with an extremely easy interface to compare, synchronize...
</description></item><item><title>Download IObit Software Updater Pro 8.2.0.11</title><pubDate> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 17:59:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iobit-software-updater-pro-2234.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iobit-software-updater-pro-2234.html
</guid><description>
IObit Software Updater Pro software is useful for those who don't download apps for Windows 10 from the store company, virtually all software was installed will not be updated automatically. The web browser will naturally inform you about a new version, software security of you will also be automatically updated, just like Windows, but almost all other apps will quietly operate in the normal mode and you will never know that the update was available, if you can't run itself.
IObit...
</description></item><item><title>Download Rhinoceros 8.25.25314.11001</title><pubDate> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 17:58:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rhinoceros-179.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rhinoceros-179.html
</guid><description>
Rhinoceros is design software 3D easy to learn, easy to use and has range of application in various industries. Rhinoceros (or Rhino, Rhino3D) is a graphics software CAD and 3D developed by Robert McNeel &amp;amp; Associates, a private company established in the year 1980. Rhinoceros is developed according to the algorithm NURBS mathematical model, algorithm, focus on the correct presentation of curves and surfaces mathematics in computer graphics (in contrast to the application polygon...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Master Collection 2025 v10</title><pubDate> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 17:58:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-master-collection-0001-8036.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-master-collection-0001-8036.html
</guid><description>
You may already know that Adobe Master Collection 2025 does not officially exist and Adobe has never released it. But now that it's here, we also need to give thanks to m0nkrus and PainteR (who put a lot of effort into creating it). Adobe Master Collection 2025 is a collection of applications from the Creative Cloud 2025 line, united by a multilingual installer with the ability to choose the installation path and interface language of installed programs. In terms of functionality,...
</description></item><item><title>Download UpdatePack7R2 25.11.11</title><pubDate> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 17:56:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-updatepack7r2-6614.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-updatepack7r2-6614.html
</guid><description>
UpdatePack7R2 is software that allows you to update a working system and integrate software updates in the distribution. Can be installed on any version of Windows 7 and Server 2008 R2, any digit and any language. Includes updates for all versions of Internet Explorer, all critical, recommended, and security updates.
How to use UpdatePack7R2 software:
	The system must have at least 10 GB of free space on the hard drive and preferably no less than 1 GB of free RAM.
	Key / Reboot to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Viber for PC 26.6.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 17:55:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-viber-2406.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-viber-2406.html
</guid><description>
Viber is a software of instant messaging, based on VoIP protocols, multi-platform due to the Viber Media development for smart phones used to send sms and make calls over the internet. Along with text messaging, users can exchange images, video and audio.
Viber - software news message, chat online
This is a program that is quite popular is mainly designed for mobile phones, but now we are talking about the version for Windows, so immediately. It will allow you to send messages to other...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Downloader 9.18.3</title><pubDate> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 17:55:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html
</guid><description>
YTD Youtube Downloader is an application that reliable and intuitive, allowing you to quickly download YouTube videos and save them to your computer. You can also convert the media files to the format desired video or extract audio streams and save separately. YTD Youtube Downloader lets you save your favorite clips of yourself from Youtube, Facebook, Vimeo and Dailymotion to your desktop. The software supports URLS from many web site hosting, multimedia and allows you to download desired...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Creative Master Collection 2025-2026 v10.11.2025 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 17:54:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-001-adobe-creative-cloud-collection-8035.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-001-adobe-creative-cloud-collection-8035.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Creative Cloud Collection 2023 - 2025 is a collection of applications from the Creative Cloud 2023, 2024, 2025 family and several firmware versions combined by a single installer with path selection settings and languages of installed programs. In terms of functionality, everything is very similar to the well-proven Adobe Master Collection CS6 in the past. Only here has the installer interface changed, the current package includes significantly more programs than the Creative Suite...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDF Architect Pro + OCR 9.1.77.23081</title><pubDate> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 17:51:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-architect-pro-ocr-6381.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-architect-pro-ocr-6381.html
</guid><description>
PDF Architect  is professional software that provides PDF creation and editing features according to your needs. Our PDF editor keeps you up to date with forward-looking features. Take complete control of your PDF files with our PDF editor. Modify text, images, and pages, and convert PDF to Word and Excel and more.
It has many advanced options and features for customizing, securing, and collaborating PDF files. All necessary features are included in this for better user experience. This...
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 7.4.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 17:51:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-11-7760.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-11-7760.html
</guid><description>
TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 is a program that allows users to discover hidden settings in Windows 11. This application is specially designed for Windows 11, groups many registry settings and distribute them from the easy and secure user interface. With TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 you can move the Windows taskbar to the top and resize the taskbar by editing the registry value. With any application that modifies the registry, we recommend that you have a backup copy...
</description></item><item><title>Download UltraSearch Professional 4.8.5.1185</title><pubDate> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 17:51:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ultrasearch-professional-10252.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ultrasearch-professional-10252.html
</guid><description>
UltraSearch Professional is the professional version that helps you find your files and documents on all connected hard drives and network drives. Search by file type, document content, or file properties. Take back your valuable time and let UltraSearch do the searching for you.
UltraSearch Professional does not maintain an index stored on your hard disk. It achieves speed by working directly on the Master File Table (MFT) of NTFS partitions. So it even identifies NTFS hardlinks. That...
</description></item><item><title>Download Moho Pro 14.4 Build 20251110</title><pubDate> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 17:50:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-smith-micro-moho-pro-4596.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-smith-micro-moho-pro-4596.html
</guid><description>
Smith Micro Moho Pro is film program of Anime Studio. Moho helps turn ideas and rich imagination of the film as lively as life. Moho is there 2 version is Moho Debut and Moho Pro, offers users tools cartoon from beginning to end. With display technology in 2D, beautifully combined with the custom made film base, anyone can learn to make films with Moho Animation Software.
Modern interface
With an intuitive interface and 1 number of powerful features such as Smart Bones Smart Warp,...
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 7.4.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 12 Nov 2025 17:50:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-10-7759.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-10-7759.html
</guid><description>
TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 is a utility that allows users to discover hidden settings in Windows 10. This application is specially designed for Windows 10, groups many registry settings and provide them from an easy and secure user interface. With TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 you can move the Windows taskbar to the top and resize the taskbar by editing the registry value. With any application that modifies the registry, we recommend that you have a backup copy to...
</description></item></channel></rss>