<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 03:33:22 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 03:33:22 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download MemoryCleaner 1.8.7</title><pubDate> Tue, 12 Aug 2025 01:13:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-memorycleaner-12469.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-memorycleaner-12469.html
</guid><description>
MemoryCleaner is a tool to free up memory on your computer. This is a free app with a simple user interface that makes it easy for users of all skill levels to use. MemoryCleaner uses many functions built into Windows to free up memory without affecting your system. You can also access Memory Cleaner's functions right from the system tray without having to open the program. The cleaning processes are silent and the only time you see a warning is to briefly display the amount of RAM...
</description></item><item><title>Download Samsung SSD Magician Tool 8.3.2.850</title><pubDate> Tue, 12 Aug 2025 01:12:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-samsung-ssd-magician-tool-4010.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-samsung-ssd-magician-tool-4010.html
</guid><description>
Samsung SSD Magician Tool is a software aid you with easy maintenance and use of the product Samsung SSD is connected to desktop or laptop. In addition to providing information about system and SSD product of users, Samsung SSD Magician also supports advanced features, such as management performance SSD, benchmarking for optimum performance, update new firmware, etc. Samsung SSD Magician Tool is a set of tools to be considered carefully, which helps users further improve performance of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Advanced SystemCare Pro Portable 18.4.0.247</title><pubDate> Tue, 12 Aug 2025 01:11:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-systemcare-pro-portable-8964.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-systemcare-pro-portable-8964.html
</guid><description>
Advanced SystemCare Pro Portable (a portable version) is system optimization and maintenance software developed by IObit. It is designed to help users improve the performance and speed of their Windows computers by cleaning junk files, optimizing system settings, and fixing various system errors.
It specializes in ONE-Click solutions to detect, clean, repair, speed up and ultimately protect PC. With new system technology, Advanced SystemCare Pro lets you run your computer faster....
</description></item><item><title>Download CyberLink PerfectCam Premium 2.3.7732.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 12 Aug 2025 01:07:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-perfectcam-premium-375.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-perfectcam-premium-375.html
</guid><description>
CyberLink PerfectCam Premium is software that supports the work of makeup face on, webcam, from the makeup artist professional.  PerfectCam will help you looks perfect on her webcam enjoy brightness, contrast and exposure, video ideal for online meetings and even applied to smooth the skin.
PerfectCam use technology face recognition is patented, the library installed virtual makeover instant of PerfectCam brings you looks professional and prepared whenever you need.
Features CyberLink...
</description></item><item><title>Download Plagius Professional 2.9.9</title><pubDate> Tue, 12 Aug 2025 01:06:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-plagius-professional-5717.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-plagius-professional-5717.html
</guid><description>
Plagius Professional is a tool capable of analyzing documents and notifying the user in case of plagiarism detection. The program automatically generates reports after checking documents or web pages and supports rendering reports into HTML files for later analysis. Plagius Professional supports several file formats, such as PDF, TXT, RTF, HTML, HTM, ODT, SXW, DOCX or DOC, but for the last two formats you need to have Microsoft Word installed on your PC (otherwise, they can't be...
</description></item><item><title>Download Monkeys Audio 11.34</title><pubDate> Tue, 12 Aug 2025 01:06:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-monkeys-audio-949.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-monkeys-audio-949.html
</guid><description>
Monkey\'s Audio is software that compresses digital music without loss of quality. Supports high quality WAV files and CD ripping. Monkeys Audio will compress .wav tracks into .ape files to reduce their size without loss of sound quality, decompress .ape, convert files, check file integrity and manage tags.
Unlike traditional methods like MP3 and OGG, which permanently remove quality to save space, Monkey\'s Audio only creates perfect copies with the same sound quality as the originals....
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Acrobat Reader DC 2025.001.20623</title><pubDate> Tue, 12 Aug 2025 01:06:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-acrobat-reader-3707.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-acrobat-reader-3707.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Acrobat Reader DC is a system of application software and Web services developed by Adobe Systems to view, create, manipulate, print and manage PDF files. With Adobe Acrobat Reader DC, you can create, export, edit, and track PDF files from anywhere - and maintain connection with the recent set of files on all your devices.
Adobe Acrobat Reader current DC is connected with Adobe Document Cloud - help working on the computers and mobile devices becomes easier than ever before. This is...
</description></item><item><title>Download All Remixes 1.5.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 12 Aug 2025 01:04:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-all-remixes-7512.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-all-remixes-7512.html
</guid><description>
All Remixes is software to discover all the remixes of your favorite artists and songs! Listen to every remix your favorite artist has ever made! Filter remixes by song title or artist in one click.
Features of All Remixes
	Discover all remixes of your favorite artists and songs!
	Listen to every remix your favorite artist has ever done!
	Filter remixes by song title or artist in one click.
	Find 100s of remixes quickly.
	Discover all the missing mixes from your music collection.
	Get...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinTools.one Professional / Home 25.8.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 12 Aug 2025 01:03:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wintoolsone-10808.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wintoolsone-10808.html
</guid><description>
WinTools.one is a program designed to help both regular and advanced users as well as computer engineers fine-tune the MS Windows operating system. It allows you to increase the performance of the operating system, maintain its performance at a high level, fix operating system errors, free up space on the computer's hard drive and control the operation of installed programs. In addition, the program allows you to store and protect your secret and confidential information, as well as work...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wise Duplicate Finder Pro Portable 2.1.8.69</title><pubDate> Tue, 12 Aug 2025 01:03:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wise-duplicate-finder-pro-portable-3491.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wise-duplicate-finder-pro-portable-3491.html
</guid><description>
Wise Duplicate Finder Pro Portable is the mobile version allows you to easily use the software full features. Wise Duplicate Finder Pro Portable can help you locate and remove unneeded duplicates, freeing up your disk space. You can select any type of duplicate how to manage with Wise Duplicate Finder , for example, find duplicate image, find duplicate video search, duplicate material, etc.
Wise Duplicate Finder Pro Portable - remove duplicate files
Wise Duplicate Finder Pro Portable...
</description></item><item><title>Download RizomUV Real &amp;amp; Virtual Space 2025.0.63</title><pubDate> Tue, 12 Aug 2025 01:03:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rizomuv-real-virtual-space-1537.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rizomuv-real-virtual-space-1537.html
</guid><description>
RizomUV Real &amp;amp; Virtual Space known as Unold3D ago, is the perfect software to design a package or build texture laser. RizomUV Real Space includes all the features of RizomUV Virtual Space, but use ultraviolet rays to build and control the UV maps to the flat version over of your model will take all the size of it. This program allows you to get the mesh is not perpendicular three-dimensional, not even lasts for a few seconds. Mesh felt is produced with real size and get delivered in...
</description></item><item><title>Download Allavsoft Video Downloader Converter Portable 3.28.2.9330</title><pubDate> Tue, 12 Aug 2025 00:58:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allavsoft-video-downloader-converter-portable-12064.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allavsoft-video-downloader-converter-portable-12064.html
</guid><description>
Allavsoft Video Downloader Converter Portable is a portable version of the software application that allows users to download videos from various websites and convert them to different formats. It supports popular video sharing platforms such as YouTube Vimeo, Dailymotion and many others.
Besides downloading videos in their original format, Allavsoft also has a one-click feature to download as well as convert downloaded videos to popular video formats like MP4, AVI, WMV, MOV, MPEG-1,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Atlantis Word Processor 4.4.6.4</title><pubDate> Tue, 12 Aug 2025 00:57:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-atlantis-word-processor-585.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-atlantis-word-processor-585.html
</guid><description>
Atlantis Word Processor is a word processor app with features format, standard text, autocorrect, and spell check.  Atlantis is a word processor in accordance with most of the tasks handled daily text. The interface is very easy to use and offers the toolbars, hotkeys and sound effects thanh can customize (can turn off). It includes a clip library for quick access to the text or images used regular preview, font format and many other features aimed at improving the process of your...
</description></item><item><title>Download MiniMeters 1.0.7.1891</title><pubDate> Tue, 12 Aug 2025 00:57:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minimeters-9410.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minimeters-9410.html
</guid><description>
MiniMeters is a simple standalone sound meter application for Windows. Monitor your System Audio*, Any Input, or insert the MiniMeter Server Plug-in (VST3/AU/CLAP) at the end of your main channel in the DAW of your choice. Customize the layout in a horizontal bar (perfect for above or below the audio engine of your choice) or pop out into modules to create custom layouts.
Features of MiniMeters
	6 modules to choose from to build your perfect metering setup: Spectrogram, Waveform,...
</description></item><item><title>Download AnyTime Organizer Deluxe 16.2.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 12 Aug 2025 00:56:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anytime-organizer-deluxe-456.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anytime-organizer-deluxe-456.html
</guid><description>
AnyTime Organizer Deluxe 16 is a powerful tool used to organize your personal and professional life. Friendly and simple interface helps you to easily access Schedule, list of jobs, Contacts, Record Books, Password, Cost and hundreds of design combinations for printable calendar. Let AnyTime Organizer help you organize your life and you will see why more people choose Anymore than any other organizational software brand.
Features of AnyTime Organizer Deluxe
Organize your calendar for...
</description></item><item><title>Download Family Tree Heritage Gold 16.0.15</title><pubDate> Tue, 12 Aug 2025 00:56:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-family-tree-heritage-gold-5596.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-family-tree-heritage-gold-5596.html
</guid><description>
Build your Family Tree and share your Family Story with Family Tree Heritage Gold. This new gold edition offers exciting, easy-to-use new features, including a new descendant View, print background images on multiple charts, improved synchronization with FamilySearch ™ Family Tree, and record non-traditional marital relationships, along with more efficient ways to enter important genealogical data.
TreeTips ™ is an advanced technology built into the Family Tree Heritage to display...
</description></item><item><title>Download SecretDNS 3.7.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 12 Aug 2025 00:56:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secretdns-12481.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secretdns-12481.html
</guid><description>
SecretDNS provides a quick means to deploy DNS over HTPS, meaning it allows DNS (short for Domain Name Server) resolution to be performed remotely using the HTTPS protocol to encrypts data between the client and the DNS resolver. Its purpose, obviously, is related to data security and user privacy, to prevent unauthorized interception and manipulation of DNS data.
Default DNS settings in SecretDNS use CloudFlare to ensure security. You can change DNS configuration in the dedicated tab...
</description></item><item><title>Download EverNote 10.150.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 12 Aug 2025 00:55:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-evernote-3261.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-evernote-3261.html
</guid><description>
EverNote is the all in one tool allows you to track notes, todo items, memos, outlines, excerpts, websites, ideas and other things and automatically synchronize them between multiple computers and mobile devices (iPhone, Android, etc.). You can choose to sort their notes into categories, password protect them, export them to XML and more. EverNote supports a number of pattern notes allow you to add to-do list, spreadsheet like Excel to calculate costs (automatic sum), notes, phone, contact...
</description></item><item><title>Download Rainbow Analyst add-in Professional 25.08.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 12 Aug 2025 00:54:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rainbow-analyst-add-in-professional-11122.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rainbow-analyst-add-in-professional-11122.html
</guid><description>
Rainbow Analyst add-in Professional is a powerful tool designed to enhance data analysis in Microsoft Excel. This add-on provides many advanced features and visualizations to help users gain valuable insights from their data.
One of the key features of Rainbow Analyst is the ability to create color-coded reports and charts. Users can assign specific colors to different data values, making it easier to identify patterns, trends, and outliers. This visual representation of data enhances...
</description></item><item><title>Download Full Discography 1.8.5</title><pubDate> Tue, 12 Aug 2025 00:54:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-full-discography-7509.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-full-discography-7509.html
</guid><description>
Full Discography is a program to discover all the releases of your favorite artists! Listen to every song your favorite artist ever made! Get to know all Albums &amp;amp; Single click by artist.
Features of Full Discography
	Discover all the releases by your favorite artists!
	Listen to every song your favorite artist ever made!
	Recognize All Albums &amp;amp; Single click by artist.
	Discover all the missing releases from your music collection.
	Get notified when your favorite artist...
</description></item><item><title>Download Fluke TruTest 1.1.0.219</title><pubDate> Tue, 12 Aug 2025 00:54:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fluke-trutest-12626.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fluke-trutest-12626.html
</guid><description>
Fluke TruTest software is designed to eliminate the hassle associated with traditional power system data management and reporting. Whether you are testing fixed wiring systems or equipment in the office, verifying repairs in the workshop or carrying out annual inspections, proper data management is critical to creating Produce easy-to-understand reports for customers. Compatible with a growing list of Fluke and Beha-Amprobe test and measurement devices TruTest software allows you to...
</description></item><item><title>Download COAA PlanePlotter 6.7.2.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 12 Aug 2025 00:53:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coaa-planeplotter-7840.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coaa-planeplotter-7840.html
</guid><description>
PlanePlotter receives and decodes digital position reports directly from the aircraft and plots them on a chart. Using PlanePlotter, you can see the radar-like display of all aircraft around you transmitting the appropriate digital messages including ACARS, ADS-B and HFDL.
PlanePlotter Features
	PlanePlotter displays a table showing messages received and decoded from direct plane transmissions.
	PlanePlotter stores all digital data it receives and decodes into a log...
</description></item><item><title>Download Omidsoft Red Burner 18.22</title><pubDate> Tue, 12 Aug 2025 00:52:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-red-burner-10119.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-red-burner-10119.html
</guid><description>
Red Burner is a lightweight burning software based on Blue Burner with full functionality to work with ISO/CUE images and drives. Start the move to a lightweight, yet powerful, and time-saving standalone optical disc burner with the simplest user interface and fastest possible burning algorithm.
Features of Red Burner
	Fastest possible CD/DVD/BD burning algorithm
	Standard, dual-layer and high-capacity media recording
	Browse ISO/CUE images via internal image browser
	Writable M-Disc,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Stackz Dictionary Edition 8.0.6</title><pubDate> Mon, 11 Aug 2025 22:01:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stackz-dictionary-edition-14037.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stackz-dictionary-edition-14037.html
</guid><description>
The Stackz flashcard organizer helps you maximize your learning efficiency, whether you have to keep up with an intensive course of 30 new words a day (intensive learning), or spend 20 minutes a week reviewing 10,000 words (maintaining mastery).
This is the Dictionary Edition of Stackz, a flashcard organizer with learning tools that runs on Windows. The core feature of Stackz is a graphical representation of your current level, making it easy to see where you're struggling. Tools are...
</description></item><item><title>Download XnViewMP 1.9.3</title><pubDate> Mon, 11 Aug 2025 19:18:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xnview-mp-1074.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xnview-mp-1074.html
</guid><description>
XnViewMP "XnView MP" is the enhanced version of XnView Classic. This is the view and convert images multi-platform powerful, compatible with more than 500 image formats, different today. XnView MP easily export images to about 70 file format is different. Similar to XnConvert, XnView MP also features integrated switch at the same time batch file to help you process photos faster. XnView is another version of the photo viewer but with the ability to support formats more limited.
XnView...
</description></item></channel></rss>