<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 17:40:14 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 17:40:14 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download VCap Downloader Pro 0.1.43.6912</title><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jan 2026 20:28:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vcap-downloader-pro-8474.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vcap-downloader-pro-8474.html
</guid><description>
VCap Downloader Pro (VCapDL) is a popular piece of software that allows you to record video and audio from websites on the internet. The interface of the software is similar to a normal browser, making it easy for users to get used to and work with this software. User just need to copy video url from favorite browser and convert it to VCap Downloader Pro. It will capture the video and make the quality available for download. You can also extract the audio track from any video and convert...
</description></item><item><title>Download AnyRail 7.14.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jan 2026 20:17:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anyrail-7570.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anyrail-7570.html
</guid><description>
AnyRail is probably the easiest to use model railway design tool available today. It's also completely standalone, so you can build with almost any track. Love your layout design with AnyRail to make sure everything fits. AnyRail lets you get through the planning or editing phase of your content and you don't need to be a geek to create successful designs.
Designing with AnyRail is like operating an ultimate model railway store. We've included every train set component you can find, so...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ondesoft Amazon Music Converter 1.9.3</title><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jan 2026 20:16:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ondesoft-amazon-music-converter-11102.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ondesoft-amazon-music-converter-11102.html
</guid><description>
Amazon Music Unlimited and Amazon Music Prime let you download music for offline playback, but you don't own the actual audio files. Luckily, Ondesoft Amazon Music Converter was developed to help Amazon Music Unlimited Prime lovers download songs to local computer. Ondesoft Amazon Music Converter is a professional music downloader and converter that helps you download Amazon Music in M4A, MP3, AAC, FLAC, WAV and AIFF formats.
With Ondesoft Amazon Music Converter, you can easily convert...
</description></item><item><title>Download Training Manager Enterprise 2026 v4.10.4000</title><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jan 2026 20:15:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-training-manager-enterprise-3928.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-training-manager-enterprise-3928.html
</guid><description>
Training Manager Enterprise is an utility comprehensive software allows you to track records and status of training of staff, allowing you to know exactly who should be trained, when and about what. The app will give you detailed reports so you see the training process overdue and upcoming in the period determined next. The report will also let you see what's coming, giving you time to prepare and schedule training. By using Training Manager Enterprise, you will be able to easily keep...
</description></item><item><title>Download Pixelmash 2026.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jan 2026 20:15:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pixelmash-3773.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pixelmash-3773.html
</guid><description>
Pixelmash is a drawing app graphics, Pixcel, brings a completely new approach for pixel art by allowing you to draw or import images high resolution, then the pixel turns non-destructive and apply the other layer to turn it into pixel art great. You can start from scratch to create pixel art from scratch or try converting an existing image you need in the format as PAD, JPG, PNG, TIF and TIFF.
Pixelmash - Drawn graphics Pixcel
The interface is quite attractive and intuitive overall....
</description></item><item><title>Download Ondesoft Spotify Music Converter 4.9.9</title><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jan 2026 20:14:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ondesoft-spotify-converter-4641.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ondesoft-spotify-converter-4641.html
</guid><description>
Ondesoft Spotify Converter is software that helps you easily download and convert the songs, albums and Spotify playlists to MP3, M4A, WAV, FLAC without any limits. Ondesoft Spotify Converter support download Spotify music with speed 5 times on PC Windows with original quality 100%. Now, you can easily transfer and play any songs and Spotify playlists, how to, mobile phone, MP3 player, iPod, HDTV, Xbox 360, Xbox one, PS4, Zune, Creative Zen, or burn to CD, etc.
The features of Ondesoft...
</description></item><item><title>Download Total Commander Ultima Prime 9.3</title><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jan 2026 17:39:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-total-commander-ultima-prime-462.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-total-commander-ultima-prime-462.html
</guid><description>
Total Commander Ultima Prime is file management software, professional data for windows can be replaced by default Windows Explorer. With this software the management of files on the computer is easy and quick. Total Commander Ultima Prime is a very good improvement of Total Commander, where you are available for additional features, which will help you arrange your files and folders more efficiently. The installation process comes with a number of steps in which you can configure some...
</description></item><item><title>Download Parted Magic 2025.12.31</title><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jan 2026 17:39:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-parted-magic-2298.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-parted-magic-2298.html
</guid><description>
Powerful tools for home or Office! - Parted Magic is a solution to manage hard disk complete. PartedMagic has the tools to complete the job. With The edit partitions, you can resize, copy, and move partitions. You can grow or shrink your C: drive. Create space for the new operating system. Attempt data rescue from lost partitions.
A pack of very powerful utility has been updated is very useful to work with partitions of your hard disk based on the disk boot Linux. Please note that you can...
</description></item><item><title>Download n-Track Studio Suite 10.2.3.10395</title><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jan 2026 17:38:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-n-track-studio-2991.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-n-track-studio-2991.html
</guid><description>
n-Track Studio is a recording software allows you record and create MIDI music and sounds top quality. The software allows you to add effects, VST3, DirectX, AU (Mac), VST and ReWire different on each track or channel. This program also allows you to automatically fade out, fade in and fade out or increase the volume of the music to indicate the voice of the singer.
n-Track Studio can record and playback the number of audio, MIDI and sound unlimited. In addition, you can handle the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Kip Morgan Usenet Explorer 1.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jan 2026 17:38:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kip-morgan-usenet-explorer-14426.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kip-morgan-usenet-explorer-14426.html
</guid><description>
Usenet Explorer is a modern Usenet (NNTP) browser for Windows that makes downloading binary files from newsgroups simple and intuitive. You can browse and subscribe to newsgroups, view article titles, and download attachments with built-in yEnc decoding support.
It includes multi-part article processing to seamlessly combine split binary files, download progress tracking, and support for multiple NNTP server connections. Whether you're accessing text discussions or binary content,...
</description></item><item><title>Download WizFlow Flowcharter Professional 7.49.2219</title><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jan 2026 17:36:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wizflow-flowcharter-professional-3604.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wizflow-flowcharter-professional-3604.html
</guid><description>
WizFlow Flowcharter Professional is a tool for drawing diagrams and diagram easy-to-use, feature-rich, abundant for Windows. WizFlow lets you define "styles" shape using more than a hundred shapes and arrow heads to be determined first. Save your styles in the template to set the method of mapping your own. WizFlow comes with the template complete diagram to help you get started. WizFlow can create flowcharts and diagrams similar with minimal effort. When you draw a diagram of WizFlow...
</description></item><item><title>Download EDGE Diagrammer 7.49.2219</title><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jan 2026 17:35:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-edge-diagrammer-9462.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-edge-diagrammer-9462.html
</guid><description>
EDGE Diagrammer is a software application used to create graphical diagrams, especially in the field of systems engineering. The term "EDGE" stands for "Enhanced Diagram Graphics Environment". It provides a user-friendly interface and a set of tools for designing and documenting complex systems, processes, and workflows.
EDGE Diagrammer is all you need for block diagrams, flowcharts, organization charts, family trees, data flow diagrams and more. Free extension packs are available to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Chaos Corona 14.1 for 3ds Max 2018 - 2026</title><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jan 2026 17:35:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chaos-corona-2986.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chaos-corona-2986.html
</guid><description>
Corona Renderer is the name of the plug-in technique and dedicated powerful, but have high functionality for Autodesk software 3ds Max. Plug before you is a standalone application known to the CLI. In addition, users can use this tool to promote their business on software Maxon Cinema 4D is also used. The manufacturers of this product believe that working with this tool is very simple and in fact you only need to press the activities rendered. With this tool easier than ever can do the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Chaos Corona 14.1 for Cinema 4D R17 - 2026</title><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jan 2026 17:35:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-corona-renderer-for-cinema-4d-6499.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-corona-renderer-for-cinema-4d-6499.html
</guid><description>
Corona Renderer  is the name of a powerful, but highly functional engineering and dedicated plug-in for Autodesk 3ds Max software. Plug in before you are a known CLI standalone application. In addition, users can use this tool to advertise their business on Maxon Cinema 4D software which is also used. The manufacturers of this product firmly believe that working with this tool is very simple, and in fact you just need to hit render the rendering operations. With this tool it's easier...
</description></item><item><title>Download Quantum SSH Terminal And SFTP 1.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jan 2026 17:31:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quantum-ssh-terminal-and-sftp-14425.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quantum-ssh-terminal-and-sftp-14425.html
</guid><description>
Quantum SSH Terminal &amp;amp; SFTP is a modern, high-performance SSH and SFTP management software built for developers, system administrators, DevOps engineers, and IT professionals who need power, speed, and reliability—without outdated interfaces or unnecessary complexity. Manage multiple servers simultaneously, securely transfer files using drag-and-drop, and monitor active sessions from a single professional dashboard.
Features of Quantum SSH Terminal And SFTP
	Connect to multiple...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tekadministrators Paperclip 1.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jan 2026 17:26:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tekadministrators-paperclip-14424.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tekadministrators-paperclip-14424.html
</guid><description>
Paperclip is a powerful, modern clipboard manager that remembers everything you copy or cut—forever. With a stunning futuristic interface and lightning-fast performance, managing your clipboard history has never been easier and more beautiful.
Features of Paperclip
	Unlimited clipboard history with large previews
	Automatically capture text, images, and files
	Drag and drop into any application
	Global shortcuts (Ctrl+Shift+V)
	Instant search and Smart filtering
	Favorites and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ultimate Document Editor 1.0.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jan 2026 17:20:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ultimate-document-editor-14423.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ultimate-document-editor-14423.html
</guid><description>
In modern enterprise software, creating, editing, viewing, and processing documents are no longer optional features—they are core requirements. From invoices, contracts, reports, and correspondence to complex multi-part documents with tables, images, and formatting rules, applications must handle rich text content accurately, efficiently, and reliably. This is where Ultimate Document Editor stands out as a complete, all-in-one platform designed to meet the growing needs of individuals,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Shotcut 25.12.31</title><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jan 2026 15:55:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-shotcut-2756.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-shotcut-2756.html
</guid><description>
Shotcut is a video editing application multi-platform free and open source for FreeBSD, Linux, macOS and Windows. Was started in 2011 by Dan Dennedy, Shotcut is developed on the multimedia MLT, which was developed from 2004. With age grow quite long years, Shotcut offers users many tools to perform the manipulation, Video editing based on adjusting each frame to enhance image quality. You can add an introduction, edit rate, bitrate, resolution or file encryption, and optionally use the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Dropbox 238.4.6305</title><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jan 2026 15:55:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dropbox-1313.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dropbox-1313.html
</guid><description>
Dropbox on taiwebs.com is free tool, the data synchronization across multiple PC become easier than never before: after installation, all what you have to do is enter your name, email address and password before opening the folder My Dropbox. If you install the software on a different computer, Dropbox will reflect the content of the online storage. So you exchange any data between the different computer is connected to Dropbox account. In addition the client is installed on the computer,...
</description></item><item><title>Download R-Studio 9.5 Build 191671 Network / Technician</title><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jan 2026 15:52:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-studio-1415.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-studio-1415.html
</guid><description>
R-Studio is a group of software data recovery and data recovery powerful and effective. -STUDIO is the solution to recover most comprehensive data for the file restored from the variants NTFS, NTFS5, ReFS, FAT12 / 16/32, exFAT, HFS / HFS + (Macintosh), Little and Big Endian of UFS1 / UFS2 (FreeBSD / OpenBSD / NetBSD / Solaris) and Ext2 / Ext3 / Ext4 partition FS (Linux).
R-Studio is also used to recover file raw (scan known file types) for the file system is damaged or not determined. It...
</description></item><item><title>Download Print Artist Premier 25.0.3.4</title><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jan 2026 15:52:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-print-artist-premier-12692.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-print-artist-premier-12692.html
</guid><description>
Print Artist Premier 25 is unlike any printing software you have ever used. Its amazing quality combined with unmatched ease of use allows you to create amazing print projects for home, school or your business. Impress friends, family and customers with the creativity that only Print Artist Premier can offer with over 28,000 professionally designed templates, over 377,000 sensational graphics, over 1,000 premium fonts and more!
With powerful yet easy-to-use design, text, and drawing...
</description></item><item><title>Download GPU-Z Portable 2.68.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jan 2026 15:51:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gpu-z-portable-11862.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gpu-z-portable-11862.html
</guid><description>
GPU-Z is a lightweight and portable software utility that provides users with detailed information about their graphics processing unit (GPU) and video card. This app is useful for monitoring your GPU's performance, verifying its specifications, and troubleshooting any problems that may arise.
GPU-Z Portable Features
	One of the main advantages of GPU-Z Portable is its portability. You can run the application directly from a USB flash drive or any other portable device without...
</description></item><item><title>Download VectorStyler 1.3.006</title><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jan 2026 15:51:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vectorstyler-7917.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vectorstyler-7917.html
</guid><description>
VectorStyler provides a complete set of drawing, design and illustration tools needed for modern design. Create illustrations, logos, icons, drawings, typography, vector art for screen, print and web. With many new features, VectorStyler redefines and extends the tools available to illustrators and designers, improving the creation of complex illustrations and designs.
Shape effects can be used to adjust the shape of objects, create different distortions, or add detail to shapes. Shape...
</description></item><item><title>Download HTML Compiler 2026.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jan 2026 15:51:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-html-compiler-2548.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-html-compiler-2548.html
</guid><description>
HTML Compiler is a program for Microsoft Windows (tm) allows you to put an entire HTML application (including HTML, CSS, JavaScript, images, etc.) into a Windows application independent can be executed like any other application window the application. HTML Compiler allows you to customize file real exam results by changing the icon of them and set some other options. For example, you can allow or not allow the ability to print the HTML pages, allow or disallow the text selection and many,...
</description></item><item><title>Download VLC Media Player 3.0.23</title><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jan 2026 15:50:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vlc-media-player-63.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vlc-media-player-63.html
</guid><description>
VLC Media Player is a multimedia player supporting many audio formats and video (MPEG-1, MPEG-2, MPEG-4, DivX, mp3, ogg, etc.) without the need for additional codecs , as well as DVDS, VCDS, and various streaming protocols different online.It also comes with a server, streaming allows you to stream media in unicast or multicast from your network.
VLC Media Player 
VLC Media Player provides a simple interface, with simple buttons control the playback standard and make the most of the...
</description></item></channel></rss>