<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 05:30:15 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 05:30:15 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Free Download Manager 6.30.2 Build 6502</title><pubDate> Fri, 17 Oct 2025 01:25:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-download-manager-3105.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-download-manager-3105.html
</guid><description>
Free Download Manager is free application download manager, Free Download Manager will significantly increase downloads by splitting the files into several smaller parts and then downloads at the same time. Speed your download will be significantly increased. Manager download free can also continue to download at broken or not responding, so you don't need start downloading from the beginning after occasionally interrupted.
Free Download Manager - Manage and speed up downloads
You can...
</description></item><item><title>Download OCCT 15.0.0.99</title><pubDate> Fri, 17 Oct 2025 01:24:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-occt-perestroika-1680.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-occt-perestroika-1680.html
</guid><description>
OCCT is a free application designed to benchmark and overclock system components. Test tool OverClock includes 4 different tests to assess the stability of your computer. CPU and CPU: Linpack to test the processor, GPU: 3D to check stability of the graphics processor and power supply combination of CPU: Linpack and GPU: 3D to download power of you up to the maximum.
OCCT - Measuring system components
The features of OCCT
	Support is enabled for a maximum of 16 cores.
	All the tests...
</description></item><item><title>Download Reg Organizer 9.88</title><pubDate> Fri, 17 Oct 2025 01:23:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reg-organizer-1595.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reg-organizer-1595.html
</guid><description>
Reg Organizer is a software to scan and clean your registry windows register errors and help optimize performance computer system. Reg Organizer is a software subscription, professional, and professional, and any way that the Windows registry are necessary and therefore, the overall performance of Windows improves, there is this software.
Reg Organizer - registry Cleaning and pc optimization
The main features of Reg Organizer
	Cleaning the registry of the lock is not valid and not...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube Downloader 3.9.17 (1510)</title><pubDate> Fri, 17 Oct 2025 01:18:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube Downloader  is a dedicated software that helps users  downloading youtube videos  Favorites on PC for offline viewing. With MediaHuman YouTube  Downloader  you can download videos from youtube website to your computer with  fast speed , with special software development technology that automatically receives videos from Websites, in addition to the ability to download videos from software websites, can convert downloaded video formats to various formats for the purpose...
</description></item><item><title>Download Office Timeline Plus 11.30.00.00 Expert / Pro / Pro+ Edition</title><pubDate> Fri, 17 Oct 2025 01:18:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-timeline-2106.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-timeline-2106.html
</guid><description>
Office Timeline is an add-on very useful and powerful software for Microsoft PowerPoint. With add-ons, you can create PowerPoint documents look more beautiful. With add-ons, you can add the time Line on the project by yourself. Application time for the composition and different segments of the document, your PowerPoint will not only increase the beauty for your work, but also for customers and your manager. The people who created this product is also believe that add-ons this is the only...
</description></item><item><title>Download AMS Software PhotoWorks 21.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 17 Oct 2025 01:17:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ams-software-photoworks-4798.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ams-software-photoworks-4798.html
</guid><description>
AMS Software PhotoWorks is the name of a comprehensive application and of course, the reality for those passionate about photography and photo editing. With the help of this powerful software, you can easily edit their pictures and put them closer to the desired image of you. In fact, with the help of this program, you can turn photos of yourself in the brightness level wrong, a photo nice and pleasant. Left with looks relatively simple, its software use this technology to handle the...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter 3.9.17 (1510)</title><pubDate> Fri, 17 Oct 2025 01:15:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-to-mp3-converter-1744.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-to-mp3-converter-1744.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter is the software support download youtube video and convert video to mp3 format fast and most simple. MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter allows you download and convert videos from YouTube and other websites to MP3 format by pasting the YouTube URL into the application. When you paste the URL, the program will display thumbnails for videos and you have the option to customize the title information, artist and album before you begin the process of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Duplicate Files Fixer 1.2.1.1092</title><pubDate> Fri, 17 Oct 2025 01:10:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-duplicate-files-fixer-3417.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-duplicate-files-fixer-3417.html
</guid><description>
Duplicate Files Fixer - You know that your system usually accumulate too many files, duplicate occupy much storage capacity do not? Tool copy duplicate files is a simple tool designed to find and delete all the duplicate files that easily! This convenient tool makes your system more organized!
Duplicate Files Fixer - Find and delete duplicate files
Copy file duplicate identify exactly all the file formats are identical. Find the text, images, audio and video files identical it's easy...
</description></item><item><title>Download UPDF 2.0.10</title><pubDate> Fri, 17 Oct 2025 01:10:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-updf-14160.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-updf-14160.html
</guid><description>
UPDF for Windows is easy-to-use PDF software for Windows! Enjoy powerful editing tools for text, images, links, and more in your PDFs. Customize backgrounds, watermarks, and page sizes as easily as in Word. AI-powered PDF editor and manager that offers a wide range of features including editing, annotating, converting, OCR (Optical Character Recognition), organizing, protecting, sharing, printing, summarizing, translating, and interpreting PDF files.
Features of UPDF
Analyze PDFs with...
</description></item><item><title>Download KMPlayer (KMP) 2025.10.16.11 x64 / 4.2.3.28 x86</title><pubDate> Fri, 17 Oct 2025 01:09:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kmplayer-kmp-902.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kmplayer-kmp-902.html
</guid><description>
KMPlayer (KMP) is software watch movies listen to music multi-function for video enthusiasts. KMPlayer development is many types of the format different. KMPlayer has improved on sound quality, images when listening to music and watching movies, the playback speed of video is faster, more codec player is added to the software video decoder is optimized.
KMPlayer also supports a variety of audio formats and video and offers a the interface can be customized with the preview coverflow and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wise Program Uninstaller 3.2.7.271</title><pubDate> Fri, 17 Oct 2025 01:08:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wise-program-uninstaller-519.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wise-program-uninstaller-519.html
</guid><description>
Wise Program Uninstaller is a software that manages the application program was installed on the computer and support the user uninstall the application from your computer. Wise Program Uninstaller can fully uninstall applications on the system in just a few seconds. Special tool to completely remove these apps and not leave traces on the system.
Thanks features uninstall, clean the application system of Wise Program Uninstaller, you will be able to cleanup the file data garbage save...
</description></item><item><title>Download iTunes 12.13.9.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 17 Oct 2025 01:02:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-itunes-2639.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-itunes-2639.html
</guid><description>
iTunes or is a multimedia library management application mobile developed by Apple. Software this each is play, download and arrange the audio and video multimedia on the personal computer according to the operating system OS X and Microsoft Windows.
iTunes allows you to browse and purchase music, videos, and apps from the Apple Store. iTunes allows you to browse the repository online music iTunes from where you can search for songs, browse genres and then download songs, music videos or...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft PowerToys for Windows 10/11 0.95.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 17 Oct 2025 01:02:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-powertoys-for-windows-6014.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-powertoys-for-windows-6014.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft PowerToys is a user-proficiency set to adjust and streamline their Windows experience for higher productivity. Inspired by Windows 95's PowerToys project, this reboot provides users with proficiency in ways to exploit the more efficient Windows 10 and customisable processes it provides for each work process.
Utility of Microsoft PowerToys
	FancyZones is a window manager that allows you to easily create complex windows layout and quickly locate windows in those layout.
	Image...
</description></item><item><title>Download Autorun Organizer 6.30</title><pubDate> Fri, 17 Oct 2025 01:01:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-autorun-organizer-2118.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-autorun-organizer-2118.html
</guid><description>
Autorun Organizer allows you to manage all the programs are set to run automatically when you start Windows. It supports launch according to schedule through the Registry, The task scheduler and the startup folder.
You can review the list of startup items, inspect additional details and choose to remove selected items from the boot configuration. In addition, you can also configure delay boot individually, this may cause the computer to your desk download a little faster without...
</description></item><item><title>Download XYplorer 28.00.0500 Beta</title><pubDate> Fri, 17 Oct 2025 01:01:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-533.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-533.html
</guid><description>
XYplorer - File Manager for Windows is software that supports users to manage files on the Window quickly and to arrange the folder tidy. XYplorer features tabbed browsing, search, files, powerful, preview, flexible, highly customizable interface, dual frame options and a variety of unique ways to automate effective tasks often repeat. It's fast, lightweight, and portable.
Features XYplorer
	XYplorer is a file manager mobile. It does not require any settings, store all configuration...
</description></item><item><title>Download Photo Supreme 2025.3.3.8119</title><pubDate> Fri, 17 Oct 2025 01:00:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photo-supreme-430.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photo-supreme-430.html
</guid><description>
Photo Supreme is a software product management professional pictures of idimager. With Photo Supreme you can arrange, manage back stock photo archive of yourself and share them with you here and relatives easily via Email or Facebook. Photo Supreme provides users method to sort images effective, logical, as well as edit and share your photos with friends and relatives in the family. Especially the Photo Supreme allows to work with multiple image formats and support mounting support,...
</description></item><item><title>Download AllMapSoft Google Maps Downloader 8.882</title><pubDate> Fri, 17 Oct 2025 00:52:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-google-maps-downloader-2796.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-google-maps-downloader-2796.html
</guid><description>
AllMapSoft Google Maps Downloader is a reliable application aimed at downloading maps from Google at high speed. The result is a set of small images can be combined in a larger map. This can serve in a large variety of projects, from creating a tile map to presentations and tutorials.
Google Maps Downloader successfully fulfills both of those conditions, providing simple means to quickly grab maps at the resolution satisfactory. In addition, it is extremely easy to use and integrated a...
</description></item><item><title>Download PhoneRescue for iOS 4.3.1.20251016</title><pubDate> Fri, 17 Oct 2025 00:51:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-phonerescue-for-ios-2851.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-phonerescue-for-ios-2851.html
</guid><description>
PhoneRescue for iOS is the solution to restore lost data of iOS devices such as iPhone, iPad with the ability to work quickly find back all the data on the device such as music, videos, photos, call logs, contacts, or even sms. With PhoneRescue is that you don't need to connect iPhone device with the computer directly, the software works through the index and account, now you can completely assured when using data on the iPhone, by all user's data are lost, you can restore back...
</description></item><item><title>Download AllmapSoft Google Satellite Maps Downloader 8.411</title><pubDate> Fri, 17 Oct 2025 00:51:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-google-satellite-maps-downloader-687.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-google-satellite-maps-downloader-687.html
</guid><description>
AllmapSoft Google Satellite Maps Downloader is software help download map images from google maps on computer for you to get the satellite images from google map. All the downloaded photos will be saved on disk. You can see the map is downloaded by viewer Or you can combine them into the map BMP, big. It supports proxy server. And you can easily get the longitude and latitude of each image tile small download.
You can use offline maps in GIS software such as Global Mapper, QGIS,...
</description></item><item><title>Download SecretDNS 3.7.7</title><pubDate> Fri, 17 Oct 2025 00:50:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secretdns-12481.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secretdns-12481.html
</guid><description>
SecretDNS provides a quick means to deploy DNS over HTPS, meaning it allows DNS (short for Domain Name Server) resolution to be performed remotely using the HTTPS protocol to encrypts data between the client and the DNS resolver. Its purpose, obviously, is related to data security and user privacy, to prevent unauthorized interception and manipulation of DNS data.
Default DNS settings in SecretDNS use CloudFlare to ensure security. You can change DNS configuration in the dedicated tab...
</description></item><item><title>Download Secret Video Downloader 1.0.4</title><pubDate> Fri, 17 Oct 2025 00:50:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secret-video-downloader-13775.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secret-video-downloader-13775.html
</guid><description>
Secret Video Downloader is a free application designed to facilitate easy video downloading from various websites. It leverages the yt-dlp command line program to efficiently grab video content, allowing users to save videos in the highest quality available without complicated installation or configuration. The tool has a minimalist interface focused on simplicity: the user pastes the video URL into the built-in browser, clicks the Download button, and the video is added to the download...
</description></item><item><title>Download ToDoList 9.1.4.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 17 Oct 2025 00:49:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-todolist-1637.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-todolist-1637.html
</guid><description>
ToDoList is an application note and task management with multiple options, set up help you to easily split and track the progress of the work. Todolist helps millions of people feel in control of their lives more and be the leader in a number of organizations inspired the world to believe. Todolist keep all to-dos of I in one place and perfectly integrated with the other tools that I use. It helps me turn everything faster.
ToDoList - management software job
Every day you have to...
</description></item><item><title>Download AnyTrans for iOS 8.9.13.20251016</title><pubDate> Fri, 17 Oct 2025 00:49:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anytrans-for-ios-755.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anytrans-for-ios-755.html
</guid><description>
AnyTrans for iOS is content manager essential fully managed iPhone, Android and content of your cloud. Including all mobile devices, all cloud drives from your iPhone, iPad, iPod touch to phones and tablets. From local disk to cloud storage. AnyTrans has protected them all, providing you convenient management for all data and your files, regardless of whether they are stored where.
AnyTrans is the one stop solution to meet all the management needs of your data. For the first time, you can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Valentina Studio Pro 16.1.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 17 Oct 2025 00:48:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-valentina-studio-pro-2122.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-valentina-studio-pro-2122.html
</guid><description>
Valentina Studio Pro is the best way to transform your data into meaningful information; create, manage, query and explore MySQL, Postgre MariaDB, MS SQL Server and SQLite database.
Valentina Studio Pro
Features of Valentina Studio Pro
SCHEMA EDITING &amp;amp; MAPPING
	Manage multiple databases in tabs and views that can be attached is
	Create / Drop / alter / Browse Tables, fields, index, trigger, constraints, links, views, stored procedures, properties, Sequences, Types, ...
	Edit the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Awesome Miner Ultimate 11.2.5</title><pubDate> Fri, 17 Oct 2025 00:47:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-awesome-miner-9041.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-awesome-miner-9041.html
</guid><description>
Awesome Miner is a software application designed to manage and monitor cryptocurrency mining operations. It supports a wide variety of mining hardware, including ASICs and GPUs, and can be used to manage mining for a variety of cryptocurrencies, including Bitcoin, Ethereum, and Litecoin.
Powerful tool to manage and monitor cryptocurrency mining activities. With support for a wide variety of mining hardware and cryptocurrencies, mobile apps, and customizable alerting and performance...
</description></item></channel></rss>