<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 23:31:52 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 23:31:52 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Office(R)Tool 16.4</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Sep 2025 01:34:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-officertool-7461.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-officertool-7461.html
</guid><description>
OfficeRTool was developed to be a free and open source tool on GitHub for users to easily install, activate, and configure Office 2016, 2019 and 2021.
Features of OfficeRTool
	User Friendly Interface
	Update Activation file
	Automatically generate package info files
	Automatic Arch Detection System.
	Visual refresh for current channels &amp;amp; LTSC
	Multi-architecture/language ISO disc support
	Online/Offline Installation Support Including ISO Creation
	Support to install from...
</description></item><item><title>Download Active File Recovery 25.1.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Sep 2025 01:34:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-active-file-recovery-354.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-active-file-recovery-354.html
</guid><description>
Active File Recovery is a recovery tool for files deleted or lost, damaged or reformatted volume even when your PC does not boot. Active File Recovery will help you recover NTFS, ReFS, FAT, exFAT, HFS +, XFS, JFS, UFS, Ext2 / 3 / 4, BtrFS. Recovery software provides the ability to detect and recover files, drives and disks lost due to deleted, formatted, damaged, physical virus.
Features Active File Recovery:
Basic features Active File Recovery
	Active File Recovery helps to restore...
</description></item><item><title>Download Topaz Gigapixel AI 8.4.3</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Sep 2025 01:33:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-ai-gigapixel-1318.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-ai-gigapixel-1318.html
</guid><description>
Topaz ONE Gigapixel is the first app and only use the power of artificial intelligence to enhance your photos, add natural details, for great results. Use technology to learn deep, AIGigapixel ™ can zoom in and fill in the details that the products change in size other are not included. The traditional method this created blurred image, a non-realistic and do not have the detail present in the image have high resolution.
Topaz A.I. Gigapixel - enhance image quality
The content of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Aiseesoft Blu-ray Player 6.7.86</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Sep 2025 01:32:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aiseesoft-blu-ray-player-118.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aiseesoft-blu-ray-player-118.html
</guid><description>
Aiseesoft Blu-ray Player Program is a multimedia good. After launch, you can produce absolutely any Blu-ray how you can work with documents, menus, and other elements, you can download at The Blu-ray Aiseesoft below. Please note, players can also play almost every video format, audio is also supported, the list is waiting for you on the official website. In addition, Aiseesoft Blu-ray Player will be able to view ISO images. It has a pleasant interface, style.
Aiseesoft Blu-ray Player -...
</description></item><item><title>Download SoftMaker FlexiPDF Professional 2025.412.0808</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Sep 2025 01:31:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-softmaker-flexipdf-professional-1513.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-softmaker-flexipdf-professional-1513.html
</guid><description>
SoftMaker FlexiPDF Professional is the perfect software to edit and create pdf files. With this program, you can easily open any pdf file in environment task simple and easy. Change the text you want. Change the color of text and paragraphs. Like software Word, you can create a section of text or italics. Can you are not satisfied with the font of the pdf, you can open the file and save it with the font you want to pdf. In addition to text, you can add forms, graphics, photos, comments,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Watchdog Anti-Malware Premium / Business 4.3.430</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Sep 2025 01:31:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-watchdog-anti-malware-7110.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-watchdog-anti-malware-7110.html
</guid><description>
Watchdog Anti-Malware is an anti-malware with many highly rated tools to help keep your computer safe. Watchdog Anti-Malware will help you with Advanced Malware Detection and Removal, Browser Hijacker Removal, Effective Rootkit and Bootkit Detection and Removal, Real-Time Protection, Anti-ransomware Protection Module.
Watchdog Anti-Malware is extremely optimized and lightweight. Software engineers designed it to work efficiently without having to tweak confusing settings. Just start...
</description></item><item><title>Download R-Wipe &amp;amp; Clean 20.0 Build 2526</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Sep 2025 01:30:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-wipe-clean-891.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-wipe-clean-891.html
</guid><description>
R-Wipe &amp;amp; Clean is software to delete junk files, unnecessary files from your computer to release the storage space and speed up your computer. In addition, R-Wipe &amp;amp; Clean also unleash the capacity of your drive and delete information invasion of privacy on different operations online and offline including your internet history and cookies, the list of downloaded files and documents were open, buffer different data, temporary files and many other items, created by the operating...
</description></item><item><title>Download ToDoList 9.1.0.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Sep 2025 01:30:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-todolist-1637.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-todolist-1637.html
</guid><description>
ToDoList is an application note and task management with multiple options, set up help you to easily split and track the progress of the work. Todolist helps millions of people feel in control of their lives more and be the leader in a number of organizations inspired the world to believe. Todolist keep all to-dos of I in one place and perfectly integrated with the other tools that I use. It helps me turn everything faster.
ToDoList - management software job
Every day you have to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Syncthing 2.0.9</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Sep 2025 01:29:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncthing-2115.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncthing-2115.html
</guid><description>
Syncthing is synchronization service, cloud and open and non-focus allows you to share and sync files with other computers and gives you full control how to share your data and who can access it. Syncthing does not store your data in any other place, there is no server side Tuesday how to join. In addition, all the communication is secured by TLS and every button is determined by the certificate the strength of the encryption. Only computers that have explicitly allowed can connect with...
</description></item><item><title>Download AllMapSoft Offline Map Maker 8.351</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Sep 2025 01:29:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-offline-map-maker-656.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-offline-map-maker-656.html
</guid><description>
AllMapSoft Offline Map Maker is software create, organize, offline map from Google Maps, Yahoo maps, Bing maps and Openstreetmap. You can view offline maps downloaded with map viewer offline. And you can zoom out or zoom in the offline map or export map under the file format .BMP with file world xxx.bpw, and can output files xxx.map for OziExplorer. If you want to make a offline map of your city by yourself, it is very useful for you.
Features AllMapSoft Offline Map Maker
	You can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Causality 4.0.17</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Sep 2025 01:28:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-causality-6895.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-causality-6895.html
</guid><description>
Causality is a new kind of writing app where you develop your stories visually, giving you an amazing overview of your stories. Friend. Causality works with your story the way it looks in your mind, but with the ability to visualize a much larger structure.
Causality supports writing in over 100 languages, checks spells in multiple languages ​​simultaneously, and comes with a gigabyte of fonts for identical rendering on all platforms. With Causality, it's easy to write screenplays...
</description></item><item><title>Download VideoMeld 1.80</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Sep 2025 01:28:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-videomeld-5549.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-videomeld-5549.html
</guid><description>
VideoMeld is a brand new multi-path digital audio and video editing program. VideoMeld has one of the most advanced effects editors in its class. Multiple effects can be applied at the same time, creating astonishing variety. Effect settings can be precisely changed over time for detailed animations.
Key features include:
	High quality HD video up to 1920x1080 and save as MPEG 4 H. 264
	High quality 8-channel audio (7.1 surround sound)
	More than 50 video effects, transition effects...
</description></item><item><title>Download Apeaksoft Blu-ray Player 1.1.68</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Sep 2025 01:26:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-apeaksoft-blu-ray-player-2458.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-apeaksoft-blu-ray-player-2458.html
</guid><description>
Apeaksoft Blu-ray Player is the software movie playback Blu-ray professional can help you play Blu-ray folder, Blu-ray disc / DVD folder, files ISO with photo effects high quality. It can also work as a media player powerful to play 4K UHD / HD 1080p / SD videos in MP4, MOV, AVI, MKV and other formats.
Apeaksoft Blu-ray Player is specially designed to play Blu-ray folder and file ISO. It supports very high for the Blu-ray movie new releases and guarantee you playback Blu-ray 1080p full...
</description></item><item><title>Download Directory Opus Pro 13.18.3 Beta</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Sep 2025 01:25:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-opus-pro-779.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-opus-pro-779.html
</guid><description>
Directory Opus Pro is a software replacement for Explorer with traditional strength and function more than any manager other files. Directory Opus Pro full support for high DPI screen (for example 4K and 5K) with the rename dialog is redesigned, with new features. Besides being a recording macro only allows you to perform mass renaming complex that don't need regular expressions. In addition, Directory Opus Pro also enhances the ability to script.Better handling of renaming recursive and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Pulsar Modular Complete Effects Bundle 2025.9.12</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Sep 2025 01:24:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pulsar-modular-complete-effects-bundle-11871.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pulsar-modular-complete-effects-bundle-11871.html
</guid><description>
Pulsar module complete effects package for high quality audio mixing and mastering, is a powerful and thorough passive EQ plugin. The program combines the power of the leading passive equalizers from 70 years ago with several unique design elements to create a completely original sound. With extremely rich sources such as synth pads or synth bass, it can also be used as a sculpting tool. It has a simple and user-friendly graphical interface with a quick and adaptable process to produce...
</description></item><item><title>Download Rapid Composer 5.5.7</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Sep 2025 01:24:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rapidcomposer-1106.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rapidcomposer-1106.html
</guid><description>
RapidComposer is software perfect for the composer gives you advanced tools to draft or edit scores. RapidComposer is a unique, non-destructive, phrase-based music composer software. RapidComposer can function complex editing allows you to edit any notes, measure, chord, or phrase, or with the help of menu Variations. You can easily copy the entire phrase or general notes, change the chord or altitude, as well as modify the tempo of the melody.
RapidComposer - Composer and composed...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Video Downloader 11.27.5</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Sep 2025 01:23:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-video-downloader-9636.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-video-downloader-9636.html
</guid><description>
YT Video Downloader is software used to easily and quickly download any video or audio content from any website in HD quality using video downloader online. Save videos from almost any website supported by a video downloader on your local hard drive. Media search is a convenient way to do this.
Features of YT Video Downloader
	Download videos from hundreds of video sites.
	Really increase your download speed by up to 500% or even more!
	Download 8K, 5K, 4K Ultra HD, 2K Quad HD, 1080p...
</description></item><item><title>Download EstlCAM 12.147</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Sep 2025 01:23:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-estlcam-13476.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-estlcam-13476.html
</guid><description>
EstlCAM is a user-friendly CNC and CAM (Computer-Aided Manufacturing) control software, designed to generate toolpaths and G-code for CNC machines, especially suitable for 2D, 2.5D and 3D milling operations. The software supports importing a variety of design file formats, including 2D drawings (.dxf, .svg, .png, .jpg) and 3D models (.stl), allowing users to position, scale, and rotate designs before generating toolpaths.
The software is especially popular among enthusiasts and...
</description></item><item><title>Download AllMapSoft Universal Maps Downloader 10.221</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Sep 2025 01:23:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-universal-maps-downloader-736.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-universal-maps-downloader-736.html
</guid><description>
AllMapSoft Universal Maps Downloader is software download map images on the computer for offline viewing support many types such as Google Maps, Yahoo maps, Bing maps, OpenStreet Maps, Yandex Maps, Ovi Maps, MapQuest Maps. All the downloaded photos will be saved on disk. You can view downloaded maps by Maps Viewer Or you can combine them into one big bmp, or jpg file tif by Maps Combiner, and also you can export all the tiles into a database format MBTiles.
AllMapSoft Universal Maps...
</description></item><item><title>Download ASUS GPU Tweak III 2.0.3.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Sep 2025 23:03:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-asus-gpu-tweak-3252.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-asus-gpu-tweak-3252.html
</guid><description>
ASUS GPU Tweak is a tools overclocking powerful and full-featured allows you to significantly enhance the performance of the graphics processor ASUS. Utility that allows you to get the best results just by few mouse clicks. ASUS GPU Tweak has a number mode allows you to adjust the parameters of graphics according to the specific needs of his. Mode OC allows you to benefit from maximum performance supplied by your graphics card. Game play mode allows you to play the game using the default...
</description></item><item><title>Download USB Device Tree Viewer 4.6.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Sep 2025 23:02:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-usb-device-tree-viewer-3286.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-usb-device-tree-viewer-3286.html
</guid><description>
USB Device Tree Viewer provides detailed information for all the ports and USB hub on the computer in the format tree. If a device is connected to a port, it also provides detailed information for the properties of the device and connection. USB Device Tree Viewer analyze your system configuration and display details about the controller server is connected, such as the manufacturer, drivers, bus types, list, location, devices, drive letters, COM ports, and debugging and statistics bus...
</description></item><item><title>Download CyberLink PowerDirector Ultimate 2026 v24.0.0910.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Sep 2025 23:00:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-powerdirector-ultimate-425.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-powerdirector-ultimate-425.html
</guid><description>
CyberLink PowerDirector Ultimate is software editor, edit video and make movies on the computer from a variety of templates are made available, complete with effects, transitions, animations, and music. CyberLink PowerDirector 17 is a combination of video editing software with advanced video editing features powerful. Cblowing need to add your clips into the time line and click on 'Production'!
The tool design video in CyberLink PowerDirector have the ability to customize helps you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sigil 2.6.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Sep 2025 22:59:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sigil-1764.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sigil-1764.html
</guid><description>
Sigil is editor ebook full of features for the EPUB file, which you can use to create electronic books of his own from scratch and export them to EPUB format. Sigil offers editing, WYSIWYG, similar to a word processor, as well as edit the code directly for advanced users. The program provides a complete set of tools allows you to insert headings, specify fonts, add numbered list or bulleted, iamges, videos, Internet links and more, without having to write any HTML code whatsoever.
Sigil...
</description></item><item><title>Download DesktopImages3D 2.51</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Sep 2025 22:59:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopimages3d-7387.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopimages3d-7387.html
</guid><description>
DesktopImages3D is a desktop 3D visualization tool for MS Windows that is great for displaying images in an interlaced and creative way! Basic functions: total transparency, size settings, fonts, as well as a selection of different 3D themes are available and can be customized.
Features of DesktopImages3D
	3D box's optional transparency
	Several themes to display images
	Resizable
	Fixed position on screen
	Freely selectable position on screen.
</description></item><item><title>Download MusConv 4.10.417 Lifetime</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Sep 2025 22:59:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html
</guid><description>
MusConv transfers playlists, albums, followed artists and liked songs across a variety of services – Spotify, Apple Music, Amazon Music, YouTube, YouTube Music, iTunes, Deezer, Tidal, SoundCloud, Pandora and more 125 music services!
Features of MusConv Ultimate
	Transfer playlists, albums, followed artists and liked tracks between over 125 music servicesManage playlists (Delete, Merge, Split, Copy...)
	More than 125 music services supported
	Access DAILY updated music charts on...
</description></item></channel></rss>