<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 21:42:53 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 21:42:53 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Imagine 2.5.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 28 Feb 2026 23:49:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-imagine-7369.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-imagine-7369.html
</guid><description>
Imagine is an application that allows you to view images and animations in a variety of formats, including JPG, BMP, PNG and GIF. With Imagine you can view file properties and EXIF ​​information, copy, move, delete and rename images. Additionally, you can also flip, resize and rotate them, swap colors, set transparency levels, import, export, and edit palettes, and change color depth.
Features of Imagine
	View and save image/animation files at lightning speed
	Multiple...
</description></item><item><title>Download Active Data Studio 26.0.0.4</title><pubDate> Sat, 28 Feb 2026 23:47:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-active-data-studio-306.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-active-data-studio-306.html
</guid><description>
Active Data Studio is software to backup and restore discs, restore documents and deleted photos, delete disks securely, monitor HDD status and can repair PC when Windows can't start normally. Active@ Data Studio is a set of both apps to the desktop with a CD / DVD boot or USB disk to boot any system into the Windows Recovery Environment.
Features Active Data Studio
Active Data Studio perform data recovery
	Active@ File Recovery - recover files and folders deleted, even when deleted,...
</description></item><item><title>Download VideoMeld 1.82</title><pubDate> Sat, 28 Feb 2026 23:47:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-videomeld-5549.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-videomeld-5549.html
</guid><description>
VideoMeld is a brand new multi-path digital audio and video editing program. VideoMeld has one of the most advanced effects editors in its class. Multiple effects can be applied at the same time, creating astonishing variety. Effect settings can be precisely changed over time for detailed animations.
Key features include:
	High quality HD video up to 1920x1080 and save as MPEG 4 H. 264
	High quality 8-channel audio (7.1 surround sound)
	More than 50 video effects, transition effects...
</description></item><item><title>Download R-Wipe &amp;amp; Clean 20.0 Build 2548</title><pubDate> Sat, 28 Feb 2026 23:46:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-wipe-clean-891.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-wipe-clean-891.html
</guid><description>
R-Wipe &amp;amp; Clean is software to delete junk files, unnecessary files from your computer to release the storage space and speed up your computer. In addition, R-Wipe &amp;amp; Clean also unleash the capacity of your drive and delete information invasion of privacy on different operations online and offline including your internet history and cookies, the list of downloaded files and documents were open, buffer different data, temporary files and many other items, created by the operating...
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 8.5.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 28 Feb 2026 23:45:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-11-7760.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-11-7760.html
</guid><description>
TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 is a program that allows users to discover hidden settings in Windows 11. This application is specially designed for Windows 11, groups many registry settings and distribute them from the easy and secure user interface. With TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 you can move the Windows taskbar to the top and resize the taskbar by editing the registry value. With any application that modifies the registry, we recommend that you have a backup copy...
</description></item><item><title>Download Atlantis Word Processor 5.0.1.4</title><pubDate> Sat, 28 Feb 2026 23:45:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-atlantis-word-processor-585.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-atlantis-word-processor-585.html
</guid><description>
Atlantis Word Processor is a word processor app with features format, standard text, autocorrect, and spell check.  Atlantis is a word processor in accordance with most of the tasks handled daily text. The interface is very easy to use and offers the toolbars, hotkeys and sound effects thanh can customize (can turn off). It includes a clip library for quick access to the text or images used regular preview, font format and many other features aimed at improving the process of your...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wise Disk Cleaner 11.3.3.853</title><pubDate> Sat, 28 Feb 2026 23:44:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wise-disk-cleaner-392.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wise-disk-cleaner-392.html
</guid><description>
Wise Disk Cleaner software to clean hard drive by finding and deleting junk files downloads accumulate over time. Wise Disk Cleaner is pre-configured with about 50 types of extension files can usually be considered disposable, and you can extend the range by adding the file types of their own.
Wise Disk Cleaner to use the advanced algorithm with the ability to quick scan and comprehensive scan of hard drive space. Users can delete browsing history as well as the personal data important...
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 8.5.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 28 Feb 2026 23:42:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-10-7759.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-10-7759.html
</guid><description>
TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 is a utility that allows users to discover hidden settings in Windows 10. This application is specially designed for Windows 10, groups many registry settings and provide them from an easy and secure user interface. With TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 you can move the Windows taskbar to the top and resize the taskbar by editing the registry value. With any application that modifies the registry, we recommend that you have a backup copy to...
</description></item><item><title>Download InnoExtractor Ultra 2026 v11.5.1.172</title><pubDate> Sat, 28 Feb 2026 23:40:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-innoextractor-plus-4009.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-innoextractor-plus-4009.html
</guid><description>
InnoExtractor Plus is a handy lightweight but strong will allow you to use technology InnoUnp to easily extract the installer Inno Setup. Using this tool, you will be able to explore the content and the internal structure of installers and extract them to a folder on the local drive or on the storage device mobile without running the file setup. InnoExtractor Plus comes with graphical interface simple and user friendly, allowing you to easily open the installed just by drag and drop...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare DVD Creator 6.6.2.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 28 Feb 2026 23:39:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-dvd-creator-131.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-dvd-creator-131.html
</guid><description>
The software allows you to edit, create a DVD or simply combine videos with photos in your DVD. Anything you want to see, Wondershare DVD Creator to do all. Just pull fiction favorite into DVD Creator for Win (Windows 10 support), adjust the quality and click burn. Or use the integrated editor's powerful DVD Creator to combine photos, videos and your own music into home movies, slideshow, really anything that your imagination can handle.
Wondershare DVD Creator - Create DVD for your...
</description></item><item><title>Download QOwnNotes 26.2.15</title><pubDate> Sat, 28 Feb 2026 23:37:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qownnotes-3178.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qownnotes-3178.html
</guid><description>
QOwnNotes is notes bookmark file simple text (GPL) open source application for GNU / Linux , Mac OS X and Windows of Patrizio Bekerle ( pbek on GitHub and IRC) (optional) activity along with the notes application of ownCloud or Nextcloud. QOwnNote store your notes as plain text files and can be synchronized with synchronization function file of ownCloud / Nextcloud. You can also use other apps like Syncthing or Dropbox . Just write out your thoughts as they appear, and edit them if...
</description></item><item><title>Download iTop Easy Desktop 4.1.1.274</title><pubDate> Sat, 28 Feb 2026 23:35:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-itop-easy-desktop-7879.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-itop-easy-desktop-7879.html
</guid><description>
iTop Easy Desktop is a lightweight and easy-to-use desktop manager that organizes desktop icons, files and folders according to your rules, helping you Freed from the tedious arrangement of icons on the screen. It provides various practical features including but not limited to grouping desktop items, awakening live search, and quickly accessing icons and files even across multiple desktop sites. desktop.
Untidy desktop If you're not one to diligently organize your Windows desktop icons...
</description></item><item><title>Download Shotcut 26.2.26</title><pubDate> Sat, 28 Feb 2026 23:34:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-shotcut-2756.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-shotcut-2756.html
</guid><description>
Shotcut is a video editing application multi-platform free and open source for FreeBSD, Linux, macOS and Windows. Was started in 2011 by Dan Dennedy, Shotcut is developed on the multimedia MLT, which was developed from 2004. With age grow quite long years, Shotcut offers users many tools to perform the manipulation, Video editing based on adjusting each frame to enhance image quality. You can add an introduction, edit rate, bitrate, resolution or file encryption, and optionally use the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Massive X 1.7</title><pubDate> Sat, 28 Feb 2026 23:33:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-native-instruments-massive-x-2123.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-native-instruments-massive-x-2123.html
</guid><description>
Massive X is a synthesizer developed by Native Instruments, designed to create a wide variety of sounds and styles for electronic music production. It is the successor of the popular Massive synthesizer and offers many new features and improvements. Based on state-of-the-art architecture, it offers pristine sound and tremendous creative flexibility for artists and sound designers alike – allowing them to create, adjust, and experiment with sounds from a variety of sources. different...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube Downloader 3.9.18 (2702)</title><pubDate> Sat, 28 Feb 2026 23:31:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube Downloader  is a dedicated software that helps users  downloading youtube videos  Favorites on PC for offline viewing. With MediaHuman YouTube  Downloader  you can download videos from youtube website to your computer with  fast speed , with special software development technology that automatically receives videos from Websites, in addition to the ability to download videos from software websites, can convert downloaded video formats to various formats for the purpose...
</description></item><item><title>Download Obsidian 1.12.4</title><pubDate> Sat, 28 Feb 2026 23:30:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-obsidian-10386.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-obsidian-10386.html
</guid><description>
Obsidian is a powerful knowledge base that operates on a local folder containing plain text Markdown files. It allows users to create internal links for notes and then display the connections as a graph. Additionally users can also organize and structure their thoughts and knowledge in a flexible, non-linear way.
Features of Obsidian
Personal notes:
	Links: Create connections between your notes.
	Graph: Visualize the relationships between your notes.
	Plugins: Build your ideal...
</description></item><item><title>Download ExifTool 13.52</title><pubDate> Sat, 28 Feb 2026 23:28:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-exiftool-1685.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-exiftool-1685.html
</guid><description>
ExifTool is a library of Perl platform-independent plus a command line application for reading, writing, and editing meta information in various file types. ExifTool supports many metadata formats including EXIF , GPS , IPTC , XMP , JFIF , GeoTIFF , ICC Profile , Photoshop IRB , FlashPix , AFCP and ID3 , as well as notes of the manufacturer of many digital cameras by Canon , Casio , DJI , FLIR , FujiFilm , GE , GoPro , HP , JVC / Victor , Kodak , Leaf , Minolta / Konica-Minolta , Motorola...
</description></item><item><title>Download Kalmuri 4.2.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 28 Feb 2026 23:27:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kalmuri-12521.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kalmuri-12521.html
</guid><description>
Kalmuri provides one of the simplest means of recording screen activity, working as both a snapshot utility and a screen recorder. It requires no installation and is ready to go at any time, waiting for your action quietly in the tray area, thus not disturbing your work.
Features of Kalmuri
	Supports video recording (specify entire screen and area)
	Entire screen, active program, window control, application area
	Supports PNG, JPG, BMP, GIF, MP4 file formats
	Supports saving documents...
</description></item><item><title>Download ToDoList 9.1.12</title><pubDate> Sat, 28 Feb 2026 23:26:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-todolist-1637.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-todolist-1637.html
</guid><description>
ToDoList is an application note and task management with multiple options, set up help you to easily split and track the progress of the work. Todolist helps millions of people feel in control of their lives more and be the leader in a number of organizations inspired the world to believe. Todolist keep all to-dos of I in one place and perfectly integrated with the other tools that I use. It helps me turn everything faster.
ToDoList - management software job
Every day you have to...
</description></item><item><title>Download nTopology 5.41.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 28 Feb 2026 23:24:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ntopology-7887.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ntopology-7887.html
</guid><description>
nTopology is software that enables engineers and designers to create any geometry no matter how complex and meet the requirements of high performance products . Our software is used from research through production to create breakthrough products and processes for the aerospace, automotive, medical and consumer industries. Our customers depend on the general design capabilities of the nTopology to get the most out of new hardware, optimize components where performance is important,...
</description></item><item><title>Download NoScript 13.5.15 Chrome + Firefox</title><pubDate> Sat, 28 Feb 2026 23:24:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-noscript-116.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-noscript-116.html
</guid><description>
NoScript is an add-ons extension Firefox , Google Chrome allows you to interactively block Java, JavaScript, Flash a one-click button.
You can choose to temporary block or allow scripts on the current web page and also allows the reliable site by you is excluded from any action to block any.
Whenever you visit a website, all content scripts potential invasive are blocked by default and you can select it on the basis of each script from the status bar of browsers like Google Chrome,...
</description></item><item><title>Download HalfpriceSoft ezW2 13.0.18</title><pubDate> Sat, 28 Feb 2026 23:22:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-halfpricesoft-ezw2-8454.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-halfpricesoft-ezw2-8454.html
</guid><description>
HalfpriceSoft ezW2 is software designed to help users prepare and file W-2, W-3 and 1099-misc forms for employee and contractor income and tax reporting. It aims to be user-friendly and efficient, allowing users to easily enter information and create the necessary forms for filing with the IRS and SSA. This software is commonly used by small businesses, accountants, and tax professionals to automate the process of preparing and filing W-2 and 1099 forms.
Features of HalfpriceSoft...
</description></item><item><title>Download CameraFTP Virtual Security System 5.1.212.398</title><pubDate> Sat, 28 Feb 2026 23:21:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cameraftp-virtual-security-system-12406.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cameraftp-virtual-security-system-12406.html
</guid><description>
CameraFTP VSS is a powerful video surveillance program that can turn your PC/Laptop into a CCTV/DVR security system. It can display live scenes on the screen and record footage to the cloud. You can watch or play back footage anywhere, anytime. VSS also provides powerful screen recording features to monitor computer usage, record online classes/meetings, TV shows and games.
Features of CameraFTP VSS
	Common surveillance camera system features: Can view up to 25 cameras on one...
</description></item><item><title>Download Scientific Toolworks Understand 7.2 Build 1246</title><pubDate> Sat, 28 Feb 2026 23:21:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-scientific-toolworks-understand-1532.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-scientific-toolworks-understand-1532.html
</guid><description>
Scientific Toolworks Understand is a tool of static analysis to management, measurement and analysis, ability to program. This tool can measure multiple metrics and give you the clear chart about the indicator code different. For example: number of layers, number of project files, number of methods, number of lines, blank lines, comments, dead code, rate, comment on code, complexity in the cycle and the level of trouble of the code, the level of dependence of code together, the rate of...
</description></item><item><title>Download HalfpriceSoft ezW2Correction 3.12.6</title><pubDate> Sat, 28 Feb 2026 23:20:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-halfpricesoft-ezw2correction-8455.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-halfpricesoft-ezw2correction-8455.html
</guid><description>
HalfpriceSoft ezW2Correction is software designed to help users prepare and submit corrected W-2 and W-3 forms for employee income and tax reports, and contractors. It aims to be user-friendly and efficient, allowing users to easily enter information and create the necessary forms for filing with the IRS and SSA. This software is commonly used by small businesses, accountants, and tax professionals to automate the process of preparing and filing modified W-2 and W-3 forms.
Features of...
</description></item></channel></rss>