<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 14:08:32 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 14:08:32 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Solid Explorer File Manager 3.3.1 build 3003011</title><pubDate> Sun, 01 Feb 2026 16:45:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-solid-explorer-file-manager-8924.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-solid-explorer-file-manager-8924.html
</guid><description>
Solid Explorer is a file management application inspired by old file management applications. Solid Explorer is a popular file management app for Android devices that allows users to manage and organize their files and folders in an intuitive and user-friendly interface. It offers many features that make it stand out from other file management apps.
Solid Explorer allows you to navigate to files stored on your device and automatically organize them into collections. You can view,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Nova Launcher 81023 (8.3.1) Final</title><pubDate> Sun, 01 Feb 2026 16:45:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-nova-launcher-10503.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-nova-launcher-10503.html
</guid><description>
Nova Launcher is a powerful, customizable, and flexible home screen replacement. Nova brings advanced features to enhance your home screen but remains a great, user-friendly choice for everyone. Whether you want to completely overhaul your home screen or are looking for a cleaner, faster home screen launcher, Nova is the answer.
Nova Launcher Features
	Latest features: Nova brings the latest Android launcher features to all other phones.
	Custom icon themes: Nova supports thousands of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Psiphon VPN: Freedom Online v449</title><pubDate> Sun, 01 Feb 2026 16:44:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-psiphon-pro-8479.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-psiphon-pro-8479.html
</guid><description>
Psiphon Pro is a VPN application for Android that allows users to access the Internet freely and securely. It uses a combination of VPN, SSH and HTTP proxy technologies to bypass censorship and firewalls, providing users with unrestricted internet access. It gives you unprecedented access to your favorite news broadcast or social media platforms. In essence, Psiphon Pro also protects you when accessing WiFi hotspots by creating a secure, private tunnel between you and the Internet....
</description></item><item><title>Download Transparent clock weather Pro 9.01.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 01 Feb 2026 16:44:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-transparent-clock-weather-pro-8872.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-transparent-clock-weather-pro-8872.html
</guid><description>
Transparent Clock Weather Pro: Get Accurate Local or Worldwide Weather Forecasts Easily with Live Weather Updates, Hourly and Daily Weather Forecasts and Timely Weather Alerts. Check The Weather for Today, Tomorrow or the weekend with our Easy to use app and widgets.
Features of Transparent Clock Weather Pro
	local Weather: Automatically keep track or your location as you move and get accurate real time weather reports and alerts
	Different Weather Preded for More Accurate Weather...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wps Wpa Tester Premium 5.7 build 1057</title><pubDate> Sun, 01 Feb 2026 16:44:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wps-wpa-tester-premium-12979.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wps-wpa-tester-premium-12979.html
</guid><description>
Do you want to know if your Wireless Access Point is vulnerable to common security flaws? And how about knowing its speed? With Wps Wpa Tester you can find out if there are any vulnerabilities in your Wi-FI Access Point and if there are any issues with your network speed while doing a SpeedTest!
If you have a device running Android less than Pie (9) or a rooted Android device, you can actually test some WPS PIN attacks to know if your wireless Access Point or router is secure or...
</description></item><item><title>Download Money Lover - Spending Manager 8.63.0.95</title><pubDate> Sun, 01 Feb 2026 16:44:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-money-lover-spending-manager-8349.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-money-lover-spending-manager-8349.html
</guid><description>
Receive personal finance awards &amp;amp; Money management app to manage money now! Track your spending, monitor your transactions, create a monthly budget, motivate yourself to save money, and more. You can also link your Money Lover wallet to your bank account to automatically track your transaction history. Money Lover is a must-have app for personal finance management. Financial management becomes super easy and fast!
Managing personal finances can be difficult for many people. You need...
</description></item><item><title>Download Flashlight Plus: Bright Light 2.8.17</title><pubDate> Sun, 01 Feb 2026 16:43:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-flashlight-plus-bright-light-12999.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-flashlight-plus-bright-light-12999.html
</guid><description>
Turn your mobile phone into a flashlight and a magnifying glass! This is a new flashlight app. This smart two-in-one app has both a flashlight and a magnifying glass. OpticView™ lets you see what you're lighting on the screen, turning your phone into one of the most compact and powerful gadgets you've ever owned!
Features
	A simple and free flashlight app, great for emergencies
	Use your device's LED as a torch and bring the brightest flashlight on your phone!
	Turn on the...
</description></item><item><title>Download KMPlayer Plus (Divx Codec) 36.01.281</title><pubDate> Sun, 01 Feb 2026 16:43:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-kmplayer-plus-divx-codec-8720.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-kmplayer-plus-divx-codec-8720.html
</guid><description>
KMPlayer Plus with DivX codec is also available for Android devices, providing a powerful media player that supports many video and audio formats. These features include ad-free playback, cloud storage support, and high-resolution video playback support.
With support for DivX, KMPlayer Plus for Android allows users to watch high-quality DivX encoded videos on their mobile devices without the need for additional codecs or software. This is a convenient feature for users who want to watch...
</description></item><item><title>Download Oxford Vocabulary PRO 2.9.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 01 Feb 2026 16:43:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-oxford-vocabulary-9270.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-oxford-vocabulary-9270.html
</guid><description>
Oxford Vocabulary refers to the vocabulary used in the Oxford English Dictionary, considered by many to be the most comprehensive and authoritative dictionary of the English language. The Oxford English Dictionary includes more than 600,000 words, phrases and definitions, as well as information about their etymology, pronunciation and usage.
Features of the Oxford Vocabulary
	More than 3000+ Oxford words with full meanings and examples.
	Over 25,000 word examples.
	Easy to use...
</description></item><item><title>Download FotMob - Soccer Live Scores 222.15590.20260120</title><pubDate> Sun, 01 Feb 2026 16:42:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-fotmob-soccer-live-scores-8241.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-fotmob-soccer-live-scores-8241.html
</guid><description>
FotMob gives you all the live scores, stats and storylines to help you keep up with the world of football. Personalized news and notifications make it easy to follow your favorite teams and players. And lightning-fast match updates ensure you never miss a goal, no matter where you are.
Features of FotMob - Live soccer scores
	Live match score
	Results, schedule, standings and lineup
	Detailed statistics, including expected goals (xG) and expected assists (xA)
	Capture map
	Player...
</description></item><item><title>Download Scientific Calculator Pro 6.10.16</title><pubDate> Sun, 01 Feb 2026 16:42:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-scientific-calculator-pro-11445.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-scientific-calculator-pro-11445.html
</guid><description>
Turn your phone into the best scientific calculator you've ever used with this essential app. Basic, advanced, and graphing modes let you use only what you need, when you need it. It's fast, easy to use and looks real.
Main features
	No advertising
	Full-color graph
	Works in landscape and portrait mode
	Trigonometry, log, exponent
	Calculate fractions
	Complex numbers
	Linear equations and polynomials
	Basic statistical functions
	Binary, decimal, hexadecimal operations
	Bitwise...
</description></item><item><title>Download Shift Work Calendar (FlexR Pro) 7.20.00</title><pubDate> Sun, 01 Feb 2026 16:42:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-shift-work-calendar-flexr-pro-8382.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-shift-work-calendar-flexr-pro-8382.html
</guid><description>
Shift Work Schedule (FlexR Pro) is the #1 app for people who work multiple shifts, giving you all the options you want in one app to track work schedules mine! This app shows a clear view of your personal schedule for the coming weeks as well as your previous schedule. Combined with the ability to sync all your schedules with Google Agenda, this app will interface with all your Google apps flawlessly.
Another great feature is the auto-backup function, this feature prevents you from...
</description></item><item><title>Download Screen Recorder Video Recorder 8.2.2.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 01 Feb 2026 16:41:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-screen-recorder-video-recorder-12115.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-screen-recorder-video-recorder-12115.html
</guid><description>
This is a powerful and easy-to-use screen recording application that provides high-quality video and screenshot recording capabilities. It makes it easy for you to record videos, tutorials, play games, video calls, and any other moment you like. You can also trim, crop, and rotate to edit the video before sharing.
Features
	High quality recording: 1080P, 16Mbps, 120FPS
	Screen recorder with internal and external audio
	Cut, Crop and Rotate: finish recording, editing and sharing videos...
</description></item><item><title>Download Today Weather: Radar &amp;amp; Widgets 2.4.1-6</title><pubDate> Sun, 01 Feb 2026 16:41:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-today-weather-alerts-widgets-8915.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-today-weather-alerts-widgets-8915.html
</guid><description>
Weather Today is a beautiful and easy-to-use weather app that provides the world's most accurate local weather forecasts.
Features of Weather Today for Android
	Displays clear, easy-to-understand weather forecasts.
	Enjoy every moment you open the app with thousands of beautiful photos corresponding to the weather and day.
	Prepare for any situation with 24/7 weather forecasts and chance of rain.
	Protect your health with air quality, UV index and pollen count.
	Capture beautiful...
</description></item><item><title>Download Reminder Pro 4.1.6</title><pubDate> Sun, 01 Feb 2026 16:41:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-reminder-pro-8695.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-reminder-pro-8695.html
</guid><description>
Are you looking for a simple pop-up reminder app? Do you want to create reminders for one-time and recurring tasks? Get reminders and increase your productivity. Never forget an important task again! Finally, a simple and easy way to set reminders or deadline notifications. This hourly reminder app gets straight to the point. Set notifications to remind you of all your tasks, chores, and to-do list items, then sit back and clear your head.
No unnecessary or complicated features....
</description></item><item><title>Download Conversations (Jabber / XMPP) 2.19.9 build 4216604</title><pubDate> Sun, 01 Feb 2026 16:40:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-conversations-jabber-xmpp-11493.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-conversations-jabber-xmpp-11493.html
</guid><description>
Free and open source Jabber/XMPP client for Android. Easy to use, reliable, battery friendly. With built-in support for images, group chats and e2e encryption.
Main features
	End-to-end encryption with OMEMO or OpenPGP
	Encrypted audio and video calls (DLTS-SRTP)
	Send and receive images
	Intuitive user interface follows Android Design guidelines
	Image / Avatar for your Contacts
	Sync with desktop client
	Conference (with bookmark support)
	Address book integration
	Multiple accounts...
</description></item><item><title>Download Diseases Dictionary Offline 5.4</title><pubDate> Sun, 01 Feb 2026 16:40:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-diseases-dictionary-offline-14076.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-diseases-dictionary-offline-14076.html
</guid><description>
Diseases Dictionary Offline is a Medical Dictionary handbook, which can act as a clinical advisor for self-diagnosis and can also be used to look up symptoms, pathologies and treatments. Download free medical dictionary like a doctor for FREE at home, providing common diseases and treatment codes.
Features of the Medical App:
Offline – The app works offline, no internet connection required;
Detailed description of all major medical conditions and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Onkyo HF Player 2.14.3</title><pubDate> Sun, 01 Feb 2026 16:40:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-onkyo-hf-player-12073.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-onkyo-hf-player-12073.html
</guid><description>
Get more control over how the music sounds on your Android device with our touch-adjustable linear phase FIR equalizer, providing 16,384 distinct HD equalizer bands without loss sound quality. Create and save your own EQ presets or choose optimized filters created by professional musicians. HF Player for Android also enables playback of High-Resolution Audio formats including FLAC, 192 kHz/24-bit WAV and DSD at no additional charge.
Features:
	Updated user interface
	Lyrics are...
</description></item><item><title>Download Multi Calculator 1.9.7 build 479</title><pubDate> Sun, 01 Feb 2026 16:39:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-multi-calculator-9018.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-multi-calculator-9018.html
</guid><description>
A general-purpose calculator is a type of calculator that allows users to perform many types of calculations in a single application. It often includes features like basic arithmetic operations, scientific functions, unit conversions, currency conversions, etc.
Universal Calculator apps are typically available for smartphones and other mobile devices as well as for desktop computers. They can be useful for many users, including students, professionals, and anyone who needs to perform...
</description></item><item><title>Download Calculator Plus with History 8.1.8</title><pubDate> Sun, 01 Feb 2026 16:39:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-calculator-plus-with-history-10531.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-calculator-plus-with-history-10531.html
</guid><description>
Plus Calculator with History is the perfect calculator for Android. It remembers everything you calculate and allows you to review it at any time, which is perfect for me when shopping, doing homework, balancing my checkbook, or even helping with taxes. And if you need to quit your job and go do something else, I'll have it all ready for you when you get back. You'll never need to re-enter the same calculation twice.
Features of Calculator Plus with History
	Show your calculations in...
</description></item><item><title>Download Signal Strength 29.1.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 01 Feb 2026 16:39:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-signal-strength-8179.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-signal-strength-8179.html
</guid><description>
Signal Strength APK App is a type of app that allows users to view the mobile and/or Wi-Fi signal strength on their devices. These types of applications typically display signal strength as a numerical value (e.g., in dBm) or as a visual representation (e.g., using a series of bars, similar to those shown above). mobile phone).
In addition, some apps can also provide you with advanced information such as network type and service provider, IP address, etc. These apps can be used to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Hypersnap 9.7.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 23:31:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hypersnap-764.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hypersnap-764.html
</guid><description>
Hypersnap is a software screen capture from Windows screen and capture text (TextSnap) from places can't copy normal text. HyperSnap combines the power of screen capture app class with utility image editing advanced is packaged in a easy to use tool! It's perfect for capturing images that you want to put into the help system, online tutorials, manuals, training guides, presentations, marketing materials, website, email, and more. Use HyperSnap to quickly share a picture perfect...
</description></item><item><title>Download Allavsoft Video Downloader Converter 3.28.8.9526</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 23:30:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allavsoft-video-downloader-converter-248.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allavsoft-video-downloader-converter-248.html
</guid><description>
Allavsoft Video Downloader Converter software supports download movies, music videos, playlist, sport videos from video sharing website for free like Facebook, Youtube and over 100 video sharing sites.
Allavsoft is many users favorite thanks to the combined features simultaneous transmission of multiple videos and speed limit download video. Besides, the program also supports pause and resume data transmission, to help you interfere with the process of transmitting download data to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Free YouTube Download 4.5.4.130 Premium</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 23:30:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-download-1177.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-download-1177.html
</guid><description>
Free YouTube Download Premium is the most popular application to download videos from YouTube. The program was released in 2006 and regularly updated since then. Use the program to download and convert YouTube videos to view offline anytime.
Free YouTube Download - added Support to download youtube
Download more videos! Save whole playlists and YouTube channels, videos from a playlist individually (history, video be favorite, favourites, Watch later), videos from many different...
</description></item><item><title>Download Coolutils Total Excel Converter 7.1.0.107</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 23:29:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-total-excel-converter-849.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-total-excel-converter-849.html
</guid><description>
Coolutils Total Excel Converter is software that converts Excel documents to other formats like ODS, XML, SQL, WK2, WKS WAB, DBF, TEX and DIF for you to use. In addition, the software also supports converting Excel files into file DOC, DOCX, PDF, HTML, Access, TXT, ODT, ODS, XML, SQL, CSV, Lotus, DBF, TEX, DIFF, SYLK and LaTeX.
Coolutils Total Excel Converter - batch convert Excel
Total Excel Converter has a perfect layout and tight. When the conversion is finished you will get an...
</description></item></channel></rss>