<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 21:36:20 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 21:36:20 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Free Music and Video Downloader 3.12</title><pubDate> Sun, 18 Jan 2026 23:25:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-music-and-video-downloader-123.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-music-and-video-downloader-123.html
</guid><description>
Free Music &amp;amp; Video Downloader (formerly the Free Music Downloader) allows you to download his favorite music at the form of MP3 files from many different online sources, including Last.FM, Grooveshark, Sogou, VKontakte, SoundCloud, and many other things.Just enter name of artist or song you are looking for and click the Search button to see a list of results and download the songs you want.You can customize the services that applications will use to search, put the download folder...
</description></item><item><title>Download Explzh 10.01</title><pubDate> Sun, 18 Jan 2026 23:24:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-explzh-2278.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-explzh-2278.html
</guid><description>
Explzh is software that originated from Japan. This program works with most formats, can extract the file directly to FTP server, split large files into multiple smaller size. I would like to note that the storage supports encryption of files compressed using AES algorithm, has a system of tabs in the main window, you can search for the information you need in the repository and work with files, batch mode is done.
Explzh - Compress and decompress file
The file is support work with the...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinTools.net Professional / Premium / Classic 26.1.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 18 Jan 2026 23:20:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wintoolsnet-304.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wintoolsnet-304.html
</guid><description>
WinTools.net is an optimal tool working performance of the operating system and delete the unnecessary program from the hard drive and control the start-up process of Windows.
WinTools.net integrates many useful tools, to support increased processing speed and ability, stable operation for the computer include: Clean Uninstaller, Scan Files, Scan Registry, Start Up, Tweak UI, Net Tweaker, The Privacy. Scan Files are often used to scan the hard drive periodically, search for junk files or...
</description></item><item><title>Download RAM Saver Professional 26.1.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 18 Jan 2026 23:19:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ram-saver-pro-565.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ram-saver-pro-565.html
</guid><description>
RAM Saver Pro is a professional software optimize RAM is for system stable operation with high performance. RAM Saver Pro aims to provide all the tools necessary to increase the amount of free memory, at any time, also monitor and check the RAM.
When using RAM Saver Pro, you will be allowed to access its main menu by right-clicking on the tray icon. Also, if you want to display the main panel of the program you just double-click the icon. In addition, from the main interface of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Premium 22.2.1142</title><pubDate> Sun, 18 Jan 2026 23:19:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-diskimage-server-4547.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-diskimage-server-4547.html
</guid><description>
O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Server is software that is specially designed for use in enterprise environments, the software allows users to backup all the files you want and keep them safe from any incident or disaster computer. O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Server comes with a variety of easy to use utility that allows users to backup entire partitions of the specific files from their PC, as well as recover the version previous data of them, all from a simple interface.
O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Server - data...
</description></item><item><title>Download ExtraMAME 26.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 18 Jan 2026 23:18:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-extramame-2608.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-extramame-2608.html
</guid><description>
ExtraMAME is a simple tool that allows simulation of the arcade game from the most popular platform but is long forgotten, thanks to which the game industry has reached the current level. After launch, you will get 11 games pre-installed, among which are: Super Mario Bros, Pac-Man Plus, Space Invaders II and other games.
The simulation of multiple machine arcade is authored by Nicola Salmoria and team MAME. MAME lets you play thousands of arcade game old school on your computer. ExtraMAME...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinDirStat 2.5.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 18 Jan 2026 23:18:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windirstat-12594.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windirstat-12594.html
</guid><description>
WinDirStat is a program that allows you to find drives that are taking up a lot of space at a glance. It does that by displaying a drive, drives or folders in a treemap that allocates larger areas to larger files and folders. Separating those areas by coloring and other means allows you to immediately see which drives are taking up a lot of space and where to dig deeper. The directory tree is displayed as a tree list and tree diagram simultaneously. One can easily get an impression of...
</description></item><item><title>Download GoodSync Enterprise 12.9.23.3</title><pubDate> Sun, 18 Jan 2026 23:17:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-goodsync-enterprise-163.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-goodsync-enterprise-163.html
</guid><description>
GoodSync Enterprise is a software that saves files and files easily and is reliable. It automatically analyts, synchronize and backup your email, family photos, contacts, MP3, financial documentation and other important files-between desktop computers, laptops, servers, external drives and Windows Mobile devices as well as remotely via FTP , SFTP, WebDAV and more. The GoodSync synchronized software combines bulletproof reliability with an extremely easy interface to compare, synchronize...
</description></item><item><title>Download O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Premium WinPE 22.2.1142</title><pubDate> Sun, 18 Jan 2026 23:17:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-diskimage-workstation-4548.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-diskimage-workstation-4548.html
</guid><description>
O&amp;amp;O DiskImage WinPE is a program user friendly designed to help users create images of partitions and hard disk to keep them safe for their data in case disaster strikes. O&amp;amp;O DiskImage WinPE includes a set the ability to backup files and drives strong, helping users to easily keep data they want to secure. Users can create images of partitions or entire computer with just a few mouse clicks and they can also create the disk can boot if necessary.
Features of O&amp;amp;O DiskImage...
</description></item><item><title>Download iDealshare VideoGo 6.8.2.9498</title><pubDate> Sun, 18 Jan 2026 23:16:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idealshare-videogo-1045.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idealshare-videogo-1045.html
</guid><description>
iDealshare VideoGo is the software fast conversion of video files, audio, media online easily and keep the original quality. In addition, you can use the iDealshare VideoGo to download video or video editing functions, audio. iDealshare VideoGo is transition powerful video can convert all format video or audio to play back successfully on all types of media player or mobile device such as Windows Media Player, iTunes, QuickTime, iPad, iPhone, iPod, Apple TV, Android, Samsung Galaxy, HTC,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Inno Setup Unpacker 2.2.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 18 Jan 2026 23:15:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-inno-setup-unpacker-12546.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-inno-setup-unpacker-12546.html
</guid><description>
Inno Setup is a popular and reliable application that creates program installers by helping you create scripts. Extracting the installation files from their container, resulting from compiling code with Inno Setup, can only be done through self-extracting files. In other words, you need to create a self-extracting executable to shell the installation documents.
Inno Setup Unpacker can help you avoid such actions, which is especially useful because some system security protocols block...
</description></item><item><title>Download App Builder 2026.3</title><pubDate> Sun, 18 Jan 2026 23:15:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-app-builder-241.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-app-builder-241.html
</guid><description>
App Builder is a software application developer to help create and design apps, HTML5, web app, web app PWA on both platforms mobile and desktop. App Builder is professional software supports users to create the program HTML5 without writing code. It is very easy to use, suitable with all users who lack of professional knowledge in the field of programming and application design.
App Builder brings to 22 different themes that users can use to design for your app. You can choose 1 or a...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Downloader 10.1.3</title><pubDate> Sun, 18 Jan 2026 23:14:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html
</guid><description>
YTD Youtube Downloader is an application that reliable and intuitive, allowing you to quickly download YouTube videos and save them to your computer. You can also convert the media files to the format desired video or extract audio streams and save separately. YTD Youtube Downloader lets you save your favorite clips of yourself from Youtube, Facebook, Vimeo and Dailymotion to your desktop. The software supports URLS from many web site hosting, multimedia and allows you to download desired...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tax Assistant for Excel Professional 7.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 18 Jan 2026 23:14:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tax-assistant-for-excel-professional-10690.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tax-assistant-for-excel-professional-10690.html
</guid><description>
Tax Assistant for Excel Professional is a custom application written for Microsoft Excel and requires Microsoft Excel 2010/2013/2016/2019/365. It simplifies your Federal Income Tax preparation by providing an Excel workbook with IRS-approved alternative forms to Form 1040 and Form 1040A with Forms A, B, C, C-EZ, D, E, SE, Forms 6251 (AMT), 4952, 6781, 8829, 8949 and 8995. There are also several worksheets related to deductions and Schedule D covering Benefits Social Security, Qualified...
</description></item><item><title>Download Easy Notes - Note Taking Apps 1.3.38.0114</title><pubDate> Sun, 18 Jan 2026 22:45:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-easy-notes-notebook-notepad-8388.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-easy-notes-notebook-notepad-8388.html
</guid><description>
Easy Notes - Great note taking app, Notepad, Notebook, Free Notes is a free easy to use note taking app for notes app. With this easy notebook and notepad app, take quick notes with colorful backgrounds and checklists to organize notes and tasks easily. Use this aesthetic note taker and note taker to add photos or audio to your notes. Easy Notes is a useful notebook and note-taking app for taking notes and organizing work.
Features of Easy Notes - Notebook, Notepad
	Free Notepad and...
</description></item><item><title>Download AR Ruler App: Tape Measure Cam 3.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 18 Jan 2026 22:45:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ar-ruler-app-tape-measure-cam-8721.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ar-ruler-app-tape-measure-cam-8721.html
</guid><description>
AR Ruler app is a mobile app that uses augmented reality (AR) technology to measure distances, angles, and sizes of objects in real-world environments. This app works by using the device's camera and sensors to create a virtual 3D representation of a real-life environment.
The AR Ruler app uses augmented reality (AR) technology to measure the real world using your smartphone's camera. Target the detected plane and start using the AR
tape measure tool
Features of AR Ruler...
</description></item><item><title>Download Password Safe and Manager 9.0.8 build 900032</title><pubDate> Sun, 18 Jan 2026 22:45:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-password-safe-and-manager-8210.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-password-safe-and-manager-8210.html
</guid><description>
Password Safe and Manager is a password management application for Android devices. The app also includes features like login autofill, a password generator, and a built-in browser to access your account directly from the app. It's a great way to securely store and manage your login information and other sensitive information.
Summary of essential functions
	securely store passwords, access data, etc.
	classify your entries in Password Security
	access via a single master...
</description></item><item><title>Download Knots 3D 10.7.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 18 Jan 2026 22:45:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-knots-3d-8500.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-knots-3d-8500.html
</guid><description>
Knots 3D is a mobile application that provides visual and interactive instructions for tying different types of knots. This app can be used to learn and practice different knots, with detailed animations and illustrations showing the correct technique for each knot. Used by arborists, fishermen, firefighters, climbers, military, and boy and girl scouts worldwide, Knots 3D will quickly teach you how to tie even the most difficult knots!
With more than 175 nautical miles, Knots 3D will be...
</description></item><item><title>Download Castro Premium - system info 4.8.4 build 370</title><pubDate> Sun, 18 Jan 2026 22:44:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-castro-premium-system-info-10230.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-castro-premium-system-info-10230.html
</guid><description>
Castro is an information utility for your tablets and smartphones. It displays various diagnostic information about the device. Castro processes and displays a huge amount of information, namely
	Detailed processor statistics (CPU and GPU);
	Battery monitoring;
	Consumes all types of memory;
	Data usage over Wi-Fi and mobile networks;
	Real-time sensor data with helpful graphs;
	Detailed information about the device's camera;
	Full list of available audio and video codecs;
	Monitor the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Bundled Notes - List, Organize 4.0.7-005</title><pubDate> Sun, 18 Jan 2026 22:44:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-bundled-notes-list-organize-13704.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-bundled-notes-list-organize-13704.html
</guid><description>
Organize everything - from personal notes, lists, and projects to movie watchlists, recipes, bookmarks, and more Whether you keep your notes and lists simple or like to customize them to meet all your organizational needs, Bundled Notes is the app for you.
Key Features:
	Beautiful Material Design You Design With Dynamic Themes
	Ad-Free Experience
	Seamless Syncing Across Devices equipped
	Markdown support with visual formatting
	Powerful organization with “bundles”
	Kanban board...
</description></item><item><title>Download Camera Editor- Sweet Selfie 5.7.1766</title><pubDate> Sun, 18 Jan 2026 22:44:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-camera-editor-sweet-selfie-13570.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-camera-editor-sweet-selfie-13570.html
</guid><description>
The best FREE selfie photo editor and beauty camera with all the features, face editor, body editor, background blur, art filters, live stickers and makeup effects! Sweet Selfie is the top selfie photo editor and beauty camera with real-time beauty effects, help you take selfies easily, edit photos, images and videos even boomerang for Instagram, Facebook, Messenger, Whatsapp, Snapchat, Twitter, Wechat, etc.
Features:
	Selfie camera can help you take perfect selfies and easily share...
</description></item><item><title>Download Balance: Meditation &amp;amp; Sleep 1.192.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 18 Jan 2026 22:43:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-balance-meditation-sleep-8559.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-balance-meditation-sleep-8559.html
</guid><description>
Improve stress, sleep and more with the world's first personalized meditation program. Balance is your personal meditation coach. Each day, you will answer questions about your meditation experience, goals, and interests. Using an audio library of thousands of files, Balance puts together the perfect daily meditation for you. The more you share over time, the more personalized and effective your meditation becomes.
Balance's daily meditation sessions are organized according to a 10-Day...
</description></item><item><title>Download Alternate Quick Audio 2.230</title><pubDate> Sun, 18 Jan 2026 16:17:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-alternate-quick-audio-2275.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-alternate-quick-audio-2275.html
</guid><description>
Alternate Quick Audio is software support audio player, already know want to find something new for yourself. This program lets you play, record and convert your music in MP3 format and WAV. The interface is very simple, even boring in places, but it does not cause confusion, everything is clear immediately after launch. Transition allows you to work with formats such as MP2, MPG, MP4, OGG, FLAC, FLV, AAC.
Alternate Quick Audio - Listen to audio recording
Alternate Quick Audio has an...
</description></item><item><title>Download ET Optimizer 6.08.15</title><pubDate> Sun, 18 Jan 2026 16:16:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-et-optimizer-9574.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-et-optimizer-9574.html
</guid><description>
ET-Optimizer is a free, open source script to improve your computer's overall performance and optimize it for your workflow through optimized scripting. With this optimization, setup takes little effort. The script is developed from many sources found on the Internet, tested and updated for different versions of the system. The whole script is contained in 1 file, it uses: command prompt, powershell, power plan configuration, startup configuration, registry changes, network interface...
</description></item><item><title>Download LrToolbox 2026.0.1.27</title><pubDate> Sun, 18 Jan 2026 16:15:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lrtoolbox-13054.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lrtoolbox-13054.html
</guid><description>
LrToolbox is a comprehensive Windows software designed to handle your Lightroom catalog with ease. Whether you are a professional photographer or an amateur, this tool will help you streamline your workflow and increase your productivity. Whether you need to extract previews from a catalog, convert your photo ratings to sidecar files, or convert RAW images to JPG, LrToolbox is here to help you with just a few clicks.
Key Features
	Compatible with Adobe Lightroom Classic 14.2 (February...
</description></item></channel></rss>