<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 13:50:38 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 13:50:38 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download ClevNote - Notepad, Checklist 2.24.10</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Dec 2025 16:34:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-clevnote-notepad-checklist-8746.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-clevnote-notepad-checklist-8746.html
</guid><description>
ClevNote is a note-taking and checklist app for Android devices. It allows users to create and manage various types of notes, such as to-do lists, grocery lists, reminders, and more. ClevNote is a memo application that helps users write necessary daily memos
Features of ClevNote for Android
	Simple and easy-to-use interface
	Supports creating and managing multiple notes and checklists
	Ability to set reminders for specific notes or tasks
	Built-in templates for common note types, such...
</description></item><item><title>Download CalenGoo - Calendar and Tasks 1.0.183 build 1696</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Dec 2025 16:33:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-calengoo-calendar-and-tasks-8600.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-calengoo-calendar-and-tasks-8600.html
</guid><description>
CalenGoo is a calendar app for Android devices that allows users to manage their schedules, appointments, and events. It syncs with Google Calendar and has features like a customizable interface, reminders, and the ability to view multiple calendars at once.
Features of CalenGoo for Android
	Sync all your past and future events with Google Calendar (just add your Google account in "Settings &amp;gt; Accounts" instead of syncing via Android calendar).&amp;lt; /li&amp;gt;
	Sync calendars with...
</description></item><item><title>Download Carly - OBD2 car scanner 49.71</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Dec 2025 16:33:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-carly-obd2-car-scanner-8278.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-carly-obd2-car-scanner-8278.html
</guid><description>
Carly is a mobile OBD2 (On-Board Diagnostics) car scanner application that allows users to diagnose, monitor and repair their vehicles. The application works by connecting to the vehicle's OBD2 port, usually located under the dashboard, and collecting data from the vehicle's computer system. The adapter and app work with Audi, BMW, Lexus, Mercedes, Mini, Porsche, Renault, Seat, Skoda, Toyota, VW and most car brands in the world with OBD2 port.
Carly - OBD2 car scanner Features
Check...
</description></item><item><title>Download Easy Notes - Note Taking Apps 1.3.35.1218</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Dec 2025 16:33:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-easy-notes-notebook-notepad-8388.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-easy-notes-notebook-notepad-8388.html
</guid><description>
Easy Notes - Great note taking app, Notepad, Notebook, Free Notes is a free easy to use note taking app for notes app. With this easy notebook and notepad app, take quick notes with colorful backgrounds and checklists to organize notes and tasks easily. Use this aesthetic note taker and note taker to add photos or audio to your notes. Easy Notes is a useful notebook and note-taking app for taking notes and organizing work.
Features of Easy Notes - Notebook, Notepad
	Free Notepad and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Duolingo: language lessons 6.60.6</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Dec 2025 16:33:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-duolingo-language-lessons-8265.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-duolingo-language-lessons-8265.html
</guid><description>
Duolingo is a popular language learning app that offers interactive lessons to help users learn new languages. This application offers many languages for you to choose from, including Spanish, French, German, Italian, Portuguese, Chinese, Japanese and many more.
This app offers an gamified learning experience with interactive lessons, exercises, and quizzes designed to help users learn new words, phrases, and grammar rules. This app is designed to be easy to use and suitable for people...
</description></item><item><title>Download PhotoDirector: AI Photo Editor 20.8.7</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Dec 2025 16:32:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-photodirector-photo-editor-8144.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-photodirector-photo-editor-8144.html
</guid><description>
PhotoDirector is a photo editing app for Android devices that allows you to edit and enhance your photos with a variety of tools and effects. With PhotoDirector, you can adjust your photo's color and lighting, remove blemishes and other imperfections, and apply filters to give your photos a unique look. You can also use PhotoDirector to create photo collages and slideshows, add text and stickers to photos, and share your edited photos on social networks or through other sharing...
</description></item><item><title>Download AI Translate Voice Translator 428.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Dec 2025 16:32:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-talkao-translate-translator-8426.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-talkao-translate-translator-8426.html
</guid><description>
You can hold a conversation in any language with the help of a voice translator, translate different texts and use the button app to chat. Learn languages ​​quickly and easily, speak your language to translate written or spoken words in the language of your choice, more than 80 languages ​​in text such as English Spanish, French, German, Italian, Korean, Chinese, Japanese and 44 languages ​​spoken such as those mentioned above and many more such as Arabic, Danish, Dutch,...
</description></item><item><title>Download ClevCalc - Calculator 2.24.3</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Dec 2025 16:32:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-clevcalc-calculator-8333.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-clevcalc-calculator-8333.html
</guid><description>
ClevCalc - Calculator is a mobile application that provides calculator functionality for Android devices. This is a simple, easy-to-use calculator application that can perform basic mathematical operations such as addition, subtraction, multiplication and division as well as more advanced functions such as square roots, logarithms and trigonometric functions.&amp;lt; /p&amp;gt;
Features of ClevCalc - Calculator
	Basic math operations such as addition, subtraction, multiplication and...
</description></item><item><title>Download KMPlayer Plus (Divx Codec) 35.12.222</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Dec 2025 16:31:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-kmplayer-plus-divx-codec-8720.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-kmplayer-plus-divx-codec-8720.html
</guid><description>
KMPlayer Plus with DivX codec is also available for Android devices, providing a powerful media player that supports many video and audio formats. These features include ad-free playback, cloud storage support, and high-resolution video playback support.
With support for DivX, KMPlayer Plus for Android allows users to watch high-quality DivX encoded videos on their mobile devices without the need for additional codecs or software. This is a convenient feature for users who want to watch...
</description></item><item><title>Download Professional barometer 5.3</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Dec 2025 16:31:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-professional-barometer-12977.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-professional-barometer-12977.html
</guid><description>
Professional barometer. You will be able to view the atmospheric pressure trend in real time, thus predicting the weather changes. Absolute precision through the parallel operation of various sensors, such as device pressure sensors, gps sensors and remote time connection to weather stations near you.
It proposes a barometer with an analog dial with the ability to select different quadrants, available with all available measurements (hPa, inHg, mmHg, mbar), you can see in addition to...
</description></item><item><title>Download OfficeMail Pro 1.8.8</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Dec 2025 16:31:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-rework-email-calendar-8803.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-rework-email-calendar-8803.html
</guid><description>
Re:Work, an email client application using ActiveSync is not only a safe and secure email application but also an application that consolidates various convenient aspects. This is a product that has been significantly improved and implemented many features such as shared mailboxes and calendars to collaborate with your colleagues.
Therefore, this will be a great gift for those who are looking for secure email for personal and work use. Re:Work will provide powerful capabilities...
</description></item><item><title>Download SD Card Test Pro 2.9 build 89</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Dec 2025 16:31:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sd-card-test-pro-8928.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sd-card-test-pro-8928.html
</guid><description>
SD Card Test Pro is an application for Android devices that allows users to test the performance and speed of SD cards. This application is designed to help users determine whether their SD card is functioning properly and whether it is capable of meeting their performance and memory needs.
Features of SD Card Test Pro
	Measuring the speed of an external (removable) SD card
	Measure your internal memory speed
	Verify written data: detect damaged or fake cards
	Read/write tests in...
</description></item><item><title>Download Signal Strength 29.0.9</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Dec 2025 16:30:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-signal-strength-8179.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-signal-strength-8179.html
</guid><description>
Signal Strength APK App is a type of app that allows users to view the mobile and/or Wi-Fi signal strength on their devices. These types of applications typically display signal strength as a numerical value (e.g., in dBm) or as a visual representation (e.g., using a series of bars, similar to those shown above). mobile phone).
In addition, some apps can also provide you with advanced information such as network type and service provider, IP address, etc. These apps can be used to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Plant Parent: Plant Care Guide 1.104</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Dec 2025 16:30:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-plant-parent-plant-care-guide-13014.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-plant-parent-plant-care-guide-13014.html
</guid><description>
Plant Parent is an all-in-one app designed to help you become the best plant caretaker you can be. Plant Parent provides everything you need to keep your green friends thriving. Whether you're a seasoned plant enthusiast or just starting out, Plant Parent offers a variety of features to make plant care easy and fun.
Why Plant Parent?
	Easy-to-use interface: Navigate through the app with a clean, intuitive design.
	Personalized care tips: Get customized care advice based on your plant...
</description></item><item><title>Download Lighting Calculations 6.1.11</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Dec 2025 16:30:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-lighting-calculations-8927.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-lighting-calculations-8927.html
</guid><description>
Lighting calculation is the best application in the field of lighting, it has many calculations that can help you in your work. Lighting calculations are used to determine the amount of light needed in a given space or area to achieve the desired lighting level. These calculations take into account a number of factors, including the size and shape of the space, the type and placement of lighting fixtures, and the brightness of the light source.
Calculate total luminous flux, Indoor...
</description></item><item><title>Download WiFi Mouse Pro 5.6.9</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Dec 2025 16:29:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wifi-mouse-pro-8925.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wifi-mouse-pro-8925.html
</guid><description>
Convert your phone into a wireless mouse, keyboard and trackpad for your computer, it allows you to control your PC/Mac/Linux easily via local network connection. Media Controller, Presentation Controller and Remote File Explorer are all included in this controller app.
Now you can relax on the sofa and control movies or games in the comfort of your own home, replacing your broken mouse and keyboard with this app.
Features of WiFi Mouse Pro
	Fully simulated mouse
	Built-in support...
</description></item><item><title>Download Voice Notes (Pro) 5.1.97</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Dec 2025 16:29:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-voice-notes-pro-12031.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-voice-notes-pro-12031.html
</guid><description>
Voice Notes (Pro) is a powerful and flexible app for Android users that allows you to easily record, save and organize voice notes on your device. Whether you need to quickly jot down reminders, voice memos, or record meetings, this app has you covered. With a user-friendly interface and powerful features, Voice Notes (Pro) is a must-have tool for those who want to stay organized and productive on the go.
Main features:
	Just one touch. It can further receive your speech and convert...
</description></item><item><title>Download MyRadar Weather Radar Premium 8.67.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Dec 2025 16:29:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-myradar-weather-radar-8127.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-myradar-weather-radar-8127.html
</guid><description>
MyRadar is a weather monitoring and forecasting application for Android devices. It provides users with real-time weather information, including radar maps, current conditions, and forecasts for locations around the world. To use MyRadar, users must download the app from the Google Play Store or other Android app store or taiwebs.com.
Features of MyRadar Weather Radar Pro APK
	Animated radar map shows the movement of precipitation over time
	Current temperature, humidity, and wind...
</description></item><item><title>Download CodeMatics Universal TV Remote Control 2.9.4</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Dec 2025 16:28:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-codematics-universal-tv-remote-control-11491.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-codematics-universal-tv-remote-control-11491.html
</guid><description>
For Smart TV/Devices, the only setting required is to connect your phone as well as your Smart TV/Device to the same Wifi network. For IR TVs, your phone must have a built-in Infrared (IR) feature for the app to work as a remote control. The IR feature is required to send signals from the phone to the TV like a regular TV remote.
You can now Cast media files stored on your mobile phone to your Smart TV screen.
Smart TV function
	Voice search
	Power control.
	Mute / Volume...
</description></item><item><title>Download COL Reminder 3.7.7.2 build 688</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Dec 2025 16:28:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-col-reminder-8193.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-col-reminder-8193.html
</guid><description>
COL Reminder is a reminder application for your Android phone. Available in over 40 languages: English, German, Italian, French, Swedish, Spanish, Chinese, Polish, Korean, Hungarian, Turkish, Czech, Slovak
Features of COL Reminder
	Text reminder
	Phone call reminder
	Remind parking time with countdown
	Birthday reminder
	Location-based reminders
	Dashclock Utility Extension
	Back up Google Drive
</description></item><item><title>Download Ultra GPS Logger 3.210</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Dec 2025 16:28:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ultra-gps-logger-8913.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ultra-gps-logger-8913.html
</guid><description>
Ultra GPS Logger is a GPS Tracker that allows you to create NMEA, KML and/or GPX logs using a GPS or GLONASS enabled Android device. It can enable GPS while in standby mode, allowing long periods of time to be recorded without interacting with the device.
Ultra GPS Logger Features
	Format: NMEA, KML, GPX, CSV
	Raw logging, by distance or time
	Sign in standby
	Auto Record, Auto Start
	Send diary/track via email
	Publish to FTP
	Log compression: Zip, KMZ
	Google Maps, Open Street...
</description></item><item><title>Download Volume Control 6.5.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Dec 2025 16:27:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-volume-control-9600.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-volume-control-9600.html
</guid><description>
Volume Control is a great app that lets you control your device's volume – instead of being controlled by it! Simply adjust existing volume profiles or create new predefined volume profiles and switch between them with a single tap. Individual profiles include: Alarm, Media, Ringer, Notifications, Voice (in-call), Bluetooth, and overall system volume.
Volume Control Features
	Volume control also detects when you plug in headphones or activate Bluetooth and automatically switches to...
</description></item><item><title>Download ASICS Runkeeper - Run Tracker 16.19</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Dec 2025 16:27:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-asics-runkeeper-run-tracker-8334.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-asics-runkeeper-run-tracker-8334.html
</guid><description>
Join a community that helps people escape difficulties and stick with running forever! Track your workouts, set goals, sweat, and see your progress. Whether you're trying to track a 5K goal or train for a marathon, use the GPS app trusted by 50 million users and counting.
ASICS Runkeeper - Run Tracker is a mobile application that allows users to track running and fitness activities on their Android devices. The app uses GPS to track the user's distance, pace, and running time as well as...
</description></item><item><title>Download Device Info: System &amp;amp; CPU Info 3.4.1.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Dec 2025 16:27:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-device-info-system-cpu-info-8723.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-device-info-system-cpu-info-8723.html
</guid><description>
Device Information: System &amp;amp; CPU Information is a mobile application that provides users with detailed information about the hardware and software specifications of their device. This app is designed to help users better understand their device's capabilities and performance as well as diagnose any potential issues or problems.
With Device Info: System and CPU Info, users can view information about the processor, memory, storage, battery, sensors, and more. of equipment. This app...
</description></item><item><title>Download Money Lover - Spending Manager 8.60.0.58</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Dec 2025 16:26:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-money-lover-spending-manager-8349.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-money-lover-spending-manager-8349.html
</guid><description>
Receive personal finance awards &amp;amp; Money management app to manage money now! Track your spending, monitor your transactions, create a monthly budget, motivate yourself to save money, and more. You can also link your Money Lover wallet to your bank account to automatically track your transaction history. Money Lover is a must-have app for personal finance management. Financial management becomes super easy and fast!
Managing personal finances can be difficult for many people. You need...
</description></item></channel></rss>