<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 21:33:09 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 21:33:09 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download LDPlayer 9.1.61.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 00:32:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ldplayer-2331.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ldplayer-2331.html
</guid><description>
LDPlayer is software that emulates Android, allowing users to play games, run apps on a Windows computer. LDPlayer support play heavy games, run chat applications, photo editing, video and many other Android apps, LDPlayer compatible with Android 5.1 and above, supports multitasking for experience not inferior when used on Mobile.
Installation is a simple process and quickly without the need for special attention from your side, there's more. installed, you can't touch them. This...
</description></item><item><title>Download Topaz Photo AI Pro 4.1.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 00:31:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-photo-ai-8105.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-photo-ai-8105.html
</guid><description>
What is Topaz Photo AI?
Topaz Photo AI is a professional software that automatically adjusts for your image quality needs. Simply import images into Topaz Photo AI and it will use specially trained AI models to first detect unique details, clarity, and resolution issues before applying the intelligently adjusts to maximize your image quality.
For users experienced with Topaz Labs image quality applications, it combines the functionality of DeNoise AI, Sharpen AI and Gigapixel AI into...
</description></item><item><title>Download Prevent Restore Pro 2025 v112</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 00:30:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-prevent-restore-pro-1473.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-prevent-restore-pro-1473.html
</guid><description>
Prevent Restore Pro is software prevent restore files deleted in any drive: external hard drives and hard drives mounted in hard drive, SSD, Flash drives, except CD-ROM and CD-RW. The software uses many security algorithms can be used to get data.Our program includes some of the most reliable and accepted as standard.
Prevent Restore Pro - Prevent restore files deleted
The features of Prevent Restore Pro
Mode to clean up quickly
	In this mode, the program will not overwrite the free...
</description></item><item><title>Download Capture One Pro 16.6.6.3111 + Enterprise</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 00:30:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capture-one-pro-624.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capture-one-pro-624.html
</guid><description>
Capture One Pro is the software solution complete photo editing. With powerful tools to organize, color grading, editing grades, and more, you have full control over the images and process his work. Capture One has been developed with quality images and easy to use. Every tool is designed to give you full control over all aspects of the process editing - preserve, restore and optimize all information from the file RAW of you. Full the tool provides the ability to expand to always achieve...
</description></item><item><title>Download iDefender 5.1.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 00:29:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idefender-13959.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idefender-13959.html
</guid><description>
iDefender is an advanced security solution designed for the home, providing both a High-Performance Intrusion Prevention System (HIPS) and Real-Time Endpoint Detection and Response (EDR). This integrated system protects against potential threats, ensuring the safety and integrity of your devices by proactively monitoring and responding to suspicious activity.
Why iDefender?
Ransomware Prevention
	Detects and blocks ransomware in real time to protect important files from malicious...
</description></item><item><title>Download PlayerFab (Ultra HD Player) 7.0.5.3</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 00:28:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dvdfab-player-ultra-68.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dvdfab-player-ultra-68.html
</guid><description>
PlayerFab (DVDFab Player Ultra) is one of the best 4K UHD media players. The software plays DVD, Blu-ray, 4K Ultra HD Blu-ray and also supports online video. It supports native navigation menus, along with HDR10, and supports high-resolution audio output. PlayerFab supports watching videos of a variety of popular streaming platforms such as Amazon, Netflix, Tubi, Peacock, and more.
Video streaming in FHD 1080p video quality and high quality EAC3 audio quality is the prerequisite and...
</description></item><item><title>Download DesktopDigitalClock 6.11</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 00:27:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopdigitalclock-4114.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopdigitalclock-4114.html
</guid><description>
DesktopDigitalClock is a program that desktop clock digital simply and beautifully with the theme and different custom for all MS-OS was inspired from the lock screen! Be made according to numerous requests of users, with the idea of the clock lock screen appearance in Windows 10 / 8.1 after login, display the time and date when the log in the left corner, to the analog clock to appear on desktop Windows.
DesktopDigitalClock - the clock on the computer
The basic function: high...
</description></item><item><title>Download iTubeGo YouTube Downloader 10.8.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 00:27:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-itubego-youtube-downloader-3681.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-itubego-youtube-downloader-3681.html
</guid><description>
iTubeGo YouTube Downloader  is the best way to download live video from 1000+ streaming sites. iTubeGo YouTube Downloader is a powerful download tool that allows you to save video and audio for free. The output format of high speed converter is high quality MP4, MP3. Fully compatible with iPhone, iPad, iTunes, iMovie, Android Phone and more.
iTubeGo YouTube Downloader - Solution for downloading high quality Youtube video 
Features of iTubeGo YouTube Downloader
	Download videos from...
</description></item><item><title>Download Stellar Repair for Photo 8.8.0.0 (All Editions)</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 00:26:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stellar-repair-for-photo-7897.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stellar-repair-for-photo-7897.html
</guid><description>
Stellar Repair for Photo is the best software to repair damaged .JPG or .JPEG format photos. Stellar Repair for Photo will fix your completely unreadable JPEG files even in situations where the header is corrupted, the JPEG data is corrupted, the JPEG file structure is invalid, the JPEG marker is unknown or invalid ratio, missing SOS marker, etc.
Stellar Repair for Photo software is easy to use with a simple and intuitive GUI. You will find a progress bar showing the exact status of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Saver Pro 10.8.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 00:19:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-saver-6830.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-saver-6830.html
</guid><description>
YT Saver is a software that supports downloading Video, Audio, Playlist from 10,000+ websites, Convert Video to MP4, MOV, AAC, WAV and more. YT Saver is a powerful downloader that allows you to save video and audio for free. The output format of the high-speed converter is high-quality MP4, MP3. Fully compatible with iPhone, iPad, iTunes, iMovie, Android Phone and more.
Supported Input Formats:
	Video: MP4, M4V, 3GP, MPEG, DAT, AVI, ASF, WMV, VOB, MKV, FLV, 3GS, 3G2, F4V, WEBM, TS,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Remote Desktop Manager Enterprise 2025.2.28</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 00:19:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-remote-desktop-manager-enterprise-242.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-remote-desktop-manager-enterprise-242.html
</guid><description>
Remote Desktop Manager Enterprise software is the complete management of remote connections and virtual machines from a single location, at the same time access support data online and cloud storage. Remote Desktop Manager supports multiple types of connections, not only connections for the protocol connect remote computer Remote Desktop Protocol (RDP).
Remote Desktop Manager easily add, edit, delete, share, organize and find your remote connection of you quickly. Compatible with...
</description></item><item><title>Download UpdatePack7R2 25.9.10</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 00:19:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-updatepack7r2-6614.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-updatepack7r2-6614.html
</guid><description>
UpdatePack7R2 is software that allows you to update a working system and integrate software updates in the distribution. Can be installed on any version of Windows 7 and Server 2008 R2, any digit and any language. Includes updates for all versions of Internet Explorer, all critical, recommended, and security updates.
How to use UpdatePack7R2 software:
	The system must have at least 10 GB of free space on the hard drive and preferably no less than 1 GB of free RAM.
	Key / Reboot to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Bandizip Pro 7.40</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 00:18:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bandizip-pro-4717.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bandizip-pro-4717.html
</guid><description>
Bandizip Pro is the professional version support for archive files ZIP, 7Z, RAR, ALZ, EGG, TAR, BH, LZH, GZ, BZ2, ISO, CAB, WIM, XZ, ARJ, and Z and user can create files self-extracting (.EXE) and archive files multi-volume (split). Bandizip Pro algorithms, Zip is very fast to compress and extract function fast Drag-and-Drop and storage Function, High-Speed.
Drag and Drop quick of BandiZip does not use temporary folder, and it just extract directly into the folder that is targeted. It...
</description></item><item><title>Download Inno Setup Compiler 6.5.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 00:17:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-inno-setup-compiler-2655.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-inno-setup-compiler-2655.html
</guid><description>
Inno Setup Compiler is a system installed based on free software created by Delphi by Jordan Russell. The first version was released in 1997. QuickStart of Inno Setup include main Inno Setup and also includes an option to install the script editor Inno Script Studio. The script editor is not official and is not mandatory for general use, but help Inno Setup easier to use.
Inno Setup Compiler - software create file setup.exe
The features of Inno Setup Compiler
	Support for every...
</description></item><item><title>Download AnyTrans for iOS 8.9.12.20250910</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 00:17:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anytrans-for-ios-755.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anytrans-for-ios-755.html
</guid><description>
AnyTrans for iOS is content manager essential fully managed iPhone, Android and content of your cloud. Including all mobile devices, all cloud drives from your iPhone, iPad, iPod touch to phones and tablets. From local disk to cloud storage. AnyTrans has protected them all, providing you convenient management for all data and your files, regardless of whether they are stored where.
AnyTrans is the one stop solution to meet all the management needs of your data. For the first time, you can...
</description></item><item><title>Download MyLanViewer Enterprise 6.5.8</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 00:16:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mylanviewer-enterprise-1274.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mylanviewer-enterprise-1274.html
</guid><description>
MyLanViewer is a program for scanning IP address, Netbios and LAN / Network powerful for Windows tool whois and traceroute, remote shutdown and process management Wake On LAN (WOL), scan and monitor wireless networks. This app will help you find all IP addresses, MAC addresses and shared folders of computers on the network wired or wireless (Wi-Fi).
MyLanViewer Enterprise - Scan IP address LAN/Network
The program scans network and displays the computer network in your window, friends...
</description></item><item><title>Download GadgetPack 39.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 00:15:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-8gadgetpack-2667.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-8gadgetpack-2667.html
</guid><description>
8GadgetPack brings back the Windows utility 7 for Windows 8, Windows 8.1 and Windows 10. It contains a set of 49 common utility and create a side bar on the computer to your desk. In addition to the side bar Windows 7, where you can easily arrange and access the active window, you can write notes, to-do list and appointments in your agenda, calendar, calendar access, private as well as create panel to launch the application, open the file / folder and visit the URL.
8GadgetPack -...
</description></item><item><title>Download AssistMyTeam PDF Merger 2.0.408.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 00:14:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-assistmyteam-pdf-merger-7974.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-assistmyteam-pdf-merger-7974.html
</guid><description>
AssistMyTeam PDF Merger is compact software used to merge your PDF files and any number of office documents, email files, images, archived compressed files , nested folders and subfolders, and more than 120 other formats into one PDF file with a single click. Add bookmarks or references for each file to a PDF file to easily navigate the documents in the PDF file.
Features of AssistMyTeam PDF Merger
	Merge multiple PDF files as consecutive pages into one PDF file.
	Automatically...
</description></item><item><title>Download PPTube 10.8.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 00:14:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pptube-12556.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pptube-12556.html
</guid><description>
PPTube Video Downloader allows you to download HD videos easily, from 720p, 1080p, 2K, 4K and 8K. You can save multiple videos at the same time. Just copy multiple video URLs from various websites and paste them into PPTube Downloader, then you can download multiple videos in seconds.
In addition, you can download HD videos from Instagram, TikTok, Facebook, Apple Music, Vimeo, adult websites, etc. and convert them to MP4, MP3, MOV, AAC and more than 20 other output formats. PPTube...
</description></item><item><title>Download AssistMyTeam PDF Converter 7.1.294.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 00:13:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-assistmyteam-pdf-converter-7856.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-assistmyteam-pdf-converter-7856.html
</guid><description>
AssistMyTeam PDF Converter is a software to convert files to PDF, it is used to save all kinds of documents, such as Word, Excel, PowerPoint, web pages, images, emails. or even ZIP to PDF files. Best of all, Windows Explorer Shell Integration makes this significantly easier, with one-click instant PDF.
Features of AssistMyTeam PDF Converter
	Convert different types of documents to PDF quickly.
	Support to convert 120+ file types to PDF.
	Save the compressed ZIP file to PDF.
	Convert...
</description></item><item><title>Download iDownerGo 10.8.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 00:12:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idownergo-12439.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idownergo-12439.html
</guid><description>
iDownerGo is the best tool that allows users to download videos, music and playlists from more than 10,000 streaming sites. It can easily convert videos to MP4, MOV, MKV, 3GP, AAC, WAV, FLAC and other formats on PC and Mac. With this amazing program, users can enjoy their favorite media content without restrictions.
iDownerGo Features
	Download any video up to 8K resolution
	Download 1080p videos online from over 10,000 popular streaming sites easily.
	Save any video in various...
</description></item><item><title>Download Aiseesoft HEIC Converter 1.0.38</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 00:12:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aiseesoft-heic-converter-7111.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aiseesoft-heic-converter-7111.html
</guid><description>
Aiseesoft HEIC Converter is a professional tool that allows you to convert iPhone, iPad, iPod photos from HEIC to JPG or PNG on Windows. With this powerful HEIC converter, you can convert all your HEIF (.heic) photos to JPG/JPEG or to PNG on your Windows or Mac computer without any hassle.
This highly efficient image format allows you to create and store images at a much smaller size without sacrificing image quality. With Aiseesoft HEIC Converter, you can simply convert HEIF (.heic)...
</description></item><item><title>Download Abelssoft SendMe (Send2Phone) 2025 v1.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 00:12:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-abelssoft-send2phone-2198.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-abelssoft-send2phone-2198.html
</guid><description>
Abelssoft Send2Phone is a program that allows you to send files from personal computer to phone your mobile, you can now easily share links, images, any files from PC to mobile or vice versa. Traffic will be encrypted using AES-256, so the authors assure you that you should not worry about blocking data, but I won't believe in a hundred percent. Thanks to the user interface simple, clear and pleasant. you can send the file just by a click of the mouse, the software can be integrated into...
</description></item><item><title>Download AmoyShare BeeConverter Pro 3.0.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 00:11:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-amoyshare-beeconverter-pro-7285.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-amoyshare-beeconverter-pro-7285.html
</guid><description>
BeeConverter Pro is a great application for video converter capable of converting multiple files simultaneously, converting videos for specific devices, handling multiple audio formats and video and most importantly, do all of this with 60x faster conversions. With its help, you can convert video or audio in any popular formats, such as MP4, MKV, AVI, FLV, WEBM and MP3, WMA, WAV, M4A, etc., as well as 4K video.
Features of BeeConverter Pro
	All popular video/audio formats are...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tixati 3.38</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Sep 2025 00:10:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tixati-2355.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tixati-2355.html
</guid><description>
A Bittorrent free, good have been updated, are designed for operating systems Microsoft Windows and Linux (for the OS Monday, you can download a version from the official website of the developer). The difference between a client and a large number of others is that users are provided a wide opportunity to control the torrent of them, they also write on your program that it consumes less memory than uTorrent and Halite famous.
Tixati - App download torrent
Tixati is also ready to...
</description></item></channel></rss>