<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 17:41:28 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 17:41:28 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download KakaoTalk 2025.10.1.4840</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 20:37:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kakaotalk-4583.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kakaotalk-4583.html
</guid><description>
KakaoTalk born with the goal is to connect people, the world, and more. This is a cross-platform instant messaging to create a completely new approach for the text and calls. Available for PC and smart phones altogether, KakaoTalk creates a channel of communication, reliable, with security features added to protect your identity.
Chat with friends for free
Purpose the main chat, the app not only provides the ability to perform the conversation individually but also create chat rooms...
</description></item><item><title>Download Digital Clock 5.1.8</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 16:35:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-digital-clock-3723.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-digital-clock-3723.html
</guid><description>
Digital Clock is a screen saver small and simple application that allows you to view the date, time and current day of the week. In addition, you can set the clock mode 12 or 24 hours, change the font color, display day of the week, current date, separators flash or seconds. hi it boots, outdoor clock, tray icon appear (if available in the system tray). Color tray icon depends on the operating system, in most cases, it is black, but on Windows 10, Windows and macOS with the dark theme,...
</description></item><item><title>Download OutlookStatView 2.32</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 16:31:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-outlookstatview-4358.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-outlookstatview-4358.html
</guid><description>
OutlookStatView is a program that is small, portable and resource displays general data on the account, your Microsoft Outlook, as the number of emails sent to a specific person. Since installation is not necessary, you can put the executable wherever you want on the local drive and run the application immediately. Other option is save a copy of the application on the pen drive or mobile device equivalent, to be able to use it on any machine easily, without need to install anything before...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare Recoverit 14.0.8.8</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 16:31:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-recoverits-374.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-recoverits-374.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare Recoverit is a data recovery software that is easily lost at a rapid rate and is used by many people. You will do what happens if one day your data is suddenly lost due to the virus or deleted it, .. Wondershare Recoverit will provide you with an environment to protect important data.
Wondershare Recoverit has all the scanning processes that are divided into multiple types, from the typical recovery of the deleted files that are deleted to the recovery of missing files due...
</description></item><item><title>Download FastStone Image Viewer 8.3 Corporate</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 16:31:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-faststone-image-viewer-278.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-faststone-image-viewer-278.html
</guid><description>
FastStone Image Viewer software is manager, converter and editor image fast, stable, user-friendly. FastStone Image Viewer has the features include image viewing, management, comparison, red-eye removal, emailing, resizing, cropping and color adjustments. Full screen mode innovative but intuitive its provides quick access to EXIF information, browse the thumbnails and the main functions via hidden toolbars that pop up when your mouse touch the four edges of the screen.
FastStone Image...
</description></item><item><title>Download Chaos Enscape 4.13.0.636</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 16:30:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-enscape-3d-4125.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-enscape-3d-4125.html
</guid><description>
Enscape 3D is the tool support simulation 3D for the software Revit, SketchUp, Rhino, ArchiCAD. With real-time technology of Enscape 3D your project is displayed in the form of walk-3D is fully displayed, can be navigated and explored from every angle, at every moment of the day. With direct link between Enscape 3D and CAD programs, you can track all updates for his plan immediately. More Enscape to your work to give yourself more time to create and innovate. Enscape 3D offers many options...
</description></item><item><title>Download Zortam Mp3 Media Studio Pro 33.55</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 16:30:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zortam-mp3-media-studio-pro-135.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zortam-mp3-media-studio-pro-135.html
</guid><description>
Zortam Mp3 Media Studio Pro brings you rich processing tools music includes extract and convert music from CD to Mp3 format, edit, music cards, music download....You can also create discs CD high-quality music, with Zortam Mp3 Media Studio search music files duplicated to remove them from the system, rename music files, switch back and forth between formats.
Zortam Mp3 Media Studio Pro is rated as perfect software in the processing of the MP3 files on the computer. First of all, you can...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDF Suite Pro + OCR 20.0.36.21543</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 16:29:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-suite-ocr-6691.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-suite-ocr-6691.html
</guid><description>
PDF Suite is the software that provides the most necessary functions such as reading, creating and editing basic PDF. You will be able to open, save, print and mark any PDF files using PDF Suite. You can see the presentation, CV, the Book of Electronics and many other electronic documents. PDF Suite has a modern conversion tool that can transfer any files that can be printed into a fully readable PDF document 100%. Convert Word, Excel, PowerPoint and other MS Office documents to PDF...
</description></item><item><title>Download Summitsoft Creative Fonts Collection 2025</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 16:29:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-summitsoft-creative-fonts-collection-5573.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-summitsoft-creative-fonts-collection-5573.html
</guid><description>
Summitsoft Creative Fonts Collection is a collection of fonts featuring an array of stunning fonts created by the professional team at SummitType Foundry. With this collection you'll have access to fonts that are perfect for any project. Plus, the included themed clip art adds variety of images to any project.
The creative team at SummitType Foundry, a division of Summitsoft, is where we design and manufacture every single font in our collection. Each font is unique and can't be found...
</description></item><item><title>Download Remote Desktop Manager Enterprise 2025.3.25</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 16:28:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-remote-desktop-manager-enterprise-242.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-remote-desktop-manager-enterprise-242.html
</guid><description>
Remote Desktop Manager Enterprise software is the complete management of remote connections and virtual machines from a single location, at the same time access support data online and cloud storage. Remote Desktop Manager supports multiple types of connections, not only connections for the protocol connect remote computer Remote Desktop Protocol (RDP).
Remote Desktop Manager easily add, edit, delete, share, organize and find your remote connection of you quickly. Compatible with...
</description></item><item><title>Download MultiPack .NET Windows Desktop Installer 2.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 16:28:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-multipack-net-windows-desktop-installer-12259.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-multipack-net-windows-desktop-installer-12259.html
</guid><description>
MultiPack .NET Windows Desktop Installer provides you with a downloadable package to install .NET Windows desktop. This .NET download package ensures you have the correct version installed on your machine. Having the latest version of Microsoft .NET gives you access to many performance improvements across the entire platform.
Installation package includes all latest .NET Desktop Runtimes 6-8 packages:
	Microsoft .NET Desktop Runtime 6 (x64 only)
	Microsoft .NET Desktop Runtime 7 (x64...
</description></item><item><title>Download PTE AV Studio Pro 11.0.20 Build 1</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 16:27:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pte-av-studio-pro-2899.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pte-av-studio-pro-2899.html
</guid><description>
PTE AV Studio Pro is software for processing video professional, allowing for enthusiasts and creative professionals the max with advanced features. Create slideshows professional photo in PTE AV Studio. Add photos, video clips and music. Use Keyframe animations and Slide Slide. Editing audio clips in view mode the time Line. Output for PC, HD video and 4K, mobile devices.
Sound editor
Edit sound clip: fade in / out, start time, duration, fading cross.
Adjust the color
Adjust...
</description></item><item><title>Download Photo Supreme 2025.3.3.8136</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 16:21:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photo-supreme-430.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photo-supreme-430.html
</guid><description>
Photo Supreme is a software product management professional pictures of idimager. With Photo Supreme you can arrange, manage back stock photo archive of yourself and share them with you here and relatives easily via Email or Facebook. Photo Supreme provides users method to sort images effective, logical, as well as edit and share your photos with friends and relatives in the family. Especially the Photo Supreme allows to work with multiple image formats and support mounting support,...
</description></item><item><title>Download AVS Image Converter 7.1.4.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 16:20:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs-image-converter-4021.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs-image-converter-4021.html
</guid><description>
AVS Image Converter is a comprehensive application and have the ability to allow you to switch quickly and easily the digital images of yourself between many formats, including RAW, JPEG, GIF, TGA, PNG, PDF, TIFF, RAS, JPEG 2000. and many other types . The application comes with a variety of presets to change image size will allow you to easily resize your photos to the different print formats. You can also use the presets this to adjust their images for slideshows can be shared on social...
</description></item><item><title>Download CoolUtils PDF Combine Pro 4.2.0.154/105</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 16:16:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-pdf-combine-pro-580.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-pdf-combine-pro-580.html
</guid><description>
CoolUtils PDF Combine Pro  is software that helps you combine  PDF, DOC, TXT, DOCX, HTML, XLS, images  h (TIFF, JPEG, PNG) and  email  as a  PDF  file. With PDF Combine Pro it is easier than ever to combine documents into one PDF file. Now you don't have to use some programs and converters to get a PDF. Everything for PDF Combine Pro to do for you.
Office, fax, email files - get combined PDF in seconds for personal use, commercial needs, electronic discovery, or manufacturing.  PDF...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinPIM Business 18.71.5910</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 16:16:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winpim-business-4685.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winpim-business-4685.html
</guid><description>
WinPIM Business is a program that helps you manage the conversations, the online meetings. WinPIM Business help you arrange your time effectively by allowing you to create a contact list with details of everyone you need. You can add name, company and telephone number of their ease.
The features of WinPIM Business
	Storage more than 60 fields and 20 custom fields.
	Create Tree Tree to manage contacts, and can map contacts.
	Quick phone dial, mail, fax, visit the website.
	Remind...
</description></item><item><title>Download MuseScore 4.6.4 + Portable</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 16:15:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musescore-2857.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musescore-2857.html
</guid><description>
MuseScore is the tool score for Windows, macOS and Linux, can compare with Finale and Sibelius, support multiple file formats and input methods. It is released as free software and open source under The GNU general public License.
MuseScore - The application composer
Features of MuseScore
	Design WYSIWYG, notes are entered on a "virtual notice"
	TrueType fonts for printing and display allows split ratio high quality for all sizes
	Enter notes easily and quickly
	Many editing...
</description></item><item><title>Download USB Device Tree Viewer 4.7.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 16:15:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-usb-device-tree-viewer-3286.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-usb-device-tree-viewer-3286.html
</guid><description>
USB Device Tree Viewer provides detailed information for all the ports and USB hub on the computer in the format tree. If a device is connected to a port, it also provides detailed information for the properties of the device and connection. USB Device Tree Viewer analyze your system configuration and display details about the controller server is connected, such as the manufacturer, drivers, bus types, list, location, devices, drive letters, COM ports, and debugging and statistics bus...
</description></item><item><title>Download O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Premium 22.0.1126</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 16:14:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-diskimage-server-4547.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-diskimage-server-4547.html
</guid><description>
O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Server is software that is specially designed for use in enterprise environments, the software allows users to backup all the files you want and keep them safe from any incident or disaster computer. O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Server comes with a variety of easy to use utility that allows users to backup entire partitions of the specific files from their PC, as well as recover the version previous data of them, all from a simple interface.
O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Server - data...
</description></item><item><title>Download InnoExtractor Ultra 2026 v11.3.0.161</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 16:14:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-innoextractor-plus-4009.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-innoextractor-plus-4009.html
</guid><description>
InnoExtractor Plus is a handy lightweight but strong will allow you to use technology InnoUnp to easily extract the installer Inno Setup. Using this tool, you will be able to explore the content and the internal structure of installers and extract them to a folder on the local drive or on the storage device mobile without running the file setup. InnoExtractor Plus comes with graphical interface simple and user friendly, allowing you to easily open the installed just by drag and drop...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sigil 2.7.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 16:09:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sigil-1764.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sigil-1764.html
</guid><description>
Sigil is editor ebook full of features for the EPUB file, which you can use to create electronic books of his own from scratch and export them to EPUB format. Sigil offers editing, WYSIWYG, similar to a word processor, as well as edit the code directly for advanced users. The program provides a complete set of tools allows you to insert headings, specify fonts, add numbered list or bulleted, iamges, videos, Internet links and more, without having to write any HTML code whatsoever.
Sigil...
</description></item><item><title>Download NewFileTime 8.15</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 16:08:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-newfiletime-1918.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-newfiletime-1918.html
</guid><description>
NewFileTime is a small utility independence allows you to change date modified, Created and Accessed of any file. You can modify the dates for one or multiple files, even entire folder structures at the same time. The date can be changed to a date and time specific or you can choose to make each file "older" or "younger," according to a certain number of days.
NewFileTime - edit time files
You can add files simply via Drag and Drop or by import from a folder. In any case, it opens...
</description></item><item><title>Download DtSearch Desktop 2025.02 Build 8845</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 16:07:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dtsearch-desktop-620.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dtsearch-desktop-620.html
</guid><description>
DtSearch Desktop is software that provides the ability to search instant files can be accessed on a desktop computer. dtSearch can instantly search terabytes of text because it builds a search index storage position of the words in the document. Indexing is easy - simply select folders or entire drives to index and dtSearch does the rest. Once dtSearch has created an index, it can automatically update it using The task scheduler in Windows to reflect the addition, delete and modification...
</description></item><item><title>Download DtSearch Engine 2025.02 Build 8845</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 16:07:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dtsearch-engine-619.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dtsearch-engine-619.html
</guid><description>
DtSearch Engine is a search tool and retrieve text support on multiple platforms like windows, mac, linux. Tool dtSearch also works on the cloud platform such as Azure and AWS. dtSearch can index over a terabyte of text in a single index, spanning multiple directories, emails and attachments, online data and other databases. The products can create and search any number of indexes and can search the index during the update. Time search is indexing often less than a second, even across...
</description></item><item><title>Download Samsung SSD Magician Tool 9.0.0.910</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 16:06:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-samsung-ssd-magician-tool-4010.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-samsung-ssd-magician-tool-4010.html
</guid><description>
Samsung SSD Magician Tool is a software aid you with easy maintenance and use of the product Samsung SSD is connected to desktop or laptop. In addition to providing information about system and SSD product of users, Samsung SSD Magician also supports advanced features, such as management performance SSD, benchmarking for optimum performance, update new firmware, etc. Samsung SSD Magician Tool is a set of tools to be considered carefully, which helps users further improve performance of the...
</description></item></channel></rss>