<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 02:10:54 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 02:10:54 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Q-Dir 12.48</title><pubDate> Fri, 06 Feb 2026 00:20:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-q-dir-348.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-q-dir-348.html
</guid><description>
Q-Dir is software to manage the entire file and folder on the computer, allowing to see file in same time 4 different positions (viewport quadro) while still maintaining all the standard features of the Explorer.
It also provides a variety of management features, additional files included the filter file color-coding, layouts and columns can be customized, quick access to file and folder favorites and more.
Other features of Q-Dir , including directory listings (.txt, .doc .html .csv),...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Acrobat Pro DC 2025.001.21151 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 23:48:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-001en-adobe-acrobat-pro-458.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-001en-adobe-acrobat-pro-458.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Acrobat Pro DC is a comprehensive software that helps you create and edit the PDF&amp;nbsp;document, or create form, sign, protect PDF, connect, split PDF, export PDF to various formats. The Acrobat Pro DC is the latest version of Adobe with improvements in the interface with the polished ribbon bar and the ability to create and handle pdf files as well as its male versions.
The highlight of the Acrobat Pro DC is probably the ability to connect, store documents on the cloud, you can...
</description></item><item><title>Download EaseUS CleanGenius 3.0.4</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 23:16:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-cleangenius-12232.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-cleangenius-12232.html
</guid><description>
EaseUS is a company with many years of experience in developing software to help enhance users' digital lives. Their security and cleaning tools will help protect your machine, enhance privacy, and improve overall performance. EaseUS CleanGenius is an all-in-one application designed to streamline and improve the performance of your computer. This app optimizes system settings, removes junk files, and increases overall speed and efficiency. With a user-friendly interface and powerful...
</description></item><item><title>Download YoWindow Weather - Unlimited 2.55.9</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 23:14:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-yowindow-weather-unlimited-8421.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-yowindow-weather-unlimited-8421.html
</guid><description>
YoWindow is a unique new weather app. The magic of YoWindow is a living landscape that reflects your real-life weather. For example, if it rains - it will rain in YoWindow. Sunset and sunrise in YoWindow take place at the same time as in real life. But the cool thing is you can roll time forward. Just swipe the screen and you'll see how the weather changes throughout the day.
YoWindow Weather Features - Unlimited
	All the weather at your fingertips. You see the current weather,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Photoshop 2026 v27.3.1.4 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 23:10:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-0010-adobe-photoshop-737.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-0010-adobe-photoshop-737.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Photoshop is a powerful raster graphics editor developed by Adobe Systems, primarily used for image editing, photo editing, and graphic design. Currently,&amp;nbsp;Adobe Photoshop 2025 is considered a graphic design software, creating and enhancing images, illustrations, and 3D artwork. In addition, it also supports website and mobile app design, video editing, real-life painting simulation, and more.
Adobe Photoshop 2025 - Graphic design
When it comes to Adobe Photoshop, it is...
</description></item><item><title>Download IObit Uninstaller Pro 15.3.0.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 23:09:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iobit-uninstaller-pro-339.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iobit-uninstaller-pro-339.html
</guid><description>
IObit Uninstaller Pro is software to delete programs not needed easily even when Windows "Remove Programs" operation not successful. IObit Uninstaller Pro will uninstall the app Windows, browser toolbars, software packages and plug-ins added. It comes with a scan function is powerful and a tool, Force Uninstall, both of which help to easily and completely remove the app stubborn, and the excess useless, to release more disk space.
With IObit Uninstaller Pro you will have peace of mind...
</description></item><item><title>Download MathType 7.11.1.462</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 23:08:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mathtype-478.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mathtype-478.html
</guid><description>
MathType software is to compose mathematical formulas, symbols, math for office applications such as mathematical equations, to handle text, web pages, desktop publishing, desktop presentations, elearning, and for TeX documents, LaTeX and MathML. MathType would be a great help for work as well as your learning.
When integrate MathType into the office software, you easily create the logo or any formula in Math will save a lot of time, work efficiency is highly increased.
Teachers,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Imagine 2.4.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 23:08:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-imagine-7369.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-imagine-7369.html
</guid><description>
Imagine is an application that allows you to view images and animations in a variety of formats, including JPG, BMP, PNG and GIF. With Imagine you can view file properties and EXIF ​​information, copy, move, delete and rename images. Additionally, you can also flip, resize and rotate them, swap colors, set transparency levels, import, export, and edit palettes, and change color depth.
Features of Imagine
	View and save image/animation files at lightning speed
	Multiple...
</description></item><item><title>Download 4K Video Downloader Plus 26.0.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 23:07:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-video-downloader-617.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-video-downloader-617.html
</guid><description>
4K Video Downloader Plus is software support downloads video, audio and subtitles from YouTube with high quality up to 4K. Download process video is very simple: just copy the video link from your browser and click Paste Url. Done! If you want that video on your iPad, iPhone or other device, we have protected you.
The feature on 4K Video Downloader Plus
	Download entire playlists and channels from YouTube and save them in MP4, MKV, M4A, MP3, FLV, 3G, create a file .m3u for...
</description></item><item><title>Download TeamViewer 15.74.5 + Portable</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 23:07:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-teamviewer-528.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-teamviewer-528.html
</guid><description>
TeamViewer is software that functions to connect and control the remote computer, the ability to connect with any system anywhere from all over the place. This is a support tool users is very convenient. TeamViewer to help users control remote computer becomes much more simple, help you interact and collaborate with others in the exchange and share of information, instruction manual, application software or fix the computer.
TeamViewer as a revolution of computer science. when you have...
</description></item><item><title>Download Drive SnapShot 1.51.0.107</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 23:06:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-drive-snapshot-701.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-drive-snapshot-701.html
</guid><description>
Drive SnapShot is a backup software, Restore disk, including operating system, installed programs, your data and all security attributes - while windows is running and you continue to work. With Drive SnapShot you backup partition or hard drive and it can also create disk image of your system. If a disaster occurs (a virus, trojan or the fixed hard disk), the recover complete and accurate your system will be able to accomplish after only a few minutes. The image file can be mounted as...
</description></item><item><title>Download Opera GX (Gaming Browser) 126.0.5750.112</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 23:06:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-gx-3170.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-gx-3170.html
</guid><description>
Opera GX is a special version of the Opera browser is built to complement gamers avid. Browser this game comes with the unique features to help users make maximum use of both the game and their browser. Opera GX is built specifically to support the game. This browser includes the unique features to help users have the best experience when gaming and surfing the web.
Opera GX - special browser for gamers
GX Control allows you to set a limit on the level of use RAM, CPU and network where...
</description></item><item><title>Download Brave Browser 1.86.148</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 23:05:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-brave-browser-2874.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-brave-browser-2874.html
</guid><description>
Brave Browser is a browser based on Chromium, the basic principle is that operation fast and privacy of users. The program can block pop-up windows and other ads, plus it blocked the mechanism for monitoring the online activities of your. Therefore, you can purchase and safely browse the website you are interested in without having to worry about the fact that your activity will be monitored and then you will be shown the necessary advertising or service provider of parties...
</description></item><item><title>Download 4K YouTube to MP3 26.0.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 23:05:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-youtube-to-mp3-622.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-youtube-to-mp3-622.html
</guid><description>
4K YouTube to MP3 is a software to convert video youtube to mp3 quickly and easily by the manipulation drag-and-drop simple. With 4K YouTube to MP3 you just drag and drop the link to the favorite songs of you and get the MP3 files to your computer, as easy as that. Transfer songs directly to iPod, iPhone and iPad everywhere you go. No install annoying and complex to solve, just a clean interface, user friendly and functional.
When using 4K YouTube to MP3, users will get the playlists,...
</description></item><item><title>Download CPU Temp 1.9.0.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 23:04:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cpu-temp-10651.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cpu-temp-10651.html
</guid><description>
CPU Temp is a free and simple application for monitoring CPU temperature, compatible with Windows 11 or older versions of Windows OS. CPU Temp seamlessly integrates, giving you real-time insights into CPU temperature, usage, clock speed, power consumption, and other essential parameters of your processor. reason.
With an intuitive and customizable interface, CPU Temp offers over 40 different user interface themes and color schemes. You can pick and choose the UI that suits your style,...
</description></item><item><title>Download reaConverter Pro 8.0.192</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 23:04:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html
</guid><description>
reaConverter Pro is software image processing feature with batch conversion and image editing periodically becomes simple. eaConverter also provide command line utilities allow you to process images automatically, thus helping you shorten the time for other work.
reaConverter Pro integrated powerful tool of Uber with many great features. It provides advanced solutions to process and adjust images. Management of the conversion process the base image with the latest version of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Quick CPU 6.2.1.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 23:04:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quick-cpu-5144.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quick-cpu-5144.html
</guid><description>
Quick CPU (Core Parking Manager v3) is an application designed to tweak and monitor the performance settings of the CPU such as Core Parking, Frequency Scaling and Turbo Boost, as well as made other adjustments. Below you will find all information about how it works, how to interpret the data and install the application and how to perform these adjustments.
Features of Quick CPU
	Performance graphs for each core. Show if the core is Active or not adjust the size for the CPU...
</description></item><item><title>Download Resolume Arena 7.24.1 rev 61371</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 23:03:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-resolume-arena-001-760.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-resolume-arena-001-760.html
</guid><description>
Resolume Arena is software Visual Jockey for DJ help adjust, mix and match image combination screen displayed directly. Software control it from the lighting and synchronize with the DJ via SMPTE time code. Adjust the ratio and position of the clip to suit your needs. Apply effects to change the powerful interface of the video. Everything running on the card screen so you get fast performance and good image quality as possible.
Resolume Arena - software Visual Jockey for DJ
Features of...
</description></item><item><title>Download MaxCut Business Edition 2.9.6.5</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 23:03:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-maxcut-business-edition-3912.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-maxcut-business-edition-3912.html
</guid><description>
MaxCut Business Edition is a software to create cutting diagrams, accurate, and cost estimate for the wood industry, cabinets and metal,.. You enter the size and material, MaxCut will do the rest! Produce optimized cutting diagrams, create estimates, orders, and labels - it's just a click. Run the application MaxCut Business Edition brings a pretty clean interface and slick quickly get you up and running. Most space represents the editing area, with the main function are stored cleverly in...
</description></item><item><title>Download eDocPrinter PDF Pro 10.68 Build 10685</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 23:02:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-edocprinter-pdf-pro-3915.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-edocprinter-pdf-pro-3915.html
</guid><description>
eDocPrinter PDF Pro is an application to create PDF files from applications in Windows 2000, Windows XP and above. eDocPrinter PDF Pro works as a printer under windows environment, hence users can print from any application window using the device printing GDI. Extremely easy to work with this tool, because it installs on your system as a virtual printer and lets you convert documents to PDF in an easy way. eDocPrinter PDF Pro comes with advanced functions that can meet the requirements of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Quick Clipboard Editor 3.3.1.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 23:02:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quick-clipboard-editor-9421.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quick-clipboard-editor-9421.html
</guid><description>
Quick Clipboard Editor is free software that provides direct access to the text stored in your clipboard, allowing you to quickly modify it to meet your needs. meet your needs before pasting the text into the app you want. It allows you to quickly retrieve previous clips from your clipboard history, find and replace specific words or phrases, insert new content into each line, trim unwanted pieces of text, keep or remove lines or characters based on different criteria, arrange text using...
</description></item><item><title>Download Vovsoft Window Resizer 4.4</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 23:01:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-window-resizer-7339.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-window-resizer-7339.html
</guid><description>
Vovsoft Window Resizer is a utility that allows you to resize any window to an exact, predefined size. This is extremely useful when designing websites, as it allows you to see how the page will look when viewed at a smaller size. This utility is also handy when compiling screenshots for documents, using Window Resizer allows you to easily maintain the same window size across monitors.
Alternatively, you can save the current positions (width, height, left, top) as a CSV file and "Load...
</description></item><item><title>Download Abelssoft GClean 2026 v226.0.69944</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 23:01:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-googleclean-676.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-googleclean-676.html
</guid><description>
GoogleClean is a software scans your computer for tracking cookies created by Google apps and prevents personal data being sent. This application offers support for Google Chrome, Internet Explorer, Mozilla Firefox, Opera ans Saferi.
GoogleClean is a software utility designed to detect tracking cookies of Google and YouTube, allow you to delete any one of them through the cookie management. It also can block Google Analystics, delete cookies Google and YouTube along with the file Windows...
</description></item><item><title>Download DiskBoss Ultimate 16.4.12 + Pro + Enterprise</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 23:00:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-diskboss-ultimate-1289.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-diskboss-ultimate-1289.html
</guid><description>
DiskBoss Ultimate is a software application professional, built to help you analyze disks, directories and network shares, arrange files and folders, perform the operation the advanced search and delete duplicate items, as well as perform management activities file automatically based on user-defined rules and policies.
DiskBoss Ultimate - analyzing disk and file manager
This tool also can synchronize disks, directories and network shares, perform the task delete data securely in batch...
</description></item><item><title>Download DiskBoss 16.4.12</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 23:00:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-diskboss-19.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-diskboss-19.html
</guid><description>
DiskBoss Free scan drives or folders and view a report of how the amount of your storage used by the file type. It automatically categorizes your files by general types (e.g. multimedia files, executables, documents, etc.) and allows you to see more details to see the results for each file type and last is a list of all the files in the group.
Other features include creating signatures the MD5, SHA1 or SHA256 for the file and text to HTML, Excel CSV and ACSII.
The free version is limited...
</description></item></channel></rss>