<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 18:04:48 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 18:04:48 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download FxSound (FxSound Enhancer Premium) 1.2.6 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Fri, 13 Feb 2026 18:55:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fxsound-enhancer-premium-2013.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fxsound-enhancer-premium-2013.html
</guid><description>
FxSound Enhancer Premium formerly DFX Audio Enhance, is accessories multimedia software most popular in the world with over 46 million downloads worldwide. FxSound enhances the sound of most of the music content and online video is live streaming on the Web, including the streaming service, YouTube, Pandora, Spotify and Apple Music. FxSound Enhancer Premium also implemented enhanced real-time audio on the player PC multimedia most popular include iTunes, Windows Media Player, Winamp and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Acrobat Pro DC 2025.001.21208 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Fri, 13 Feb 2026 18:54:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-001en-adobe-acrobat-pro-458.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-001en-adobe-acrobat-pro-458.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Acrobat Pro DC is a comprehensive software that helps you create and edit the PDF&amp;nbsp;document, or create form, sign, protect PDF, connect, split PDF, export PDF to various formats. The Acrobat Pro DC is the latest version of Adobe with improvements in the interface with the polished ribbon bar and the ability to create and handle pdf files as well as its male versions.
The highlight of the Acrobat Pro DC is probably the ability to connect, store documents on the cloud, you can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Acrobat Reader DC 2025.001.21208</title><pubDate> Fri, 13 Feb 2026 18:53:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-acrobat-reader-3707.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-acrobat-reader-3707.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Acrobat Reader DC is a system of application software and Web services developed by Adobe Systems to view, create, manipulate, print and manage PDF files. With Adobe Acrobat Reader DC, you can create, export, edit, and track PDF files from anywhere - and maintain connection with the recent set of files on all your devices.
Adobe Acrobat Reader current DC is connected with Adobe Document Cloud - help working on the computers and mobile devices becomes easier than ever before. This is...
</description></item><item><title>Download O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro 22.1.244 / Server</title><pubDate> Fri, 13 Feb 2026 18:52:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-diskimage-pro-218.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-diskimage-pro-218.html
</guid><description>
O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro is software backup data comprehensive and effective is provided to protect the data of the computer system, it creates images for individual drives or the entire system that still does not affect your system.
O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro allows the user to backup the entire computer or drive, the and files whenever you want even while the computer is being used. Or can use O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro to create a copy chinh sac of computer disk drives, can be used instead of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download CPUID HWMonitor Free 1.62</title><pubDate> Fri, 13 Feb 2026 18:51:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cpuid-hwmonitor-free-8486.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cpuid-hwmonitor-free-8486.html
</guid><description>
CPUID HWMonitor Free is a free system monitoring software that allows users to monitor various hardware components in their computer, such as CPU, GPU, memory memory and temperature. It can be used to monitor performance and troubleshoot problems with the system. The software is compatible with the Windows operating system and can be downloaded from the CPUID website.
Features of CPUID HWMonitor Free
	Real-time monitoring of various hardware components such as CPU, GPU, memory and...
</description></item><item><title>Download FxSound Pro 1.2.6 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Fri, 13 Feb 2026 18:41:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fxsound-5966.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fxsound-5966.html
</guid><description>
FxSound Pro is a professional software that helps to enhance the quality of sound, volume, depth, and sound on your PC. FxSound brings you a great sound just with a downloadable download. After using FxSound, you will know if it is for you or not. Most people do n' t know what they ' re missing in their sound until they try their software/sound hardware better. It ' s hard to convey if you do n' t really experience yourself.
Reason to use FxSound Pro:
	The perfect sound on every...
</description></item><item><title>Download Minimal Firewall 2.6.8</title><pubDate> Fri, 13 Feb 2026 15:52:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minimal-firewall-13877.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minimal-firewall-13877.html
</guid><description>
Minimal Firewall works in conjunction with Windows Firewall to block all unknown connections by default, prompting you to create application-based rules to mitigate malware, telemetry, and data leaks. Completely eliminate applications that call home without your knowledge. Minimal Firewall provides a more secure and integrated approach by interacting directly with the native Windows Firewall, eliminating the need for risky system modifications.
Core Features
	Lockdown Mode: The core...
</description></item><item><title>Download AB Download Manager 1.8.6</title><pubDate> Fri, 13 Feb 2026 15:51:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ab-download-manager-12399.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ab-download-manager-12399.html
</guid><description>
With this application, you can easily download files from anywhere. Enjoy fast, free downloads with seamless browser extension support. It is built to be a desktop application that allows you to manage and organize your downloads better than before.
AB Download Manager features
	Simple and modern UI: Simple UI and dark mode by default
	Faster download speeds: Download files using multiple connections to increase your download speed by up to 500%
	Download Queue: Create and manage your...
</description></item><item><title>Download Visual Studio Code 1.109.3</title><pubDate> Fri, 13 Feb 2026 15:51:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-visual-studio-code-3182.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-visual-studio-code-3182.html
</guid><description>
Visual Studio Code is the encryption tool of Microsoft has met most of the needs of the developer. Environment this encoding was introduced to compete with other products such as Sublime and Nodepad ++ . Microsoft, in its new product, has not been released in many years, has provided many features in a simple environment. In addition to the familiar with a dozen programming languages, the syntax and get to know coding language as soon as be encrypted and allows for syntax highlighting, it...
</description></item><item><title>Download TreeSize Professional 9.7.0.2200</title><pubDate> Fri, 13 Feb 2026 15:49:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-treesize-professional-390.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-treesize-professional-390.html
</guid><description>
TreeSize Pro is a software to manage hard disk space powerfully and flexibly for Windows 2003/2008 / XP / Vista / 7/8/10. TreeSize will find out which directory the largest on your drives and recover megabytes on disk. TreeSize Professional shows you the size, allocated and wasted space, number of files, 3D charts, last accessed date, file owner and permissions, the speed NTFS compression and much more information for several folders or drives you choose. It also lets you search drives,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Free YouTube Download 4.5.6.210 Premium</title><pubDate> Fri, 13 Feb 2026 15:49:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-download-1177.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-download-1177.html
</guid><description>
Free YouTube Download Premium is the most popular application to download videos from YouTube. The program was released in 2006 and regularly updated since then. Use the program to download and convert YouTube videos to view offline anytime.
Free YouTube Download - added Support to download youtube
Download more videos! Save whole playlists and YouTube channels, videos from a playlist individually (history, video be favorite, favourites, Watch later), videos from many different...
</description></item><item><title>Download Syncovery Premium 11.12.10.164</title><pubDate> Fri, 13 Feb 2026 15:48:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncovery-pro-enterprise-232.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncovery-pro-enterprise-232.html
</guid><description>
Syncovery Pro Enterprise is a great application used to back up data and to synchronize personal computers, servers, laptops, notepads and storage online. The software comes with support for FTP and secure FTP servers, SSH, WebDAV, Amazon S3, http, update the part file, ZIP compression, data encryption, and schedule automatic backups.
Syncovery Pro Enterprise have the ability to freely select files and folders across the whole folder hierarchy in tree view and supports email...
</description></item><item><title>Download PowerShell HelpWriter 2026 v3.0.73</title><pubDate> Fri, 13 Feb 2026 15:48:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sapien-powershell-helpwriter-7224.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sapien-powershell-helpwriter-7224.html
</guid><description>
PowerShell HelpWriter is the premier editor for Windows PowerShell XML help files. Create and edit help files for all command types, including cmdlets, functions, workflows, and CIM commands. PowerShell HelpWriter parses your module and generates startup help files that match the cmdlets and convert the help based on existing comments.
Features of PowerShell HelpWriter
	Create help files for modules.
	Create and edit themes.
	Check spelling in real time.
	Create and design modular...
</description></item><item><title>Download Avast Ransomware Decryption Tools 1.0.0.817</title><pubDate> Fri, 13 Feb 2026 15:47:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avast-ransomware-decryption-tools-5371.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avast-ransomware-decryption-tools-5371.html
</guid><description>
Avast Ransomware Decryption Tools is a package of ransomware decryption tools to help you get back files from 20 different ransomware encrypted. Avast Ransomware Decryption Tools supports decryption AES_NI, Alcatraz Locker, Apocalypse, BadBlock, Bart, BTCWare, Crypt888, CryptoMix (Offline), CrySiS, EncrypTile, FindZip, Globe HiddenTear, Jigsaw, Legion NoobCrypt, Stampado, SZFLocker, TeslaCrypt, XData.
Features of Avast Ransomware Decryption Tools
	Easily remove ransomware
	Decrypt and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Diffchecker 6.8.3</title><pubDate> Fri, 13 Feb 2026 15:47:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-diffchecker-5025.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-diffchecker-5025.html
</guid><description>
Diffchecker is a application compare text, images and powerful file to desktop of your. Available for Windows, macOS. Compare text files, documents, PDF. Compare photos, graphics. Because Diffchecker Desktop running entirely on your computer, so it does not have to communicate with our servers to create your difference. This means that there is no other way in addition you can view your sensitive data, you.
Diffchecker Desktop run offline, that means you can use it anytime, anywhere and...
</description></item><item><title>Download SAPIEN PrimalScript 2026 v8.1.224</title><pubDate> Fri, 13 Feb 2026 15:46:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sapien-primalscript-6923.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sapien-primalscript-6923.html
</guid><description>
PrimalScript is the next generation of our industry-leading Universal Script Environment. As a system, database or network administrator, web developer, or end-user developer, you need to work with multiple technologies, languages, and file formats at the same time. The ribbon interface of PrimalScript has been carefully designed to provide almost all the functions you use every day on the Home tab. Create scenario templates based on your requirements and business needs to drive faster...
</description></item><item><title>Download SAPIEN PowerShell Studio 2026 v5.10.264</title><pubDate> Fri, 13 Feb 2026 15:46:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sapien-powershell-studio-7201.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sapien-powershell-studio-7201.html
</guid><description>
PowerShell Studio is the premier editing and tooling environment for PowerShell. Create graphical tools using PowerShell with an easy-to-use GUI designer. Eliminates the need to manually write hundreds of lines of code. Use PowerShell Studio's built-in templates and wired controls to create advanced GUIs quickly. Create a PowerShell script module in minutes with PowerShell Studio. Easily convert your existing functions into a deliverable module. PowerShell Studio has a powerful editor...
</description></item><item><title>Download SAPIEN CIM Explorer 2026 v2.4.117</title><pubDate> Fri, 13 Feb 2026 15:46:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sapien-cim-explorer-6920.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sapien-cim-explorer-6920.html
</guid><description>
CIM Explorer is the next generation tool for exploring the vast universe of Windows Management Instrumentation databases. The CIM database represents an extensive repository of information about your servers and clients that you, as a network or system administrator, need to use every day.
Use CIM Explorer's Windows PowerShell code generation capabilities to generate code for queries or even a GUI application with just a few clicks. The built-in PowerShell console for Windows PowerShell...
</description></item><item><title>Download SAPIEN VersionRecall 2026 v1.8.178</title><pubDate> Fri, 13 Feb 2026 15:45:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sapien-versionrecall-8198.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sapien-versionrecall-8198.html
</guid><description>
VersionRecall automates the most widely used manual process for creating backups and maintaining multiple versions of your files. It removed the complexity of APIs, database backends, developer tools, and foreign file formats. Your versioned files are stored as files in their original format, not in a database or some proprietary, modified format. With the ability to automatically submit custom scheduled changes, you don't even have to worry about manually "checking in" your code;...
</description></item><item><title>Download Imagiro Piano 2.2.310</title><pubDate> Fri, 13 Feb 2026 15:45:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-imagiro-piano-9987.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-imagiro-piano-9987.html
</guid><description>
Imagiro Piano is a virtual piano instrument packed with lofi character. combines gentle, intimate piano recordings with creative processing. Recorded in the bedroom and pulled from extensive internet repositories, the imagiro's piano delivers piano sounds with flawless beauty. Use loops and inversions to create lush frozen piano sounds, or use the ADSR controls to turn a celeste into an EDM strum.
Features of Imagiro Piano
	loop mode for infinite intimacy
	reverse mode for mellower...
</description></item><item><title>Download Devart Entity Developer 7.4.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 13 Feb 2026 15:45:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-devart-entity-developer-14252.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-devart-entity-developer-14252.html
</guid><description>
The leading visual ORM designer for .NET ORM frameworks with powerful code generation. Entity Developer is a premium ORM designer for Entity Framework, Entity Framework Core, NHibernate, LinqConnect, Telerik Data Access, and LINQ to SQL. Entity Developer introduces new approaches to building ORM models and supports fast and efficient database application development.
Key Features
	Support for open source database connectors
	Support for all dotConnect products
	Easy integration with...
</description></item><item><title>Download dbForge Studio for MySQL Enterprise 2025.3.93</title><pubDate> Fri, 13 Feb 2026 15:44:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbforge-studio-for-mysql-enterprise-edition-7743.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbforge-studio-for-mysql-enterprise-edition-7743.html
</guid><description>
dbForge Studio for MySQL is a popular GUI tool for developing, managing, and administering MySQL and MariaDB databases. The IDE allows you to create and execute queries, develop and debug stored procedures, automate database object management, and analyze table data through an intuitive interface. The MySQL client provides data and schema comparison and synchronization tools, database reporting tools, backup options with scheduling, and much more.
Features of dbForge Studio for...
</description></item><item><title>Download Benthic Golden 8.3.0.830</title><pubDate> Fri, 13 Feb 2026 15:44:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-benthic-software-golden-4113.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-benthic-software-golden-4113.html
</guid><description>
Benthic Software Golden is a query tool for Oracle database. It includes the possibility of advanced queries, edit data and ability to import and export powerful, including support for Excel spreadsheet and Calc. It features compatibility closely with sqlplus estimate scenario consists of the variable binding, variable prompting and parameter scripts to go through. Benthic Software Golden can export directly to Excel files xls and xlsx. Exports can be scripted and run automatically using...
</description></item><item><title>Download Softwarenetz Invoice Rechnung 11.27</title><pubDate> Fri, 13 Feb 2026 15:43:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-softwarenetz-invoice-5588.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-softwarenetz-invoice-5588.html
</guid><description>
Softwarenetz Invoice is a useful program for self-employed, freelancers and small companies who are in need of a simple and user-friendly program for invoicing. The invoice program contains the complete address / customer database. You can see at a glance all invoices, payments and reminders for a particular customer. The memo field gives you the opportunity to enter customer specific information. Importing existing client from csv file is also included.
You can print your invoice on your...
</description></item><item><title>Download SAPIEN PowerShell ModuleManager 2026 v2.0.34</title><pubDate> Fri, 13 Feb 2026 15:43:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sapien-powershell-modulemanager-8197.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sapien-powershell-modulemanager-8197.html
</guid><description>
SAPIEN PowerShell ModuleManager makes it easy to find and manage modules installed on your local or remote machine, ensuring that your modules are always up and running. update. It also allows you to easily view module information such as description, release notes, version information, tags, dependencies, and commands. Search repositories, such as the PowerShell Library, to install new modules and view module details to help you decide if this is the right module for your needs mine or...
</description></item></channel></rss>