<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 09:15:34 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 09:15:34 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Topaz Photo Pro 1.0.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 23:42:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-photo-ai-8105.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-photo-ai-8105.html
</guid><description>
What is Topaz Photo AI?
Topaz Photo AI is a professional software that automatically adjusts for your image quality needs. Simply import images into Topaz Photo AI and it will use specially trained AI models to first detect unique details, clarity, and resolution issues before applying the intelligently adjusts to maximize your image quality.
For users experienced with Topaz Labs image quality applications, it combines the functionality of DeNoise AI, Sharpen AI and Gigapixel AI into...
</description></item><item><title>Download Topaz Video 1.0.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 23:39:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-video-enhance-ai-3733.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-video-enhance-ai-3733.html
</guid><description>
Topaz Video Enhance AI is a tool to increase video quality with this great technology ONE. Topaz Video Enhance WHO wide open your video to resolutions up to 8K with the details and consistency of motion. Until the present, there is no way to re-create a perfect high resolution video from the footage is low resolution. From the family film to SD low quality to DVD quality and more than that, Video Enhance WHO will convert your video into the footage is upgrade clear with resolutions up to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Topaz Gigapixel Pro 1.0.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 23:37:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-ai-gigapixel-1318.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-ai-gigapixel-1318.html
</guid><description>
Topaz ONE Gigapixel is the first app and only use the power of artificial intelligence to enhance your photos, add natural details, for great results. Use technology to learn deep, AIGigapixel ™ can zoom in and fill in the details that the products change in size other are not included. The traditional method this created blurred image, a non-realistic and do not have the detail present in the image have high resolution.
Topaz A.I. Gigapixel - enhance image quality
The content of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tiny11 24H2 Build 26100.6584</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 23:36:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tiny11-8649.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tiny11-8649.html
</guid><description>
Tiny11 is a compact Windows operating system based on Windows 11 Pro 22H2, Tiny11 has everything you need for a comfortable, hassle-free computing experience. cumbersome and messy like a standard Windows installation. The operating system requires only 8GB of disk space and 2GB of RAM, and requires no TPM (Trusted Platform Module) and Secure Boot support.
The main goal of Tiny11 is to extend the reach of systems that can access Windows 11. The custom edition can run on any system...
</description></item><item><title>Download Agisoft Metashape Professional 2.2.2 Build 21287</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 23:35:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-agisoft-metashape-professional-1731.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-agisoft-metashape-professional-1731.html
</guid><description>
Agisoft Metashape (formerly PhotoScan) is a software product independently perform image processing and digital data creation, 3D space used in GIS applications, material cultural heritage and the production visual effects as well as the indirect measurement of the different subjects scale. Technical digital photography is deployed wisely is applied with the method of computer vision led to the system processor, smart auto, on the one hand, can be managed by a new person in the field of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Psiphon 186.20250921</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 23:34:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-psiphon-7347.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-psiphon-7347.html
</guid><description>
Psiphon is a firewall bypass tool by Psiphon Inc. Uses VPN, SSH and HTTP Proxy technology to give you uncensored access to Internet content. Your Psiphon app automatically learns about new hotspots to maximize your chances of bypassing censorship.
The way the software works is that Psiphon constantly changes the proxy, so the user's IP address is also constantly changing, the server will not detect the user's real address, so you can feel free. roof. access to websites and software...
</description></item><item><title>Download CyberLink Director Suite 2026 v14.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 23:34:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-director-suite-6784.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-director-suite-6784.html
</guid><description>
CyberLink Director Suite is a toolkit, a final editing studio for all creators. Broaden your creative vision with the most advanced tools for editing videos, photos, sounds and colors. The toolbox all in your one for editing videos, photos, colors and sounds.
With the launch effects and powerful tools for editing videos, photos, colors and sounds, CyberLink Director Suite 365 is a complete editor for content creator. Take everything you need to create beautiful, professional, or...
</description></item><item><title>Download Boris FX Music Studio 2025.0.1.25261</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 23:32:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-magix-samplitude-music-studio-5122.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-magix-samplitude-music-studio-5122.html
</guid><description>
MAGIX Samplitude Music Studio - Brings the vision of your music come to life. Compose, record, mix and master. Use the creative tools and workflows, object-oriented, to create the complex arrangement. Choose from a variety of audio tools needed to prepare your songs for the stage. Discover music studio Samplitude. Everything a musician needs.
This program allows you to record your own music in a professional way, from creating it to burn CDS. In a very simple interface, you can easily...
</description></item><item><title>Download Boris FX Samplitude Suite 2025.0.1.25261</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 23:30:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-magix-samplitude-pro-x4-suite-623.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-magix-samplitude-pro-x4-suite-623.html
</guid><description>
MAGIX Samplitude Pro X4 Suite is software offered the highest quality level to record, mix and master the task, as well as to music production professional. With the professional effects, editing functions efficiently, as well as a tool, powerful sound, the latest version continues to set new standards in the field of professional audio.
MAGIX Samplitude Pro X4 Suite very impressed with the additional features such as handle DDP. Record and edit and work at the level of high quality...
</description></item><item><title>Download Boris FX Sequoia 2025.0.1 v17.4.2.25261</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 23:28:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-magix-sequoia-12379.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-magix-sequoia-12379.html
</guid><description>
Sequoia is your go-to solution for professional audio production.
From the recording studio to the mastering desk – stability, seamless processing and innovative editing features are key for engineers around the world. Our partners, including Europe's most prominent broadcasters, rely on its scalable, flexible hardware integration and network.
Your Audio Production Toolkit
Sequoia's feature set covers every step of your daily production workflow. Check out the core functionality in...
</description></item><item><title>Download Flyby11 1.21.411</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 23:26:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-flyby11-12467.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-flyby11-12467.html
</guid><description>
Flyby11 is a simple patcher that removes annoying restrictions that prevent you from installing Windows 11 (24H2) on unsupported hardware. Do you have an old PC? No TPM, Secure Boot or your processor is not supported? Flyby11 allows you to install Windows 11 24H2. There are no complicated steps. Just run the tool and you'll be running Windows 11 on your outdated machine in no time.
Technical overview
Flyby11 takes advantage of a feature of the Windows 11 setup process that uses the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Flyoobe 1.21.411</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 23:26:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oobelux-13956.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oobelux-13956.html
</guid><description>
Flyoobe was born out of the frustration many users felt with the Windows 11 setup experience. Whether it was the mandatory online account, the endless "Next, next, next..." screens, or the incomplete configuration options when you finally reached the desktop, the current setup lacked focus on what users really wanted.
Why choose Flyoobe?
	Simplifies the Windows 11 setup process right out of the box.
	Allows easy local account creation without need to hunt for hidden options.
	Includes...
</description></item><item><title>Download Imagine 2.2.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 23:26:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-imagine-7369.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-imagine-7369.html
</guid><description>
Imagine is an application that allows you to view images and animations in a variety of formats, including JPG, BMP, PNG and GIF. With Imagine you can view file properties and EXIF ​​information, copy, move, delete and rename images. Additionally, you can also flip, resize and rotate them, swap colors, set transparency levels, import, export, and edit palettes, and change color depth.
Features of Imagine
	View and save image/animation files at lightning speed
	Multiple...
</description></item><item><title>Download Vladovsoft Sklad Plus 16.3</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 23:25:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vladovsoft-sklad-plus-3994.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vladovsoft-sklad-plus-3994.html
</guid><description>
Vladovsoft Sklad Plus is a warehouse management software easy to use. It helps you keep track of products and customers, simplifies the process of delivery, sales and invoicing and the management and control of warehouse / your store easier than ever. Vladovsoft Sklad Plus help you to easily export tables and reports as interactive web pages (in HTML format) and to XML. Automatically calculate the weighted average after product delivery. Preview, print, choose printer and print tables,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Database Tour Pro 11.5.5.795</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 23:25:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-database-tour-pro-5321.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-database-tour-pro-5321.html
</guid><description>
Database Tour Pro application is a comprehensive software that allows you to organize all the database is connected his. It provides support for Borland Database Engine (BDE) and Microsoft ActiveX Data Objects (ADO), SQL scripts, reports, along with conversion and data export, among others.
It contains a browser object for the function, package, triggers, folders, users, roles, profiles, sequences, work, style, Java, exception, link, database, general properties, table, schema, and...
</description></item><item><title>Download BASQ Audio Grooveliner 1.6.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 23:21:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-basq-audio-grooveliner-11534.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-basq-audio-grooveliner-11534.html
</guid><description>
Grooveliner is a MIDI sequencer plugin (VST3, AU) and standalone application that handles grooves out of the box in many ways. With just a mouse gesture, you can easily create rotations, adjust emphasis, introduce subtle time changes, humanize and different time/velocity transitions, all according to your needs. real time way. As a MIDI sequencer, it can be applied to any audio source, bringing endless possibilities to your music production.
Main features:
	Create multiple samples,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Neo Lighting Control 4.2.0 Build 104</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 23:20:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-neo-lighting-control-12375.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-neo-lighting-control-12375.html
</guid><description>
NEO Software provides a scalable control system that meets the needs and requirements of our most demanding customers. The system's extensibility allows users to grow and take advantage of the LED revolution with an intuitive and flexible software base. NEO Software can be fully integrated into the Vision.net system, allowing for seamless control of both production and architectural lighting.
</description></item><item><title>Download Bogren Digital MLC S_Zero 100 1.0.1067</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 23:20:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bogren-digital-mlc-szero-100-10346.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bogren-digital-mlc-szero-100-10346.html
</guid><description>
Experience your guitar tracks with one of the most exclusive, high-quality guitar amplifiers available today. Modeled using groundbreaking new technology and sounds designed by Jens Bogren, Bogren Digital MLC S_Zero 100 is a sonic powerhouse that truly stands out from the crowd of digital amp simulations.
</description></item><item><title>Download Loomer String 1.17.3</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 20:24:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-loomer-string-14171.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-loomer-string-14171.html
</guid><description>
Loomer String is a virtual polyphonic string synthesizer plugin that emulates classic 1970s string synthesizers. Its authentic tones are created by accurately emulating the split oscillator technology used in iconic 1970s string synthesizers. String has two separate sound generation layers, each with three phase-locked oscillators tuned to different octave ranges, which can produce a rich and variable range of tones. It includes flexible keyboard routing and split layers, allowing each...
</description></item><item><title>Download Loomer Resound 1.9.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 20:19:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-loomer-resound-14170.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-loomer-resound-14170.html
</guid><description>
Resound is a software audio delay effects processor that emulates the sound and behavior of classic tape echo devices. Controllable noise levels allow for just the right amount of grit, distortion, and flutter. Reverse mode adds flexibility: by playing each delay backwards, Resound can create unique effects that go far beyond the capabilities of hardware tape decks.
Features of Loomer Resound
	Up to 30 seconds of delay time when synchronized with the host tempo, up to 2 seconds when...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cymatics VOXITY Vocal Mixing Plugin 1.0.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 20:15:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cymatics-voxity-vocal-mixing-plugin-14169.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cymatics-voxity-vocal-mixing-plugin-14169.html
</guid><description>
VOXITY is an all-in-one vocal mixing plugin designed to help any artist or producer achieve outstanding, industry-standard vocals in seconds. Partnering with world-class mix engineers and sound designers to deliver crystal-clear, industry-standard sound quality with a comprehensive library of presets for every genre. Just focus on your performance, let VOXITY do the rest.
What makes VOXITY special?
	When it comes to vocal mixing, it can easily make or break your song idea.
	VOXITY is...
</description></item><item><title>Download Loomer Manifold 1.9.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 20:12:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-loomer-manifold-14168.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-loomer-manifold-14168.html
</guid><description>
Manifold is a harmonic audio effect that works by dividing the input signal into up to 20 separate voices, each of which is detuned and dispersed around the stereo landscape. Manifold is capable of creating a wide range of effects; from subtle modulations that add interest to lifeless sounds, to extreme detuning that accentuates the weakest input sources.
Key Features
	The input audio signal is split into 4 to 20 separate voices.
	Processing only a specific frequency range using...
</description></item><item><title>Download Display Driver Uninstaller (DDU) 18.1.3.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 19:34:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-display-driver-uninstaller-1999.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-display-driver-uninstaller-1999.html
</guid><description>
Display Driver Uninstaller (DDU) help to easily completely remove the packages and drivers graphics cards AMD, NVIDIA and Intel from your system without leaving any rest whatsoever. Display Driver Uninstaller will automatically detect your current GPU and allows you to delete drivers, registry and files related only by the click of a button. It will also prevent Windows automatically re-install drivers when you reboot your computer, leaving you a drivers graphics common until you install...
</description></item><item><title>Download R-Wipe &amp;amp; Clean 20.0 Build 2527</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 19:32:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-wipe-clean-891.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-wipe-clean-891.html
</guid><description>
R-Wipe &amp;amp; Clean is software to delete junk files, unnecessary files from your computer to release the storage space and speed up your computer. In addition, R-Wipe &amp;amp; Clean also unleash the capacity of your drive and delete information invasion of privacy on different operations online and offline including your internet history and cookies, the list of downloaded files and documents were open, buffer different data, temporary files and many other items, created by the operating...
</description></item><item><title>Download ExtraMAME 25.9</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 19:31:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-extramame-2608.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-extramame-2608.html
</guid><description>
ExtraMAME is a simple tool that allows simulation of the arcade game from the most popular platform but is long forgotten, thanks to which the game industry has reached the current level. After launch, you will get 11 games pre-installed, among which are: Super Mario Bros, Pac-Man Plus, Space Invaders II and other games.
The simulation of multiple machine arcade is authored by Nicola Salmoria and team MAME. MAME lets you play thousands of arcade game old school on your computer. ExtraMAME...
</description></item></channel></rss>