<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 15:35:35 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 15:35:35 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Database Tour Pro 11.5.9.707</title><pubDate> Sat, 15 Nov 2025 18:35:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-database-tour-pro-5321.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-database-tour-pro-5321.html
</guid><description>
Database Tour Pro application is a comprehensive software that allows you to organize all the database is connected his. It provides support for Borland Database Engine (BDE) and Microsoft ActiveX Data Objects (ADO), SQL scripts, reports, along with conversion and data export, among others.
It contains a browser object for the function, package, triggers, folders, users, roles, profiles, sequences, work, style, Java, exception, link, database, general properties, table, schema, and...
</description></item><item><title>Download PentaLogix CAMMaster 11.24.70</title><pubDate> Sat, 15 Nov 2025 18:34:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pentalogix-cammaster-5559.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pentalogix-cammaster-5559.html
</guid><description>
CAMMaster Designer is CAM software of choice by the Designer for the most demanding jobs. Experience the industry's best CAD companion to get your work done. The disinfection process is fast with all the features available in this package. Exploiting Netlist and DRC sets industry standards. Basically, CamMaster provides many functions depending on the relevant needs of the user. It also provides nearly five free technical support. Furthermore, net list comparison and class comparison make...
</description></item><item><title>Download K-Lite Codec Pack Update 19.3.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 15 Nov 2025 18:34:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-update-5145.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-update-5145.html
</guid><description>
K-Lite Codec Pack Update is the update of the set of codecs and related tools. Codec stands for Compressor-decompressor. Codec is necessary to encode and decode (play) audio and video. K-Lite Codec Pack Update is designed as a user-friendly solution with users to play all movie files your. With Codec Pack K-Lite, you can play 99% of all the movies found on your computer. A number of packages codec is not friendly with computers, as they tend to slow down Windows, break down multimedia...
</description></item><item><title>Download NoteCase Pro 4.8.5</title><pubDate> Sat, 15 Nov 2025 18:33:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-notecase-pro-8093.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-notecase-pro-8093.html
</guid><description>
NoteCase Pro is a program that supports cross-platform Windows, Macintosh, Linux, FreeBSD, OpenBSD and Solaris,... it is used to collect, organize, protect , access and recycle your information quickly. NoteCase Pro can import data from more than 30 different file formats, including Evernote, XMind, TreePad, Tomboy formats. This allows you to quickly migrate your data from other programs.
Also, for advanced users, they can extend NoteCase Pro's feature set using Plugins, or even write...
</description></item><item><title>Download PentaLogix CAMMaster Designer 11.24.70</title><pubDate> Sat, 15 Nov 2025 18:33:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pentalogix-cammaster-designer-13705.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pentalogix-cammaster-designer-13705.html
</guid><description>
CAMMaster Designer is the CAM software of choice for designers for their most demanding jobs. Experience the industry's best CAD companion to get your work done. Panelization is easy with all the features included in this package. Netlist and DRC extraction set the industry standard.
Highlights
	Contour-based netlist extraction
	Advanced DFM inspection
	Automatic aperture conversion
	Layer comparison
	Network conversion
	Automatic conversion from draw to flash
	Solder mask...
</description></item><item><title>Download Splunk Enterprise 10.0.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 15 Nov 2025 18:32:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-splunk-enterprise-7216.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-splunk-enterprise-7216.html
</guid><description>
Splunk Enterprise makes it easy to collect, analyze, and act on the untapped value of big data due to its technological infrastructure, secure systems, and your business application generates, giving you insights to drive performance and business results.
Features of Splunk Enterprise:
	Collect and index logs and machine data from any source
	Powerful search, analytics, and visualization capabilities empower users of all types
	The app provides solutions for security, IT operations,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mypal 74.1.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 15 Nov 2025 16:33:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mypal-4504.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mypal-4504.html
</guid><description>
Mypal is a web browser Windows XP current and to be maintained. Mypal is based on the code of Pale Moon by Moonchild Productions, it is separated from the code of Mozilla's FireFox a few years ago, but is well maintained and preserved. The goal of Mypal is to provide a web browser current, safe and reliable for Windows XP. Mypal operation identical to Pale Moon with some small exceptions. Introduced system new mobile and a number of certain settings, including code Mozilla old not used,...
</description></item><item><title>Download The Dude 7.20.4</title><pubDate> Sat, 15 Nov 2025 16:29:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-the-dude-3238.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-the-dude-3238.html
</guid><description>
The Dude is a new application by MikroTik which can dramatically improve the way you manage your network environment. It will automatically scan all devices in the subnet is specified, draw and layout a map of your networks, monitor services of your devices and alert you in case some service has problems.is a new application by MikroTik which can dramatically improve the way you manage your network environment. It will automatically scan all devices in the subnet is specified, draw and...
</description></item><item><title>Download AIMP 5.40 Build 2698 + Portable</title><pubDate> Sat, 15 Nov 2025 16:29:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aimp-1302.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aimp-1302.html
</guid><description>
AIMP is a free audio with support for large number of formats and playlists. It works with multiple playlists immediately, allows creation of bookmarks and also has the playback queue.
AIMP - audio player
Features of AIMP
	Clear sound, technology of re-creating fundamentally different from Winamp and WMP
	The balance sensitivity
	Maximum functions from minimal resource
	Minimum consumption of system resources
	Multi-language support
	Support the audio format
	Adjust the hot keys for...
</description></item><item><title>Download Windows Firewall Control 6.23</title><pubDate> Sat, 15 Nov 2025 16:28:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-firewall-control-3395.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-firewall-control-3395.html
</guid><description>
Windows Firewall Control is a application which help extend the functionality of the Microsoft Windows Firewall and provides quick access to the most common options of Windows firewall. It works in the system tray and allows users to adjust firewall simple root which does not have to lose time by navigating to the specific part of the firewall.
Windows Firewall Control - firewall App for windows
It runs in the system tray and allows user to control the firewall easily without having to...
</description></item><item><title>Download System Info 18.38</title><pubDate> Sat, 15 Nov 2025 16:27:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-system-info-11391.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-system-info-11391.html
</guid><description>
System Info is a simple piece of software that displays various information about your system, including its hardware, operating system, and more. Having everything presented in a single interface, where you can copy and share that data elsewhere, can finally become convenient for regular users. That's what System Information does: it gives you various data about your system, including hardware specifications, operating system, network, and more. without installation.
This application...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mobile Scanner App - Scan PDF 2.13.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 15 Nov 2025 16:24:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-mobile-scanner-app-scan-pdf-9644.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-mobile-scanner-app-scan-pdf-9644.html
</guid><description>
Mobile Scanner is an all-in-one scanner app. Scan any document, paper note, photo, receipt, and book into clear PDFs and images. Convert images to text using OCR technology and export searchable PDFs. It allows you to capture documents with your smartphone camera and save them as high-quality PDF files. It offers features like automatic edge detection, text recognition, and integration.
Features of Mobile Scanner App - Scan PDF
Super fast scanning
	Scan anything - receipts, photos,...
</description></item><item><title>Download PowerDirector - Video Editor 15.9.0 build 251131</title><pubDate> Sat, 15 Nov 2025 16:24:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-powerdirector-video-editor-8123.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-powerdirector-video-editor-8123.html
</guid><description>
PowerDirector APK - Video Editor (Unlocked Version) is video editing software developed by CyberLink. It is available for Windows and Android devices. If you are looking for the Android version of PowerDirector, you can download the APK (Android Package Kit) file from the Google Play Store or from taiwebs.com.
Features of PowerDirector APK - Unlocked Version:
	Easy-to-use interface: PowerDirector has a user-friendly interface that makes it easy to edit and create videos, even if...
</description></item><item><title>Download HiEdu Calculator Pro 1.8.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 15 Nov 2025 16:24:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-hiedu-calculator-pro-8218.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-hiedu-calculator-pro-8218.html
</guid><description>
HiEdu Calculator Pro is a simple yet powerful calculator that includes standard, scientific and programming modes, as well as unit converters, Mathematical, Physical and Chemical Formulas, Graphing and Equation Solver. It is the perfect tool for adding bills, converting measurements in recipes or other projects, and is a great tool for education to help solve complex math, algebra, or geometry problems.
HiEdu Calculator Pro Features
	Advanced Math Functions: The Pro version may offer...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDF Scanner app - TapScanner 3.0.90</title><pubDate> Sat, 15 Nov 2025 16:23:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pdf-scanner-app-tapscanner-12104.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pdf-scanner-app-tapscanner-12104.html
</guid><description>
TapScanner is a mobile application that allows you to scan documents with your smartphone camera and convert them into PDF files or image formats. It essentially turns your device into a portable scanner, making capturing and digitizing physical documents convenient on the go.
TapScanner Features
	Scan documents, receipts, QRs and business cards
	Document Scanner App - Automatic Border Detection
	Tweak your images with multiple filters to achieve perfection
	Easily manage your...
</description></item><item><title>Download Photo Studio PRO 2.8.7.4631</title><pubDate> Sat, 15 Nov 2025 16:23:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-photo-studio-pro-8247.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-photo-studio-pro-8247.html
</guid><description>
Photo Studio APK is a powerful multifunctional photo editing application for photographers of all levels. It contains a huge set of editing tools for basic and advanced editing of your photos. Turn each of your photos into a finished work of art using a variety of effects, filters, text editing and color enhancement tools, and many other available features.
Features of Photo Studio Pro APK
	More than 200 unique filters, amazing special effects, large collection of picture-in-picture...
</description></item><item><title>Download iTranslate Translator 7.1.0 build 1084</title><pubDate> Sat, 15 Nov 2025 16:23:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-itranslate-translator-11915.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-itranslate-translator-11915.html
</guid><description>
iTranslate is the leading translation and dictionary app. Translate text, web pages or start voice chat easily in over 100 languages. With over 100 languages ​​supported, iTranslate Translator allows users to easily translate text, voice, and even images. Whether you're traveling abroad, learning a new language, or simply need to communicate with someone in another language, iTranslate Translator is the perfect tool to overcome language barriers.
iTranslate features
	Translates...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tap To Translate Screen 1.105</title><pubDate> Sat, 15 Nov 2025 16:22:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-tap-to-translate-screen-10152.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-tap-to-translate-screen-10152.html
</guid><description>
Tap to translate screen is an effective screen translation tool to serve all the needs of users. The ability to translate quickly combined with different languages ​​makes the application special. The diversity of Tap to translate screen languages ​​has users excited. With hundreds of languages ​​and different translations, the application will stand out more than ever. Users just need to select the target language and then translate it immediately; A paragraph will match...
</description></item><item><title>Download HiEdu Calculator He-580 Pro 1.6.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 15 Nov 2025 16:22:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-hiedu-calculator-he-580-pro-8206.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-hiedu-calculator-he-580-pro-8206.html
</guid><description>
HiEdu Calculator He-580 Pro is the perfect tool for everyday calculations. With a memorization function similar to a small handheld calculator. Now, there is no need to write paper notes to remember math formulas, just let this app save all the formulas on your favorite phone. This app has over 1000 math formulas and more.
The layout of the buttons in this app is very scientific, making entering math operations as simple and convenient as possible. The numeric and function buttons in...
</description></item><item><title>Download Multi Timer StopWatch 2.13.26 build 498</title><pubDate> Sat, 15 Nov 2025 16:22:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-multi-timer-stopwatch-8914.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-multi-timer-stopwatch-8914.html
</guid><description>
Multi Timer is a beautifully designed time management app. Multiple timers can be set, started and run independently at the same time. Stopwatch results can be stored. Use Multi Timer for cooking, sports, machine washing, studying, working, gaming - whatever you like.
Features of Multi Timer StopWatch
	Multiple timers at once: Store the timers you often use for cooking, sports, studying, working, gaming, whatever you want. Start them with just one tap, anytime you need.
	Timer in...
</description></item><item><title>Download Money Manager Expense &amp;amp; Budget 4.10.3 GF build 1130</title><pubDate> Sat, 15 Nov 2025 16:21:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-money-manager-expense-budget-13837.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-money-manager-expense-budget-13837.html
</guid><description>
Money Manager - the #1 financial planning, budgeting, expense tracking and personal wealth management app for Android! Money Manager makes managing your personal finances as easy as pie! Now you can easily record personal and business financial transactions, generate spending reports, review daily, weekly and monthly financial data and manage your assets with Money Manager's spending tracker and budget planner.
Key Features
- Adopt double-entry bookkeeping system
Money Manager...
</description></item><item><title>Download Graphing Calculator - Algeo 2.47</title><pubDate> Sat, 15 Nov 2025 16:21:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-graphing-calculator-algeo-8784.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-graphing-calculator-algeo-8784.html
</guid><description>
Algeo is the most beautiful scientific graphing calculator available on the Play Store. It's fast and powerful and you'll never have to carry a large physical TI calculator again. The intuitive interface displays your drawn functions as if you wrote them on paper instead of putting everything on one line. And you don't need an internet connection unlike other graphing calculators, it works offline too! Useful for calculus, physics or solving those x+y equations.
This free app has more...
</description></item><item><title>Download AdGuard Ad Blocker 4.14.5 Nightly</title><pubDate> Sat, 15 Nov 2025 16:21:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-adguard-block-ads-without-root-8215.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-adguard-block-ads-without-root-8215.html
</guid><description>
AdGuard for Android is the only root-free ad blocker for Android that removes ads in apps and browsers, protects your privacy, and helps you manage your apps. Adguard is designed to block unwanted ads, pop-ups and banners while you browse the web on your device. It uses a combination of local VPN technology and a custom DNS server to block ads, meaning it can block ads in apps as well as in web browsers.
In addition, Adguard also blocks tracking scripts from collecting information about...
</description></item><item><title>Download myTuner Radio App: FM stations 9.7.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 15 Nov 2025 16:20:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-mytuner-radio-app-fm-stations-11072.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-mytuner-radio-app-fm-stations-11072.html
</guid><description>
Now available for Samsung TVs, LG TVs AND Roku! With the myTuner Radio app, you can listen to live radio from around the world on your Android phone or tablet. With a modern, beautiful and easy-to-use interface, myTuner gives you the best experience when listening to online radio, internet radio, AM and FM radio.
myTuner Radio App Features: FM Radio
	listen to more than 50,000 radio stations from more than 200 countries and territories;
	follow your favorite shows and over 1 million...
</description></item><item><title>Download Transparent clock weather Pro 8.99.11</title><pubDate> Sat, 15 Nov 2025 16:20:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-transparent-clock-weather-pro-8872.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-transparent-clock-weather-pro-8872.html
</guid><description>
Transparent Clock Weather Pro: Get Accurate Local or Worldwide Weather Forecasts Easily with Live Weather Updates, Hourly and Daily Weather Forecasts and Timely Weather Alerts. Check The Weather for Today, Tomorrow or the weekend with our Easy to use app and widgets.
Features of Transparent Clock Weather Pro
	local Weather: Automatically keep track or your location as you move and get accurate real time weather reports and alerts
	Different Weather Preded for More Accurate Weather...
</description></item></channel></rss>