<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 19:52:10 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 19:52:10 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Display Driver Uninstaller (DDU) 18.1.3.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 19:34:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-display-driver-uninstaller-1999.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-display-driver-uninstaller-1999.html
</guid><description>
Display Driver Uninstaller (DDU) help to easily completely remove the packages and drivers graphics cards AMD, NVIDIA and Intel from your system without leaving any rest whatsoever. Display Driver Uninstaller will automatically detect your current GPU and allows you to delete drivers, registry and files related only by the click of a button. It will also prevent Windows automatically re-install drivers when you reboot your computer, leaving you a drivers graphics common until you install...
</description></item><item><title>Download R-Wipe &amp;amp; Clean 20.0 Build 2527</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 19:32:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-wipe-clean-891.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-wipe-clean-891.html
</guid><description>
R-Wipe &amp;amp; Clean is software to delete junk files, unnecessary files from your computer to release the storage space and speed up your computer. In addition, R-Wipe &amp;amp; Clean also unleash the capacity of your drive and delete information invasion of privacy on different operations online and offline including your internet history and cookies, the list of downloaded files and documents were open, buffer different data, temporary files and many other items, created by the operating...
</description></item><item><title>Download ExtraMAME 25.9</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 19:31:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-extramame-2608.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-extramame-2608.html
</guid><description>
ExtraMAME is a simple tool that allows simulation of the arcade game from the most popular platform but is long forgotten, thanks to which the game industry has reached the current level. After launch, you will get 11 games pre-installed, among which are: Super Mario Bros, Pac-Man Plus, Space Invaders II and other games.
The simulation of multiple machine arcade is authored by Nicola Salmoria and team MAME. MAME lets you play thousands of arcade game old school on your computer. ExtraMAME...
</description></item><item><title>Download OkMap Desktop 19.1.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 19:30:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-okmap-desktop-581.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-okmap-desktop-581.html
</guid><description>
OkMap Desktop is interactive software working on the computer with web maps or digital maps bought or scanned. OkMap can also import a data vector from the most common formats and data DEM related to information height.
Through the map you can organize your path by creating waypoints , routesand tracks on the screen your computer, and upload this data to your GPS . OkMap set data high speedautomatic and estimated moving time . Furthermore OkMap provides you also have autorouting and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Substance 3D Sampler 5.1.1 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 19:30:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-substance-3d-sampler-6625.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-substance-3d-sampler-6625.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Substance 3D Sampler allows you to create and iterate on collections of materials by refining and blending existing materials or by extracting new materials from scans ( one or more images). A new set of powerful tools that combine different technologies and creation methods (AI-based and manual) will help you manage your entire document library and export them to other applications.
Features of Adobe Substance 3D Sampler
	AI-powered scan processing
	Use your content everywhere....
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Substance 3D Designer 15.0.2 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 19:28:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-substancee-designer-adobe-908.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-substancee-designer-adobe-908.html
</guid><description>
Substance Designer is the tool aggregated structure to help design, create 3D material. Create the file Quality or texture bitmap. Substance Designer helps users to create materials with full control and infinite variations. Edit the texture complete immediately and create texture, Quality and material of MDL will be handled directly in the renderer or game engine of you.
Substance Designer - design, create 3D material
The main features of Substance Designer
	Substance Designer...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinTools.net Professional / Premium / Classic 25.10.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 19:28:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wintoolsnet-304.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wintoolsnet-304.html
</guid><description>
WinTools.net is an optimal tool working performance of the operating system and delete the unnecessary program from the hard drive and control the start-up process of Windows.
WinTools.net integrates many useful tools, to support increased processing speed and ability, stable operation for the computer include: Clean Uninstaller, Scan Files, Scan Registry, Start Up, Tweak UI, Net Tweaker, The Privacy. Scan Files are often used to scan the hard drive periodically, search for junk files or...
</description></item><item><title>Download uTorrent Pro 3.6.0 Build 47222</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 19:27:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-utorrent-pro-79.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-utorrent-pro-79.html
</guid><description>
uTorrent - Download the torrent file
uTorrent Pro is an application BitTorrent efficient for Windows. Most of the features in the BitTorrent client and others have in uTorrent, including priority bandwidth, scheduling, automatic download at RSS and Mainline DHT. Additionally, uTorrent supports specification joint protocol encryption and peer exchange of goods. Unlike many torrent clients, it does not hog system resources have value - typically using less than 6MB of memory, allowing you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Topaz Video AI Pro 7.1.4 RC2 / 7.2.0 Beta 3</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 19:26:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-video-enhance-ai-3733.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-video-enhance-ai-3733.html
</guid><description>
Topaz Video Enhance AI is a tool to increase video quality with this great technology ONE. Topaz Video Enhance WHO wide open your video to resolutions up to 8K with the details and consistency of motion. Until the present, there is no way to re-create a perfect high resolution video from the footage is low resolution. From the family film to SD low quality to DVD quality and more than that, Video Enhance WHO will convert your video into the footage is upgrade clear with resolutions up to...
</description></item><item><title>Download RAM Saver Professional 25.9.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 19:26:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ram-saver-pro-565.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ram-saver-pro-565.html
</guid><description>
RAM Saver Pro is a professional software optimize RAM is for system stable operation with high performance. RAM Saver Pro aims to provide all the tools necessary to increase the amount of free memory, at any time, also monitor and check the RAM.
When using RAM Saver Pro, you will be allowed to access its main menu by right-clicking on the tray icon. Also, if you want to display the main panel of the program you just double-click the icon. In addition, from the main interface of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download AllmapSoft Google Satellite Maps Downloader 8.410</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 19:25:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-google-satellite-maps-downloader-687.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-google-satellite-maps-downloader-687.html
</guid><description>
AllmapSoft Google Satellite Maps Downloader is software help download map images from google maps on computer for you to get the satellite images from google map. All the downloaded photos will be saved on disk. You can see the map is downloaded by viewer Or you can combine them into the map BMP, big. It supports proxy server. And you can easily get the longitude and latitude of each image tile small download.
You can use offline maps in GIS software such as Global Mapper, QGIS,...
</description></item><item><title>Download ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro 15.25.0920</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 19:25:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-videotube-downloader-pro-1276.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-videotube-downloader-pro-1276.html
</guid><description>
ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro is the professional version support download videos and playlists from YouTube, videos from Dailymotion, BBC iPlayer, ITV Player, ABC,  FOX,CBS.com Vimeo, Prosieben, Metacafe, Blip.tv CBC.ca many more video sites. After the video is downloaded, you can convert them to the formats compatible with iPad, iPhone, iPod, MPEG-4, H. 264, MP3, AC3.
ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro - Download videos on Youtube
This is one of the software download the most...
</description></item><item><title>Download AllMapSoft Offline Map Maker 8.353</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 19:24:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-offline-map-maker-656.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-offline-map-maker-656.html
</guid><description>
AllMapSoft Offline Map Maker is software create, organize, offline map from Google Maps, Yahoo maps, Bing maps and Openstreetmap. You can view offline maps downloaded with map viewer offline. And you can zoom out or zoom in the offline map or export map under the file format .BMP with file world xxx.bpw, and can output files xxx.map for OziExplorer. If you want to make a offline map of your city by yourself, it is very useful for you.
Features AllMapSoft Offline Map Maker
	You can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Folder Lock 10.1.9</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 19:24:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-folderlock-1115.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-folderlock-1115.html
</guid><description>
Folder Lock is software protect your data by locking and encrypting with a password and backup data quickly. Folder Lock allows you to keep personal files of his are protected in many different ways, in both PC and portable drives and offers optional backup of protected files to the online storage.
Folder Lock - Lock and protect files
Folder Lock uses 256-bit encryption is active and backup them in real-time to the online storage, and store them on any mobile device any. The program...
</description></item><item><title>Download AllMapSoft Google Maps Terrain Downloader 7.202</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 19:23:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-google-maps-terrain-downloader-6476.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-google-maps-terrain-downloader-6476.html
</guid><description>
AllMapSoft Google Maps Terrain Downloader  is a tool that can automatically download Google topographic map images to your PC. It can download small squares and save them to your hard disk. Once downloaded, you can view the map offline with its Maps Viewer tool, or you can combine the small images into one large map image. If you want to make your own city map, it is very useful for you.
</description></item><item><title>Download VovSoft Directory Monitor 2.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 19:23:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-directory-monitor-6900.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-directory-monitor-6900.html
</guid><description>
Monitor and detect what happens in your directory. VovSoft Directory Monitor will monitor changes, deletions, modifications, new files of files and folders in real time. Any changes made by users or processes can be detected. You can export directory change logs to TXT or CSV files so you can save and analyze them later.
VovSoft Directory Monitor is an intuitive utility that makes it easy to monitor possible modifications in a directory or a network share. The whole workflow is pretty...
</description></item><item><title>Download Audio Modeling SWAM Solo Brass 3.10.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 19:22:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-audio-modeling-swam-solo-brass-bundle-10441.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-audio-modeling-swam-solo-brass-bundle-10441.html
</guid><description>
Audio Modeling SWAM Solo Brass Bundle is a collection of acoustic instruments based on Physical Modeling technology and does not use any samples. It includes 15 instruments, grouped by product line: SWAM Trumpet, SWAM Trombone and SWAM Horns and Tubas. It enables composers, musicians and performers to play - both in the recording studio and in live performances - the most realistic and expressive virtual trumpet solo ever conceived, through musical instruments can be controlled in real...
</description></item><item><title>Download Nobe OmniScope 1.11.15</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 19:21:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nobe-omniscope-10985.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nobe-omniscope-10985.html
</guid><description>
Nobe OmniScope is a powerful and flexible video monitoring and analysis tool used by professionals in the film, television and post-production industries. It provides a comprehensive set of features and tools for monitoring, analyzing, and editing video footage. Nobe OmniScope is equipped with many powerful features to help classify colors easily. GPU acceleration, HDR support, StreamDeck. Use the benefits of GPU acceleration and monitor your images in real time with virtually no...
</description></item><item><title>Download MyLanViewer Enterprise 6.5.9</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 19:21:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mylanviewer-enterprise-1274.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mylanviewer-enterprise-1274.html
</guid><description>
MyLanViewer is a program for scanning IP address, Netbios and LAN / Network powerful for Windows tool whois and traceroute, remote shutdown and process management Wake On LAN (WOL), scan and monitor wireless networks. This app will help you find all IP addresses, MAC addresses and shared folders of computers on the network wired or wireless (Wi-Fi).
MyLanViewer Enterprise - Scan IP address LAN/Network
The program scans network and displays the computer network in your window, friends...
</description></item><item><title>Download AllMapSoft Google Maps Downloader 8.881</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 19:20:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-google-maps-downloader-2796.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-google-maps-downloader-2796.html
</guid><description>
AllMapSoft Google Maps Downloader is a reliable application aimed at downloading maps from Google at high speed. The result is a set of small images can be combined in a larger map. This can serve in a large variety of projects, from creating a tile map to presentations and tutorials.
Google Maps Downloader successfully fulfills both of those conditions, providing simple means to quickly grab maps at the resolution satisfactory. In addition, it is extremely easy to use and integrated a...
</description></item><item><title>Download AllMapSoft Google Hybrid Maps Downloader 8.442</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 19:20:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-google-hybrid-maps-downloader-6479.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-google-hybrid-maps-downloader-6479.html
</guid><description>
AllMapSoft Google Hybrid Maps Downloader  is a tool that can automatically download a Google combined map image to your PC. It can download small squares and save them to your hard disk. Once downloaded, you can view the map offline with its Maps Viewer tool, or you can combine the small images into one large map image. If you want to make your own city map, it is very useful for you.
</description></item><item><title>Download FlowHeater 4.5.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 19:20:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-flowheater-7776.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-flowheater-7776.html
</guid><description>
FlowHeater is software that converts MS Access, MS Excel, MS SQL Server, MySQL, SQLite, PostgreSQL, Oracle, OleDB and ODBC data sources as well as formats text format (CSV​, TXT, ASC, ASCII, Flat File...) in a simple way. In addition, the software also supports unlimited data exchange streams.
Features of FlowHeater
	Text file for reading and writing text files (CSV, TXT, ASCII, FlatFile, etc.).
	MS Access is used to import and export data directly into and out of Microsoft Access...
</description></item><item><title>Download Google Earth Images Downloader 6.46</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 19:19:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-earth-images-downloader-2802.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-earth-images-downloader-2802.html
</guid><description>
Google Earth Images Downloader is a tool that helps you grab images tile satellite offline from google earth (not google maps). It can work without google earth installed. Google Earth Images Downloader has four parameters are used to determine the target area, namely the longitude left and right and the highest point and lower latitudes. You can also limit the number of images to be downloaded at a time, limited active in a range of zoom levels specific.
Google Earth Images Downloader...
</description></item><item><title>Download Vladovsoft Hotel 16.4.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 19:19:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vladovsoft-hotel-6008.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vladovsoft-hotel-6008.html
</guid><description>
Vladovsoft Hotel is an easy-to-use, affordable hotel management software. It tracks all delivery, sales, booking and dining and helps your hotel management more easily than ever.
Features of Vladovsoft Hotel
	Activities with non-limited product and service numbers
	Activity with no limited number of rooms, reservation and accommodation
	Work with operators with different user rights
	The forms for making delivery and sales
	Activity with bar code scanner and bar code reader
	Can be...
</description></item><item><title>Download AllMapSoft Universal Maps Downloader 10.223</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 19:18:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-universal-maps-downloader-736.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-universal-maps-downloader-736.html
</guid><description>
AllMapSoft Universal Maps Downloader is software download map images on the computer for offline viewing support many types such as Google Maps, Yahoo maps, Bing maps, OpenStreet Maps, Yandex Maps, Ovi Maps, MapQuest Maps. All the downloaded photos will be saved on disk. You can view downloaded maps by Maps Viewer Or you can combine them into one big bmp, or jpg file tif by Maps Combiner, and also you can export all the tiles into a database format MBTiles.
AllMapSoft Universal Maps...
</description></item></channel></rss>