<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 17:57:15 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 17:57:15 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Wise Disk Cleaner 11.3.2.852</title><pubDate> Fri, 30 Jan 2026 20:42:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wise-disk-cleaner-392.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wise-disk-cleaner-392.html
</guid><description>
Wise Disk Cleaner software to clean hard drive by finding and deleting junk files downloads accumulate over time. Wise Disk Cleaner is pre-configured with about 50 types of extension files can usually be considered disposable, and you can extend the range by adding the file types of their own.
Wise Disk Cleaner to use the advanced algorithm with the ability to quick scan and comprehensive scan of hard drive space. Users can delete browsing history as well as the personal data important...
</description></item><item><title>Download Advanced SystemCare Pro 19.2.0.188</title><pubDate> Fri, 30 Jan 2026 20:39:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-systemcare-pro-368.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-systemcare-pro-368.html
</guid><description>
Advanced SystemCare Pro is software that provides features to optimize a PC system professional cleanup, repair, speed up and protect PC.  Advanced SystemCare Pro tab Protect new is added, is designed to provide quick access to protect browsing from being tracked by automatically delete traces of privacy when browser closed and detect and resist the attack of the plugin / malicious toolbar by Browser Anti -Backing and Plugin / toolbar cleaner.
Program speed up pc top
Advanced SystemCare...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare PDFelement Pro 12.1.8.3995</title><pubDate> Fri, 30 Jan 2026 20:39:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-pdfelement-pro-105.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-pdfelement-pro-105.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare PDFelement Pro support users to convert PDF to office documents for easier use, modify in every situation. Is one of the software conversion material is rated best today, integrated with many features. We recommend that you should use experience software many useful features this.
Wondershare PDFelement Pro - conversion Fie PDF more features, multi-language
Wondershare PDFelement Pro what?
Convert PDF into Word, Excel, PowerPoint...
• Convert PDF and protected PDF into...
</description></item><item><title>Download Aiarty Image Enhancer 3.9</title><pubDate> Fri, 30 Jan 2026 20:38:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aiarty-image-enhancer-12181.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aiarty-image-enhancer-12181.html
</guid><description>
Aiarty Image Enhancer is an AI-powered image enhancement software to de-noise, de-blur, enhance images and create more image details. It uses advanced deep learning technologies to enhance and upscale images while creating realistic details. Whether you want to enlarge low-resolution images by 200%, 400% or 800% for printing, deliver 2K/4K/8K images while preserving realistic details, correcting low-quality photos , remove blur and noise or restore compressed JPEGs, Aiarty Image Enhancer...
</description></item><item><title>Download Chaos Enscape 4.15.0.276</title><pubDate> Fri, 30 Jan 2026 20:38:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-enscape-3d-4125.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-enscape-3d-4125.html
</guid><description>
Enscape 3D is the tool support simulation 3D for the software Revit, SketchUp, Rhino, ArchiCAD. With real-time technology of Enscape 3D your project is displayed in the form of walk-3D is fully displayed, can be navigated and explored from every angle, at every moment of the day. With direct link between Enscape 3D and CAD programs, you can track all updates for his plan immediately. More Enscape to your work to give yourself more time to create and innovate. Enscape 3D offers many options...
</description></item><item><title>Download Digiarty Aiarty Video Enhancer 3.5</title><pubDate> Fri, 30 Jan 2026 20:37:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-digiarty-aiarty-video-enhancer-13862.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-digiarty-aiarty-video-enhancer-13862.html
</guid><description>
Digiarty Aiarty Video Enhancer is an AI-powered desktop software designed to upscale, denoise, deblur, and enhance videos up to 4K resolution with professional quality and speed. It uses advanced AI models optimized for GPU acceleration and Turbo mode, enabling real-time or near-real-time video processing, including frame interpolation for smooth motion up to 90fps, 120fps, or higher. This tool is effective in restoring low-resolution, old, blurry, jerky or underexposed footage,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Calibre 9.0.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 30 Jan 2026 20:36:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-calibre-1669.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-calibre-1669.html
</guid><description>
Calibre  is an eBook library management application that allows you to manage your eBook collection, convert eBooks between different formats, Sync with popular e-reading devices and read your e-books with included viewer. You can sort books by author, title, date and other details, download meta information and book covers, add personalized tags and comments, and view your images in the cover display.
Collection of essential tools for adding metadata editing books or managing your...
</description></item><item><title>Download FotoWorks XL 2026 v26.0.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 30 Jan 2026 20:36:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fotoworks-xl-667.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fotoworks-xl-667.html
</guid><description>
FotoWorks XL is a photo editing software and digital graphics very easy allows you to fix and enhance digital photos. The extended functionality to edit photos with this easy photo editing this is sorted according to menu structure very clear and to control better, you can always see the original image and edited version of the photo of yourself.
Editing software for Windows 10 or Windows7,8 provides the function to print and edit photos extensively for the album, photo, photo montage...
</description></item><item><title>Download ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro 15.26.0129</title><pubDate> Fri, 30 Jan 2026 20:36:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-videotube-downloader-pro-1276.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-videotube-downloader-pro-1276.html
</guid><description>
ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro is the professional version support download videos and playlists from YouTube, videos from Dailymotion, BBC iPlayer, ITV Player, ABC,  FOX,CBS.com Vimeo, Prosieben, Metacafe, Blip.tv CBC.ca many more video sites. After the video is downloaded, you can convert them to the formats compatible with iPad, iPhone, iPod, MPEG-4, H. 264, MP3, AC3.
ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro - Download videos on Youtube
This is one of the software download the most...
</description></item><item><title>Download FireAlpaca 2.15.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 30 Jan 2026 20:35:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-firealpaca-2882.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-firealpaca-2882.html
</guid><description>
FireAlpaca is software painting Digital free available in 10 languages and is compatible with both Mac and Windows. The tools and simple controls allow you to draw a easy illustration. Convenient tool will be adding this one to the other! Download FireAlpaca right now! FireAlpaca is the utility to create and edit image files, add image overlays, as well as providing many other advanced features, bring an effective tool to help you draw a picture or edit a photo from the most basic...
</description></item><item><title>Download MAME 0.285</title><pubDate> Fri, 30 Jan 2026 20:34:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mame-3320.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mame-3320.html
</guid><description>
MAME is an emulator of open source and free are designed to recreate the hardware of the game system arcade in software on the personal computer modern and other platforms. The goal is to preserve gaming history by preventing classic games from being lost or being forgotten.
MAME - emulator classic game
MAME (Multiple Arcade Machine Emulator) is a software that has the ability to simulate an arcade machine, allowing you to play the classic arcade game on his computer. This tool can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Macro Expert Enterprise 4.9.8.8</title><pubDate> Fri, 30 Jan 2026 20:34:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-macro-expert-enterprise-3558.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-macro-expert-enterprise-3558.html
</guid><description>
Macro Expert Enterprise is a powerful tool that will help you save time and money by empowering you to automate fully the work repetitive and regular. Macro Expert Enterprise can simplify a lot of work your computer, providing more than 260 action will meet most all your needs, automate your task. To keep they have the ability to access and organize high Macro Expert Enterprise split these actions into separate groups: Email, Excel document, database, Text, window, FTP, Internet, File,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cutting Optimization Pro 5.18.19.3</title><pubDate> Fri, 30 Jan 2026 20:33:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cutting-optimization-pro-6573.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cutting-optimization-pro-6573.html
</guid><description>
Cutting Optimization Pro is a cutting software used to obtain the optimal cut layout for one-dimensional (1D) and two-dimensional (2D) pieces. The software also allows you to define and process complex products, such as desks, tables, cabinets, cabinets, bookshelves... Cutting Optimization Pro can be used to cut rectangular panels made of glass, wood, metal, plastic or any other material used in industrial applications.
Features of Cutting Optimization Pro
	Optimize 1D and 2D in the...
</description></item><item><title>Download MassTube 2026 v21.3.2.184 Ultra</title><pubDate> Fri, 30 Jan 2026 20:32:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-masstube-plus-461.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-masstube-plus-461.html
</guid><description>
MassTube Plus is a small utility used to download the favorite videos of you on youtube on your computer. This is a software compact, has a simple design with few options to download videos fastest. The you complete peace of mind because the software is easy to use, built exclusively for a single goal: to retrieve the video file from YouTube, so it doesn't pack the other useful features such as search engine integrated and a download audio file.
MassTube can work with multiple output...
</description></item><item><title>Download EF Commander 26.02</title><pubDate> Fri, 30 Jan 2026 20:32:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ef-commander-92.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ef-commander-92.html
</guid><description>
EF Commander is an application specialized software can help you to manage your files effectively can help you full control over the files and folders, suitable for both beginners to experts with interface according to the card format Tab. The application supports ID3 tags, enhanced sound quality and use less resources with the format OGG/ Vorbis, FLAC, WMA and WAV and other formats can be heard on Winamp,...
EF Commander - a file manager effectively 
With EF Commander : When starting...
</description></item><item><title>Download Syncovery Premium 11.12.3.157</title><pubDate> Fri, 30 Jan 2026 20:24:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncovery-pro-enterprise-232.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncovery-pro-enterprise-232.html
</guid><description>
Syncovery Pro Enterprise is a great application used to back up data and to synchronize personal computers, servers, laptops, notepads and storage online. The software comes with support for FTP and secure FTP servers, SSH, WebDAV, Amazon S3, http, update the part file, ZIP compression, data encryption, and schedule automatic backups.
Syncovery Pro Enterprise have the ability to freely select files and folders across the whole folder hierarchy in tree view and supports email...
</description></item><item><title>Download Database Tour Pro 11.6.2.1332</title><pubDate> Fri, 30 Jan 2026 20:23:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-database-tour-pro-5321.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-database-tour-pro-5321.html
</guid><description>
Database Tour Pro application is a comprehensive software that allows you to organize all the database is connected his. It provides support for Borland Database Engine (BDE) and Microsoft ActiveX Data Objects (ADO), SQL scripts, reports, along with conversion and data export, among others.
It contains a browser object for the function, package, triggers, folders, users, roles, profiles, sequences, work, style, Java, exception, link, database, general properties, table, schema, and...
</description></item><item><title>Download 3D Youtube Downloader 1.26</title><pubDate> Fri, 30 Jan 2026 20:20:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-3d-youtube-downloader-1631.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-3d-youtube-downloader-1631.html
</guid><description>
3D Youtube Downloader is application support users to download the videos from Youtube website with great quality. The advantage of this software is the ability to download the videos in 3D, make the download process is fully automated and the download speed is extremely fast. In addition to Youtube, this tool also allows to download videos from many other sites, so users can own any favorite videos yet. 3D Youtube Downloader is a downloads simple but powerful from Youtube, Vimeo,...
</description></item><item><title>Download SeekFast 6.1 Build 1</title><pubDate> Fri, 30 Jan 2026 20:12:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-seekfast-7524.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-seekfast-7524.html
</guid><description>
SeekFast has the ability to quickly search for specific text in all documents on your computer. SeekFast then sorts the results in a way that makes it easy to find the text you're looking for, see its context, and open the file that contains it. All you have to do is select a folder to search for and enter search words or phrases - you'll get all the sentences they appear in within seconds. This is especially useful if you need to find something quickly.
SeekFast uses state-of-the-art...
</description></item><item><title>Download FFmpeg 8.0.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 30 Jan 2026 19:59:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ffmpeg-6232.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ffmpeg-6232.html
</guid><description>
FFmpeg is an open and open-source software project, consisting of a large set of libraries and programs for handling videos, sounds as well as files and multimedia streams. It is a free software consisting of a giant suite of libraries and programs for video processing, audio, multimedia files and streams. Its core is the FFmpeg program itself, which is designed to handle videos and audio based on the command line and is widely used for switching formats, basic editing (cutting and...
</description></item><item><title>Download yt-dlp 2026.01.29</title><pubDate> Fri, 30 Jan 2026 19:12:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-dlp-6802.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-dlp-6802.html
</guid><description>
yt-dlp is a youtube-dl branch based on youtube-dlc currently not working. The main focus of this project is the addition of new features and patches while still updating the original project.
</description></item><item><title>Download O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro 22.1.241 / Server</title><pubDate> Fri, 30 Jan 2026 19:10:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-diskimage-pro-218.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-diskimage-pro-218.html
</guid><description>
O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro is software backup data comprehensive and effective is provided to protect the data of the computer system, it creates images for individual drives or the entire system that still does not affect your system.
O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro allows the user to backup the entire computer or drive, the and files whenever you want even while the computer is being used. Or can use O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro to create a copy chinh sac of computer disk drives, can be used instead of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube Downloader 3.9.18 (2901)</title><pubDate> Fri, 30 Jan 2026 19:09:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube Downloader  is a dedicated software that helps users  downloading youtube videos  Favorites on PC for offline viewing. With MediaHuman YouTube  Downloader  you can download videos from youtube website to your computer with  fast speed , with special software development technology that automatically receives videos from Websites, in addition to the ability to download videos from software websites, can convert downloaded video formats to various formats for the purpose...
</description></item><item><title>Download TidyWindow 4.4.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 30 Jan 2026 19:09:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tidywindow-14454.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tidywindow-14454.html
</guid><description>
TidyWindow is a Windows desktop assistant that automates developer PC setup, cleanup, diagnostics, software package installation, registry tweaking, and driver updates—powered by a WPF interface and robust PowerShell 7 automation capabilities in the background.
Key Features
	Essentials Repair Center (docs/essentials.md): Queues selected automation tasks Filter for network, Defender, printing, and Windows Update issues. Each task supports preview run, sequential execution, restore...
</description></item><item><title>Download The Dude 7.21.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 30 Jan 2026 19:08:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-the-dude-3238.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-the-dude-3238.html
</guid><description>
The Dude is a new application by MikroTik which can dramatically improve the way you manage your network environment. It will automatically scan all devices in the subnet is specified, draw and layout a map of your networks, monitor services of your devices and alert you in case some service has problems.is a new application by MikroTik which can dramatically improve the way you manage your network environment. It will automatically scan all devices in the subnet is specified, draw and...
</description></item></channel></rss>