<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:53:14 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:53:14 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download IntraWEB Ultimate 16.1.10</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:52:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intraweb-ultimate-2007.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intraweb-ultimate-2007.html
</guid><description>
IntraWEB Ultimate is a tool to build the website. With this tool, the developer can create the page using the same method used to build the Windows program. Because the HTML page directly from the concept design to the user's computer does not download a bit more complicated and in fact is required from web server. So, the template IntraWeb on the server and download server and displays them to the user. Things technology direction of the IntraWEB Ultimate provides part flexibility and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Android Studio 2025.2.3.9</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:50:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-android-studio-3890.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-android-studio-3890.html
</guid><description>
Android Studio is an Android development environment, completely new, provides many improvements and new features compared to Eclipse ADT. This software solution will is IDE the official Android when is finishing. This tool provides many tools and features such as editing, layout, rich set of tools to capture usability, compatibility version, performance and other issues, create a lot APK, build system based on Gradle flexibility, extended support for Google Services, integrated support...
</description></item><item><title>Download Valentina Studio Pro 16.5.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:44:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-valentina-studio-pro-2122.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-valentina-studio-pro-2122.html
</guid><description>
Valentina Studio Pro is the best way to transform your data into meaningful information; create, manage, query and explore MySQL, Postgre MariaDB, MS SQL Server and SQLite database.
Valentina Studio Pro
Features of Valentina Studio Pro
SCHEMA EDITING &amp;amp; MAPPING
	Manage multiple databases in tabs and views that can be attached is
	Create / Drop / alter / Browse Tables, fields, index, trigger, constraints, links, views, stored procedures, properties, Sequences, Types, ...
	Edit the...
</description></item><item><title>Download QOwnNotes 26.1.7</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:44:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qownnotes-3178.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qownnotes-3178.html
</guid><description>
QOwnNotes is notes bookmark file simple text (GPL) open source application for GNU / Linux , Mac OS X and Windows of Patrizio Bekerle ( pbek on GitHub and IRC) (optional) activity along with the notes application of ownCloud or Nextcloud. QOwnNote store your notes as plain text files and can be synchronized with synchronization function file of ownCloud / Nextcloud. You can also use other apps like Syncthing or Dropbox . Just write out your thoughts as they appear, and edit them if...
</description></item><item><title>Download Brave Browser 1.86.139</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:43:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-brave-browser-2874.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-brave-browser-2874.html
</guid><description>
Brave Browser is a browser based on Chromium, the basic principle is that operation fast and privacy of users. The program can block pop-up windows and other ads, plus it blocked the mechanism for monitoring the online activities of your. Therefore, you can purchase and safely browse the website you are interested in without having to worry about the fact that your activity will be monitored and then you will be shown the necessary advertising or service provider of parties...
</description></item><item><title>Download ET Optimizer 6.08.10</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:42:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-et-optimizer-9574.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-et-optimizer-9574.html
</guid><description>
ET-Optimizer is a free, open source script to improve your computer's overall performance and optimize it for your workflow through optimized scripting. With this optimization, setup takes little effort. The script is developed from many sources found on the Internet, tested and updated for different versions of the system. The whole script is contained in 1 file, it uses: command prompt, powershell, power plan configuration, startup configuration, registry changes, network interface...
</description></item><item><title>Download FabFilter Total Bundle 2026.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:42:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fabfilter-total-bundle-896.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fabfilter-total-bundle-896.html
</guid><description>
FabFilter Total Bundle is a collection of all the plugis FabFilter. Package includes EQ, compressor, limiter, de-esser, gate/expander, multi-band distortion, stereo delay, filter and synthesizer plug-ins available today.
FabFilter Total Bundle - synthesizer Plugins FabFilter
The inner pack software FabFilter Total Bundle includes:
	FabFilter Pro-Q 2 - Allround EQ plug-in for mixing and mastering purposes, with up to 24 bands and a gorgeous interface for easy and precise...
</description></item><item><title>Download GForce impOSCar 3 1.0.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:41:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gforce-imposcar-3-12011.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gforce-imposcar-3-12011.html
</guid><description>
GForce impOSCar 3 is the design of the legendary British hardware synthesizer OSCar. Like the original, its hybrid construction combines the precision of a digital oscillator with the warmth of an analog filter, delivering a wide range of sonic possibilities. Create expansive, lush, dark or ambient pads, resonant bells and precise leads with this exceptional recreation. Refined filters, matched with the new wavetable editor, combine the finest digital clarity with unparalleled analog...
</description></item><item><title>Download Valentina Server 16.5.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:41:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-valentina-server-10771.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-valentina-server-10771.html
</guid><description>
Valentina Server is software that provides reports from all major databases or with its own advanced object-relational database system. It will combine an enterprise reporting server and two database servers into a single solution. You get all the technical features of Valentina Server in terms of usage, more connections and live technical support.
Features of Valentina Server
	Enterprise report server turns data into highly formatted reports in the form of multimedia web pages, text,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Elasticsearch Enterprise 9.2.4</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:41:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-elasticsearch-enterprise-12537.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-elasticsearch-enterprise-12537.html
</guid><description>
Elasticsearch Enterprise is a suite of products and services designed to enhance the search capabilities of applications and websites, primarily through the use of Elastic Enterprise Search and Elastic Cloud Enterprise (ECE). These tools provide advanced features to manage and optimize search functionality across different platforms.
Features
	Elastic Search AI Platform: Get relevant results at unprecedented speed with open and flexible enterprise solutions. Accelerate business...
</description></item><item><title>Download Solid Explorer File Manager 3.2.14 build 200356</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:38:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-solid-explorer-file-manager-8924.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-solid-explorer-file-manager-8924.html
</guid><description>
Solid Explorer is a file management application inspired by old file management applications. Solid Explorer is a popular file management app for Android devices that allows users to manage and organize their files and folders in an intuitive and user-friendly interface. It offers many features that make it stand out from other file management apps.
Solid Explorer allows you to navigate to files stored on your device and automatically organize them into collections. You can view,...
</description></item><item><title>Download PowerDirector - Video Editor 16.0.0 build 2601142</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:38:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-powerdirector-video-editor-8123.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-powerdirector-video-editor-8123.html
</guid><description>
PowerDirector APK - Video Editor (Unlocked Version) is video editing software developed by CyberLink. It is available for Windows and Android devices. If you are looking for the Android version of PowerDirector, you can download the APK (Android Package Kit) file from the Google Play Store or from taiwebs.com.
Features of PowerDirector APK - Unlocked Version:
	Easy-to-use interface: PowerDirector has a user-friendly interface that makes it easy to edit and create videos, even if...
</description></item><item><title>Download All PDF Editor &amp;amp; Reader | Xodo 10.11.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:38:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-xodo-pdf-reader-editor-8451.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-xodo-pdf-reader-editor-8451.html
</guid><description>
Xodo PDF Reader &amp;amp; Editor is a mobile application for reading and editing PDF documents on Android and iOS devices. The app allows users to view, annotate, and edit PDF files using a variety of tools, including highlighting, underlining, and adding notes. With Xodo, you can read, annotate, sign, and share PDFs and fill out PDF forms, all while syncing with Google Drive, Dropbox, and OneDrive.
Xodo PDF Reader &amp;amp; Editor Features
	PDF Viewer: Application that allows users to view...
</description></item><item><title>Download Save Location GPS 9.9</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:37:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-save-location-gps-12095.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-save-location-gps-12095.html
</guid><description>
Save your favorite places. Never forget where you parked your car. Share important locations with your friends or colleagues. Visiting a new friend for the first time? The Save Location app will quickly display and save location details with pinpoint accuracy so you can refer to it later for your next visit!
All location data can be saved within the app for reference from other devices, all with security to ensure only you and the people you want to see your location data with can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Duolingo: language lessons 6.62.5</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:37:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-duolingo-language-lessons-8265.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-duolingo-language-lessons-8265.html
</guid><description>
Duolingo is a popular language learning app that offers interactive lessons to help users learn new languages. This application offers many languages for you to choose from, including Spanish, French, German, Italian, Portuguese, Chinese, Japanese and many more.
This app offers an gamified learning experience with interactive lessons, exercises, and quizzes designed to help users learn new words, phrases, and grammar rules. This app is designed to be easy to use and suitable for people...
</description></item><item><title>Download Polarr: Photo Filters &amp;amp; Editor 6.11.8</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:37:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-polarr-photo-filters-editor-8389.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-polarr-photo-filters-editor-8389.html
</guid><description>
Polarr: Photo Filters &amp;amp; Editor is a mobile application for editing and enhancing photos on Android and iOS devices. It offers a wide range of editing tools, including basic adjustments like cropping, rotation, and brightness control, as well as advanced features like color grading, masking, and layer-based editing. . The app also includes many filters and presets that can be used to change the look of your photos.
Polar Features: Filters &amp;amp; Photo Editor
	Basic adjustments:...
</description></item><item><title>Download Folder Player Pro 5.37 build 364</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:36:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-folder-player-pro-8330.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-folder-player-pro-8330.html
</guid><description>
Folder Player Pro is a mobile music player application available for Android devices. It allows users to play and organize their music files by folders, instead of just by artist or album. This app is perfect for users who have a lot of music files on their device and want to listen to them in a more organized way.
Features of Folder Player Pro APK
	Ability to play music files by folder, making it easy to find and listen to specific songs or albums
	Supports many audio file formats,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Lark Player:Music Player &amp;amp; MP3 6.35.8</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:36:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-music-player-mp3lark-player-11711.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-music-player-mp3lark-player-11711.html
</guid><description>
Lark Player is a stylish and free offline music and video player for Android, it supports playing all major formats of offline music and videos. This free music player has powerful equalizer lyrics and best user interface. It also supports file management on the device such as deleting files and creating playlists. Currently, more than 100 million users worldwide use Lark Player to play music offline.
Other free features:
	Powerful equalizer gives you the best sound effect with sound...
</description></item><item><title>Download 1Weather: Forecast &amp;amp; Radar 12.0.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:36:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-1weather-forecast-radar-8846.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-1weather-forecast-radar-8846.html
</guid><description>
1Weather is the most popular weather application on Google Play. Whether you want to check temperatures, forecast precipitation, Doppler radar, or simply track the current phases of the sun and moon, 1Weather has you covered. Plus, it's got an outstanding design that makes getting your weather information easy and fun.
Track current conditions and forecasts for your location and up to 12 locations of your choice. Access charts, precipitation forecasts, maps, weather information and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Computer Science Calculations 4.2.8</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:35:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-computer-science-calculations-11750.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-computer-science-calculations-11750.html
</guid><description>
Computer Science Calculations is the best application in the IT field, it has many calculations that can help you in your work. It can't miss in your smartphone!
Features:
All available tools:
	Byte conversion - Conversion of December, bin, October, hexadecimal - Signed number representation: Signed magnitude, One's complement, Two's complement - Bitwise operations - Bit shifting and rotation - Password generation - Random number generation - Base 64 encoding/decoding - URL...
</description></item><item><title>Download Route4Me Route Planner 5.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:35:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-route4me-route-planner-13077.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-route4me-route-planner-13077.html
</guid><description>
It is the most downloaded multi-stop route planning software on the planet. Route4Me is used by Thousands of Businesses &amp;amp; Drivers - in Hundreds of different Industries, for Last Mile Delivery Planning &amp;amp; Services (grocery, package + other deliveries)
AND it has been used by many UPS, FedEx and professional delivery drivers as the ultimate route navigation app. This app is for professional drivers &amp;amp; couriers... not recreational road users.
It's a better route planner than...
</description></item><item><title>Download Chat Smith: AI Chatbot &amp;amp; Agent 8.260112.1 build 1276</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:35:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ai-chat-smith-smart-assistant-13276.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ai-chat-smith-smart-assistant-13276.html
</guid><description>
Ask AI Chat Smith Smart Assistant anything about the latest AI Models and get instant answers. Open &amp;amp; Chat with the most advanced AI! With advanced artificial intelligence, enjoy a personalized experience and chat with your AI Chatbot personal assistant. Chat Smith's intuitive and user-friendly interface makes it easy to interact and get informative responses to your questions.
AI Chatbot Chat Smith offers a variety of useful smart assistants to choose from: Business, Content,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Multi Timer StopWatch 2.13.34</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:34:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-multi-timer-stopwatch-8914.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-multi-timer-stopwatch-8914.html
</guid><description>
Multi Timer is a beautifully designed time management app. Multiple timers can be set, started and run independently at the same time. Stopwatch results can be stored. Use Multi Timer for cooking, sports, machine washing, studying, working, gaming - whatever you like.
Features of Multi Timer StopWatch
	Multiple timers at once: Store the timers you often use for cooking, sports, studying, working, gaming, whatever you want. Start them with just one tap, anytime you need.
	Timer in...
</description></item><item><title>Download SpeedChecker Speed Test 2.9.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:34:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-speedchecker-speed-test-8162.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-speedchecker-speed-test-8162.html
</guid><description>
SpeedChecker Speed ​​Test is a mobile application that allows users to test the speed of their internet connection. To use the app, users simply download and install the app on their Android device, open the app, and then follow the on-screen instructions to run a speed test. The application will measure the download and upload speed of the user's internet connection and display the results in a clear and easy-to-read format.
It can also provide additional information such as...
</description></item><item><title>Download Anti Spy Detector - Spyware 6.7.5 build 6752</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:34:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-anti-spy-scanner-spyware-8753.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-anti-spy-scanner-spyware-8753.html
</guid><description>
Anti-spy scanner &amp;amp; Spyware is an Android app that scans your device for spyware and other harmful applications that can compromise your privacy and security. This is a useful tool for users who want to ensure their devices are not infected with spyware or other malware that could collect sensitive information or cause other harm.
Anti Spy has been developed to scan Android devices to detect potential spies effectively. Thanks to artificial intelligence (AI), real-time signature...
</description></item></channel></rss>