<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 17:34:53 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 17:34:53 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download ImageMagick 7.1.2-5</title><pubDate> Tue, 07 Oct 2025 17:26:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-imagemagick-1319.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-imagemagick-1319.html
</guid><description>
ImageMagick is software image processing command line to create, edit, compose, or convert bitmap images. ImageMagick is completely free for users and you easily download it on taiwebs.com. Typical functions most of software is able to read and write images in many formats (over 100) including DPX, EXR, GIF, JPEG, JPEG-2000, PDF, PhotoCD, PNG, Postcript, SVG, and TIFF.
ImageMagick - image Processing
The Windows version of ImageMagick is installed. Just click on the appropriate version...
</description></item><item><title>Download NPS Image Editor 4.4.1.7573</title><pubDate> Tue, 07 Oct 2025 17:25:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nps-image-editor-12735.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nps-image-editor-12735.html
</guid><description>
NPS Image Editor is a unique, free image editor that is perfect for pixel art, drawing, and photo editing. It is lightweight, customizable, and intuitive, yet incredibly powerful. The goal of NPS Image Editor is to provide the world with an easy-to-use image editing application that also allows me (as a developer) to learn new skills and improve my programming knowledge.
In addition, NPS Image Editor also includes an advanced color picker that can run standalone (without opening the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Internet Download Manager (IDM) 6.42 Build 49</title><pubDate> Tue, 07 Oct 2025 17:18:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-inetnet-download-manager-161.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-inetnet-download-manager-161.html
</guid><description>
Internet Download Manager is the download acceleration software, the best download support now, it can help you speed up the download up to five times, continue and schedule downloads. The latest version of IDM adds the compatibility of Windows 10 and Windows 11, it has supported all current popular browsers such as Internet Explorer, Mozilla Firefox, Opera, Google Chrome, ..
Download IDM with the latest version on taiwebs.com making it easy to download and manage your downloaded files...
</description></item><item><title>Download IDM Retail 6.42 Build 49</title><pubDate> Tue, 07 Oct 2025 17:17:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-internet-download-manager-retail-3609.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-internet-download-manager-retail-3609.html
</guid><description>
IDM - Internet Download Manager Retail is a reliable utility and high efficiency will help you to increase your download speed and manage download at better. The program allows you to easily schedule, pause and resume downloads with a single click. Moreover, the application provides error resilience robust and can restart the download at the interrupted or broken. You can restore the download is interrupted due to network problems, lost connections, unexpected power outages, computer...
</description></item><item><title>Download Soft Organizer Pro 10.32</title><pubDate> Tue, 07 Oct 2025 17:17:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-soft-organizer-498.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-soft-organizer-498.html
</guid><description>
Soft Organizer is versatile software just install the software to help uninstall software quickly and safely to release the hard drive or restore when necessary.  That side, Soft Organizer also keep track of the changes made to the system during installation of new utilities or help test the new version of the software on the computer to update timely, classification, and management of programs for users to follow easily.
Soft Organizer has a modern interface with simple manipulation to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Office Timeline Plus 11.28.00.00 Expert / Pro / Pro+ Edition</title><pubDate> Tue, 07 Oct 2025 17:16:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-timeline-2106.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-timeline-2106.html
</guid><description>
Office Timeline is an add-on very useful and powerful software for Microsoft PowerPoint. With add-ons, you can create PowerPoint documents look more beautiful. With add-ons, you can add the time Line on the project by yourself. Application time for the composition and different segments of the document, your PowerPoint will not only increase the beauty for your work, but also for customers and your manager. The people who created this product is also believe that add-ons this is the only...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cockos REAPER 7.48</title><pubDate> Tue, 07 Oct 2025 17:16:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cockos-reaper-889.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cockos-reaper-889.html
</guid><description>
Cockos REAPER is a powerful software for for windows, chp lets you record, arrange, edit, and display the audio waveform multi-track. Cockos REAPER offers an extensive feature set includes many effects and a sample project. REAPER supports ASIO, Kernel Streaming, WaveOut, and DirectSound for playback and recording. It reads the files in WAV, OGG and MP3 files and records WAV files. You can arrange any number of items in any number of tracks and use plug-in sound processing (DirectX and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Files Inspector Pro 4.41</title><pubDate> Tue, 07 Oct 2025 17:15:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-files-inspector-pro-2289.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-files-inspector-pro-2289.html
</guid><description>
Files Inspector is a software that allows you to analyze the data on the hard drive and delete the file obsolete, since it frees up space and improve performance of the system. Despite the fact that the hard drives are becoming cheaper and more voluminous, you have a place to store a large number of files are not really necessary in most cases, due to the repetition and simple data is outdated. If not maintained properly, you can fill the space trash and clean up will eventually become a...
</description></item><item><title>Download PingPlotter Professional 5.25.20.9089</title><pubDate> Tue, 07 Oct 2025 17:15:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pingplotter-professional-4090.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pingplotter-professional-4090.html
</guid><description>
PingPlotter Professional is monitoring software network graphics, drawing graphs latency and data packet loss for maximum hundreds of targets at the same time. It includes everything in PingPlotter Standard, plus tools to monitor multi-targets, communicating with other systems, and collect data remotely. PingPlotter Professional is accessed through interface like web browser. PingPlotter Pro check out hundreds of targets at the same time. Summary chart available to the organization goals...
</description></item><item><title>Download Reg Organizer 9.87</title><pubDate> Tue, 07 Oct 2025 17:14:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reg-organizer-1595.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reg-organizer-1595.html
</guid><description>
Reg Organizer is a software to scan and clean your registry windows register errors and help optimize performance computer system. Reg Organizer is a software subscription, professional, and professional, and any way that the Windows registry are necessary and therefore, the overall performance of Windows improves, there is this software.
Reg Organizer - registry Cleaning and pc optimization
The main features of Reg Organizer
	Cleaning the registry of the lock is not valid and not...
</description></item><item><title>Download ExpanDrive 2025.09.30</title><pubDate> Tue, 07 Oct 2025 17:09:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-expandrive-609.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-expandrive-609.html
</guid><description>
ExpanDrive is software sync cloud storage strong support BackBlaze B2, Google Team Drive, SMB / CIFS and new interface and easy user search file version, share links and much more.  ExpanDrive mapped network drives for macOS and Micosoft Windows connect with all the provide major cloud storage such as Dropbox, Google Drive, Google Team Drive, Amazon Drive, Box, OneDrive, OneDrive for Business, Sharepoint, Openstack Swift , BackBlaze B2, Amazon S3 or SFTP servers, FTP or WebDAV on your own...
</description></item><item><title>Download MusConv 4.10.424 Lifetime</title><pubDate> Tue, 07 Oct 2025 17:08:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html
</guid><description>
MusConv transfers playlists, albums, followed artists and liked songs across a variety of services – Spotify, Apple Music, Amazon Music, YouTube, YouTube Music, iTunes, Deezer, Tidal, SoundCloud, Pandora and more 125 music services!
Features of MusConv Ultimate
	Transfer playlists, albums, followed artists and liked tracks between over 125 music servicesManage playlists (Delete, Merge, Split, Copy...)
	More than 125 music services supported
	Access DAILY updated music charts on...
</description></item><item><title>Download HttpMaster Pro 6.2.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 07 Oct 2025 17:08:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-httpmaster-pro-1925.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-httpmaster-pro-1925.html
</guid><description>
A useful application for web developers who need to automate the test the web application by requesting multiple resources from a specified site web-based application. The professional version httpMaster in order to meet the requirements of many people when related to the test application. When working with HttpMaster Pro, most of the time you will manage the attributes and properties of the project HttpMaster of the items required in project. Project properties provides the global options...
</description></item><item><title>Download Telegram for Desktop 6.1.4</title><pubDate> Tue, 07 Oct 2025 17:08:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-telegram-3376.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-telegram-3376.html
</guid><description>
Telegram is an instant messaging service and voice over IP services on the cloud platform. Client application Telegram is available for Android, iOS, Windows Phone, Windows NT, macOS, and Linux. Users can send messages and exchange photos, videos, stickers, audio and files of any kind.
Telegram - Messaging and free phone calls
Telegram seamless sync across all your devices and can be used on desktop, tablet and phone. You can send unlimited amount of messages, photos, videos and files...
</description></item><item><title>Download VIDBOX VHS to DVD 11.2.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 07 Oct 2025 17:07:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vidbox-vhs-to-dvd-6374.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vidbox-vhs-to-dvd-6374.html
</guid><description>
VIDBOX VHS to DVD is a software that helps users easily switch VHS to DVD, which will help you save your precious memories on the DVD. With advanced mode including the ability to edit video and upload social media. This flexible VIDBOX VHS to DVD convertier even generates an image projector and audio file to record all of your special moments.
Features of VIDBOX VHS to DVD
	Includes the VIDBOX USB video camera, USB cable and RCA cables.
	Take VHS tapes, Beta, 8mm or old cameras and...
</description></item><item><title>Download MasterCook 24.0.2.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 07 Oct 2025 17:07:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mastercook-6541.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mastercook-6541.html
</guid><description>
Arrange your recipes, make cookbooks and manage the diet and nutrition with the MasterCook 2020, which is ranked 9.8 out of 10 by TopTenReviews. The flexible tools for the family chef and professional chef to organize all of your kitchen activities and your cooking.
Features of MasterCook
	The flexible tools for family chef and professional chefs arrange all your kitchen and cooking activities.
	Set up a daily or weekly food budget for each ration, formula or menu.
	Change the rations...
</description></item><item><title>Download Exif Pilot 6.28</title><pubDate> Tue, 07 Oct 2025 17:06:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-exif-pilot-3900.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-exif-pilot-3900.html
</guid><description>
Exif Pilot is a tool that small and simple will help you to easily edit the EXIF data contained in digital photos of you. Using this tool, you will be able to view and manage multiple types of data, such as IPTC, EXIF, GPS, XMP, etc. the program also allows you to create data EXIF, IPTC and GPS. The new card also can be added to your photo. Exif Pilot allows you to import and export data, IPTC and EXIF from / to files, MS Excel, CSV and XML. The program allows you to add, delete and edit...
</description></item><item><title>Download Patch My PC 5.3.1.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 07 Oct 2025 17:06:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-patch-my-pc-3748.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-patch-my-pc-3748.html
</guid><description>
Patch My PC is a comprehensive application and reliable will provide the simple solution for managing patch party Tuesday. The category Enterprise SCUP will provide an incentive simple and unique about the updates and the application updates of the Tuesday easy and updated. The update application can be easily installed on your computer in a few minutes, through the function software updates are integrated into The configuration manager center system MS. No additional agent or server...
</description></item><item><title>Download ZWCAD MFG 2026 v26.10 Build 2025.09.05</title><pubDate> Tue, 07 Oct 2025 17:04:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zwcad-mfg-9533.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zwcad-mfg-9533.html
</guid><description>
ZWCAD MFG is a computer-aided design (CAD) software solution designed specifically for the manufacturing industry. It is developed by ZWSOFT, a company known for its CAD and CAM software solutions. ZWCAD MFG is designed to assist manufacturers in creating and optimizing designs for different manufacturing processes.
Original design features such as creating and editing two-dimensional, three-dimensional geometry, drawing and file sharing, ZWCAD also features creativity, collaboration,...
</description></item><item><title>Download MyLanViewer Enterprise 6.6.0 / Business</title><pubDate> Tue, 07 Oct 2025 17:04:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mylanviewer-enterprise-1274.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mylanviewer-enterprise-1274.html
</guid><description>
MyLanViewer is a program for scanning IP address, Netbios and LAN / Network powerful for Windows tool whois and traceroute, remote shutdown and process management Wake On LAN (WOL), scan and monitor wireless networks. This app will help you find all IP addresses, MAC addresses and shared folders of computers on the network wired or wireless (Wi-Fi).
MyLanViewer Enterprise - Scan IP address LAN/Network
The program scans network and displays the computer network in your window, friends...
</description></item><item><title>Download CCleaner Browser 140.0.32231.210</title><pubDate> Tue, 07 Oct 2025 17:02:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ccleaner-browser-1851.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ccleaner-browser-1851.html
</guid><description>
Piriform, the company produces CCleaner - software cleanup system popular on Windows, has launched Chromium browser new of his own name CCleaner Browser. New browser comes with every feature have been Google's Chrome, and is integrated ad blockers. CCleaner Browser interface is quite similar to Google Chrome, the difference is the appearance of the icon CCleaner familiar on the bar enter the address of the browser, that's all.
CCleaner Browser - web browser ad blocker
In CCleaner...
</description></item><item><title>Download Atlantis Word Processor 5.0.0.4</title><pubDate> Tue, 07 Oct 2025 17:02:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-atlantis-word-processor-585.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-atlantis-word-processor-585.html
</guid><description>
Atlantis Word Processor is a word processor app with features format, standard text, autocorrect, and spell check.  Atlantis is a word processor in accordance with most of the tasks handled daily text. The interface is very easy to use and offers the toolbars, hotkeys and sound effects thanh can customize (can turn off). It includes a clip library for quick access to the text or images used regular preview, font format and many other features aimed at improving the process of your...
</description></item><item><title>Download RizomUV Real &amp;amp; Virtual Space 2025.0.104</title><pubDate> Tue, 07 Oct 2025 17:01:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rizomuv-real-virtual-space-1537.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rizomuv-real-virtual-space-1537.html
</guid><description>
RizomUV Real &amp;amp; Virtual Space known as Unold3D ago, is the perfect software to design a package or build texture laser. RizomUV Real Space includes all the features of RizomUV Virtual Space, but use ultraviolet rays to build and control the UV maps to the flat version over of your model will take all the size of it. This program allows you to get the mesh is not perpendicular three-dimensional, not even lasts for a few seconds. Mesh felt is produced with real size and get delivered in...
</description></item><item><title>Download SeaTools for Windows 5.2.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 07 Oct 2025 17:01:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-seatools-for-windows-7464.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-seatools-for-windows-7464.html
</guid><description>
SeaTools for Windows is an easy-to-use, comprehensive diagnostic tool that helps you quickly determine the health of a drive in an external hard drive, desktop or laptop computer. hand. It includes several tests that will check the physical media on a Seagate, Maxtor or Samsung drive and any non-Seagate drive. SeaTools for Windows will run on both internal and external hard drives.
Before you ship a drive, it's in your best interest to determine if a replacement drive is really needed....
</description></item><item><title>Download Minimal Firewall 2.4.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 07 Oct 2025 17:00:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minimal-firewall-13877.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minimal-firewall-13877.html
</guid><description>
Minimal Firewall works in conjunction with Windows Firewall to block all unknown connections by default, prompting you to create application-based rules to mitigate malware, telemetry, and data leaks. Completely eliminate applications that call home without your knowledge. Minimal Firewall provides a more secure and integrated approach by interacting directly with the native Windows Firewall, eliminating the need for risky system modifications.
Core Features
	Lockdown Mode: The core...
</description></item></channel></rss>