<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 10:36:58 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 10:36:58 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Visual C++ Redistributable Runtimes All-in-One Dec 2025</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 23:46:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-visual-c-redistributable-runtimes-all-in-one-7466.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-visual-c-redistributable-runtimes-all-in-one-7466.html
</guid><description>
This repository contains the latest versions (April 2022) of all VCRedist Visual Studio C++ runtimes, which can be installed with one click by running the bundled batch file installer.
To install, run install_all.bat with administrator privileges (right click, "Run as administrator").
The download includes the VC_Redist runtime packages for Visual C++ 2005, 2008, 2010, 2012, 2013, 2015, 2017, 2019 and 2021. Both 32-bit and 64-bit are supported. Included files are English language...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ashampoo Backup Pro 27.5.24</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 23:45:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-backup-pro-716.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-backup-pro-716.html
</guid><description>
Ashampoo Backup Pro is software to backup and restore data professional to save the file, the important data for your computer. Ashampoo Backup Pro will remove the fear of viruses, ransomware, or hardware errors. Ashampoo® Backup Pro offers you various options to backup individual files or entire disk partitions on any storage media or on the cloud. User friendly, intuitive, fast. Even in case an error occurs the entire system, application integrated emergency can bring your...
</description></item><item><title>Download Serato DJ Pro 4.0.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 23:44:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-serato-dj-pro-169.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-serato-dj-pro-169.html
</guid><description>
Serato DJ Pro is software mix DJ music, professional support, sound effects, and combined to create music, Great DJ. Serato DJ Pro supports the sound effects such as Delay, Reverb, Flanger, Echo, PingPong Delay, Phaser, Distortion, High and Low Pass Filter, as well as combinations of them. Supports MIDI in full, be made in the program, providing the ability to adapt to the controller and program for every need. It allows you to use at the same time from two to four floors. Program Serato...
</description></item><item><title>Download Aiseesoft FoneLab for Android 6.1.8</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 23:44:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aiseesoft-fonelab-for-android-3929.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aiseesoft-fonelab-for-android-3929.html
</guid><description>
Aiseesoft FoneLab for Android is one of the software Android data recovery best. Aiseesoft FoneLab for Android is recovery software data great for Android users that helps you recover text messages, deleted messages, attached, lost, contacts lost, call history and Photos, Photo, Videos, Music, documents on Android phone, tablet and your SD card. Regardless of whether you lost files due to mistakenly deletion, root, upgrade, format the memory card, attack of virus or due to you crashing,...
</description></item><item><title>Download FTP Rush 3.6.5</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 23:44:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ftp-rush-6410.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ftp-rush-6410.html
</guid><description>
FTP Rush is a free transfer software for Windows, Mac, Linux, Android and iOS. And it ' s not just the FTP/SFTP client app but also the cloud hosting app (supporting Google Drive, DropBox, OneDrive and Amazon S3). With the Explorer-like interface on the card, you can create multiple tabs on the card for different connections and easily download or load files up through the Pull &amp;amp; Drop. It uses a local computer as a bridge to perform the transfer function between the servers of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Argente System Repair 1.0.4.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 23:43:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-argente-system-repair-13813.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-argente-system-repair-13813.html
</guid><description>
Argente System Repair is a lightweight utility designed to diagnose and fix common Windows system problems. It scans your system to identify errors in operating system components, file systems, installation files, and other system components, and then applies targeted fixes to resolve these problems. The tool provides different scan modes, including simple scan, recommended scan, and custom scan, allowing users to customize the repair process according to their needs.
System Repair...
</description></item><item><title>Download Yamicsoft Windows 11/10 Manager 2.2.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 23:43:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yamicsoft-windows-11-manager-6779.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yamicsoft-windows-11-manager-6779.html
</guid><description>
Windows 11 Manager is an all-in-one utility for Microsoft Windows 11 specially, it includes over forty different utilities to optimize, tweak, clean up, speed up and repair your Windows 11, helps make your system perform faster, eliminate system fault, increase stability and security, personalize your copy of Windows 11, and meet all of your expectations.
Features of Windows 11 Manager:
Information:
	Creates the system restore point manually;
	Gets detailed information about your...
</description></item><item><title>Download GiliSoft File Lock Pro 15.6</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 23:42:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-file-lock-pro-858.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-file-lock-pro-858.html
</guid><description>
GiliSoft File Lock Pro is program encryption software file power can lock and hide fast and secure files, folders and drives, and it can use AES 256 bit encryption (encryption standard is the government of The United States apply) protect your files located on HDD or any portable media drive such as USB.
GiliSoft File Lock Pro - file encryption
Features of GiliSoft File Lock Pro
	GiliSoft File Lock Pro can hide the folders and drives of your private
	The file / folder / drive locking...
</description></item><item><title>Download Internet Download Manager Portable 6.42 Build 56</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 23:42:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-internet-download-manager-portable-11965.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-internet-download-manager-portable-11965.html
</guid><description>
Internet Download Manager (IDM) is a popular software tool that helps users download files from the internet at faster speeds. It is designed to increase download speeds up to five times, resume and schedule downloads, and support multiple download queues. IDM also has many features that make it easy to use and customize to fit your needs.
IDM has a simple and friendly interface that makes it easy to use. The software integrates seamlessly with popular web browsers such as Google Chrome,...
</description></item><item><title>Download MedCalc 23.4.3</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 23:41:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-medcalc-1536.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-medcalc-1536.html
</guid><description>
MedCalc is a statistical software for biomedical research can analyze many performance curve system with a set of rich functionality, chart types and advanced module. MedCalc was designed to meet the needs and requirements of the study nature and aims to analyze the statistical calculations of the project. This software provides the tools and means essential to analyze the characteristic curve of the system (ROC), drawing data and perform the statistical calculations.
MedCalc -...
</description></item><item><title>Download Advanced System Repair Pro 2.0.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 23:41:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-system-repair-pro-80.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-system-repair-pro-80.html
</guid><description>
Advanced System Repair Pro gives you all the tools you need in a program to clean, repair, protect, optimize and increase your PC!
Advanced System Repair Pro speed 300% faster help your computer run faster by increasing the launch speed, optimizing registry, as well as get rid of unwanted apps and files, useless other causing your computer to run slower.
Advanced System Repair Pro - optimized system
Features, characteristics, Advanced System Repair Pro
Get a computer cleaner in a few...
</description></item><item><title>Download 3DCoat 2025.15</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 23:40:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-3d-coat-1269.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-3d-coat-1269.html
</guid><description>
3D Coat is a computer program that trade for modeling objects of different organic and 3D models low-poly. The app provides a variety of tools allow users to create sculptures, adding topology, create UV maps, texture surface interactions of the model, showing the static and animated round of the pattern.
3D Coat - 3D modeling
The content in the software 3D Coat:
Texture simple and PBR:
	Support drawing drawings top en model, draw the pixel and Ptex
	Rendered physics-based (PBR)...
</description></item><item><title>Download Argente Malware Cleaner 3.0.4.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 23:40:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-argente-malware-cleaner-13494.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-argente-malware-cleaner-13494.html
</guid><description>
Argente Malware Cleaner is a lightweight utility designed to detect and remove a wide range of malware, including spyware, adware, Trojans and other threats that can compromise your privacy and data. It works as a complementary tool alongside your main antivirus software, helping to detect malware that may slip through the cracks.
Key features of Argente Malware Cleaner include:
	Easy-to-use, clean, and user-friendly interface that suits both casual and advanced users.
	Deep scanning...
</description></item><item><title>Download Brave Browser 1.85.111</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 23:39:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-brave-browser-2874.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-brave-browser-2874.html
</guid><description>
Brave Browser is a browser based on Chromium, the basic principle is that operation fast and privacy of users. The program can block pop-up windows and other ads, plus it blocked the mechanism for monitoring the online activities of your. Therefore, you can purchase and safely browse the website you are interested in without having to worry about the fact that your activity will be monitored and then you will be shown the necessary advertising or service provider of parties...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wise Registry Cleaner Pro 11.3.0.732 Beta</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 23:39:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wise-registry-cleaner-pro-468.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wise-registry-cleaner-pro-468.html
</guid><description>
Wise Registry Cleaner Pro software is dọp registry cleaner, defragment the hard drive to help optimize system and speed up computer. The advantage is, before cleanup registry software will allow users to create a backup safety. Therefore the cleanup, speed up pc back up safe and does not encounter the bug, what I wanted.
Wise Registry Cleaner is used as a tool to manage the program and lets you search for and delete obsolete files, folders, register, temporary hot key combination and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cash Register Pro 4.0.7</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 23:38:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cash-register-pro-3853.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cash-register-pro-3853.html
</guid><description>
Cash Register Pro a software cash register full of features and creative for a Windows computer, it will help you to better handle all the activities of the computer money. The application comes with the user interface logical and user friendly allows you to work quickly and do not commit the common error. The program can be used on a number of computers and offers a wide range of authorization secure and reliable. Cash Register Pro will help you track products and goods remain...
</description></item><item><title>Download WaveMetrics Igor Pro 10.0.12.29764</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 23:38:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wavemetrics-igor-pro-9545.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wavemetrics-igor-pro-9545.html
</guid><description>
WaveMetrics Igor Pro is a powerful scientific and engineering graph and data analysis software. It is commonly used in various fields such as physics, chemistry, engineering and biology to analyze and display experimental data. Igor Pro provides a comprehensive environment for data manipulation, mathematical analysis and presentation.
Igor Pro combines powerful tools with an easy-to-use point-and-click interface for casual users and a programming environment for professional users. Igor...
</description></item><item><title>Download Seamless3d 3.038.10</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 23:37:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-seamless3d-10257.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-seamless3d-10257.html
</guid><description>
Seamless3d is one of the easiest 3D modeling and animation programs that offers artistic freedom. It is designed to be a powerful and practical way to create 3D models that will appeal to anyone who wants to create quality 3D animated content for the web. A versatile NURBS-based 3D Modeler/Animator designed for ease of use without compromising artistic freedom, allowing you to create unique models.
Features of Seamless3d
	WYSIWYG
	Undo/Redo
	Export clean, efficient files
	Dedicated...
</description></item><item><title>Download Opera GX (Gaming Browser) 124.0.5705.89</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 23:36:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-gx-3170.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-gx-3170.html
</guid><description>
Opera GX is a special version of the Opera browser is built to complement gamers avid. Browser this game comes with the unique features to help users make maximum use of both the game and their browser. Opera GX is built specifically to support the game. This browser includes the unique features to help users have the best experience when gaming and surfing the web.
Opera GX - special browser for gamers
GX Control allows you to set a limit on the level of use RAM, CPU and network where...
</description></item><item><title>Download MobiOffice: Word, Sheets, PDF 16.0.58406</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 22:43:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-officesuite-word-sheets-pdf-8508.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-officesuite-word-sheets-pdf-8508.html
</guid><description>
OfficeSuite allows you to easily view, edit, and create Word, Excel, and PowerPoint documents and perform advanced PDF operations. Our integrated file manager, Chat app with document exchange capabilities, and tons of other handy tools make this the most feature-rich mobile office solution available on Android. Pre-installed by leading manufacturers including Sony, ZTE, Amazon, Sharp, Acer, CAT, Alcatel, Kyocera, Toshiba, etc.
Features of OfficeSuite for Android
	View, create, and...
</description></item><item><title>Download PhotoDirector: AI Photo Editor 20.8.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 22:43:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-photodirector-photo-editor-8144.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-photodirector-photo-editor-8144.html
</guid><description>
PhotoDirector is a photo editing app for Android devices that allows you to edit and enhance your photos with a variety of tools and effects. With PhotoDirector, you can adjust your photo's color and lighting, remove blemishes and other imperfections, and apply filters to give your photos a unique look. You can also use PhotoDirector to create photo collages and slideshows, add text and stickers to photos, and share your edited photos on social networks or through other sharing...
</description></item><item><title>Download Revo Uninstaller for Android 3.4.480G</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 22:42:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-revo-uninstaller-for-android-10156.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-revo-uninstaller-for-android-10156.html
</guid><description>
Revo uninstaller for Android helps you uninstall Android apps as well as organize and clean your device. Remove all leftover and hidden files for a clean and bloatware-free device. Easy-to-use tool to uninstall Android apps, their leftovers and hidden files. We specialize in uninstalling apps and optimizing smartphone storage space.
Every application leaves residual data after uninstallation. Revo Uninstall Mobile detects these leftovers and deletes them after showing you the files, so...
</description></item><item><title>Download Pacer Pedometer &amp;amp; Step Tracker vp12.12.1 build 2025120100</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 22:42:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pacer-pedometer-step-tracker-11194.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pacer-pedometer-step-tracker-11194.html
</guid><description>
Pacer App: “Pedometer, Pedometer, and Weight Loss Tracker App” that syncs steps and calories with MyFitnessPal and Fitbit! Track your steps, walking and weight loss with this free health counter. Lose weight and track distance walked and calories burned using 24/7 step counting from our pedometer, pedometer and health tracker app.
Main features:
	Best pedometer for any phone
	Accurate activity and step tracking
	Lose weight, track BMI and count calories burned
	Daily exercise...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mock Locations (fake GPS path) 1.35.9</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 22:42:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-mock-locations-fake-gps-path-10782.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-mock-locations-fake-gps-path-10782.html
</guid><description>
Mock Locations allows you to fake information about your phone's location according to GPS and network operator. You just need to navigate the route on the map and press the "Go!" there are apps all over your phone that provide fake location information. This will help with application development or if you don't want anyone to know where you really are.
Simulated Location Features
	Simulated GPS location and according to service provider.
	Ability to create routes on the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Equalizer &amp;amp; Bass Booster - XEQ 31.21.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 04 Dec 2025 22:41:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-equalizer-bass-booster-xeq-10095.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-equalizer-bass-booster-xeq-10095.html
</guid><description>
This XEQ app is a powerful yet easy-to-use Music Equalizer with Bass Boost, Volume Boost, Auto Volume Boost and 3D Virtualizer effects, which can improve the sound quality of your device. your Android device.
This is the only equalizer fx app you will ever need for your smartphone. With this feature, you can not only equalize the bass boost, but also increase the normal sound volume of your Android phone, add virtual 3D effects, save custom presets, automatically recall presets of audio...
</description></item></channel></rss>