<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 19:59:44 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 19:59:44 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download KeyNote NF 2.1.1.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:49:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-keynote-nf-11953.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-keynote-nf-11953.html
</guid><description>
KeyNote NF is a tabbed notebook with a RichText editor, multi-level note taking, and powerful encryption. KeyNote NF was written to overcome significant limitations in other popular information managers, both freeware and shareware. KeyNote is the only information manager that offers a combination of simple notes and tree notes, a rich text editor, the ability to freely combine multiple notes of different types in one file unique and securely encrypted.
Main features:
Unicode...
</description></item><item><title>Download Abelssoft KeyDepot 2026 v12.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:48:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-abelssoft-keydepot-14052.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-abelssoft-keydepot-14052.html
</guid><description>
Abelssoft KeyDepot is a password manager software designed to securely store and manage passwords, logins, and other sensitive data. The software uses advanced encryption technology, specifically AES-256 encryption, to protect user data from unauthorized access. KeyDepot allows users to create a master password to secure access to their password vault, and this master password will never be stored on Abelssoft servers for added security.
Features of Abelssoft KeyDepot
	Secure password...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tenorshare 4DDiG File Repair 4.2.2.8</title><pubDate> Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:48:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tenorshare-4ddig-file-repair-5630.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tenorshare-4ddig-file-repair-5630.html
</guid><description>
Tenorshare 4DDiG File Repair is AI-powered software to repair damaged or damaged videos, photos, files and audios, improve their quality and add color to black media white. 4DDiG photo editing solves all photo problems like blurry photos, overexposed photos, etc. Powered by AI, it can dramatically improve image resolution and colorize black and white photos in seconds, not hours.
Features of Tenorshare 4DDiG File Repair
	Easily repair any blurry, overexposed and damaged videos, photos...
</description></item><item><title>Download AI Image Background Remover Pro 1.1.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:47:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ai-image-background-remover-pro-13963.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ai-image-background-remover-pro-13963.html
</guid><description>
Easily remove image backgrounds with pixel-perfect precision with AI Image Background Remover Pro. Designed for e-commerce sellers, graphic designers, photographers, and social media managers, this powerful desktop tool gives you complete control over your creative process. Unlike online tools, AI Image Background Remover Pro works 100% offline on your computer, keeping your images and projects completely private and secure. No uploads, no data collection, and no registration...
</description></item><item><title>Download GPU Caps Viewer 1.64.3.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:46:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gpu-caps-viewer-2926.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gpu-caps-viewer-2926.html
</guid><description>
GPU Caps Viewer is a software OpenCL and OpenGL is designed for Microsoft Windows, which allows you to view important information about the GPU, such as type, driver version, video memory, etc. The application can also display OpenCL, extensions, API support and the ability to OpenGL (texture size, version, number of texture units, etc.).
GPU Caps Viewer can also be used to view system configuration, provides information such as the amount of system memory, CPU type and speed, operating...
</description></item><item><title>Download Download Master 7.2.2.1739</title><pubDate> Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:45:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-download-master-2005.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-download-master-2005.html
</guid><description>
Download Master is a software to improve the speed of file download from the Internet. Download Master replace the standard module of the load in the popular browsers such as Google Chrome, Firefox, Safari, Yandex.Browser, Opera, Internet Explorer etc. The software support download the file from the current position after the break of the network connection. Download Master lets you download videos or music from various services and have the priority function of the load. The software...
</description></item><item><title>Download Intel Graphics Driver for Windows 10 / 11 32.0.101.8136</title><pubDate> Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:45:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intel-graphics-driver-for-windows-10-5954.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intel-graphics-driver-for-windows-10-5954.html
</guid><description>
Intel Graphics Driver for Windows 10 supports Intel ' s latest 8th-generation Core processor, introducing the Intel ® UHD graphics, with the ability to immerve in the top 4K UHD entertainment from your laptop for a maximum of 10 hours. Along with some security fixes, this driver also optimised the system's inactivity to reduce power consumption.
Look at the complete new interface of gameplay.intel.com, where you will find the proposed game settings for many of your favorite PC games....
</description></item><item><title>Download Prevent Restore Pro 2025 v114</title><pubDate> Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:44:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-prevent-restore-pro-1473.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-prevent-restore-pro-1473.html
</guid><description>
Prevent Restore Pro is software prevent restore files deleted in any drive: external hard drives and hard drives mounted in hard drive, SSD, Flash drives, except CD-ROM and CD-RW. The software uses many security algorithms can be used to get data.Our program includes some of the most reliable and accepted as standard.
Prevent Restore Pro - Prevent restore files deleted
The features of Prevent Restore Pro
Mode to clean up quickly
	In this mode, the program will not overwrite the free...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wireshark 4.6.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:44:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wireshark-56.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wireshark-56.html
</guid><description>
Wireshark (aka Ethereal) is a network protocol analyzer allows you to capture and examine data from a live network or from a snapshot file on disk.You can browse the captured data in an interactive way and view summary information and details for each package. Wireshark has several powerful features, including a language filter rich display and ability to view flow created back of the TCP.
Wireshark - network protocol analyzer
The program can read the capture file from tcpdump...
</description></item><item><title>Download Helium Music Manager Premium 17.4.535</title><pubDate> Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:39:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-helium-music-manager-premium-164.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-helium-music-manager-premium-164.html
</guid><description>
Helium Music Manager is a music manager that can rip, tag, play, browse, search, rename, burn and synchronize your music with the mobile. You can control your music collection with Helium Music Manager. Stop using time looking for the file on your computer or looking through CDS, vinyl records and tapes - instead, simply enjoy and explore your music! Helium Music Manager can replace the ripper, the player, tag editor and related software to audio your other.
Helium Music Manager...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ocenaudio 3.16.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:39:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ocenaudio-837.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ocenaudio-837.html
</guid><description>
Ocenaudio: software for windows, this is the sound editing easy, fast and powerful. ocenaudio is a program for audio editing multi-platform, easy to use, fast and functional. This is the ideal software for those who need to edit and analyze audio files.
Ocenaudio - editor powerful audio for windows
This software is based on Ocen Framework , a powerful library developed to simplify and standardize the development of application analysis and sound processing on many platforms.
Features...
</description></item><item><title>Download Google Drive (Backup and Sync) 115.0.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:39:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-drive-6751.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-drive-6751.html
</guid><description>
Using Google Drive is a great way to store your files safely in secure data centers, where your files will not be lost. Even if your computer, phone or tablet is broken, the files you store in the Google Drive are safe. Download photos, videos, documents, and other files that are important to you up to Google Drive. Continue with the memory up to 15GB. Free. Google Drive helps you access your file faster by recognizing the objects in your image and text in the scanned documents.
Easy to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Coder Technologies Coder 2.26.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:38:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coder-oss-enterprise-8726.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coder-oss-enterprise-8726.html
</guid><description>
Coder OSS Enterprise is a development platform that provides a complete cloud-based solution for software development, testing and deployment. It is designed to simplify the software development process by providing developers with a collaborative and streamlined environment.
Coder offloads development from local workstations to your on-premises infrastructure and public cloud. Boost developer productivity with powerful server resources and instant integration. Keep the code and data...
</description></item><item><title>Download OpenCloseDriveEject 3.48</title><pubDate> Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:38:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-openclosedriveeject-4783.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-openclosedriveeject-4783.html
</guid><description>
OpenCloseDriveEject is a small program and effective when it comes to Open, Close, DVD-, CD, Blue-Ray Drive Eject USB and SSD, SD,... unlike other programs that only function part in routine tasks this, you will find everything under one roof, removed the drive safely and open the DVD drive, Blue-Ray will be a regular work and easy as Microsoft has provided for all Windows operating system. Here, you can still open the disk in the drive to set the drive name directly, this can be very...
</description></item><item><title>Download GoldSqall 2.2.222</title><pubDate> Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:37:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-benthic-software-goldsqall-6446.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-benthic-software-goldsqall-6446.html
</guid><description>
GoldSqall  is an SQL query, editing, and export tool. GoldSqall can natively connect with Oracle, PostgreSQL, MySQL, Firebird and SQL Server. GoldSqall also allows connection to any database using OLEDB or ODBC driver. GoldSqall has an advanced syntax highlighting SQL Editor and formatter, a lightning-fast data grid with sort, filter, format data and transform views.
Features of GoldSqall
	Native driver support for Oracle, MySQL, PostgreSQL, Firebird and SQLServer.
	Supports OLEDB and...
</description></item><item><title>Download CameraFTP Virtual Security System 5.1.175.358</title><pubDate> Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:37:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cameraftp-virtual-security-system-12406.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cameraftp-virtual-security-system-12406.html
</guid><description>
CameraFTP VSS is a powerful video surveillance program that can turn your PC/Laptop into a CCTV/DVR security system. It can display live scenes on the screen and record footage to the cloud. You can watch or play back footage anywhere, anytime. VSS also provides powerful screen recording features to monitor computer usage, record online classes/meetings, TV shows and games.
Features of CameraFTP VSS
	Common surveillance camera system features: Can view up to 25 cameras on one...
</description></item><item><title>Download FFmpeg Batch AV Converter 3.2.6 + Portable</title><pubDate> Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:37:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ffmpeg-batch-av-converter-10540.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ffmpeg-batch-av-converter-10540.html
</guid><description>
FFmpeg Batch AV Converter is an ffmepg gui, a user interface for Windows ffmpeg users and for Linux via Wine, allowing to use the full potential of the ffmpeg command line only with a few mouse clicks in a convenient GUI. Among other things, you can drag and drop, view progress information, change encoding priority, pause and resume, and set auto shutdown. It's good for seasoned ffmpeg users as well as beginners.
It offers unlimited batch encoding of one or more files for almost any...
</description></item><item><title>Download ReIcon 2.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:36:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reicon-7317.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reicon-7317.html
</guid><description>
ReIcon saves and restores your desktop icon layout by allowing you to save the desktop layout and restore it with the click of a button. If you frequently change your screen resolution to play games or use applications that require a specific resolution, you are probably familiar with the fact that your desktop icons are often cluttered. after you switch back to normal resolution. ReIcon solves this problem by allowing you to save your desktop layout and restore it with the click of a...
</description></item><item><title>Download EverNote 10.157.3.8633</title><pubDate> Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:35:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-evernote-3261.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-evernote-3261.html
</guid><description>
EverNote is the all in one tool allows you to track notes, todo items, memos, outlines, excerpts, websites, ideas and other things and automatically synchronize them between multiple computers and mobile devices (iPhone, Android, etc.). You can choose to sort their notes into categories, password protect them, export them to XML and more. EverNote supports a number of pattern notes allow you to add to-do list, spreadsheet like Excel to calculate costs (automatic sum), notes, phone, contact...
</description></item><item><title>Download Disable Windows Defender 1.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 09 Oct 2025 13:43:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-disable-windows-defender-14217.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-disable-windows-defender-14217.html
</guid><description>
Usually, we need to disable Windows Defender to prevent it from deleting known files due to false positives. Sometimes, it can slow down your computer or interrupt your work. In such cases, you can easily disable it and enable it again later with just one click. We can also disable this feature (Real-time Monitoring) using the Defender Settings panel, but it will be automatically enabled after a period of time. This tool ensures that this feature is 100% disabled. It also disables all...
</description></item><item><title>Download Comet Browser 140.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 09 Oct 2025 13:34:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-comet-browser-14216.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-comet-browser-14216.html
</guid><description>
Comet Browser, developed by Perplexity, is an AI-powered web browser designed to enhance user productivity by automating tasks and providing intelligent assistance. Comet Browser represents a significant step forward in web browsing technology by integrating AI to streamline tasks and enhance productivity. Its ability to automate complex processes and provide contextual assistance makes it a unique tool for users looking to optimize their online experience.
Key Features of Comet...
</description></item><item><title>Download Q-Dir 12.37</title><pubDate> Wed, 08 Oct 2025 23:50:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-q-dir-348.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-q-dir-348.html
</guid><description>
Q-Dir is software to manage the entire file and folder on the computer, allowing to see file in same time 4 different positions (viewport quadro) while still maintaining all the standard features of the Explorer.
It also provides a variety of management features, additional files included the filter file color-coding, layouts and columns can be customized, quick access to file and folder favorites and more.
Other features of Q-Dir , including directory listings (.txt, .doc .html .csv),...
</description></item><item><title>Download PhotoPad Image Editor Pro 14.44</title><pubDate> Wed, 08 Oct 2025 23:41:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photopad-image-editor-572.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photopad-image-editor-572.html
</guid><description>
PhotoPad Image Editor is a software to help edit photos and supports lots of features like edit, cut, rotate, resize and flip digital photos. With PhotoPad Image Editor, you can freely perform the basic editing for their images and also can add some neat effect. It has the option to create a photo collage and mosaic images from your photos, and you can also add text and captions. If you prefer, you can complete your masterpiece by adding the frame or contour is simple.
The main features...
</description></item><item><title>Download Windows 11 Enterprise 25H2 v26200.6725 NoTPM Multilingual Preactivated</title><pubDate> Wed, 08 Oct 2025 23:41:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-11-pro-enterprise-untouched-6672.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-11-pro-enterprise-untouched-6672.html
</guid><description>
Windows 11 is the latest version of the Windows operating system released, with new interfaces and other new features such as the new Microsoft Store, the new source of personalized data supported by AI and the best browser performance in the segment from Microsoft Edge, the chat from Microsoft Teams is integrated in the taskbar and more!
Attention when installing Windows 11 Pro Enterprise: The settings environment and Windows installation is to upgrade from the Windows 10 20H2 ISO,...
</description></item><item><title>Download SysNucleus WebHarvy 7.8.0.244</title><pubDate> Wed, 08 Oct 2025 23:40:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sysnucleus-webharvy-881.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sysnucleus-webharvy-881.html
</guid><description>
SysNucleus WebHarvy is software to extract data website such as Text, image, URL &amp;amp; email from the website and save the content... WebHarvy is a tool which scans website intuitive. Absolutely no need to write any scripts or code to scrape data. You will use the browser built-in of WebHarvy to navigate the website.
WebHarvy automatically identifies patterns of data occurring in web pages. So if you need a list of items (name, address, email, price etc) from a website, you do not need to...
</description></item></channel></rss>