<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 15:37:58 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 15:37:58 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Reverso Translate and Learn 14.7.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 02 Oct 2025 17:30:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-reverso-translate-and-learn-8356.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-reverso-translate-and-learn-8356.html
</guid><description>
Reverso is a comprehensive tool that helps you get high-quality translations and continuously improve your language skills. The best part about the Reverso app? It is available for free. Teachers or translators, students or business professionals, beginners or advanced learners use Reverso to enrich their vocabulary and read, write and speak more accurately and confidently.
Download the Reverso app and you'll have millions of words and expressions at your fingertips, with their...
</description></item><item><title>Download Firewall Security AI - No Root 2.5.3 build 2531</title><pubDate> Thu, 02 Oct 2025 17:30:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-firewall-no-root-8224.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-firewall-no-root-8224.html
</guid><description>
No Root Firewall is an Android application that allows users to block Internet access to specific applications on their device without requiring root access. Blocks internet attacks and protects you from unwanted access to the internet. Determine which applications can and cannot access the internet. With powerful firewall technology, secure filter lists and artificial intelligence, you protect your privacy comprehensively and also stay informed about what is being shared with the...
</description></item><item><title>Download OsmAnd+ — Maps &amp;amp; GPS Offline 5.2.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 02 Oct 2025 17:29:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-osmand-maps-gps-offline-8245.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-osmand-maps-gps-offline-8245.html
</guid><description>
OsmAnd+ (OSM Automatic Navigation Directions) is a mapping and navigation application with access to free, global, and high-quality OpenStreetMap (OSM) data. Enjoy voice and optical navigation, view POIs (points of interest), create and manage GPX routes, use contour visualization and elevation information, choose between driving modes, cyclists, pedestrians, OSM editing, etc.
This is a mobile navigation app that uses OpenStreetMap (OSM) data to provide users with detailed maps and...
</description></item><item><title>Download BitTorrent®- Torrent Downloads 8.2.53</title><pubDate> Thu, 02 Oct 2025 17:29:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-bittorrent-pro-torrent-app-9913.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-bittorrent-pro-torrent-app-9913.html
</guid><description>
Find torrents and download them directly to your phone or tablet, WITHOUT ADS, with the official BitTorrent® Pro app for Android -- now with battery saver and auto-shutdown features.
Features of BitTorrent Pro - Torrent App
	Neat, light and beautiful design
	Wi-Fi only mode to save mobile data
	No speed limit and no size limit
	Easy access to your media with integrated music and video libraries
	Select files to download in torrents to minimize your storage space
	Better music and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Smart Tools - Multipurpose Kit 1.2.24</title><pubDate> Thu, 02 Oct 2025 17:29:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-smart-tools-multipurpose-kit-9884.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-smart-tools-multipurpose-kit-9884.html
</guid><description>
Smart Tools is the most useful and handy app that provides more than 20 tools like Flash, Compass, Ruler, Calculator, Speedometer, Sound Meter, Stopwatch , etc. The smart tool uses the device's built-in sensors and provides the most accurate measurements. It is useful for a wide range of users from students to Engineering professionals
Smart Tool is an all-in-one App. You don't need to download separate standalone utility apps for daily use. Using this application will help you save a...
</description></item><item><title>Download Calculator Plus with History 8.1.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 02 Oct 2025 17:28:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-calculator-plus-with-history-10531.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-calculator-plus-with-history-10531.html
</guid><description>
Plus Calculator with History is the perfect calculator for Android. It remembers everything you calculate and allows you to review it at any time, which is perfect for me when shopping, doing homework, balancing my checkbook, or even helping with taxes. And if you need to quit your job and go do something else, I'll have it all ready for you when you get back. You'll never need to re-enter the same calculation twice.
Features of Calculator Plus with History
	Show your calculations in...
</description></item><item><title>Download NokoPrint - Mobile Printing 5.24.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 02 Oct 2025 17:28:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-nokoprint-mobile-printing-8528.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-nokoprint-mobile-printing-8528.html
</guid><description>
Print photos and share them with family and friends. Print documents, PDFs, invoices, receipts, boarding passes, and more. at home, at work or on the go! You can print images, photos, web pages, PDF and Microsoft Office documents without downloading any additional apps or printing tools anytime, anywhere on almost any WiFi, Bluetooth or USB printer .
Features of NokoPrint for Android
	Print directly from your Android phone or tablet to almost any inkjet, laser or thermal...
</description></item><item><title>Download Maple Calculator: Math Solver 4.2.9</title><pubDate> Thu, 02 Oct 2025 17:28:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-maple-calculator-math-solver-13489.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-maple-calculator-math-solver-13489.html
</guid><description>
Powered by Maple, the world's most powerful math engine, this all-in-one calculator solves math problems, creates 2-D and 3-D visualizations, and provides step-by-step solutions to a wide variety of math homework problems encountered in high school and college.
This app is a graphing calculator, scientific calculator, algebra calculator, integral calculator, and calculator integration all rolled into one! Take a picture of your problem with your phone's camera or type it in through the...
</description></item><item><title>Download BetterSleep: Sleep tracker 25.17</title><pubDate> Thu, 02 Oct 2025 17:27:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-bettersleep-sleep-tracker-8274.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-bettersleep-sleep-tracker-8274.html
</guid><description>
BetterSleep is a sleep tracking app that helps users track and improve their sleeping habits. The app uses the phone's sensors to track movement and sounds during sleep, then provides users with detailed sleep reports and analysis. It also includes features such as a sleep log, smart alarm, and white noise generation to help users fall asleep and wake up more refreshed. Additionally, BetterSleep allows users to set sleep goals, track their progress, and receive personalized...
</description></item><item><title>Download Device Info: System &amp;amp; CPU Info 3.4.0.4</title><pubDate> Thu, 02 Oct 2025 17:27:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-device-info-system-cpu-info-8723.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-device-info-system-cpu-info-8723.html
</guid><description>
Device Information: System &amp;amp; CPU Information is a mobile application that provides users with detailed information about the hardware and software specifications of their device. This app is designed to help users better understand their device's capabilities and performance as well as diagnose any potential issues or problems.
With Device Info: System and CPU Info, users can view information about the processor, memory, storage, battery, sensors, and more. of equipment. This app...
</description></item><item><title>Download Digital Compass 17.5</title><pubDate> Thu, 02 Oct 2025 17:27:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-digital-compass-13590.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-digital-compass-13590.html
</guid><description>
This app is a smart compass with high accuracy and a great tool for outdoor activities. This compass app allows you to easily determine the direction you are facing. This app is built using the device's gyroscope, accelerometer, magnetometer, gravity sensor to determine the direction. Make sure your device has an accelerometer and magnetometer sensor or it will not work.
Features
	Show current location (longitude, latitude, address)
	Show altitude
	Show magnetic field strength
	Show...
</description></item><item><title>Download Computer Science Calculations 4.2.6</title><pubDate> Thu, 02 Oct 2025 17:26:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-computer-science-calculations-11750.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-computer-science-calculations-11750.html
</guid><description>
Computer Science Calculations is the best application in the IT field, it has many calculations that can help you in your work. It can't miss in your smartphone!
Features:
All available tools:
	Byte conversion - Conversion of December, bin, October, hexadecimal - Signed number representation: Signed magnitude, One's complement, Two's complement - Bitwise operations - Bit shifting and rotation - Password generation - Random number generation - Base 64 encoding/decoding - URL...
</description></item><item><title>Download OTT Navigator IPTV 1.7.3.3</title><pubDate> Thu, 02 Oct 2025 17:26:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ott-navigator-iptv-11547.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ott-navigator-iptv-11547.html
</guid><description>
Watch your provider's IPTV on any device (phone, tablet, TV, TV-box). It serves as a platform to watchIPTV unlimited channels. Developed by SIA Scillarium Studio, it works well with your chosen provider's playlists on any available device such as smartphone, tablet, TV or TV-box.
Main features:
Live streaming
	watch live TV
	automatically group favorite channels and categories
	start playing last channel at launch
	timeshift support for providers with repositories
	picture-in-picture...
</description></item><item><title>Download Map My Run GPS Running Tracker 25.8.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 02 Oct 2025 17:26:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-map-my-run-by-under-armour-8145.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-map-my-run-by-under-armour-8145.html
</guid><description>
Map My Run by Under Armor is a mobile app that allows users to track their running, walking, and other outdoor activities using GPS. The app is available to download from the Google Play Store and Apple App Store. It was developed by Under Armour, a company specializing in sports apparel and equipment. In addition to tracking workouts, the app also provides users with tools to analyze performance and set goals.
Features of Map My Run by Under Armor APK
	GPS tracking: The app uses GPS...
</description></item><item><title>Download Auto Text: Schedule Messages 5.8.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 02 Oct 2025 17:25:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-auto-text-auto-send-message-8447.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-auto-text-auto-send-message-8447.html
</guid><description>
Auto Text: Auto send WA &amp;amp; SMS is a feature or application that allows users to automatically send pre-written text messages at a specific time or in response to a request. specific activation. This feature can be useful in many situations, such as sending reminders, sending messages to loved ones at a specific time, or sending messages in response to certain events, such as calls to or location-based triggers.
Auto Text features: Auto send WA &amp;amp; SMS
	Automatically send happy...
</description></item><item><title>Download IgeBlock - Tube ad blocker 2.0.6</title><pubDate> Thu, 02 Oct 2025 17:25:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-igeblock-tube-ad-blocker-11113.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-igeblock-tube-ad-blocker-11113.html
</guid><description>
IgeBlock is an app that allows you to watch videos without ads, watch videos with sound, and watch videos in pop-up player while using other apps.
IgeBlock Features
Block ads
	Automatically skip annoying video ads.
	Automatically skip ads even in sound and pop-up player mode.
Pop-up player (PIP)
	You can play videos in floating mode without additional permissions.
Can be added
	Full screen touch lock function
	looped video
	Bookmark function without logging in
	Timer to turn...
</description></item><item><title>Download Windy.app - Enhanced forecast 84.2.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 02 Oct 2025 17:25:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-windyapp-windy-weather-map-10522.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-windyapp-windy-weather-map-10522.html
</guid><description>
WINDY - wind, wave and weather forecast app for surfers, kitesurfers, windsurfers and sailors.
Features
	Wind reports, forecasts and statistics: wind compass, wind map, wind speed meter, wind gusts and wind direction. It is very useful for extreme wind sports.
	Weather history (archived) 2012-2016: view wind data, temperature (day and night) and atmospheric pressure. The weather archive will help you choose the best month to go to that location.
	Local forecast from NOAA: temperature...
</description></item><item><title>Download Battery One: Charging &amp;amp; Health 1.9.4.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 02 Oct 2025 17:24:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-batteryone-battery-10988.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-batteryone-battery-10988.html
</guid><description>
BatteryOne collects, processes and displays various battery status data. For example, charging or discharging speed, voltage, temperature, actual capacity, average consumption and much more. It's no secret that a phone's battery has a limited resource. It depends on many factors, ranging from temperature to charging frequency. By analyzing data from BatteryOne, you can track the impact of these factors on your battery.
Features of BatteryOne
	Average battery charge/discharge...
</description></item><item><title>Download Lighting Calculations 6.1.8</title><pubDate> Thu, 02 Oct 2025 17:23:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-lighting-calculations-8927.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-lighting-calculations-8927.html
</guid><description>
Lighting calculation is the best application in the field of lighting, it has many calculations that can help you in your work. Lighting calculations are used to determine the amount of light needed in a given space or area to achieve the desired lighting level. These calculations take into account a number of factors, including the size and shape of the space, the type and placement of lighting fixtures, and the brightness of the light source.
Calculate total luminous flux, Indoor...
</description></item><item><title>Download ASICS Runkeeper - Run Tracker 16.14</title><pubDate> Thu, 02 Oct 2025 17:23:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-asics-runkeeper-run-tracker-8334.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-asics-runkeeper-run-tracker-8334.html
</guid><description>
Join a community that helps people escape difficulties and stick with running forever! Track your workouts, set goals, sweat, and see your progress. Whether you're trying to track a 5K goal or train for a marathon, use the GPS app trusted by 50 million users and counting.
ASICS Runkeeper - Run Tracker is a mobile application that allows users to track running and fitness activities on their Android devices. The app uses GPS to track the user's distance, pace, and running time as well as...
</description></item><item><title>Download Moon+ Reader Pro 10.2 build 1002000</title><pubDate> Thu, 02 Oct 2025 17:22:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-moon-reader-pro-8577.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-moon-reader-pro-8577.html
</guid><description>
Moon+ Reader Pro is an all-in-one ebook document manager and better designed book reader with powerful and fully functional controls, supporting EPUB, PDF, DJVU, AZW3, MOBI, FB2, PRC, CHM, CBZ, CBR, UMD, DOCX, ODT, RTF, TXT, HTML, MD(MarkDown), WEBP, RAR, ZIP or OPDS formats.
This is a versatile e-book reading application that gives users a rich reading experience, while helping them easily access and manage their e-book library. Whether you're looking to read your favorite novels,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Weather &amp;amp; Radar USA - Pro 2025.20</title><pubDate> Thu, 02 Oct 2025 17:22:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-weather-radar-usa-pro-8391.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-weather-radar-usa-pro-8391.html
</guid><description>
Weather &amp;amp; Radar USA is a mobile application that provides users with real-time weather information and forecasts for locations in the United States. The app includes many features such as current weather conditions, hourly and daily forecasts, radar and satellite images, and severe weather alerts. It also includes many customizable settings, such as the ability to set up multiple locations and receive notifications about specific weather conditions.
Features of Weather &amp;amp; Radar...
</description></item><item><title>Download Rain Alarm 6.0.6</title><pubDate> Thu, 02 Oct 2025 17:22:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-rain-alarm-8639.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-rain-alarm-8639.html
</guid><description>
This weather app alerts you when rain is approaching. Alerts are a reliable short-term forecast based on near real-time data. This app is more accurate and reliable than a traditional forecast. It is useful for all outdoor activities - including cycling, motorcycling, hiking, gardening, BBQs, picnics, dog walking and DIY.
Features of Rain Alarm for Android
	Alerts for all types of precipitation, whether rain, snow or hail
	Alerts as a notification with vibration and/or sound
	Simple...
</description></item><item><title>Download MacroDroid - Device Automation 5.57.5</title><pubDate> Thu, 02 Oct 2025 17:21:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-macrodroid-device-automation-9863.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-macrodroid-device-automation-9863.html
</guid><description>
MacroDroid is the easiest way to automate everyday tasks on your Android smartphone or tablet. Through its smart user interface, MacroDroid provides a simple solution to perform automated tasks on your device in just a few taps. Developed by ArloSoft, MacroDroid simplifies repetitive tasks by automating various actions and processes on your Android device. It offers a user-friendly interface and a variety of triggers, actions, and constraints to create personalized...
</description></item><item><title>Download TextArt - Add Text To Photo 2.6.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 02 Oct 2025 17:21:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-textart-add-text-to-photo-9346.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-textart-add-text-to-photo-9346.html
</guid><description>
Text on Photo is a free application that helps users easily add text to photos. You just need to enter the content you want to write and insert it into the image. You can browse through many different colors and fonts for images. Therefore, Text to photo helps you have sparkling photos without wasting much time.
Features of TextArt for Android
	Easy-to-use professionally designed interface for adding text to photos
	Write on photos with many text effects, fonts and sample...
</description></item></channel></rss>