<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 13:51:20 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 13:51:20 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Kotato All Video Downloader Pro 10.0.8</title><pubDate> Mon, 22 Dec 2025 16:50:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kotato-all-video-downloader-pro-5228.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kotato-all-video-downloader-pro-5228.html
</guid><description>
Kotato All Video Downloader Pro is a Windows application professional to download and convert your favorite videos from the video sharing website. It speeds up your downloads up to 5 times! Kotato All Video Downloader Pro can download videos from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion and hundreds of video sharing sites, other. After downloading, you will be able to play them smoother on your PC or your mobile device, even when you don't have Internet access.
The main features of Kotato All...
</description></item><item><title>Download ProShot 8.32.4 build 540</title><pubDate> Mon, 22 Dec 2025 16:16:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-proshot-8195.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-proshot-8195.html
</guid><description>
ProShot is a camera app for Android devices that offers advanced manual controls for photography enthusiasts. It allows users to manually adjust settings such as shutter speed, ISO, white balance, and focus. It also offers a level of integration, a powerful time-lapse mode, and many other features for advanced photography. It's designed for advanced users who want more control over their photos than the default camera app offers.
Camera features of ProShot
	Auto, Program, Manual and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Multi language Translator Text 97.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 22 Dec 2025 16:16:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-multi-language-translator-text-11918.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-multi-language-translator-text-11918.html
</guid><description>
In today's globalized world, it is normal to communicate with people who speak different languages. Whether you are traveling abroad, conducting business with international customers, or simply trying to connect with people from different cultures, the ability to quickly and accurately translate text is essential. necessity. This is where a multilingual text translation app can become a valuable tool.
Multi language Translator Text is a mobile application that allows users to translate...
</description></item><item><title>Download Photo Studio PRO 2.8.8.4702</title><pubDate> Mon, 22 Dec 2025 16:16:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-photo-studio-pro-8247.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-photo-studio-pro-8247.html
</guid><description>
Photo Studio APK is a powerful multifunctional photo editing application for photographers of all levels. It contains a huge set of editing tools for basic and advanced editing of your photos. Turn each of your photos into a finished work of art using a variety of effects, filters, text editing and color enhancement tools, and many other available features.
Features of Photo Studio Pro APK
	More than 200 unique filters, amazing special effects, large collection of picture-in-picture...
</description></item><item><title>Download Chat Smith: AI Chatbot &amp;amp; Agent 8.251215.2 build 1209</title><pubDate> Mon, 22 Dec 2025 16:15:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ai-chat-smith-smart-assistant-13276.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ai-chat-smith-smart-assistant-13276.html
</guid><description>
Ask AI Chat Smith Smart Assistant anything about the latest AI Models and get instant answers. Open &amp;amp; Chat with the most advanced AI! With advanced artificial intelligence, enjoy a personalized experience and chat with your AI Chatbot personal assistant. Chat Smith's intuitive and user-friendly interface makes it easy to interact and get informative responses to your questions.
AI Chatbot Chat Smith offers a variety of useful smart assistants to choose from: Business, Content,...
</description></item><item><title>Download AI Video Editor - VideoShow AI 11.0.2.4</title><pubDate> Mon, 22 Dec 2025 16:15:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-video-editor-maker-videoshow-8149.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-video-editor-maker-videoshow-8149.html
</guid><description>
Video Editor &amp;amp; Maker VideoShow is a video editing and movie making app that allows you to create and edit videos on your mobile device. With this movie maker, creating memes, creating videos or slideshows with photos, images, music, stickers and sound effects is easy and fun. Providing the latest Halloween materials! Young filmmakers can even beautify videos with text, FX, effects, GIFs, trendy filters, transitions or live dubbing in a creative and personalized way.
All-in-one...
</description></item><item><title>Download Annotium - Photo Annotation 3.13.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 22 Dec 2025 16:10:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-annotium-photo-annotation-11211.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-annotium-photo-annotation-11211.html
</guid><description>
Users can draw lines/curves with many types of arrows and formats, besides rectangles, ellipses, rounded rectangles, triangles, quadrilaterals, polygons, many types of text like plain text, caption text box (comics), cursor text, spotlight, magnifier, text highlight, free drawing, icon... User can point and illustrate directly directly to the point of attention, helping work faster and more effectively.
Main features:
	Many built-in tools such as lines, curves, rectangles, ovals,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Add Text: Text on Photo Editor 12.8.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 22 Dec 2025 16:10:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-add-text-text-on-photo-editor-10483.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-add-text-text-on-photo-editor-10483.html
</guid><description>
Add Text app is an all-in-one tool for creating text. You can add text to photos, gradients, solid colors, or transparent backgrounds.
Highlights
	Besides text, add other overlays: photos, shapes, stickers, and saved text styles
	Design parts of text separately: supported in Format, Color, Stroke, Markup tools
	3D Text Tools: 3D Rotation, 3D Depth, Perspective
	In addition to 800+ fonts, add an unlimited number of custom fonts (including emoji fonts)
	Change text size, line wrapping,...
</description></item><item><title>Download YoWindow Weather - Unlimited 2.54.11</title><pubDate> Mon, 22 Dec 2025 16:09:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-yowindow-weather-unlimited-8421.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-yowindow-weather-unlimited-8421.html
</guid><description>
YoWindow is a unique new weather app. The magic of YoWindow is a living landscape that reflects your real-life weather. For example, if it rains - it will rain in YoWindow. Sunset and sunrise in YoWindow take place at the same time as in real life. But the cool thing is you can roll time forward. Just swipe the screen and you'll see how the weather changes throughout the day.
YoWindow Weather Features - Unlimited
	All the weather at your fingertips. You see the current weather,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Lucky Patcher 11.9.8</title><pubDate> Mon, 22 Dec 2025 16:09:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-lucky-patcher-11914.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-lucky-patcher-11914.html
</guid><description>
Lucky Patcher is a free Android app that can modify many apps and games, Block ads, remove unwanted system apps, backup apps before and after modification, Move apps apps to SD card, remove license verification from paid apps and games, etc.
Lucky Patcher features and details:
	Remove or block ads on Android apps and games. You can easily block ads with Lucky Patcher.
	Block in-app purchase verification with the app. You can use premium apps and games for free by removing in-app...
</description></item><item><title>Download WillyWeather 4.1.7</title><pubDate> Mon, 22 Dec 2025 16:08:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-willyweather-10929.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-willyweather-10929.html
</guid><description>
WillyWeather is a feature-packed weather app that includes radar and NOAA satellites, detailed forecasts for wind, rain, tides, ocean waves and UV, as well as moon phases as well like sunrise and sunset times. In addition to our regular weather service, we process and refine coordinate-specific forecast data for more than 175,000 locations across the United States, including all towns, cities, beaches, rivers, parks, lakes and islands.
Weather data
	Weather - Six-day NOAA weather...
</description></item><item><title>Download Today Weather: Radar &amp;amp; Widgets 2.4.1-5</title><pubDate> Mon, 22 Dec 2025 16:08:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-today-weather-alerts-widgets-8915.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-today-weather-alerts-widgets-8915.html
</guid><description>
Weather Today is a beautiful and easy-to-use weather app that provides the world's most accurate local weather forecasts.
Features of Weather Today for Android
	Displays clear, easy-to-understand weather forecasts.
	Enjoy every moment you open the app with thousands of beautiful photos corresponding to the weather and day.
	Prepare for any situation with 24/7 weather forecasts and chance of rain.
	Protect your health with air quality, UV index and pollen count.
	Capture beautiful...
</description></item><item><title>Download WPSApp Pro 1.7.04</title><pubDate> Mon, 22 Dec 2025 16:07:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wpsapp-pro-8802.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wpsapp-pro-8802.html
</guid><description>
WPSApp Pro is an ad-free version of WPSApp that tests your network security using the WPS protocol. This protocol allows you to connect to a WiFi network using an 8-digit pin number that is usually predefined in the router, the problem is that the pin codes of many routers from different companies are known or know how to calculate.
This application uses these pins to try connections and check if the network is vulnerable. It implements some known algorithms to generate pins and some...
</description></item><item><title>Download Image Search - ImageSearchMan 3.52</title><pubDate> Mon, 22 Dec 2025 16:07:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-image-search-imagesearchman-9208.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-image-search-imagesearchman-9208.html
</guid><description>
ImageSearchMan is an Android application that allows users to search for images on the web using keywords or by uploading photos from their device's gallery. ImageSearchMan allows users to search for images using keywords, providing access to a huge library of images on the web.
The app includes a reverse image search feature that allows users to upload photos from their device's library to find similar images or identify the source of the image.
ImageSearchMan Features
	Image...
</description></item><item><title>Download CodeMatics Universal TV Remote Control 2.9.3</title><pubDate> Mon, 22 Dec 2025 16:07:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-codematics-universal-tv-remote-control-11491.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-codematics-universal-tv-remote-control-11491.html
</guid><description>
For Smart TV/Devices, the only setting required is to connect your phone as well as your Smart TV/Device to the same Wifi network. For IR TVs, your phone must have a built-in Infrared (IR) feature for the app to work as a remote control. The IR feature is required to send signals from the phone to the TV like a regular TV remote.
You can now Cast media files stored on your mobile phone to your Smart TV screen.
Smart TV function
	Voice search
	Power control.
	Mute / Volume...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sectograph. Day &amp;amp; Time planner 5.41</title><pubDate> Mon, 22 Dec 2025 16:06:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sectograph-day-time-planner-8322.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sectograph-day-time-planner-8322.html
</guid><description>
Sectograph is a day and time planning app available for Android devices as an APK file. It is a calendar and scheduling app that allows users to plan and organize their day, view upcoming events and appointments, and set reminders. The app also includes many customization options, such as the ability to change the color scheme and background image. Additionally, it has a built-in time tracking feature, allowing users to track time spent on various activities.
Sectograph features. Day...
</description></item><item><title>Download Circuit Route Planner 3.60.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 22 Dec 2025 16:06:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-circuit-route-planner-11536.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-circuit-route-planner-11536.html
</guid><description>
Easy-to-use multi-stop route planning and delivery app downloaded by over 10 million drivers! Deliver more packages and complete your routes faster. Save time, money and gas with Circuit Route Planner. Adding a stop to a route takes just a few seconds. One click optimizes all your deliveries and automatically maps out the fastest routes. Avoid traffic congestion, find packages faster and deliver more efficiently.
Circuit Route Planner Features
	Easily find and add stops with your...
</description></item><item><title>Download IMDb: Movies &amp;amp; TV Shows 9.2.4.109240400</title><pubDate> Mon, 22 Dec 2025 16:05:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-imdb-movies-tv-shows-8258.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-imdb-movies-tv-shows-8258.html
</guid><description>
IMDb (Internet Movie Database) is a popular application that provides information about movies, TV shows, and other video content. This app allows users to search and browse information about a variety of movies and TV shows, including cast and crew information, user ratings and reviews, trailers, and more. Users can also create watchlists and rate the movies and shows they've watched.
Some key features of the IMDb application include:
	Browse movies and TV shows by popularity,...
</description></item><item><title>Download FotMob - Soccer Live Scores 220.15365.20251218.rc</title><pubDate> Mon, 22 Dec 2025 16:05:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-fotmob-soccer-live-scores-8241.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-fotmob-soccer-live-scores-8241.html
</guid><description>
FotMob gives you all the live scores, stats and storylines to help you keep up with the world of football. Personalized news and notifications make it easy to follow your favorite teams and players. And lightning-fast match updates ensure you never miss a goal, no matter where you are.
Features of FotMob - Live soccer scores
	Live match score
	Results, schedule, standings and lineup
	Detailed statistics, including expected goals (xG) and expected assists (xA)
	Capture map
	Player...
</description></item><item><title>Download Learn Coding/Programming: Mimo 7.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 22 Dec 2025 16:05:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-learn-codingprogramming-mimo-11634.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-learn-codingprogramming-mimo-11634.html
</guid><description>
Code in Python, JavaScript, HTML, CSS or SQL and start your career in Technology in 5 minutes a day! Whether you're an aspiring developer or just starting your journey Code in HTML, JavaScript, or other programming languages, the Mimo programming and coding app is designed to make learning to code accessible, engaging, and effective. Learn to code in these languages popular programming languages ​​like Python, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, SQL, etc. With Mimo coding app, you can learn...
</description></item><item><title>Download Retrica 8.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 22 Dec 2025 16:05:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-retrica-9784.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-retrica-9784.html
</guid><description>
Retrica is the catalyst for great photos with special effects and over 190 filters. Add vignette, grain or blur effects to bring that vintage atmosphere to your photos and videos. Take photos and videos with filters and effects in real time, or edit them from your phone's album.
Features of Retrica Pro for Android
Easy, simple and attractive
	Enhanced user interface provides an easy, simple, comfortable and enjoyable photography experience. Retrica also offers multiple aspect ratios,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Multi Timer: Timer + Stopwatch 2.2.17</title><pubDate> Mon, 22 Dec 2025 16:04:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-timer-plus-with-stopwatch-10105.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-timer-plus-with-stopwatch-10105.html
</guid><description>
Multi Timer is a comprehensive mobile app designed to revolutionize how you track and manage time. The stopwatch and digital timer are simple, easy -to -use and accurate applications for Android to help you measure the time of all situations, such as sports, cooking, etc. With the time application, you will enjoy the freedom of the time counter and the timer and the full -featured and complete stopwatch with the ring and the clear display function.
Features of Multi Timer
	Easy to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Running Tracker App – FITAPP 8.9.8</title><pubDate> Mon, 22 Dec 2025 16:04:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-fitapp-track-my-run-running-8392.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-fitapp-track-my-run-running-8392.html
</guid><description>
FITAPP Track My Run &amp;amp; Running is a fitness tracking mobile application that allows users to track and analyze their running activities. It often includes features like GPS tracking, allowing users to track their route, distance, speed, and time. It also includes many tools for analyzing performance, such as graphs and charts that display data such as heart rate, calories burned, and elevation.
FITAPP will also help you lose weight, count calories, maintain your target weight or...
</description></item><item><title>Download Screen Recorder Video Recorder 8.2.1.3</title><pubDate> Mon, 22 Dec 2025 16:03:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-screen-recorder-video-recorder-12115.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-screen-recorder-video-recorder-12115.html
</guid><description>
This is a powerful and easy-to-use screen recording application that provides high-quality video and screenshot recording capabilities. It makes it easy for you to record videos, tutorials, play games, video calls, and any other moment you like. You can also trim, crop, and rotate to edit the video before sharing.
Features
	High quality recording: 1080P, 16Mbps, 120FPS
	Screen recorder with internal and external audio
	Cut, Crop and Rotate: finish recording, editing and sharing videos...
</description></item><item><title>Download COL Reminder 3.7.7.2 build 687</title><pubDate> Mon, 22 Dec 2025 16:03:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-col-reminder-8193.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-col-reminder-8193.html
</guid><description>
COL Reminder is a reminder application for your Android phone. Available in over 40 languages: English, German, Italian, French, Swedish, Spanish, Chinese, Polish, Korean, Hungarian, Turkish, Czech, Slovak
Features of COL Reminder
	Text reminder
	Phone call reminder
	Remind parking time with countdown
	Birthday reminder
	Location-based reminders
	Dashclock Utility Extension
	Back up Google Drive
</description></item></channel></rss>