<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 12:45:35 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 12:45:35 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download yt-dlp 2026.02.21</title><pubDate> Mon, 23 Feb 2026 00:23:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-dlp-6802.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-dlp-6802.html
</guid><description>
yt-dlp is a youtube-dl branch based on youtube-dlc currently not working. The main focus of this project is the addition of new features and patches while still updating the original project.
</description></item><item><title>Download VanDyke SecureCRT and SecureFX 9.7.1.3815</title><pubDate> Mon, 23 Feb 2026 00:21:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vandyke-securecrt-and-securefx-815.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vandyke-securecrt-and-securefx-815.html
</guid><description>
VanDyke SecureCRT and SecureFX is a file transfer app safety, flexibility with an intuitive interface provides remote access, secure file transfer. VanDyke provides simulation terminal firmly to the expert computing, enhance productivity with management enhanced and a variety of ways to save time and streamline the task repeated. SecureCRT has the security firm of SSH, session management extension and advanced commands, SecureCRT will help enhance your productivity.
VanDyke SecureCRT...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube Downloader 3.9.18 (2202)</title><pubDate> Mon, 23 Feb 2026 00:20:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube Downloader  is a dedicated software that helps users  downloading youtube videos  Favorites on PC for offline viewing. With MediaHuman YouTube  Downloader  you can download videos from youtube website to your computer with  fast speed , with special software development technology that automatically receives videos from Websites, in addition to the ability to download videos from software websites, can convert downloaded video formats to various formats for the purpose...
</description></item><item><title>Download AllMapSoft Universal Maps Downloader 10.238</title><pubDate> Mon, 23 Feb 2026 00:17:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-universal-maps-downloader-736.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-universal-maps-downloader-736.html
</guid><description>
AllMapSoft Universal Maps Downloader is software download map images on the computer for offline viewing support many types such as Google Maps, Yahoo maps, Bing maps, OpenStreet Maps, Yandex Maps, Ovi Maps, MapQuest Maps. All the downloaded photos will be saved on disk. You can view downloaded maps by Maps Viewer Or you can combine them into one big bmp, or jpg file tif by Maps Combiner, and also you can export all the tiles into a database format MBTiles.
AllMapSoft Universal Maps...
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow Fast ImageConverter 4.3.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 23 Feb 2026 00:16:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fast-imageconverter-10916.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fast-imageconverter-10916.html
</guid><description>
Fast ImageConverter is a simple yet powerful application for converting many image files to another format. Currently the application supports Gif, Heif/Heic, PNG, JPG/JPEG and WEBP. In addition, the application also allows you to resize and add watermarks automatically.
Features of Fast ImageConverter
	Convert multiple images to PNG, JPEG, WEBP or PDF format
	Create a PDF file from multiple images
	Scale multiple images
	Add watermark to multiple images
	Add QR codes to multiple...
</description></item><item><title>Download MedCalc 23.4.9</title><pubDate> Mon, 23 Feb 2026 00:15:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-medcalc-1536.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-medcalc-1536.html
</guid><description>
MedCalc is a statistical software for biomedical research can analyze many performance curve system with a set of rich functionality, chart types and advanced module. MedCalc was designed to meet the needs and requirements of the study nature and aims to analyze the statistical calculations of the project. This software provides the tools and means essential to analyze the characteristic curve of the system (ROC), drawing data and perform the statistical calculations.
MedCalc -...
</description></item><item><title>Download FreeFileSync 14.8</title><pubDate> Mon, 23 Feb 2026 00:14:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-freefilesync-2447.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-freefilesync-2447.html
</guid><description>
FreeFileSync is a program open source and free to be used to sync files. It's available on Windows, Linux and OS X. The project is supported by donations. Donors get a few extra features like the automatic updates, synchronize, parallel, mobile version and install silent.
FreeFileSync - sync data
Features of FreeFileSync
	Detect moved and renamed files and folders
	Copy the file locked (Volume Shadow Copy Service)
	Detect conflicts and propagate delete
	Compare binary
	Full support...
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 8.0.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 23 Feb 2026 00:14:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-11-7760.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-11-7760.html
</guid><description>
TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 is a program that allows users to discover hidden settings in Windows 11. This application is specially designed for Windows 11, groups many registry settings and distribute them from the easy and secure user interface. With TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 you can move the Windows taskbar to the top and resize the taskbar by editing the registry value. With any application that modifies the registry, we recommend that you have a backup copy...
</description></item><item><title>Download eM Client Pro 10.4.4867</title><pubDate> Mon, 23 Feb 2026 00:13:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-em-client-pro-953.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-em-client-pro-953.html
</guid><description>
eM Client Pro is an email app full features with modern interface. eM Client offers calendar, tasks, contacts and chat. Software is best Email app for windows today. eM Client supports all major services including Gmail, Exchange, iCloud and Outlook.com. You can find more information in the server part on our website.
eM Client Pro - the best email App for windows
eM Client is very simple , can automatically set everything up for most of the services. It is also effective to import...
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 8.0.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 23 Feb 2026 00:13:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-10-7759.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-10-7759.html
</guid><description>
TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 is a utility that allows users to discover hidden settings in Windows 10. This application is specially designed for Windows 10, groups many registry settings and provide them from an easy and secure user interface. With TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 you can move the Windows taskbar to the top and resize the taskbar by editing the registry value. With any application that modifies the registry, we recommend that you have a backup copy to...
</description></item><item><title>Download QuickUserInfos 3.11.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 23 Feb 2026 00:12:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quickuserinfos-7482.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quickuserinfos-7482.html
</guid><description>
QuickUserInfos is an administrator help tool that allows user/computer information recovery and more. It is designed to recover information quickly, providing you with detailed information about users, group memberships and registered accounts. It's available in installable and portable versions, so you can always have it on hand no matter where you are.
Additionally, QuickUserInfos also includes other useful tools for resetting user account passwords and comparing several user accounts...
</description></item><item><title>Download X1 Search Enterprise 10.3 Revision 9</title><pubDate> Mon, 23 Feb 2026 00:11:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-x1-search-enterprise-11828.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-x1-search-enterprise-11828.html
</guid><description>
Why should you use X1 Search?
Do you spend valuable time individually searching through Microsoft Outlook, OneDrive, SharePoint, Teams, Google Drive, Gmail and more without being able to find what you're looking for? With X1 Search, you can instantly search across emails, attachments, documents, local files, M365 data, including Teams Chat and Channels, and more, and find the exact information you need. with a single command, across all your data sources, saving you hours every...
</description></item><item><title>Download AllMapSoft Offline Map Maker 8.369</title><pubDate> Mon, 23 Feb 2026 00:10:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-offline-map-maker-656.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-offline-map-maker-656.html
</guid><description>
AllMapSoft Offline Map Maker is software create, organize, offline map from Google Maps, Yahoo maps, Bing maps and Openstreetmap. You can view offline maps downloaded with map viewer offline. And you can zoom out or zoom in the offline map or export map under the file format .BMP with file world xxx.bpw, and can output files xxx.map for OziExplorer. If you want to make a offline map of your city by yourself, it is very useful for you.
Features AllMapSoft Offline Map Maker
	You can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Monkeys Audio 12.35</title><pubDate> Sun, 22 Feb 2026 16:21:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-monkeys-audio-949.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-monkeys-audio-949.html
</guid><description>
Monkey\'s Audio is software that compresses digital music without loss of quality. Supports high quality WAV files and CD ripping. Monkeys Audio will compress .wav tracks into .ape files to reduce their size without loss of sound quality, decompress .ape, convert files, check file integrity and manage tags.
Unlike traditional methods like MP3 and OGG, which permanently remove quality to save space, Monkey\'s Audio only creates perfect copies with the same sound quality as the originals....
</description></item><item><title>Download Screenpresso Pro 2.2.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 22 Feb 2026 16:18:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-screenpresso-pro-1362.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-screenpresso-pro-1362.html
</guid><description>
Screenpresso Pro is a program easy to take great photos on your screen! Screenpresso blocked Print Screen key and screen capture the best in a few seconds. Allows you to capture windows and screen area, roll the part of the screen, edit the images obtained, add effects, resize a group of images, send screenshots by email and post them to Web resources.
Screenpresso Pro - Shooting the computer screen
Features of Screenpresso Pro
	Take the window and screen area. Take a partial screen...
</description></item><item><title>Download Secure Delete Professional 2026 v217</title><pubDate> Sun, 22 Feb 2026 16:18:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secure-delete-professional-4991.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secure-delete-professional-4991.html
</guid><description>
Secure Delete Professional is very simple tool but very effective to delete files and folders in a secure way. After using this tool, the files and folders selected will not be available for recovery. We have attached a number of security options so you can choose the security level that you need (this reflects the processing speed).
You can use this application in 3 ways. First, you can drag and drop the file or folder that you want to delete securely to the main window of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Photoshop 2026 v27.4.0.15 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Sun, 22 Feb 2026 16:17:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-0010-adobe-photoshop-737.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-0010-adobe-photoshop-737.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Photoshop is a powerful raster graphics editor developed by Adobe Systems, primarily used for image editing, photo editing, and graphic design. Currently,&amp;nbsp;Adobe Photoshop 2025 is considered a graphic design software, creating and enhancing images, illustrations, and 3D artwork. In addition, it also supports website and mobile app design, video editing, real-life painting simulation, and more.
Adobe Photoshop 2025 - Graphic design
When it comes to Adobe Photoshop, it is...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDF Architect Pro + OCR 9.1.88.23120</title><pubDate> Sun, 22 Feb 2026 16:16:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-architect-pro-ocr-6381.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-architect-pro-ocr-6381.html
</guid><description>
PDF Architect  is professional software that provides PDF creation and editing features according to your needs. Our PDF editor keeps you up to date with forward-looking features. Take complete control of your PDF files with our PDF editor. Modify text, images, and pages, and convert PDF to Word and Excel and more.
It has many advanced options and features for customizing, securing, and collaborating PDF files. All necessary features are included in this for better user experience. This...
</description></item><item><title>Download DiskDigger Pro 2.0.13.4177</title><pubDate> Sun, 22 Feb 2026 16:15:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-diskdigger-pro-435.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-diskdigger-pro-435.html
</guid><description>
DiskDigger Pro is software restore data files, videos, pictures, sounds, media files, from a USB Flash drive, memory card.  DiskDigger can recover all the deleted files from your means, can help even when files or folders lost due to virus attack. It gives users the ability to restore various types of data including: pictures, video, audio, text.
DiskDigger Pro support in multiple files with different formats: JPG, PNG, GIF, BMP, TIFF, ICO, ANI, DOC, DOCX, XLS, PPT, PDF, VSD, PPTX,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Balabolka 2.15.0.913</title><pubDate> Sun, 22 Feb 2026 16:06:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-balaboka-142.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-balaboka-142.html
</guid><description>
Balabolka is a text-to-speech (TTS) program. It can read text on your screen in a human-like voice. You can use Balabolka to listen to text from a variety of file formats, convert text to spoken audio files, and adjust speech parameters such as speed and pitch. It is often used for accessibility purposes, helping people who have difficulty reading or multi-tasking by listening to text while doing other activities. Balabolka supports multiple languages and uses different TTS engines,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Spencer 1.37</title><pubDate> Sun, 22 Feb 2026 15:56:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-spencer-1881.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-spencer-1881.html
</guid><description>
Spencer provide an easy way to bring start Menu Windows XP classic for Windows 8 your. This program is a standalone application and requires no installation. Just copy the file spencer.exe to desktop your and click that file to display a menu with all Menu items, start your current.
Spencer - Create Menu Windows XP classic
If you want to integrate it into your taskbar to make it look like the start Button is actually more, you can choose the option "Pin to taskbar" from right click...
</description></item><item><title>Download Homedale 2.23</title><pubDate> Sun, 22 Feb 2026 15:55:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-homedale-1914.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-homedale-1914.html
</guid><description>
Homedale is a screen wireless network simple allows you to view the status and signal strength of nearby access points. In addition to displaying technical information like infrastructure, channels and bitrate are supported, the program also includes a chart signals allows you to monitor signal strength of multiple access points in real time.
Because this is a mobile program, it is important to mention that it does not leave any traces in the Windows Registry. You can copy it on any USB...
</description></item><item><title>Download VovSoft Text Edit Plus 15.7</title><pubDate> Sun, 22 Feb 2026 15:54:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-text-edit-plus-2872.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-text-edit-plus-2872.html
</guid><description>
VovSoft Text Edit Plus is app designed replacement for Notepad by offering a feature set wider. Text Edit Plus is a lightweight tool that allows users to easily create new text document or edit the existing document. This app is designed replacement for Notepad by offering a feature set wider.
VovSoft Text Edit Plus - text editing
A number of features: dark Mode. Add date and time. The change of the background color and the font. Encrypt and decrypt text. Combine the lines. System...
</description></item><item><title>Download Apisonic Audio Speedrum 2.3.4</title><pubDate> Sun, 22 Feb 2026 15:51:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-apisonic-labs-speedrum-6993.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-apisonic-labs-speedrum-6993.html
</guid><description>
Speedrum is an MPC style drum sampler. Designed for easy startup and fast workflow, but with powerful features if you need them. 32 pads with essential effects, and with 8 sample layers per pad. 16 pads layout A/B with view to all pad FX or 32 pads layout with one FX view at a time.
Features of Speedrum:
	Speedrum is an MPC style drum sampler.
	Designed for easy startup and fast workflow, but with powerful features if you need them.
	32 pads with essential effects, and with 8 sample...
</description></item><item><title>Download GeoGebra 6.0.916</title><pubDate> Sun, 22 Feb 2026 15:51:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-geogebra-992.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-geogebra-992.html
</guid><description>
GeoGebra is software the mathematics on the computer for you to solve problems more quickly and accurately data problem given. GeoGebra supports connect geometry, algebra and elements of mathematics other in an interactive way and tight. Besides, GeoGebra also allows users to directly enter and manipulate mathematical equations and coordinates, and make use of the points, vector, lines, triangles, cones..
GeoGebra - graph the function
GeoGebra is designed for math classes in junior...
</description></item></channel></rss>