<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 13:46:02 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 13:46:02 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Turbo Alarm: Alarm clock 10.0.13</title><pubDate> Sun, 30 Nov 2025 16:45:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-turbo-alarm-alarm-clock-10935.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-turbo-alarm-alarm-clock-10935.html
</guid><description>
Turbo Alarm is the most complete and advanced alarm clock available. It has everything you need to get out of bed easier. Perfect for both heavy sleepers and early risers. Elegant, simple, reliable material design, allowing you to play your own music.
Main features of Turbo Alarm
	Music playlist - set a folder of your songs or music playlist as ringtone to have a different music alarm clock every day!
	Skip any day of the week – long press a day to skip and you'll never forget to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Clipboard CopyPaster Pro v56</title><pubDate> Sun, 30 Nov 2025 16:45:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-clipboard-copypaster-pro-11369.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-clipboard-copypaster-pro-11369.html
</guid><description>
Clipboard CopyPaster Pro is a manager that simplifies work with standard clipboards; you can use it to copy and paste various texts and images as well as manage clipboard history.
CopyPaster Pro is a clipboard manager and has many additional and very useful functions:
	Save all copied data (text, links, images).
	Copy the saved data and paste it to the desired location.
	Edit data.
	Create your own notes.
	Share saved data.
	Voice listens to saved notes
	Search in saved data.
	Create...
</description></item><item><title>Download BetterSleep: Sleep tracker 25.21.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 30 Nov 2025 16:45:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-bettersleep-sleep-tracker-8274.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-bettersleep-sleep-tracker-8274.html
</guid><description>
BetterSleep is a sleep tracking app that helps users track and improve their sleeping habits. The app uses the phone's sensors to track movement and sounds during sleep, then provides users with detailed sleep reports and analysis. It also includes features such as a sleep log, smart alarm, and white noise generation to help users fall asleep and wake up more refreshed. Additionally, BetterSleep allows users to set sleep goals, track their progress, and receive personalized...
</description></item><item><title>Download Castro Premium - system info 4.8.3 build 368</title><pubDate> Sun, 30 Nov 2025 16:45:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-castro-premium-system-info-10230.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-castro-premium-system-info-10230.html
</guid><description>
Castro is an information utility for your tablets and smartphones. It displays various diagnostic information about the device. Castro processes and displays a huge amount of information, namely
	Detailed processor statistics (CPU and GPU);
	Battery monitoring;
	Consumes all types of memory;
	Data usage over Wi-Fi and mobile networks;
	Real-time sensor data with helpful graphs;
	Detailed information about the device's camera;
	Full list of available audio and video codecs;
	Monitor the...
</description></item><item><title>Download myTuner Radio App: FM stations 9.7.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 30 Nov 2025 16:44:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-mytuner-radio-app-fm-stations-11072.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-mytuner-radio-app-fm-stations-11072.html
</guid><description>
Now available for Samsung TVs, LG TVs AND Roku! With the myTuner Radio app, you can listen to live radio from around the world on your Android phone or tablet. With a modern, beautiful and easy-to-use interface, myTuner gives you the best experience when listening to online radio, internet radio, AM and FM radio.
myTuner Radio App Features: FM Radio
	listen to more than 50,000 radio stations from more than 200 countries and territories;
	follow your favorite shows and over 1 million...
</description></item><item><title>Download Fitify: Fitness, Home Workout 1.113.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 30 Nov 2025 16:44:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-fitify-fitness-home-workout-8397.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-fitify-fitness-home-workout-8397.html
</guid><description>
Fitify is a mobile app that offers users a variety of workout routines and workouts, including bodyweight exercises with weights, resistance bands, and kettlebells as well as stretching exercises and start up. It also includes features like progress tracking, creating custom workout plans, and setting fitness goals. The app also includes many customizable settings, such as the ability to choose between different types of exercises, such as strength, cardio, and flexibility, as well as...
</description></item><item><title>Download Visual C++ Redistributable Runtimes All-in-One Nov 2025</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 23:54:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-visual-c-redistributable-runtimes-all-in-one-7466.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-visual-c-redistributable-runtimes-all-in-one-7466.html
</guid><description>
This repository contains the latest versions (April 2022) of all VCRedist Visual Studio C++ runtimes, which can be installed with one click by running the bundled batch file installer.
To install, run install_all.bat with administrator privileges (right click, "Run as administrator").
The download includes the VC_Redist runtime packages for Visual C++ 2005, 2008, 2010, 2012, 2013, 2015, 2017, 2019 and 2021. Both 32-bit and 64-bit are supported. Included files are English language...
</description></item><item><title>Download DISMTools 0.7.1 Update 1</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 23:50:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dismtools-12200.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dismtools-12200.html
</guid><description>
Inspired by Visual Studio, DISMTools is a user interface for DISM that allows you to manage Windows Imaging (WIM) files and much more. You can use it to uninstall apps, add driver or tool packages, etc.
DISM: This is a tool used to maintain and repair Windows images. This includes Windows Recovery Environment, Windows Setup, and Windows PE (WinPE). You can also use DISM to repair Windows images locally on your computer.
DISMTools: This is a user-friendly interface that allows you to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Crucial Storage Executive 11.08.082025.00</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 23:49:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-crucial-storage-executive-5938.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-crucial-storage-executive-5938.html
</guid><description>
Crucial Storage Executive is a free software tool that helps optimize your SSD Crucial performance. With Storage Executive, you can view how much storage capacity (GB), download the latest base program, track the temperature of the drive, reset the encryption password and activate the Momentum Cache feature, which helps multiple SSD operations more than 10 times faster.
The features of Crucial Storage Executive
	Enable the Momentum Cache feature and make many operations of the SSD...
</description></item><item><title>Download Topaz Photo Pro 1.0.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 17:44:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-photo-ai-8105.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-photo-ai-8105.html
</guid><description>
What is Topaz Photo AI?
Topaz Photo AI is a professional software that automatically adjusts for your image quality needs. Simply import images into Topaz Photo AI and it will use specially trained AI models to first detect unique details, clarity, and resolution issues before applying the intelligently adjusts to maximize your image quality.
For users experienced with Topaz Labs image quality applications, it combines the functionality of DeNoise AI, Sharpen AI and Gigapixel AI into...
</description></item><item><title>Download CyberLink ColorDirector Ultra 2026 v14.0.5921.11</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 17:43:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-colordirector-ultra-283.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-colordirector-ultra-283.html
</guid><description>
CyberLink ColorDirector Ultra is a necessary tool to create impressive, stories, and evoking responses from your video viewers. ColorDirector provides all the video creators of all skill levels the means to dramatically improve their projects through the use of tools to control color and light.
Features of CyberLink ColorDirector Ultra
HDR Video : Apply HDR to your videos to add more dynamic range than in your scenes, bring out the detail and highlight the best parts of your...
</description></item><item><title>Download FastStone Capture 11.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 17:43:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-faststone-capture-2044.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-faststone-capture-2044.html
</guid><description>
FastStone Capture is a screen capture tool and screen video recording, powerful, lightweight, yet full-featured. FastStone Capture that allows you to easily capture and annotate anything on the screen including windows, objects, menus, full screen, rectangular area / freedom / fixed as well as scrolling the window / web page. It also allows you to record all the activity on the screen, including changes on the screen, speech from microphone, mouse movement and click on the video file is...
</description></item><item><title>Download Free YouTube Download 4.4.46.1127 Premium</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 17:42:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-download-1177.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-download-1177.html
</guid><description>
Free YouTube Download Premium is the most popular application to download videos from YouTube. The program was released in 2006 and regularly updated since then. Use the program to download and convert YouTube videos to view offline anytime.
Free YouTube Download - added Support to download youtube
Download more videos! Save whole playlists and YouTube channels, videos from a playlist individually (history, video be favorite, favourites, Watch later), videos from many different...
</description></item><item><title>Download SysNucleus WebHarvy 7.9.0.245</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 17:41:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sysnucleus-webharvy-881.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sysnucleus-webharvy-881.html
</guid><description>
SysNucleus WebHarvy is software to extract data website such as Text, image, URL &amp;amp; email from the website and save the content... WebHarvy is a tool which scans website intuitive. Absolutely no need to write any scripts or code to scrape data. You will use the browser built-in of WebHarvy to navigate the website.
WebHarvy automatically identifies patterns of data occurring in web pages. So if you need a list of items (name, address, email, price etc) from a website, you do not need to...
</description></item><item><title>Download XYplorer 28.00.1100</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 17:41:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-533.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-533.html
</guid><description>
XYplorer - File Manager for Windows is software that supports users to manage files on the Window quickly and to arrange the folder tidy. XYplorer features tabbed browsing, search, files, powerful, preview, flexible, highly customizable interface, dual frame options and a variety of unique ways to automate effective tasks often repeat. It's fast, lightweight, and portable.
Features XYplorer
	XYplorer is a file manager mobile. It does not require any settings, store all configuration...
</description></item><item><title>Download CyberLink PowerDirector Ultimate 2026 v24.0.1128.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 17:40:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-powerdirector-ultimate-425.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-powerdirector-ultimate-425.html
</guid><description>
CyberLink PowerDirector Ultimate is software editor, edit video and make movies on the computer from a variety of templates are made available, complete with effects, transitions, animations, and music. CyberLink PowerDirector 17 is a combination of video editing software with advanced video editing features powerful. Cblowing need to add your clips into the time line and click on 'Production'!
The tool design video in CyberLink PowerDirector have the ability to customize helps you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium 4.4.46.1127</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 17:40:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-to-mp3-converter-premium-844.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-to-mp3-converter-premium-844.html
</guid><description>
Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium version is a software used to convert YouTube to MP3, extract audio from playlists YouTube, show listings, charts, video responses, channels, favorites of the user. With Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium, you can download and convert playlists, channels, stream original tv series and get them into iTunes at the same time.
Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium - convert YouTube to MP3
Features Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium from the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Maplesoft Maple 2025.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 17:39:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-maplesoft-maple-1365.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-maplesoft-maple-1365.html
</guid><description>
Maplesoft Maple is a package of computer engineering top Maple has been performed for all the mathematical functions and includes the basic operations and algorithms handling complex data. Maplesoft Maple be download easy on taiwebs.com. In addition, the package includes more than 400 math functions and chart types. According to the manufacturer, package Maple is the leading company on scalability and performance (thanks to the support of multi-core processors). Package Maple has a unique...
</description></item><item><title>Download MobaXterm Professional 25.4 / Personal / Educational</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 17:39:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mobaxterm-professional-2026.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mobaxterm-professional-2026.html
</guid><description>
MobaXterm Professional is an SSH Client application server administration remotely via SSH for the client quite well and are more convenient. MobaXterm Professional offers a multitude of functions suitable for programmers, webmasters, IT administrators and pretty much the user need to handle the job from far more simple way. MobaXterm provides all the tools network key remote (SSH, X11, RDP, VNC, FTP, MOSH, ...) and Unix commands (bash, ls, cat, sed, grep, awk, rsync, ...) , in a file exe...
</description></item><item><title>Download ManicTime Pro 2025.3.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 17:38:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-manictime-18.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-manictime-18.html
</guid><description>
ManicTime is a software automatically collect information about how to use your computer. It records the time of operation of the machine, see the change data in the machine, how much data you share, received on or moved away, what software you use, use at any time
ManicTime allows you to keep up the work of the staff, send progress reports accurately and manage your time better than ever. This type of software can help your business more efficient when it comes to the internal problems...
</description></item><item><title>Download MusConv 4.10.435 Lifetime</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 17:37:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html
</guid><description>
MusConv transfers playlists, albums, followed artists and liked songs across a variety of services – Spotify, Apple Music, Amazon Music, YouTube, YouTube Music, iTunes, Deezer, Tidal, SoundCloud, Pandora and more 125 music services!
Features of MusConv Ultimate
	Transfer playlists, albums, followed artists and liked tracks between over 125 music servicesManage playlists (Delete, Merge, Split, Copy...)
	More than 125 music services supported
	Access DAILY updated music charts on...
</description></item><item><title>Download ExamDiff Pro Master Edition 16.0.1.15</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 17:37:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-examdiff-pro-master-312.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-examdiff-pro-master-312.html
</guid><description>
ExamDiff Pro Master is a tool to compare files and folders intuitive and easy to use, intuitive and easy to use for Windows. ExamDiff Pro Master has unique features distinguishes ExamDiff Pro with the program compare other. ExamDiff Pro Master to help perform reviews of code and share other reports with your colleagues and compare local website with FTP server by plug-ins more integrated.
ExamDiff Pro Master can create a snapshot folder for comparison and storage in the future, compare...
</description></item><item><title>Download Realtek Ethernet Controller All-In-One Drivers 11.27.1128.2025</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 17:36:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-realtek-ethernet-controller-all-in-one-drivers-6485.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-realtek-ethernet-controller-all-in-one-drivers-6485.html
</guid><description>
Realtek Ethernet All-In-One Controller Driver is the software driver for the Realtek Ethernet cards. It is a program used to communicate from the Windows PC OS to the device. This software is required in most cases for the hardware device to function properly. In most cases, drivers come with Windows or can be found by going to Windows Update in Control Panel and checking for updates as well as downloaded from the Realtek support website.
</description></item><item><title>Download Ahnenblatt 4.38.0.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 17:36:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ahnenblatt-3844.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ahnenblatt-3844.html
</guid><description>
Ahnenblatt is a genealogy software full-featured, easy to use suitable for beginners and even pedigree has the experience to organize genealogy research by you. Use plausibility checks to find out the inaccuracies in your family and create the chart impressive with just a few mouse clicks.
Ahnenblatt - Create family tree,
Recently, there has been strong increase of the general interest of the public for genealogical tree. Users who desire to track their heritage have many tools at...
</description></item><item><title>Download SoftwareNetz Budget Book 7.26</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 17:36:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-softwarenetz-budget-book-3857.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-softwarenetz-budget-book-3857.html
</guid><description>
SoftwareNetz Budget Book support you can view stats and reports about how you have spend your money. All your family can use Window budget without problems. You can specify a maximum of 30 people. You can determine the cost for people is done. With the help of a budget plan, you can control your costs. At any time you can also see the amount of money you have left from your monthly budget yourself.
SoftwareNetz Budget Book - notepads spend
The features of SoftwareNetz Budget...
</description></item></channel></rss>