<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 20:01:23 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 20:01:23 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Wise Care 365 Pro 7.3.2.716</title><pubDate> Thu, 06 Nov 2025 20:47:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wise-care-365-pro-106.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wise-care-365-pro-106.html
</guid><description>
Wise Care 365 pro is a package of utilities registry, disk, and other systems important for your PC. Easy to use and effective, Wise Care 365 is the best solution to improve the performance of your computer. Get Wise Care 365 and your computer will never run slow again!
Wise Care 365 pro is what?
Wise Care 365 Pro
	Check PC a clicks
	Pc cleaning &amp;amp; speed up
	Inventory hardware
	Protecting your privacy
	Protect real-time system
	Silent mode
	Boot speed faster
	Freeing up disk...
</description></item><item><title>Download EmEditor Pro 25.4.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 06 Nov 2025 20:47:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-emeditor-pro-69.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-emeditor-pro-69.html
</guid><description>
EmEditor Pro - the professional version of editor text powerful for programmers, web developers and ordinary users with illumination of syntax and Unicode support. The features of the editor such as search and replace in files using regular expressions, automatic code detect, bookmark link and address email, block selection mode, configure the button bar, menu, font and elements color. With each language you can set separate configuration.
EmEditor Pro - text Editor professional
The...
</description></item><item><title>Download CyberLink PhotoDirector Ultra 2026 v17.0.1031.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 06 Nov 2025 20:46:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-photodirector-ultra-129.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-photodirector-ultra-129.html
</guid><description>
Cyberlink PhotoDirector Ultra is known to be photo editing tools and videos with the effect is extremely rich, help you to change the style for the individual images or the videos of his favorite. This software integrated the 3D engine helps to speed up Video processing, which allows accessing the repository effect online and extract the Videos into the movies 3D Bru-ray, 3D AVCHD.
Cyberlink PhotoDirector Ultra to offer users a more professional tool to handle their images, remove...
</description></item><item><title>Download PhotoPad Image Editor Pro 14.48</title><pubDate> Thu, 06 Nov 2025 20:46:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photopad-image-editor-572.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photopad-image-editor-572.html
</guid><description>
PhotoPad Image Editor is a software to help edit photos and supports lots of features like edit, cut, rotate, resize and flip digital photos. With PhotoPad Image Editor, you can freely perform the basic editing for their images and also can add some neat effect. It has the option to create a photo collage and mosaic images from your photos, and you can also add text and captions. If you prefer, you can complete your masterpiece by adding the frame or contour is simple.
The main features...
</description></item><item><title>Download A4ScanDoc 2.0.9.30</title><pubDate> Thu, 06 Nov 2025 20:45:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-a4scandoc-4421.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-a4scandoc-4421.html
</guid><description>
A4ScanDoc is a software solution useful provide you with a set of features reasonable and support the document feeder and two-sided printing, at the same time provides a fast scanning engine handy based on the profile of users to create. It is very easy to use, and it has a minimalist interface, while somewhat outdated, has intuitive layout. However, the application does not provide materials to help first-time users.
A4ScanDoc - Scan and print documents
When one or more documents have...
</description></item><item><title>Download AmoyShare AnyVid 10.9.5</title><pubDate> Thu, 06 Nov 2025 20:45:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-amoyshare-anyvid-7833.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-amoyshare-anyvid-7833.html
</guid><description>
AmoyShare AnyVid is the best video downloader that allows you to download videos from 1000+ websites. It offers HD video downloads of various categories, including streaming videos, TV episodes, TV series and more. Besides video format, you can directly convert video to MP4 or MP3 with the best video downloader.
Easy to download videos from any website, such as TikTok, Facebook, Instagram, Reddit, Tumblr, Twitch, Niconico, V Live, Naver, Lynda, TED Talk. With AmoyShare AnyVid, you can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cisdem PDF Converter OCR 3.7.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 06 Nov 2025 20:44:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cisdem-pdf-converter-ocr-8699.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cisdem-pdf-converter-ocr-8699.html
</guid><description>
Cisdem PDF Converter OCR is user-friendly and offers many customization options, allowing users to control the output format and conversion process. This software is suitable for professionals and individuals who work with PDF files and need to convert them to other formats for editing, sharing or archiving.
Features of Cisdem PDF Converter OCR
	Convert PDF: Cisdem PDF Converter OCR can convert PDF files to many other formats, including Word, Excel, PowerPoint, HTML, and more.
	OCR...
</description></item><item><title>Download Pegasun System Utilities 9.3.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 06 Nov 2025 20:44:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pegasun-system-utilities-10950.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pegasun-system-utilities-10950.html
</guid><description>
Pegasun System Utilities is a software suite designed to optimize and improve the performance of Windows computers. It provides various tools to clean junk files, optimize system settings, manage startup programs, and enhance overall system speed and stability. This software aims to streamline system processes, improve drive performance, and enhance overall computer performance.
System utilities provide more than 28 tools to meet almost any PC need. Whether you need to clean up your...
</description></item><item><title>Download VideoPad Video Editor Pro 17.51</title><pubDate> Thu, 06 Nov 2025 20:44:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-videopad-video-editor-pro-268.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-videopad-video-editor-pro-268.html
</guid><description>
VideoPad Video Editor Pro is software edit video from any camcorder, DV camcorder, VHS player or webcam for best quality. The interface of this utility is divided into several parts (for example: list of multi-media, Effects, transitions, Files, Clips, video track, audio track, overlay), which makes everything seem difficult to operate. You can capture videos from camcorder or other devices like webcam or capture card TV and after you have added files and sequence clips to the queue, you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Enolsoft PDF Converter OCR 2.2.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 06 Nov 2025 20:43:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-enolsoft-pdf-converter-ocr-14101.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-enolsoft-pdf-converter-ocr-14101.html
</guid><description>
Presenting information in different file formats can have completely different effects. We are used to storing and processing data in Excel, using PPT in meetings, taking notes in Text. But how to quickly create those formats with just one PDF file?
Enolsoft PDF Converter OCR can help you easily convert native PDF and scanned PDF to Word, Excel, PPT, Keynote, Pages, HTML, EPUB, Text, RTFD, images, etc. Whether you want to analyze data, report work to your boss, or meet with colleagues, it...
</description></item><item><title>Download Typora 1.12.3</title><pubDate> Thu, 06 Nov 2025 20:43:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-typora-6764.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-typora-6764.html
</guid><description>
Typora gives you a seamless experience as both a reader and a writer. It removes the preview window, the mode switcher, the syntax symbols of the markup source code, and all other unnecessary distractions. Instead, it provides an actual live preview to help you focus on the content itself.
Features of Typora:
	Typora allows you to manage your files easily, providing both a file tree panel and a side panel (file list).
	Automatically view the Outline structure of your document in the...
</description></item><item><title>Download TicToz 10.9.5</title><pubDate> Thu, 06 Nov 2025 20:42:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tictoz-14241.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tictoz-14241.html
</guid><description>
TicToz is one of the best TikTok video downloaders available, allowing you to download TikTok videos that have had their download settings disabled by the creator. Moreover, you can also download TikTok clips for free and convert them to MP4 in just a few seconds. Just copy the TikTok link and paste it into this downloader, you will quickly download TikTok videos.
Unique Features of Pro TikTok Downloader
	Bulk download TikTok videos, clips and playlists
	Support downloading from 1000+...
</description></item><item><title>Download DeskFX Audio Enhancer Plus 7.15</title><pubDate> Thu, 06 Nov 2025 20:42:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-deskfx-audio-enhancer-5543.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-deskfx-audio-enhancer-5543.html
</guid><description>
DeskFX Audio Enhancer applies real-time audio effects to play audio on your computer. DeskFX comes with an easy to use interface that allows you to enhance your audio. DeskFX audio enhancement software is designed for you to modify and enhance the music and sound played through your speakers and headphones, to give you the best audio experience possible.
DeskFX Audio Enhancer Features
	Sound effects including equalization, amplification, reverb, chorus, wahwah, vibrate, tremolo and...
</description></item><item><title>Download AmoyShare AnyMusic 10.9.5</title><pubDate> Thu, 06 Nov 2025 20:41:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-amoyshare-anymusic-14132.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-amoyshare-anymusic-14132.html
</guid><description>
AmoyShare AnyMusic is a multi-purpose music downloader and player. The app allows users to search, explore and download unlimited high-quality music (MP3, M4A, WebM, etc.) from over 1,000 online music streaming sites, including SoundCloud, Bandcamp, TikTok, etc. Users can download entire playlists, batch download multiple songs, and enjoy music offline with the built-in music player. The software supports music video downloading and provides fast download speed with multi-threading...
</description></item><item><title>Download Remote Desktop Manager Enterprise 2025.3.21</title><pubDate> Thu, 06 Nov 2025 20:41:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-remote-desktop-manager-enterprise-242.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-remote-desktop-manager-enterprise-242.html
</guid><description>
Remote Desktop Manager Enterprise software is the complete management of remote connections and virtual machines from a single location, at the same time access support data online and cloud storage. Remote Desktop Manager supports multiple types of connections, not only connections for the protocol connect remote computer Remote Desktop Protocol (RDP).
Remote Desktop Manager easily add, edit, delete, share, organize and find your remote connection of you quickly. Compatible with...
</description></item><item><title>Download Debut Video Capture Software Pro 12.01</title><pubDate> Thu, 06 Nov 2025 20:40:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-debut-video-capture-software-pro-951.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-debut-video-capture-software-pro-951.html
</guid><description>
Debut Video Capture Software Pro is software record and capture video from any source and features editing video color, resolution, and output settings. Debut Video Capture Software Pro is designed to use very easy and intuitive, giving you the ability to record everything from the video recording from your webcam, screen or video input device such as recorder, VHS in few minutes after download.
Debut Video Capture Software Pro - Recording and video recording
The main features of Debut...
</description></item><item><title>Download dbForge Studio for Oracle Enterprise 2025.2.109</title><pubDate> Thu, 06 Nov 2025 20:39:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbforge-studio-for-oracle-enterprise-14049.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbforge-studio-for-oracle-enterprise-14049.html
</guid><description>
dbForge Studio for Oracle is a trusted integrated development environment (IDE) for Oracle SQL developers. This database solution speeds up PL/SQL coding, synchronizes data between different Oracle servers, and automates the process of managing schema changes during development. The solution is equipped with a graphical user interface (GUI) and versatile data editing tools, making it easy to manage both internal and external data.
Key features of the studio include a PL/SQL coding...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT-DL 11.7</title><pubDate> Thu, 06 Nov 2025 20:39:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-dl-5876.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-dl-5876.html
</guid><description>
YT-DL is a small program to download videos from YouTube and other video sites. Our goal is to make the program as simple as its name.
The features of YT-DL
	Download the video from YouTube and other video sites
	Increase download speed up to 400%
	Download multiple videos at the same time
	Pause and continue to download at any time
	Preview video content while downloading
</description></item><item><title>Download Robin YouTube Video Downloader Pro 6.18</title><pubDate> Thu, 06 Nov 2025 20:39:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-video-downloader-pro-2828.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-video-downloader-pro-2828.html
</guid><description>
YouTube Video Downloader Pro is a Windows application professional to download and convert videos from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion and thousands of video sharing sites, other. It accelerates your download up to 5 times. YouTube Video Downloader Pro allows you to download multiple videos at the same time. It also allows you to pause, resume and cancel a download at any time.
YouTube Video Downloader Pro - Download online videos on social networks
Features of YouTube Video Downloader...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Geek YTDL Pro 11.7</title><pubDate> Thu, 06 Nov 2025 20:39:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-geek-ytdl-pro-9895.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-geek-ytdl-pro-9895.html
</guid><description>
YT Geek YTDL Pro is software that helps users easily download videos from YouTube and hundreds of other video sites. It is very easy to use, just paste the video URL and you can download the video while keeping the original quality. Not only videos on Youtube, users can download any video from social networking sites like Facebook, Vimeo, Myspace video,...
Features of YT Geek YTDL Pro
	Download videos from YouTube and other video sites.
	Increase download speed up to 400%.
	Download...
</description></item><item><title>Download Disk Pulse Ultimate 17.4.28 + Enterprise + Pro</title><pubDate> Thu, 06 Nov 2025 20:37:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-disk-pulse-ultimate-1465.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-disk-pulse-ultimate-1465.html
</guid><description>
Disk Pulse Ultimate is a monitoring solution change disk real-time allows one to monitor one or more disks or directories, save reports and statistics monitoring disk changes, the change is detected to the SQL database focus, execute custom commands and send E-Mail notifications when unauthorized changes are detected in the file system important.
Disk Pulse Ultimate - Monitor disc change
DiskPulse provides the ability for users to start / stop the monitoring operation disc change,...
</description></item><item><title>Download AI Image Object Replacer Pro 1.0.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 06 Nov 2025 18:22:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ai-image-object-replacer-pro-14249.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ai-image-object-replacer-pro-14249.html
</guid><description>
Are you tired of unwanted objects, people, or text cluttering up your perfect photos? Do you wish you could magically replace a dull sky or fix a buggy background without having to learn complicated software?
AI Image Object Replacer Pro brings the power of advanced image-rendering AI right to your desktop. Easily remove, replace, or add anything you can imagine to your photos with just a few clicks and a simple text prompt. Our intuitive tools and powerful AI models make professional...
</description></item><item><title>Download Advanced Renamer Commercial 4.19</title><pubDate> Thu, 06 Nov 2025 18:22:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-renamer-2647.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-renamer-2647.html
</guid><description>
Advanced Renamer is a program to rename multiple files and folders at the same time. By configuring the method name change, the name can be manipulated in many different ways. It's easy to set up a batch job using multiple methods on a large number of files. 14 different modes allow you to change the name, attributes and timestamp of the file in once. The file can also be copied or moved to new location based on information in the file.
The program can rename files in many different ways,...
</description></item><item><title>Download AnyMP4 Blu-ray Ripper 8.1.68</title><pubDate> Thu, 06 Nov 2025 18:21:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anymp4-blu-ray-ripper-3150.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anymp4-blu-ray-ripper-3150.html
</guid><description>
AnyMP4 Blu-ray Ripper is an advanced application and comprehensive allowing you to easily and quickly extract the Blu-Ray to your hard drive. You can rip discs to a variety of formats audio and video file downloads. This app also includes a set of functions powerful editing allows you to trim video length. change video effect, crop video frame, add watermark to your video, and more.
AnyMP4 Blu-ray Ripper - ripping Blu-Ray
The app will allow you to extract Blu-Ray formats various...
</description></item><item><title>Download Xfer Records Serum 2.0.23</title><pubDate> Thu, 06 Nov 2025 18:21:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-serum-serum-fx-3557.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-serum-serum-fx-3557.html
</guid><description>
Serum &amp;amp; Serum FX has an editor Wavetable built right in - you can create the wavetables of his own in many different ways. Import audio directly from audio files - Serum &amp;amp; Serum FX there are many methods and options for analyzing audio to separate audio into the waveform individually. Of course, you can import the wavetables of a cycle, as well as many at the same time (with the option to arrange to be built or re-order craft). Morphology between the wavetables different using...
</description></item></channel></rss>