<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 15:44:12 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 15:44:12 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Alternate Quick Audio 2.230</title><pubDate> Sun, 18 Jan 2026 16:17:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-alternate-quick-audio-2275.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-alternate-quick-audio-2275.html
</guid><description>
Alternate Quick Audio is software support audio player, already know want to find something new for yourself. This program lets you play, record and convert your music in MP3 format and WAV. The interface is very simple, even boring in places, but it does not cause confusion, everything is clear immediately after launch. Transition allows you to work with formats such as MP2, MPG, MP4, OGG, FLAC, FLV, AAC.
Alternate Quick Audio - Listen to audio recording
Alternate Quick Audio has an...
</description></item><item><title>Download ET Optimizer 6.08.15</title><pubDate> Sun, 18 Jan 2026 16:16:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-et-optimizer-9574.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-et-optimizer-9574.html
</guid><description>
ET-Optimizer is a free, open source script to improve your computer's overall performance and optimize it for your workflow through optimized scripting. With this optimization, setup takes little effort. The script is developed from many sources found on the Internet, tested and updated for different versions of the system. The whole script is contained in 1 file, it uses: command prompt, powershell, power plan configuration, startup configuration, registry changes, network interface...
</description></item><item><title>Download LrToolbox 2026.0.1.27</title><pubDate> Sun, 18 Jan 2026 16:15:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lrtoolbox-13054.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lrtoolbox-13054.html
</guid><description>
LrToolbox is a comprehensive Windows software designed to handle your Lightroom catalog with ease. Whether you are a professional photographer or an amateur, this tool will help you streamline your workflow and increase your productivity. Whether you need to extract previews from a catalog, convert your photo ratings to sidecar files, or convert RAW images to JPG, LrToolbox is here to help you with just a few clicks.
Key Features
	Compatible with Adobe Lightroom Classic 14.2 (February...
</description></item><item><title>Download Active Partition Recovery Ultimate WINPE 26.0.2.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 18 Jan 2026 16:11:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-active-partition-recovery-ultimate-winpe-6313.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-active-partition-recovery-ultimate-winpe-6313.html
</guid><description>
Active Partition Recovery Ultimate WINPE is an optimal data recovery tool set. In addition to the Professional features, it contains an ISO image that can boot that you can write to a CD-ROM or write to the USB Flash drive and launch Windows from this CD-ROM/USB drive to restore the partition. (including the system) as well as to restore specific files and folders from within the familiar Windows environment.
The general boot creator prepares a DOS, Windows or Linux boot disk for any...
</description></item><item><title>Download Plagius Professional 2.9.13</title><pubDate> Sun, 18 Jan 2026 16:10:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-plagius-professional-5717.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-plagius-professional-5717.html
</guid><description>
Plagius Professional is a tool capable of analyzing documents and notifying the user in case of plagiarism detection. The program automatically generates reports after checking documents or web pages and supports rendering reports into HTML files for later analysis. Plagius Professional supports several file formats, such as PDF, TXT, RTF, HTML, HTM, ODT, SXW, DOCX or DOC, but for the last two formats you need to have Microsoft Word installed on your PC (otherwise, they can't be...
</description></item><item><title>Download O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro 22.1.237 / Server</title><pubDate> Sun, 18 Jan 2026 16:10:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-diskimage-pro-218.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-diskimage-pro-218.html
</guid><description>
O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro is software backup data comprehensive and effective is provided to protect the data of the computer system, it creates images for individual drives or the entire system that still does not affect your system.
O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro allows the user to backup the entire computer or drive, the and files whenever you want even while the computer is being used. Or can use O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro to create a copy chinh sac of computer disk drives, can be used instead of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download VectorStyler 1.3.008</title><pubDate> Sun, 18 Jan 2026 16:09:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vectorstyler-7917.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vectorstyler-7917.html
</guid><description>
VectorStyler provides a complete set of drawing, design and illustration tools needed for modern design. Create illustrations, logos, icons, drawings, typography, vector art for screen, print and web. With many new features, VectorStyler redefines and extends the tools available to illustrators and designers, improving the creation of complex illustrations and designs.
Shape effects can be used to adjust the shape of objects, create different distortions, or add detail to shapes. Shape...
</description></item><item><title>Download K-Lite Codec Pack Update 19.4.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 18 Jan 2026 16:09:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-update-5145.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-update-5145.html
</guid><description>
K-Lite Codec Pack Update is the update of the set of codecs and related tools. Codec stands for Compressor-decompressor. Codec is necessary to encode and decode (play) audio and video. K-Lite Codec Pack Update is designed as a user-friendly solution with users to play all movie files your. With Codec Pack K-Lite, you can play 99% of all the movies found on your computer. A number of packages codec is not friendly with computers, as they tend to slow down Windows, break down multimedia...
</description></item><item><title>Download ButterScroll 1.4</title><pubDate> Sun, 18 Jan 2026 16:08:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-butterscroll-13824.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-butterscroll-13824.html
</guid><description>
Smooth scrolling on Windows just got better. Smooth scrolling for Windows is what ButterScroll is all about. It improves the way your mouse scrolls using customizable speed and ease settings.
Smooth scrolling for all types of mice.
ButterScroll improves your everyday scrolling experience with smooth scrolling precision, customizable controls, and a satisfying feel across all your Windows apps — from browsers to spreadsheets.
ButterScroll Features
	Easy to set up and use
	Smooth,...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaMonkey Gold 2024.2.1.3203 Beta</title><pubDate> Sun, 18 Jan 2026 16:07:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediamonkey-gold-231.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediamonkey-gold-231.html
</guid><description>
MediaMonkey Gold is music manager and music player multimedia for the music collection and iPod users. MediaMonkey lists the audio file of you as CD, OGG, WMA, MPC, FLAC, APE, WAV and MP3 and includes the edit smart card and an automatic file and folder to arrange your music library.
MediaMonkey Gold also has CD ripper, CD / DVD Burner, and audio converter for saving music, and manual or editor list automatically to create mixed music.
Features MediaMonkey Gold
	Automatically find...
</description></item><item><title>Download NCSS: Statistical Software 2026 v26.0.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 18 Jan 2026 16:02:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ncss-statistical-software-12302.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ncss-statistical-software-12302.html
</guid><description>
NCSS (Number Cruncher Statistical System) is a statistical software package that uses data analysis and statistical modeling. It provides many tools and processes for conducting statistical analysis, making it a valuable tool for researchers, statisticians, and data analysts.
You can start a free trial, watch the video on the right, or view the infographic below to learn more about NCSS's diverse capabilities. NCSS software for data analysis comes with integrated documentation, free...
</description></item><item><title>Download Macro Commander Pro+ 2.8.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 18 Jan 2026 16:02:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-macro-commander-pro-12815.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-macro-commander-pro-12815.html
</guid><description>
Macro Commander is an all-in-one data entry and desktop automation software. It is designed to empower users to easily create, manage, and trigger macros and scripts to automate manual, repetitive tasks quickly and error-free. Its clean user interface allows for quick and easy creation and organization of macros either manually or using the built-in macro recorder.
While Macro Commander offers powerful data entry features to quickly and easily fill in data in other applications, it also...
</description></item><item><title>Download Becky! Internet Mail 2.83.00</title><pubDate> Sun, 18 Jan 2026 16:01:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-becky-internet-mail-3926.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-becky-internet-mail-3926.html
</guid><description>
Becky! Internet Mail is a client E-mail features dedicated to Windows and the Internet. Since its inception in 1996, Becky! Internet Mail is constantly improving its functions to listen to user feedback and it has become one of the products email share most successful. Becky! Internet Mail is an email application that creates multiple mailboxes. You will find many features to be expected for a software E-mail Internet and a number of features will exceed your expectations. It has almost...
</description></item><item><title>Download NCSS PASS 2026 v26.0.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 18 Jan 2026 16:01:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ncss-pass-13683.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ncss-pass-13683.html
</guid><description>
PASS software provides sample size calculators for over 1,200 statistical test scenarios and confidence intervals - twice the capabilities of any other sample size calculator. Each tool has been carefully validated with published articles and/or literature.
PASS has been refined for over 25 years and is now the leading sample size calculator software choice for clinical trials, pharmaceuticals, and other medical research. It has also become a mainstay in all other fields where sample...
</description></item><item><title>Download SliQTools SliQ Invoicing Plus 6.10.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 18 Jan 2026 16:00:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sliqtools-sliq-invoicing-plus-12516.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sliqtools-sliq-invoicing-plus-12516.html
</guid><description>
SliQ Invoicing is software developed that can be used to create/upgrade and track professional invoices, credit receipts, purchase orders, delivery receipts, quotes and customer statements goods, helping you get paid accurately and on time. SliQ is easy to learn. No special accounting knowledge is needed and you'll be able to create your first invoice or quote in minutes. SliQ Invoicing Plus even includes inventory control features to help you keep track of inventory.
Basic...
</description></item><item><title>Download QOwnNotes 26.1.8</title><pubDate> Sun, 18 Jan 2026 16:00:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qownnotes-3178.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qownnotes-3178.html
</guid><description>
QOwnNotes is notes bookmark file simple text (GPL) open source application for GNU / Linux , Mac OS X and Windows of Patrizio Bekerle ( pbek on GitHub and IRC) (optional) activity along with the notes application of ownCloud or Nextcloud. QOwnNote store your notes as plain text files and can be synchronized with synchronization function file of ownCloud / Nextcloud. You can also use other apps like Syncthing or Dropbox . Just write out your thoughts as they appear, and edit them if...
</description></item><item><title>Download Solid Explorer File Manager 3.2.15 build 200357</title><pubDate> Sun, 18 Jan 2026 15:28:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-solid-explorer-file-manager-8924.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-solid-explorer-file-manager-8924.html
</guid><description>
Solid Explorer is a file management application inspired by old file management applications. Solid Explorer is a popular file management app for Android devices that allows users to manage and organize their files and folders in an intuitive and user-friendly interface. It offers many features that make it stand out from other file management apps.
Solid Explorer allows you to navigate to files stored on your device and automatically organize them into collections. You can view,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Currency Converter Plus 3.1.10</title><pubDate> Sun, 18 Jan 2026 15:28:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-currency-converter-plus-8174.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-currency-converter-plus-8174.html
</guid><description>
Advanced currency converter - With multiple currency fields, historical rate charts, and a built-in calculator for convenience, compare prices wherever you travel abroad to ensure Make sure you get the best deal at today's price. All conversions use live exchange rates from AccuRate™, providing the most accurate rates available in the world. Plus, it still works offline for moves when exchange rate data isn't available. This app even supports Bitcoin!
Features of Currency Converter...
</description></item><item><title>Download PowerDirector - Video Editor 16.0.0 build 2601151</title><pubDate> Sun, 18 Jan 2026 15:28:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-powerdirector-video-editor-8123.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-powerdirector-video-editor-8123.html
</guid><description>
PowerDirector APK - Video Editor (Unlocked Version) is video editing software developed by CyberLink. It is available for Windows and Android devices. If you are looking for the Android version of PowerDirector, you can download the APK (Android Package Kit) file from the Google Play Store or from taiwebs.com.
Features of PowerDirector APK - Unlocked Version:
	Easy-to-use interface: PowerDirector has a user-friendly interface that makes it easy to edit and create videos, even if...
</description></item><item><title>Download Clear Scan - PDF Scanner App 10.1.30</title><pubDate> Sun, 18 Jan 2026 15:27:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-clear-scan-pdf-scanner-app-9020.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-clear-scan-pdf-scanner-app-9020.html
</guid><description>
Clear Scan - PDF Scanner App is a mobile PDF scanning app that allows users to easily create digital copies of documents, receipts, and other paper-based documents. The app uses the device's camera to take a photo of the document, then automatically detects edges and applies filters to enhance the readability and quality of the scan.
Now convert your smartphone into a mini pocket scanner and enjoy high quality images in your device with just one tap with the best mobile scanning app...
</description></item><item><title>Download AR Plan 3D Tape Measure, Ruler 4.10.4</title><pubDate> Sun, 18 Jan 2026 15:27:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ar-plan-3d-tape-measure-ruler-8786.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ar-plan-3d-tape-measure-ruler-8786.html
</guid><description>
AR Floorplan 3D – Innovative measurement application, augmented reality (AR, lidar scanner) for quick room measurement. AR camera sensor technology allows placing virtual tape measure on real surface, making the process of measuring and creating 3D floor plan much easier and faster. Using the device's camera sensor - sketch a house, draw a blueprint, build a design.
With the AR Plan 3D ruler app, you can
	Measure the perimeter and height of a room in Metric or Imperial units (cm, m,...
</description></item><item><title>Download PhotoDirector: AI Photo Editor 20.9.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 18 Jan 2026 15:27:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-photodirector-photo-editor-8144.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-photodirector-photo-editor-8144.html
</guid><description>
PhotoDirector is a photo editing app for Android devices that allows you to edit and enhance your photos with a variety of tools and effects. With PhotoDirector, you can adjust your photo's color and lighting, remove blemishes and other imperfections, and apply filters to give your photos a unique look. You can also use PhotoDirector to create photo collages and slideshows, add text and stickers to photos, and share your edited photos on social networks or through other sharing...
</description></item><item><title>Download Transparent clock weather Pro 9.01.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 18 Jan 2026 15:26:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-transparent-clock-weather-pro-8872.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-transparent-clock-weather-pro-8872.html
</guid><description>
Transparent Clock Weather Pro: Get Accurate Local or Worldwide Weather Forecasts Easily with Live Weather Updates, Hourly and Daily Weather Forecasts and Timely Weather Alerts. Check The Weather for Today, Tomorrow or the weekend with our Easy to use app and widgets.
Features of Transparent Clock Weather Pro
	local Weather: Automatically keep track or your location as you move and get accurate real time weather reports and alerts
	Different Weather Preded for More Accurate Weather...
</description></item><item><title>Download Smart Alarm (Alarm Clock) 2.7.3</title><pubDate> Sun, 18 Jan 2026 15:26:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-smart-alarm-alarm-clock-8343.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-smart-alarm-alarm-clock-8343.html
</guid><description>
This is a simple and highly functional alarm clock. It is also very easy to use! You can listen to the alarm at the time that has been indicated by the alarm function even when the alarm has stopped. The alarm may be placed for weekly on the weekly specified days. The wallpaper used in the device can be displayed as a wallpaper for this application using transparent settings.
The features of Smart Alarm (Alarm Clock)
	Corresponding to holidays in the United States. The holiday is...
</description></item><item><title>Download AI Speech to text 1.35</title><pubDate> Sun, 18 Jan 2026 15:26:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ai-speech-to-text-app-13800.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ai-speech-to-text-app-13800.html
</guid><description>
Welcome to AI Speech to Text: Audio to Text, an innovative and sophisticated solution designed to enhance your transcription experience. Our AI Speech to Text app sets new standards in speech to text conversion by combining cutting-edge technology with user-friendly features. Whether you are a professional who wants to transcribe real-time conversations, an academic who needs to convert audio files, or a business professional managing important meeting notes, our AI audio to text...
</description></item></channel></rss>