<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 13:54:59 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 13:54:59 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Wondershare PDFelement Pro 12.1.7.3970</title><pubDate> Fri, 23 Jan 2026 16:38:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-pdfelement-pro-105.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-pdfelement-pro-105.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare PDFelement Pro support users to convert PDF to office documents for easier use, modify in every situation. Is one of the software conversion material is rated best today, integrated with many features. We recommend that you should use experience software many useful features this.
Wondershare PDFelement Pro - conversion Fie PDF more features, multi-language
Wondershare PDFelement Pro what?
Convert PDF into Word, Excel, PowerPoint...
• Convert PDF and protected PDF into...
</description></item><item><title>Download TidyWindow 3.9.3</title><pubDate> Fri, 23 Jan 2026 16:38:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tidywindow-14454.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tidywindow-14454.html
</guid><description>
TidyWindow is a Windows desktop assistant that automates developer PC setup, cleanup, diagnostics, software package installation, registry tweaking, and driver updates—powered by a WPF interface and robust PowerShell 7 automation capabilities in the background.
Key Features
	Essentials Repair Center (docs/essentials.md): Queues selected automation tasks Filter for network, Defender, printing, and Windows Update issues. Each task supports preview run, sequential execution, restore...
</description></item><item><title>Download Opera One 126.0.5750.59</title><pubDate> Fri, 23 Jan 2026 16:37:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-972.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-972.html
</guid><description>
Opera is a fast, safe, configurable and compliant intranet web browser, which includes both the reader and the application. The Opera browser supports web browsing, listening to music, watching high speed movies, you can open many tabs on the Opera without affecting your browsing speed. Opera now supports almost all devices and operating systems such as windows, IOS, Android, linux, MacOS ...
Opera is a beautiful interface and many interesting features, operating on both PCs and mobile,...
</description></item><item><title>Download CyberLink PhotoDirector Ultra 2026 v17.1.1321.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 23 Jan 2026 16:36:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-photodirector-ultra-129.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-photodirector-ultra-129.html
</guid><description>
Cyberlink PhotoDirector Ultra is known to be photo editing tools and videos with the effect is extremely rich, help you to change the style for the individual images or the videos of his favorite. This software integrated the 3D engine helps to speed up Video processing, which allows accessing the repository effect online and extract the Videos into the movies 3D Bru-ray, 3D AVCHD.
Cyberlink PhotoDirector Ultra to offer users a more professional tool to handle their images, remove...
</description></item><item><title>Download iWatermark Pro 2 v4.0.35</title><pubDate> Fri, 23 Jan 2026 16:36:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iwatermark-pro-1908.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iwatermark-pro-1908.html
</guid><description>
iWatermark Pro is great tool to stamp copyright image, create own mark on the digital image to protect the image copyright. iWatermark Pro works as a digital app independently of the browser other photos, such as Lightroom, Picasa and ACDSee. iWatermark Pro is designed to save time photographers, it support stamped a series of images at a time to save your work.
iWatermark Pro - stamped images copyright
The features of iWatermark Pro
	Stamped copyright the entire images folder at the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft Office 2021-2024 Professional Plus VL (64-bit) 2512 Build 19530.20184 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Fri, 23 Jan 2026 16:35:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-office-2024-6670.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-office-2024-6670.html
</guid><description>
Since the end of February 2021, Microsoft has announced two new versions of Office 2021 including: Office 2021 and Office LTSC. Reportedly, Office 2021 is the next version of Office 2019, promising to bring users a better experience in the new Word, Excel or PowerPoint tools.
With each office user, the Microsoft Office toolkit is essential and indispensable software in the job. Microsoft Office has undergone numerous editions from Office 2010, 2013, 2016, 2019 to Microsoft 365 developed...
</description></item><item><title>Download JRiver Media Center 35.0.38</title><pubDate> Fri, 23 Jan 2026 16:34:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jriver-media-center-110.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jriver-media-center-110.html
</guid><description>
JRiver Media Center can help you strictly manage all your files media and enjoy them in a completely new way. Launching the application for the first time, users will be immediately impressed with the intuitive and eye-catching interface with many interesting features to explore. Most people who have used JRiver Media Center evaluate that the software interface design is youthful and modern.
The software for arranging cover art of music files is also extremely neat, especially Insert...
</description></item><item><title>Download Urban VPN 4.0.7</title><pubDate> Fri, 23 Jan 2026 16:34:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-urban-vpn-7155.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-urban-vpn-7155.html
</guid><description>
Urban VPN is a subsidiary of Urban Cyber ​​Security and the creators of one of the world's most trusted and free virtual private networks. VPN Browser Extension Gives You Quick and Easy Activation &amp;amp; Unlimited bandwidth! Urban VPN helps you keep your device activities safe and private. Protect your device from harmful ads and protect your device from malware and other security holes when using public Wi-Fi connections. With Urban VPN, you can safely surf the web without fear of...
</description></item><item><title>Download MEmu Android Emulator 9.3.2.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 23 Jan 2026 16:34:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-memu-2975.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-memu-2975.html
</guid><description>
MEmu or also known as Android Emulator is the Android emulator light and free, allowing Windows users to enjoy Android experience the original on the computer and device Microsoft their. This app provides outstanding performance, allowing you to play on PC a series of games designed to run on Android devices. This app allows you to play the game favorite Android on larger screens, to bring you a better gaming experience.
MEmu - Android emulator, lightweight and free
Software MEmu also...
</description></item><item><title>Download Readiris PDF Corporate / Business 25.3.30.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 23 Jan 2026 16:33:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iris-readiris-corporate-120.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iris-readiris-corporate-120.html
</guid><description>
Readiris PDF v22 is a powerful PDF management software that allows file input from various formats to compose, edit, annotate, split, sort, modify, zip, digitally sign and share your own build of one or more secured PDFs. It supports you for daily tasks such as assisting you to work with contracts, text documents, JPG files, Excel spreadsheets, blueprints, Tender projects, Meeting minutes, document conversion PDF documents, edit text documents,...
Readiris Pro converts documents to eBooks...
</description></item><item><title>Download CapCut PC 7.9.0.3294 / 8.0.0.3347 Beta 7</title><pubDate> Fri, 23 Jan 2026 16:32:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capcut-pc-9995.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capcut-pc-9995.html
</guid><description>
CapCut PC is a simple video editing tool that you can freely use anywhere. You can create videos on your browser, desktop and laptop, or on your phone. Versatile editing, magical AI tools, team collaboration, and built-in assets. Create videos in a whole new way.
You can edit videos based on editing the timeline, in the process you can add different elements and effects to the video to give the best effect to your work. It is a simple and intuitive set of editing tools and effects that...
</description></item><item><title>Download AITextTune 1.6.5</title><pubDate> Fri, 23 Jan 2026 16:32:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aitexttune-12973.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aitexttune-12973.html
</guid><description>
AITextTune is an AI-powered tool designed to enhance and refine text content. It offers features such as improving clarity and coherence, generating summaries, and translating text into multiple languages. Users can easily adjust their writing style from formal to creative. This tool is very flexible and can be used on many different software and platforms.
AITextTune Features
	WRITE PERFECTLY: Improve the clarity and coherence of your writing! Create summaries and...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDF24 PDF Creator 11.29.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 23 Jan 2026 16:31:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf24-pdf-creator-926.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf24-pdf-creator-926.html
</guid><description>
PDF24 PDF Creator is a printer driver application that lets you convert any document or image can be printed into PDF format. With any application that supports printing any user can also create a PDF file of the document through the virtual printer PDF24. Virtual printer can also save the file under format image files other than PDF such as PNG, JPEG, BMP, TIFF, and PSD. After printing, a help section of the program that pops up allows the user to view, save, send, edit that...
</description></item><item><title>Download Visual Studio Code 1.108.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 23 Jan 2026 16:31:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-visual-studio-code-3182.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-visual-studio-code-3182.html
</guid><description>
Visual Studio Code is the encryption tool of Microsoft has met most of the needs of the developer. Environment this encoding was introduced to compete with other products such as Sublime and Nodepad ++ . Microsoft, in its new product, has not been released in many years, has provided many features in a simple environment. In addition to the familiar with a dozen programming languages, the syntax and get to know coding language as soon as be encrypted and allows for syntax highlighting, it...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDF Annotator 10.0.0.1007</title><pubDate> Fri, 23 Jan 2026 16:30:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-annotator-178.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-annotator-178.html
</guid><description>
PDF Annotator software user open any PDF file and add annotations, using the mouse or pen Tablet PC, directly on the Page of the PDF file. PDF Annotator allows users to perform editing operations on PDF files such as: add notes, edit signature, highlight, insert images or text... From the this useful tool, you can completely modify PDF files as you like in order to meet the different work.
PDF Annotator
With the PDF Annotator the document has annotations can then be saved directly back...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mocha Pro for Adobe 2026.0.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 23 Jan 2026 16:30:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mocha-pro-1029.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mocha-pro-1029.html
</guid><description>
Mocha Pro 2019 is the tool for visual effects and postproduction. Tool Tracking and VFX and is plugins for Adobe. Mocha is the artist and editor effects appreciate about the unique ability of his to reduce the time using keyframing related to VFX and premium finishing.
Mocha Pro 2019
Mocha Pro 2019 features track and remove objects that are GPU acceleratedtools, rotoscoping, advanced, stable, solved 3D camera, supports stereo 360 / VR, etc. Using Mocha AE CC in Adobe After Effects? See...
</description></item><item><title>Download FreeFileSync Donation Edition 14.7</title><pubDate> Fri, 23 Jan 2026 16:30:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-freefilesync-donation-edition-13970.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-freefilesync-donation-edition-13970.html
</guid><description>
FreeFileSync Donation Edition is a special version of the FreeFileSync file synchronization software for donors who financially support projects. It is used to compare and synchronize folders, create and manage backups of all your important files. Instead of copying every file each time, FreeFileSync determines the difference between the source and destination folders and transfers only the minimum amount of data necessary.
FreeFileSync version with additional functionality and...
</description></item><item><title>Download foobar2000 2.25.6</title><pubDate> Fri, 23 Jan 2026 16:29:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-foobar2000-1812.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-foobar2000-1812.html
</guid><description>
foobar2000 is the media player for media formats MP3, WAV, OGG and other formats multimedia other. It has no bells and whistles, however, under the hood, the program offers quite many features, including format, title and layout of the interface can be customized, convert WAV, Equalizer, Resampler, note cards, MP3, playlists, music album, CD, drag / drop and more. It also includes all the standard features like shuffle, random play, etc.
foobar2000 - The media player
foobar2000 running...
</description></item><item><title>Download O&amp;amp;O Defrag Pro 30.5.1213</title><pubDate> Fri, 23 Jan 2026 16:29:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-o-o-defrag-pro-149.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-o-o-defrag-pro-149.html
</guid><description>
O&amp;amp;O Defrag Pro is the professional software has the ability to defragment the hard disk and can work with the file system different from FAT / 32 to NTFS / 5, and support for the different arrays Volume / Stripe Sets. You can also set the schedule which O &amp;amp; O Defrag will be booted and perform a number of manipulation certain. Regular defragmentation of the disk partition optimized performance of your computer. The user interface is very easy to use. It has a ribbon bar displays all...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mixxx 2.5.4</title><pubDate> Fri, 23 Jan 2026 16:29:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mixxx-43.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mixxx-43.html
</guid><description>
Mixxx is free and open source DJ software designed for both professional and amateur DJs. It runs on multiple platforms, including Windows, macOS, and Linux. Mixxx allows DJs to mix and control audio tracks in real time, offering a wide range of features like beatmatching, crossfading, looping, EQ, effects, and more.
With Mixxx, DJs can import audio files in a variety of formats, including MP3, WAV, OGG, FLAC, and AAC, and organize them into playlists. The software also supports...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mocha Pro for OFX 2026.0.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 23 Jan 2026 16:28:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mocha-pro-for-ofx-4303.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mocha-pro-for-ofx-4303.html
</guid><description>
Mocha Pro for OFX is the tracking tool flat the world's most powerful for VFX and postproduction. With the tracking feature and remove objects that are GPU accelerated, mask advanced with snapshot feature edge, stable, corrective lens, the 3D camera, supports stereo 360 / VR, v. v. Mocha Pro for OFX is a plugin for Adobe Premiere Pro &amp;amp; After Effects, servers Avid Media Composer &amp;amp; OFX as Flame, Nuke, Fusion, HitFilm, and VEGAS Pro.
Mocha Pro for OFX 2020
New features in version...
</description></item><item><title>Download Macrorit Data Wiper 8.5.0 All Editions</title><pubDate> Fri, 23 Jan 2026 16:28:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-macrorit-data-wiper-911.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-macrorit-data-wiper-911.html
</guid><description>
Macrorit Data Wiper software delete data, partitions and disks safe. Macrorit Data Wiper completely delete the system / boot partition. This is a very good tool for those who want to delete data permanently from the system to prevent others from using.
Macrorit Data Wiper - Delete all data and partitions safe
The main features of Macrorit Data Wiper
	Completely delete the system / boot partition.
	Completely erase USB flash drives, memory cards, micro SD or TF card
	Wipe data...
</description></item><item><title>Download O&amp;amp;O Defrag Server 30.5.1213</title><pubDate> Fri, 23 Jan 2026 16:27:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-defrag-server-2521.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-defrag-server-2521.html
</guid><description>
O&amp;amp;O Defrag Server professional software has the ability to defragment the hard disk and can work with the file system different from FAT / 32 to NTFS / 5, and support for the different arrays Volume / Stripe Sets. You can also set the schedule which O &amp;amp; O Defrag will be booted and perform a number of manipulation certain. Regular defragmentation of the disk partition optimized performance of your computer. The user interface is very easy to use. It has a ribbon bar displays all the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Rusolut Platform 10.0.0.7</title><pubDate> Fri, 23 Jan 2026 16:26:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rusolut-visual-nand-reconstructor-13878.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rusolut-visual-nand-reconstructor-13878.html
</guid><description>
Rusolut Visual NAND Reconstructor is a solution for extracting and recovering data from eMMC chips via the NAND interface. It is an optimized and revolutionary technology, primarily designed for law enforcement purposes (mobile forensics and other fields). This technology provides the deepest level of data recovery from eMMC chip areas never before possible.
Key Features
	RECOVER DATA FROM OVERWRITTEN/GARBAGE BLOCKS OF EMMC NAND MEMORY
	RECOVER DATA AFTER FACTORY RESET/FORMAT
	RECOVER...
</description></item><item><title>Download Boris FX Mocha Pro for AVX 2026.0.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 23 Jan 2026 16:25:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-boris-fx-mocha-pro-for-avx-13995.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-boris-fx-mocha-pro-for-avx-13995.html
</guid><description>
Boris FX Mocha Pro for AVX is the industry-leading version of the plane tracking and visual effects software, designed to work as a plugin supporting AVX (Avid Video Extensions) servers such as Avid Media Composer. Mocha Pro integrates advanced plane tracking, rotoscoping, 3D camera resolution, object removal, image stabilization, and masking tools into supported hosts, including AVX-based editing software.
Key points about Boris FX Mocha Pro for AVX:
	This is part of the Boris FX...
</description></item></channel></rss>