<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 13:50:41 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 13:50:41 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download WinRAR 7.13 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Thu, 31 Jul 2025 16:05:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winrar-127.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winrar-127.html
</guid><description>
WinRAR is a compression utility data advanced supports multiple formats including RAR, ZIP, CAB, ARJ, LZH, ACE, TAR, GZip, UUE, ISO, BZIP2, Z and 7-Zip. It allows you to create, organize and manage archives in a comfortable way and quickly. WinRAR naturally are is a leading software currently in the compression and decompression of data. With the enhanced algorithm is applied, the software allows users to compress bulk files in different formats into synthetic 1 single file to facilitate...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mass Image Compressor 4.1.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 31 Jul 2025 15:56:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mass-image-compressor-12571.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mass-image-compressor-12571.html
</guid><description>
Mass Image Compressor is easy to use - a point-and-shoot mass image compression and conversion tool for Web page optimization, photographers, HTML game creators, and regular Windows users.
MassImageCompressor reduces image size significantly (&amp;gt;90%) according to user-selected size and quality parameters. Reduce large numbers of images in a folder (and optional subfolders) with just one click. Batch compressing images for websites, emails or mobile storage has never been easier! Most...
</description></item><item><title>Download COM Port Info 1.2.4</title><pubDate> Thu, 31 Jul 2025 15:53:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-com-port-info-7499.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-com-port-info-7499.html
</guid><description>
COM Port Info is designed to give you detailed information about COM ports and some management features. This is a simple handy interface that gives you a glimpse of your computer's COM ports. It can display two views with COM port and connection type (BusTypes).
You can also securely erase hardware and reboot your device to restore them after "secure erase" (requires administrator privileges). You will also be allowed to make COM port number changes/swaps (requires administrator...
</description></item><item><title>Download Massive X 1.6</title><pubDate> Thu, 31 Jul 2025 15:52:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-native-instruments-massive-x-2123.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-native-instruments-massive-x-2123.html
</guid><description>
Massive X is a synthesizer developed by Native Instruments, designed to create a wide variety of sounds and styles for electronic music production. It is the successor of the popular Massive synthesizer and offers many new features and improvements. Based on state-of-the-art architecture, it offers pristine sound and tremendous creative flexibility for artists and sound designers alike – allowing them to create, adjust, and experiment with sounds from a variety of sources. different...
</description></item><item><title>Download PrivaZer Donors 4.0.109</title><pubDate> Thu, 31 Jul 2025 15:48:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-privazer-donors-198.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-privazer-donors-198.html
</guid><description>
PrivaZer Donors  cleans and removes filth traces from the system. Intensive cleaning of unwanted traces of what you've done, viewed, downloaded, deleted, etc. Take ownership of your security and freedom - Free up disk space. Keep your PC snug and secure !!!
With one click, PrivaZer can safely clean: Internet browsers, Index.dat, Cookies, Tor Cookies, Flash Cookies, Silverlight Cookies, DOM Storing, IndexedDB, AppCache Registry, RAM, Pagefile.sys and Hiberfil.sys files.  PrivaZer  can...
</description></item><item><title>Download AVS Video Editor 11.1.1.181</title><pubDate> Thu, 31 Jul 2025 15:48:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs-video-editor-426.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs-video-editor-426.html
</guid><description>
AVS Video Editor is software professional video editing for windows with full features useful, easy-to-use.  When using AVS Video Editor you can record a video, to impose various effects, create and burn DVD, export movies to various video formats, convert video to iPod, PSP, mobile phones and the other portable device.
Features AVS Video Editor
Format support
	AVS Video Editor supports all major video formats. Edit and save the video file in the codec AVI, VOB, MP4, DVD, WMV, 3GP,...
</description></item><item><title>Download DriverMax Pro 16.19.0.23</title><pubDate> Thu, 31 Jul 2025 15:47:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-drivermax-pro-156.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-drivermax-pro-156.html
</guid><description>
DriverMax Pro : utility that allows to download the update the latest driver for your computer. In addition, DriverMax collects information about the drivers installed in system and prints a list of devices that use them. It scans and collects information about drivers installed in the system and create a list of the driver version, date, digital signature and many more.
DriverMax Pro offers information about the driver version, date, developer, number of files and you have digital...
</description></item><item><title>Download AVS Video Converter 14.1.1.181</title><pubDate> Thu, 31 Jul 2025 15:46:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs-video-converter-427.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs-video-converter-427.html
</guid><description>
AVS Video Converter is a software to convert video format, burn VCD, SVCD, DVD, editor video raise.  AVS Video Converter can convert the formats AVI, MPEG, WMV, DVD to the formats AVI, MPEG, WMV, RM, burn DVD, SVCD or VCD, package conversion, editing, effects and filters, video overlay, extract audio from video and save in a file, separate audio, extract a frame (frame) and save as images, split into segments and connect video, rotate video, more in the form of text, banners, logos,...
</description></item><item><title>Download PreSonus Studio One Pro 7 v7.2.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 31 Jul 2025 15:46:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-presonus-studio-one-pro-780.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-presonus-studio-one-pro-780.html
</guid><description>
PreSonus Studio One Pro is software production music professional perfect combination between the studio model with the production process according to the beat and loop today so you can bring music ideas to actual sounds. Screen interface, simple, effective contains the number of tracks is not limited to , the editing tools are intuitive and the tools advanced virtual. Spend precious time to create music instead of wondering what to click next. Studio One does not dictate how you work or...
</description></item><item><title>Download Boris FX Sapphire Plug-ins for After Effects 2025.52</title><pubDate> Thu, 31 Jul 2025 15:45:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-boris-fx-sapphire-plug-ins-for-adobe-5314.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-boris-fx-sapphire-plug-ins-for-adobe-5314.html
</guid><description>
Boris FX, Sapphire Plug-ins for Adobe is a collection of very useful gadgets with additional powerful, as well as the effects to create the effect of the attractive images in the movies and video files. The film today is not complete without photo effects and include a number of photo effects to increase the beauty for their film. To add effect, clip to your movie, you can use a number of different applications and BorisFX Genarts Sapphire is one of them.
Boris FX, Sapphire Plug-ins for...
</description></item><item><title>Download JRiver Media Center 34.0.51</title><pubDate> Thu, 31 Jul 2025 15:45:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jriver-media-center-110.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jriver-media-center-110.html
</guid><description>
JRiver Media Center can help you strictly manage all your files media and enjoy them in a completely new way. Launching the application for the first time, users will be immediately impressed with the intuitive and eye-catching interface with many interesting features to explore. Most people who have used JRiver Media Center evaluate that the software interface design is youthful and modern.
The software for arranging cover art of music files is also extremely neat, especially Insert...
</description></item><item><title>Download Subtitle Edit 4.0.13</title><pubDate> Thu, 31 Jul 2025 15:45:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-subtitle-edit-2177.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-subtitle-edit-2177.html
</guid><description>
Subtitle Edit is software can both create new and edit captions already on your hard drive and added videos. The program will give the user a set of tools reliable and of high quality. If you believe that the author of the development and simply reviews on the Internet, then that is a large number of useful tools can distinguish this product with other similar substances, also provides the ability to overlay subtitles on the video. With Subtitle Edit you can easily configure caption,...
</description></item><item><title>Download GoodSync Enterprise 12.9.3.3</title><pubDate> Thu, 31 Jul 2025 15:44:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-goodsync-enterprise-163.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-goodsync-enterprise-163.html
</guid><description>
GoodSync Enterprise is a software that saves files and files easily and is reliable. It automatically analyts, synchronize and backup your email, family photos, contacts, MP3, financial documentation and other important files-between desktop computers, laptops, servers, external drives and Windows Mobile devices as well as remotely via FTP , SFTP, WebDAV and more. The GoodSync synchronized software combines bulletproof reliability with an extremely easy interface to compare, synchronize...
</description></item><item><title>Download Boris FX Sapphire Plug-ins for Photoshop 2025.52</title><pubDate> Thu, 31 Jul 2025 15:40:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-boris-fx-sapphire-plug-ins-for-photoshop-7185.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-boris-fx-sapphire-plug-ins-for-photoshop-7185.html
</guid><description>
Sapphire 2022 adds new host support for Adobe Photoshop. Featuring 270+ resolution independent and non-destructive effects built into a one-of-a-kind nodal based effects compositor. Photoshop artists will delight at 3000+ easily searchable presets organized by name, type, or intended use. Sapphire Photoshop has the same extensive parameter set as Sapphire plugins, giving artists complete control over every aspect of an effect.
Anything created with Sapphire Photoshop can be shared with...
</description></item><item><title>Download R-Studio 9.5 Build 191578 Network / Technician</title><pubDate> Thu, 31 Jul 2025 15:40:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-studio-1415.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-studio-1415.html
</guid><description>
R-Studio is a group of software data recovery and data recovery powerful and effective. -STUDIO is the solution to recover most comprehensive data for the file restored from the variants NTFS, NTFS5, ReFS, FAT12 / 16/32, exFAT, HFS / HFS + (Macintosh), Little and Big Endian of UFS1 / UFS2 (FreeBSD / OpenBSD / NetBSD / Solaris) and Ext2 / Ext3 / Ext4 partition FS (Linux).
R-Studio is also used to recover file raw (scan known file types) for the file system is damaged or not determined. It...
</description></item><item><title>Download AVS Video ReMaker 8.1.1.181</title><pubDate> Thu, 31 Jul 2025 15:39:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs-video-remaker-1196.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs-video-remaker-1196.html
</guid><description>
AVS Video ReMaker is software that support quick editing of video files without reducing the video quality. Detection algorithm scenes used in AVS Video ReMaker will save time when processing video images and split it into the set. So, no need to preview every frame of the video file to find the transitions manually. With the help of AVS Video ReMaker, you can delete the unwanted parts and TV commercials from video files or file format DVD, recorded by various cameras, various video...
</description></item><item><title>Download Office Timeline Plus 11.16.00.00 Expert / Pro / Pro+ Edition</title><pubDate> Thu, 31 Jul 2025 15:39:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-timeline-2106.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-timeline-2106.html
</guid><description>
Office Timeline is an add-on very useful and powerful software for Microsoft PowerPoint. With add-ons, you can create PowerPoint documents look more beautiful. With add-ons, you can add the time Line on the project by yourself. Application time for the composition and different segments of the document, your PowerPoint will not only increase the beauty for your work, but also for customers and your manager. The people who created this product is also believe that add-ons this is the only...
</description></item><item><title>Download Boris FX Sapphire Plug-ins for OFX 2025.52</title><pubDate> Thu, 31 Jul 2025 15:38:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-genarts-sapphire-839.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-genarts-sapphire-839.html
</guid><description>
GenArts Sapphire is the latest upgrade for the plugin VFX. The application includes LensFlare and Flare Designer been refurbished and completely revamped effects , digital art, new and is optimized for performance, CPU and GPU maximum. The current GenArts Sapphire is supported for Adobe, Avid, them Autodesk Flame and OFX as Resolve, Fusion, NUKE, Baselight (only version 4.3 and 4.4), VEGAS Pro and Harmony.
GenArts Sapphire - edit, add visual effects
The main features of GenArts...
</description></item><item><title>Download Abelssoft YouTube Song Downloader Plus 2025 v25.08</title><pubDate> Thu, 31 Jul 2025 15:38:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-abelssoft-youtube-song-downloader-plus-111.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-abelssoft-youtube-song-downloader-plus-111.html
</guid><description>
Abelssoft YouTube Song Downloader Plus 2018.18.17 Program YouTube Song Downloader Plus will help you search the music and video files from YouTube, after you can download them at. To search for music you just need to enter song name in the required field and you will get results, then you can download all videos and audio files. The program can search the entire album, this function will help to find individual songs from separate albums, because of this we specify the name of the artist...
</description></item><item><title>Download Boris FX Sapphire Plug-ins for Avid 2025.52</title><pubDate> Thu, 31 Jul 2025 15:37:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-boris-fx-sapphire-plug-ins-for-avid-12269.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-boris-fx-sapphire-plug-ins-for-avid-12269.html
</guid><description>
Sapphire Plug-ins is an image processing and compositing effects package for use with Avid AVX products including Media Composer, Symphony, Xpress Pro, Newscutter and DS. It includes more than 250 AVX 2 plug-ins, each with multiple parameters that can be adjusted and animated to create unlimited results.
Key features include 270+ effects and 3000+ presets, powerful Transition and Effect Builder, integrated tracking and overlay with Academy Award-winning Mocha. Sapphire's superior image...
</description></item><item><title>Download Vector 35 Binary Ninja 5.1.8005 Personal</title><pubDate> Thu, 31 Jul 2025 15:35:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vector-35-binary-ninja-8951.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vector-35-binary-ninja-8951.html
</guid><description>
Vector 35 Binary Ninja is a reverse engineering platform designed to help security researchers, developers and binary code analysts. It is a software tool that allows users to disassemble, decompile, and debug binaries, making it easier to understand how the program works and to identify potential vulnerabilities.
This tool provides a user-friendly interface that makes it easy to navigate and analyze binary files. It includes a wide range of features for code separation, including...
</description></item><item><title>Download Hasleo Backup Suite WinPE 5.4.2.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 31 Jul 2025 15:35:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hasleo-backup-suite-winpe-11366.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hasleo-backup-suite-winpe-11366.html
</guid><description>
Hasleo Backup Suite is Windows backup and recovery software, integrating backup, restore, and replication features. This software is designed for Windows operating system users and can be used on both Windows PCs and Servers. Hasleo Backup Suite's backup and restore feature can help you back up and restore your Windows operating system, drives, and partitions to protect the security of your Windows operating system and personal data. Hasleo Backup Suite's cloning feature can help you...
</description></item><item><title>Download UniGetUI 3.3.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 31 Jul 2025 15:34:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-unigetui-12209.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-unigetui-12209.html
</guid><description>
UniGetUI (formerly WingetUI) is a graphical user interface for WinGet (and other package managers), a command-line package manager for Windows 10 and Windows 11 such as Winget, Scoop, Chocolatey, Pip, NPM, .NET Tool and PowerShell Gallery. It allows users to install, update and uninstall software from the package manager easily. Additionally, it provides features like backup, restore, group and update your packages and receive notifications about new updates.
With this program, you can...
</description></item><item><title>Download AnyTrans for iOS 8.9.12.20250730</title><pubDate> Thu, 31 Jul 2025 15:34:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anytrans-for-ios-755.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anytrans-for-ios-755.html
</guid><description>
AnyTrans for iOS is content manager essential fully managed iPhone, Android and content of your cloud. Including all mobile devices, all cloud drives from your iPhone, iPad, iPod touch to phones and tablets. From local disk to cloud storage. AnyTrans has protected them all, providing you convenient management for all data and your files, regardless of whether they are stored where.
AnyTrans is the one stop solution to meet all the management needs of your data. For the first time, you can...
</description></item><item><title>Download AVS4YOU Software AIO Installation Package 6.1.1.181</title><pubDate> Thu, 31 Jul 2025 15:33:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs4you-software-aio-installation-package-1200.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs4you-software-aio-installation-package-1200.html
</guid><description>
AVS4YOU Software AIO Installation Package is the package includes programs to work with video, audio, graphics, documents, and system cleaning. You can install as a complete package, or separate. Which program are presented: AVS Video Editor, AVS Video Converter, AVS Video ReMaker, AVS Media Player, AVS Audio Editor, AVS Audio Converter, AVS Disc Converter, AVS Image Converter, AVS Document Converter, AVS Registry Cleaner.
AVS4YOU Software AIO Installation Package - Full set of tools,...
</description></item></channel></rss>