<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 09:03:43 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 09:03:43 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Syncthing 2.0.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 23 Aug 2025 00:57:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncthing-2115.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncthing-2115.html
</guid><description>
Syncthing is synchronization service, cloud and open and non-focus allows you to share and sync files with other computers and gives you full control how to share your data and who can access it. Syncthing does not store your data in any other place, there is no server side Tuesday how to join. In addition, all the communication is secured by TLS and every button is determined by the certificate the strength of the encryption. Only computers that have explicitly allowed can connect with...
</description></item><item><title>Download SysNucleus WebHarvy 7.7.0.242</title><pubDate> Sat, 23 Aug 2025 00:54:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sysnucleus-webharvy-881.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sysnucleus-webharvy-881.html
</guid><description>
SysNucleus WebHarvy is software to extract data website such as Text, image, URL &amp;amp; email from the website and save the content... WebHarvy is a tool which scans website intuitive. Absolutely no need to write any scripts or code to scrape data. You will use the browser built-in of WebHarvy to navigate the website.
WebHarvy automatically identifies patterns of data occurring in web pages. So if you need a list of items (name, address, email, price etc) from a website, you do not need to...
</description></item><item><title>Download ProfiCAD 13.1.7</title><pubDate> Sat, 23 Aug 2025 00:54:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-proficad-1546.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-proficad-1546.html
</guid><description>
ProfiCAD is a software Program to draw diagram and circuit diagram of the electrical circuit and electronics with many features to support users. ProfiCAD will search the control circuit is different then help, you can design a variety of diagram techniques, such as diagrams, pneumatic and hydraulic. One of the obvious features of this product is the simplicity of it. Simple in the tool bar and the icons represent the parts. Simply arrange the menu, just put the items on the screen and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wise Disk Cleaner 11.2.6.846</title><pubDate> Sat, 23 Aug 2025 00:53:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wise-disk-cleaner-392.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wise-disk-cleaner-392.html
</guid><description>
Wise Disk Cleaner software to clean hard drive by finding and deleting junk files downloads accumulate over time. Wise Disk Cleaner is pre-configured with about 50 types of extension files can usually be considered disposable, and you can extend the range by adding the file types of their own.
Wise Disk Cleaner to use the advanced algorithm with the ability to quick scan and comprehensive scan of hard drive space. Users can delete browsing history as well as the personal data important...
</description></item><item><title>Download Synchredible Professional 9.001</title><pubDate> Sat, 23 Aug 2025 00:53:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-synchredible-professional-1923.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-synchredible-professional-1923.html
</guid><description>
Synchredible Professional is the most advanced version help synchronize the folder and your drive quickly and easily. Whether it is a single file or an entire drive - Synchredible Professional will synchronize, copy and save them for you. The software guide will assist you to identify the work that is scheduled in advance or be done through the USB connection. This way, you can keep your files in sync - automatically.
In the past years, the advanced technology of the us in Synchredible...
</description></item><item><title>Download Flyby11 1.3.174</title><pubDate> Sat, 23 Aug 2025 00:53:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-flyby11-12467.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-flyby11-12467.html
</guid><description>
Flyby11 is a simple patcher that removes annoying restrictions that prevent you from installing Windows 11 (24H2) on unsupported hardware. Do you have an old PC? No TPM, Secure Boot or your processor is not supported? Flyby11 allows you to install Windows 11 24H2. There are no complicated steps. Just run the tool and you'll be running Windows 11 on your outdated machine in no time.
Technical overview
Flyby11 takes advantage of a feature of the Windows 11 setup process that uses the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Room Arranger 10.2.0.732</title><pubDate> Sat, 23 Aug 2025 00:52:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-room-arranger-3779.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-room-arranger-3779.html
</guid><description>
Room Arranger is a 3D application lets you easily plan for the room, office or his apartment just a few mouse clicks. The application comes with a simple interface will significantly simplify your work. You can draw many kinds of objects and items to create furniture of your own. This app also includes a library of object rich.
Software Room Arranger enables you to view your project in 3D form. You can also upload the 3D scene interact on your blog or your website. The application uses...
</description></item><item><title>Download Flyoobe 1.3.174</title><pubDate> Sat, 23 Aug 2025 00:52:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oobelux-13956.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oobelux-13956.html
</guid><description>
Flyoobe was born out of the frustration many users felt with the Windows 11 setup experience. Whether it was the mandatory online account, the endless "Next, next, next..." screens, or the incomplete configuration options when you finally reached the desktop, the current setup lacked focus on what users really wanted.
Why choose Flyoobe?
	Simplifies the Windows 11 setup process right out of the box.
	Allows easy local account creation without need to hunt for hidden options.
	Includes...
</description></item><item><title>Download CopyQ 11.0.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 23 Aug 2025 00:48:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-copyq-1368.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-copyq-1368.html
</guid><description>
CopyQ is software clipboard manager for windows that helps you easily copy, save, text, clipboard. CopyQ absolutely free on taiwebs.com it allows you to save more than one default entry to the clipboard is limited to Windows. Each time you copy or cut something, it will be saved to the clipboard expansion of CopyQ , both files and text can all be saved.
CopyQ - clipboard Manager
Features of CopyQ
	Support for Linux, Windows and OS X 10.9+
	Store text, HTML, image or any customized...
</description></item><item><title>Download Pazu StreamGet All-In-One Video Downloader 2.7.8</title><pubDate> Sat, 23 Aug 2025 00:47:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pazu-streamget-all-in-one-video-downloader-12037.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pazu-streamget-all-in-one-video-downloader-12037.html
</guid><description>
StreamGet All-In-One Video Downloader is the ultimate downloading solution for you. It supports downloading any movies and shows from the most popular streaming sites including Netflix, Prime Video, Disney Plus, Max, Hulu, and Apple TV Plus. The downloader is continuously updated to support more platforms in the future.
Download movies and shows from various streaming platforms to MP4/MKV on your Windows device and enjoy them anywhere you want.
Features of Pazu StreamGet All-In-One...
</description></item><item><title>Download MP3jam 1.1.6.14</title><pubDate> Sat, 23 Aug 2025 00:47:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mp3jam-2084.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mp3jam-2084.html
</guid><description>
MP3jam is a the database songs, safe and fast, with the ability to access over 20 million songs. MP3jam allows you to search, listen and full album for free only with one click! The software is optimized to search YouTube music fast and so you can save any track or album in seconds.
MP3jam
MP3jam does not use torrents, algorithms, p2p or the website, copyright infringement and only search for music in public access. MP3jam allows you to listen to music in MP3 format. Moreover, you can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ghostery for Firefox 10.5.5 + Chrome / Opera / Edge</title><pubDate> Sat, 23 Aug 2025 00:46:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ghostery-for-firefox-320.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ghostery-for-firefox-320.html
</guid><description>
Ghostery for Firefox is a browser add-on for Firefox allows you to see what kind of technical track is used by the current website, including tags, error web, pixels and beacons. Ghostery also gives you the hints to learn about the objects that are "of interest" to you includes the privacy policy useful links other.
Ghostery for Firefox comes with the option to block any elements of this, including ads, cookies, tracking, analysis, social extensions and more. You can select the items to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Photo Supreme 2025.3.3.8033</title><pubDate> Sat, 23 Aug 2025 00:45:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photo-supreme-430.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photo-supreme-430.html
</guid><description>
Photo Supreme is a software product management professional pictures of idimager. With Photo Supreme you can arrange, manage back stock photo archive of yourself and share them with you here and relatives easily via Email or Facebook. Photo Supreme provides users method to sort images effective, logical, as well as edit and share your photos with friends and relatives in the family. Especially the Photo Supreme allows to work with multiple image formats and support mounting support,...
</description></item><item><title>Download NetSpeedTray 1.1.2 + Portable</title><pubDate> Sat, 23 Aug 2025 00:45:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-netspeedtray-14068.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-netspeedtray-14068.html
</guid><description>
NetSpeedTray is a lightweight, open source network monitor for Windows that displays upload/download speeds directly on the Taskbar with a native look and feel.
Designed to blend seamlessly with Windows 10/11 user interface. Includes intelligent detection of light and dark themes on the taskbar to ensure text is always visible. Sits quietly in the system tray without hogging resources. Features "Dynamic Update Rate" that automatically reduces update frequency when the network is idle to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Helium Music Manager Premium 17.4.482</title><pubDate> Sat, 23 Aug 2025 00:38:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-helium-music-manager-premium-164.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-helium-music-manager-premium-164.html
</guid><description>
Helium Music Manager is a music manager that can rip, tag, play, browse, search, rename, burn and synchronize your music with the mobile. You can control your music collection with Helium Music Manager. Stop using time looking for the file on your computer or looking through CDS, vinyl records and tapes - instead, simply enjoy and explore your music! Helium Music Manager can replace the ripper, the player, tag editor and related software to audio your other.
Helium Music Manager...
</description></item><item><title>Download Calcpad 7.3.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 23 Aug 2025 00:38:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-calcpad-12576.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-calcpad-12576.html
</guid><description>
Calcpad is free software for mathematical and engineering calculations. It is a flexible and modern programmable calculator with Html report generator. Calcpad uses a simple programming language that is fast and easy to learn. It does not require any special programming skills, which makes it suitable for engineers without any computer programming background. You can create calculation notes simply by writing your formula and text, enclosed in 'quotation marks'.
The program includes...
</description></item><item><title>Download Boris FX Sequoia 2025.0.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 23 Aug 2025 00:37:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-magix-sequoia-12379.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-magix-sequoia-12379.html
</guid><description>
Sequoia is your go-to solution for professional audio production.
From the recording studio to the mastering desk – stability, seamless processing and innovative editing features are key for engineers around the world. Our partners, including Europe's most prominent broadcasters, rely on its scalable, flexible hardware integration and network.
Your Audio Production Toolkit
Sequoia's feature set covers every step of your daily production workflow. Check out the core functionality in...
</description></item><item><title>Download Synchredible 9.001</title><pubDate> Sat, 23 Aug 2025 00:36:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-synchredible-53.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-synchredible-53.html
</guid><description>
Synchredible is an easy to use tool to synchronize folders and files. It provides a wizard interface lets you set up the sync job, select files to exclude, schedule the job to execute automatically, and more.Additional features include support for network and external drives, check CRC32, and more.
Synchredible - synchronization of folders and files
Among other things, you can use the filter for the file type specific data synchronization according to the time or routine deletion of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Fort Firewall 3.19.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 23 Aug 2025 00:36:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fort-firewall-6439.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fort-firewall-6439.html
</guid><description>
Fort Firewall is a network security system that monitors and controls network traffic and goes based on predefined security rules. A firewall often establishes a barrier between a trusted internal network and untrusted external networks, such as the Internet.
Features of Fort Firewall
	Filter by network address, application group
	Support of representative characters in the name path name
	Application group speed limit
	Access Traffic Statistics
	Display bandwidth
	Based on the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Siemens FiberSIM 17.5.0 for NX 2306-2506 Series</title><pubDate> Sat, 23 Aug 2025 00:35:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-siemens-fibersim-8967.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-siemens-fibersim-8967.html
</guid><description>
Siemens FiberSIM is the world's leading composites product development software used by leading organizations including Bombardier Aerospace, General Motors and Nordex. The Fibersim software portfolio enables the concurrent design and manufacturing methods needed to design innovative, durable and lightweight composite products. Fibersim helps throughout the product development process from concept to implementation, including initial sizing requirements, detailed laminate definitions,...
</description></item><item><title>Download RarmaRadio Pro 2.77.7</title><pubDate> Sat, 23 Aug 2025 00:34:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rarmaradio-pro-789.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rarmaradio-pro-789.html
</guid><description>
RarmaRadio Pro is the professional version allows you to listen to and record radio stations from around the world. While listening to the favorite radio station, you can record anytime you want by RarmaRadio Pro. Browse through the radio stations or just select a random station and enjoy Internet radio! You have full control of his radio, allowing you to add or delete a station anytime you want. Need to play a station from another application then just enable global hotkeys and control it...
</description></item><item><title>Download RoboTask 10.5</title><pubDate> Sat, 23 Aug 2025 00:34:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-robotask-6157.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-robotask-6157.html
</guid><description>
RoboTask is software that allows you to automate any task combination on your computer, from just launching applications, checking your email, moving or backup files to upload or download, email and more. The program allows easy task to create simple tasks, as well as highly complex automation, involving the IF/ELSE statements that have conditions, loops, customization variables, and other advanced options.
Just a few minutes with RoboTask will give you a lot of ideas about how you can...
</description></item><item><title>Download QILING File Shredder 4.5.0 Build 20250818</title><pubDate> Fri, 22 Aug 2025 21:51:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qiling-file-shredder-14092.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qiling-file-shredder-14092.html
</guid><description>
Permanently wipe shared drives or data, remove sensitive data easily and efficiently. File Shredder provides powerful protection for your important information and privacy. Certified data erasure algorithms ensure your data cannot be recovered by others. High-speed wiping saves your precious time, and rarely takes up system resources.
Why use QILING File Shredder to erase data:
	File Shredder: Permanently erase and remove unnecessary files from your computer after recovery
	Hard Drive...
</description></item><item><title>Download QILING Deep Data Recovery 4.5.0 Build 20250814</title><pubDate> Fri, 22 Aug 2025 21:43:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qiling-deep-data-recovery-14091.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qiling-deep-data-recovery-14091.html
</guid><description>
Mistakenly deleted, formatted drive or inaccessible RAW drive? Don't worry, Deep Data Recovery software will help you quickly scan and recover deleted and lost files. QILING Deep Data Recovery is a reliable data recovery software for Windows, designed to help users effectively recover deleted, lost or inaccessible files from various storage devices such as hard drives, USB drives, SD cards and digital cameras. The software can recover a wide range of files, including photos, videos, audio...
</description></item><item><title>Download Boris FX Vita 2025</title><pubDate> Fri, 22 Aug 2025 21:33:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-boris-fx-vita-14090.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-boris-fx-vita-14090.html
</guid><description>
Boris FX Vita is a collection of virtual instruments built into music software products. Vita instruments include a variety of sounds such as Analog Synth, Jazz Drums, Orchestral Ensemble, Century Keys and Space Pad. These instruments allow users to play loops and samples as melodic or rhythmic elements, making Vita a versatile sampler plugin in the ecosystem.
Key Instrument Features
	Play any loop as an instrument using the Vita sampler.
	Integrate with a MIDI keyboard or pad for...
</description></item></channel></rss>