<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 13:47:27 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 13:47:27 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download InnoExtractor Ultra 2026 v11.2.0.157</title><pubDate> Mon, 17 Nov 2025 16:47:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-innoextractor-plus-4009.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-innoextractor-plus-4009.html
</guid><description>
InnoExtractor Plus is a handy lightweight but strong will allow you to use technology InnoUnp to easily extract the installer Inno Setup. Using this tool, you will be able to explore the content and the internal structure of installers and extract them to a folder on the local drive or on the storage device mobile without running the file setup. InnoExtractor Plus comes with graphical interface simple and user friendly, allowing you to easily open the installed just by drag and drop...
</description></item><item><title>Download Monkeys Audio 11.83</title><pubDate> Mon, 17 Nov 2025 16:46:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-monkeys-audio-949.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-monkeys-audio-949.html
</guid><description>
Monkey\'s Audio is software that compresses digital music without loss of quality. Supports high quality WAV files and CD ripping. Monkeys Audio will compress .wav tracks into .ape files to reduce their size without loss of sound quality, decompress .ape, convert files, check file integrity and manage tags.
Unlike traditional methods like MP3 and OGG, which permanently remove quality to save space, Monkey\'s Audio only creates perfect copies with the same sound quality as the originals....
</description></item><item><title>Download Antivirus Removal Tool 2025.11 (v.1)</title><pubDate> Mon, 17 Nov 2025 16:46:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-antivirus-removal-tool-4936.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-antivirus-removal-tool-4936.html
</guid><description>
Antivirus Removal Tool is removal tool virus was designed to detect and remove completely software anti-virus. It will help you determine the current setting and the past, and it will give you the uninstall specialized official. They are designed by the manufacturer program anti-virus to delete completely all the files, drivers, services, and registration records were left by the programs that they create.
The features of the Antivirus Removal Tool
	Determine program anti-virus is...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sandboxie 5.71.7</title><pubDate> Mon, 17 Nov 2025 16:45:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sandboxie-818.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sandboxie-818.html
</guid><description>
Sandboxie software to browse the Web securely while still keeping all the functionality your browser for content works against harmful agents such as sanbox up your computer. You may not know, when you browse the Web, the change will occur with the system of your computer. When you use Sandboxie, the software will protect the web browser of their own.
Sandboxie - web protection, safe browsing
The main features of Sandboxie
Stay safe on the Internet with Sandboxie
	Run the program in...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sandboxie Plus 1.16.7</title><pubDate> Mon, 17 Nov 2025 16:45:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sandboxie-plus-4962.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sandboxie-plus-4962.html
</guid><description>
Sandboxie Plus is an application version of the open source project on Github, equipped with software to protect your information while browsing the web or running valuable software. doubt. Web browsing, downloading or running software can affect system security. To prevent this from happening, a high user experience and strong layers of protection are needed to prevent malware from spreading to the system. For example, by opening an unknown application, malware in flash memory can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Scale Photo Up 2.0.10</title><pubDate> Mon, 17 Nov 2025 16:45:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-scale-photo-up-13763.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-scale-photo-up-13763.html
</guid><description>
Are you tired of low-resolution, pixelated footage that stifles your creativity? Say goodbye to grainy memories and say hello to Scale Photo Up – groundbreaking AI software that doubles resolution, enhances detail, and smooths out imperfections in your photos and videos with stunning clarity!
Why Scale Photo Up?
	Upscale 2x – No loss of quality! – Turn blurry, low-resolution photos and videos into sharp, high-resolution masterpieces. Perfect for breathing new life into old...
</description></item><item><title>Download iToolab UnlockGo 6.3.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 17 Nov 2025 16:44:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-itoolab-unlockgo-5936.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-itoolab-unlockgo-5936.html
</guid><description>
iToolab UnlockGo is software that allows you to easily cross your iPhone ' s password and have full access to the device. It removes all types of passwords easily including 4-digit code, 6-digit code, custom code, letter and number, Touch ID or Face ID.
The opening process is very simple with UnlockGo that anyone can unlock the iCloud code or lock it in three simple steps without requiring the expertise.
The features of iToolab UnlockGo
	Deleting 4-digit code/6 digits, Touch ID &amp;amp;...
</description></item><item><title>Download Chaos Vantage 3.0.3</title><pubDate> Mon, 17 Nov 2025 16:44:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chaos-vantage-6178.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chaos-vantage-6178.html
</guid><description>
Explore and interact with enough 3D detail in real time. Chaos Vantage is even more outstanding than the V-Ray even though you ' re using the V-Ray version. Artists and designers only need to pull and drop their V-Ray (.vrscene) scenes to discover them immediately in real time-without taking the time to optimize the geometry, opening up the UV package. When in Vantage, the user has the freedom to define and recall views and scenes, create a role in the role and communicate better than...
</description></item><item><title>Download Revive Faces 2.0.10</title><pubDate> Mon, 17 Nov 2025 16:43:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-revive-faces-13762.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-revive-faces-13762.html
</guid><description>
Have you ever looked at an old photo or video and wished you could see those faces clearly again? Time, blurriness, and pixels shouldn't steal the smiles, glances, or stories of the people you love. With Revive Faces, our breakthrough AI-powered restoration software, blurry, smudged, and pixelated faces can now shine with stunning clarity—as if they were taken yesterday.
Why Restore Faces?
	See the unseen again – Our advanced AI not only sharpens images, but also recreates lost...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinCatalog 2024.15.0.1116</title><pubDate> Mon, 17 Nov 2025 16:43:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wincatalog-615.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wincatalog-615.html
</guid><description>
WinCatalog 2018 is a software cataloguer multi-function for the disk, file, folder, and any objects not files. Not always easy to track the location of a number of files in your computer, especially if you have a huge collection of CD and DVD. If you are one of those users, then surely there will be appropriate tools to work with such a task. WinCatalog is a software utility designed to help you find documents and data from your computer by building an index that allows you immediate...
</description></item><item><title>Download Autodesk Revit 2026.4 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Mon, 17 Nov 2025 16:43:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-autodesk-revit-0002-6809.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-autodesk-revit-0002-6809.html
</guid><description>
Autodesk Revit is a software package for computer-aided design that implements the principles of Building Information Modeling (BIM). Autodesk Revit is aimed at architects, designers and design engineers, providing the ability to 3D model building elements and draw 2D design elements, Create custom objects, collaborate on a project, from concept to release drawings and working specifications.
Autodesk Revit provides a high degree of cooperation between experts from different fields and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Luxion KeyShot Studio Enteprise 2025.3 v14.2.0.211</title><pubDate> Mon, 17 Nov 2025 16:42:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-luxion-keyshot-enteprise-10602.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-luxion-keyshot-enteprise-10602.html
</guid><description>
Luxion KeyShot Enteprise is a popular computer program used for 3D visualization and visualization. It is designed primarily to display 3D models, making them look as realistic as possible. KeyShot is commonly used in a variety of industries, including product design, automotive design, architecture, and more.
Overall, KeyShot is known for its ease of use and ability to produce high-quality, realistic renderings with minimal setup and configuration. This is a valuable tool for designers...
</description></item><item><title>Download Let It Be Light 2.0.10</title><pubDate> Mon, 17 Nov 2025 16:41:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-let-it-be-light-13761.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-let-it-be-light-13761.html
</guid><description>
Let It Be Light – Illuminate the Invisible, Unleash Infinite Content! Tired of dark, underexposed footage that could be your next viral hit? Say hello to Let It Be Light – revolutionary AI image and video processing software that turns dull clips into beautiful, well-lit masterpieces!
Why Let It Be Light?
	Unlock Hidden Content – ​​Turn dark, grainy, or underexposed footage from film, old archives, or social media into crisp, bright, and useful content. No more discarding...
</description></item><item><title>Download Watchdog Anti-Malware Premium / Business 4.3.467</title><pubDate> Mon, 17 Nov 2025 16:39:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-watchdog-anti-malware-7110.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-watchdog-anti-malware-7110.html
</guid><description>
Watchdog Anti-Malware is an anti-malware with many highly rated tools to help keep your computer safe. Watchdog Anti-Malware will help you with Advanced Malware Detection and Removal, Browser Hijacker Removal, Effective Rootkit and Bootkit Detection and Removal, Real-Time Protection, Anti-ransomware Protection Module.
Watchdog Anti-Malware is extremely optimized and lightweight. Software engineers designed it to work efficiently without having to tweak confusing settings. Just start...
</description></item><item><title>Download KS DB Merge Tools for Cross-DBMS 1.16.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 17 Nov 2025 16:39:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ks-db-merge-tools-for-cross-dbms-12825.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ks-db-merge-tools-for-cross-dbms-12825.html
</guid><description>
Designed specifically for comparing two different databases, KS DB Merge Tools for Cross-DBMS provides a fast way to run comparisons in parallel and ensure the databases are synchronized. It can run side-by-side comparisons of schemas, data, and programming objects, highlighting differences, so you can easily synchronize two databases.
Key Features
	Compare both schema and data across different DBMS
	Quick filters to show all/new/changed
	Merge table data changes in both...
</description></item><item><title>Download AntiPlagiarism.NET 4.151</title><pubDate> Mon, 17 Nov 2025 16:38:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-antiplagiarismnet-2457.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-antiplagiarismnet-2457.html
</guid><description>
AntiPlagiarism NET is software to check the originality of some given text, most people find a section of text on the Internet, often the search engines quickly put out the answer to this question. Sometimes the results can be wrong, because not all results are accurate, a hundred percent. Fortunately, there are other solutions to the problem, for example, AntiPlagiarism.NET it can help you determine the originality of some given text. Application to operate correctly, you need to install...
</description></item><item><title>Download WakeMeOnLan 1.95</title><pubDate> Mon, 17 Nov 2025 16:38:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wakemeonlan-4543.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wakemeonlan-4543.html
</guid><description>
WakeMeOnLan is a small tool and portable to send the alarm signal (WOL) to the remote computer via the local network, thus allowing you to control them. This utility allows you to easily turn on one or more computers remotely by sending packet Wake-on-LAN (WOL) to the remote computer. When your computer is turned on, WakeMeOnLan allows you to scan the network and collect the MAC addresses of all your computers, and save the list of computers into a file. Later on, when your computer is off...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinTools.one Professional / Home 25.11.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 16 Nov 2025 23:43:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wintoolsone-10808.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wintoolsone-10808.html
</guid><description>
WinTools.one is a program designed to help both regular and advanced users as well as computer engineers fine-tune the MS Windows operating system. It allows you to increase the performance of the operating system, maintain its performance at a high level, fix operating system errors, free up space on the computer's hard drive and control the operation of installed programs. In addition, the program allows you to store and protect your secret and confidential information, as well as work...
</description></item><item><title>Download Allavsoft Video Downloader Converter 3.28.5.9439</title><pubDate> Sun, 16 Nov 2025 23:43:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allavsoft-video-downloader-converter-248.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allavsoft-video-downloader-converter-248.html
</guid><description>
Allavsoft Video Downloader Converter software supports download movies, music videos, playlist, sport videos from video sharing website for free like Facebook, Youtube and over 100 video sharing sites.
Allavsoft is many users favorite thanks to the combined features simultaneous transmission of multiple videos and speed limit download video. Besides, the program also supports pause and resume data transmission, to help you interfere with the process of transmitting download data to...
</description></item><item><title>Download reaConverter Pro 8.0.156</title><pubDate> Sun, 16 Nov 2025 23:42:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html
</guid><description>
reaConverter Pro is software image processing feature with batch conversion and image editing periodically becomes simple. eaConverter also provide command line utilities allow you to process images automatically, thus helping you shorten the time for other work.
reaConverter Pro integrated powerful tool of Uber with many great features. It provides advanced solutions to process and adjust images. Management of the conversion process the base image with the latest version of...
</description></item><item><title>Download AllMapSoft Google Hybrid Maps Downloader 8.443</title><pubDate> Sun, 16 Nov 2025 23:42:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-google-hybrid-maps-downloader-6479.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-google-hybrid-maps-downloader-6479.html
</guid><description>
AllMapSoft Google Hybrid Maps Downloader  is a tool that can automatically download a Google combined map image to your PC. It can download small squares and save them to your hard disk. Once downloaded, you can view the map offline with its Maps Viewer tool, or you can combine the small images into one large map image. If you want to make your own city map, it is very useful for you.
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Media Encoder 2025 v25.6.0.098 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Sun, 16 Nov 2025 23:41:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-0010-adobe-media-encoder-1360.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-0010-adobe-media-encoder-1360.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Media Encoder 2024 is a professional audio and video converter that allows you to encode audio and video files into various distribution formats for applications different uses and audiences. Such video and audio formats are characterized by a high degree of compression. By downloading this program on taiwebs.com, you can export videos in formats supported by various devices, from DVD players and websites to mobile phones, portable media players and High Definition and High...
</description></item><item><title>Download Reportizer 6.6.1.405</title><pubDate> Sun, 16 Nov 2025 23:40:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reportizer-5205.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reportizer-5205.html
</guid><description>
Reportizer is a tools report database. Easily create, modify, and print reports database. Allows to manage collection reports. Support database BDE or ADO. Tested on dBase (DBF), Paradox (DB), Text (TXT), the values are separated by commas (CSV), Oracle, Interbase, Microsoft Access, Microsoft Excel, SQL Server, Visual FoxPro, MySQL, PostgreQuery, HTML.
The design reports visually. Reports can be edited in the report design, intuitive and convenient with the toolbar and powerful tool. For...
</description></item><item><title>Download AllMapSoft Google Maps Terrain Downloader 7.203</title><pubDate> Sun, 16 Nov 2025 23:40:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-google-maps-terrain-downloader-6476.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-google-maps-terrain-downloader-6476.html
</guid><description>
AllMapSoft Google Maps Terrain Downloader  is a tool that can automatically download Google topographic map images to your PC. It can download small squares and save them to your hard disk. Once downloaded, you can view the map offline with its Maps Viewer tool, or you can combine the small images into one large map image. If you want to make your own city map, it is very useful for you.
</description></item><item><title>Download ArmorTools Professional / Home 25.11.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 16 Nov 2025 23:40:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-armortools-7726.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-armortools-7726.html
</guid><description>
ArmorTools is a set of tools that extend the capabilities of the MS Windows operating system in the field of security and protection of user confidential information. ArmorTools allows you to create secure virtual disks encrypted with AES128/AES256 algorithms, encrypting files and folder contents using any file as a password.
ArmorTools erases the user's work traces on the computer, deletes the history of accessing websites, deletes confidential information without the possibility of...
</description></item></channel></rss>