<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 17:34:44 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 17:34:44 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download pdfFactory Pro 9.15</title><pubDate> Wed, 27 Aug 2025 18:07:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdffactory-pro-277.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdffactory-pro-277.html
</guid><description>
pdfFactory Pro is software to create PDF files according to standards in a simple and secure documents secure. pdfFactory Pro on taiwebs.com that support encryption (40 or 128bit) and control access to the PDF file.
pdfFactory Pro has all the features of pdfFactory and adds bookmarks, job order, title a letter and the email function automatically. Only pdfFactory allows printing to paper or PDF without printing twice. Acrobat is not needed for the printing. Increases the convenience of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare Filmora 14.9.3.14445</title><pubDate> Wed, 27 Aug 2025 18:07:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-filmora-2025-31.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-filmora-2025-31.html
</guid><description>
In early November 2020 Wondershare came up with a new version called Wondershare Filmora 13 with two new ways to edit: Action Cam Tool (Lens distortion correction, Clean up your audio, Control speed new) and Instant Cutter (Cut or merge clips quickly, Export instantly).
Wondershare Filmora 13  allows you to add your favorite tracks to your videos, creating a more stylish, romantic film reel, with a rich music library besides Users can manually add their favorite songs to the editing...
</description></item><item><title>Download IObit Uninstaller Pro 15.0.0.5</title><pubDate> Wed, 27 Aug 2025 18:06:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iobit-uninstaller-pro-339.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iobit-uninstaller-pro-339.html
</guid><description>
IObit Uninstaller Pro is software to delete programs not needed easily even when Windows "Remove Programs" operation not successful. IObit Uninstaller Pro will uninstall the app Windows, browser toolbars, software packages and plug-ins added. It comes with a scan function is powerful and a tool, Force Uninstall, both of which help to easily and completely remove the app stubborn, and the excess useless, to release more disk space.
With IObit Uninstaller Pro you will have peace of mind...
</description></item><item><title>Download Red Eye Pilot 3.14.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 27 Aug 2025 18:05:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-red-eye-pilot-6308.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-red-eye-pilot-6308.html
</guid><description>
Red Eye Pilot is this red eye removal program that allows you to adjust the field and brightness, and watch the results in real time. The program holds the structure of the students. With an automated mode of editing, which needs to adjust the brightness and contrast, you can adjust these parameters, you can use the editor with a tuning size to clear the editing effects, flip or rotate images at different angles, such as changing size or cutting files.
Red Eye Pilot can be used as a...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft Office 2021-2024 Professional Plus VL (64-bit) 2508 Build 19127.20154</title><pubDate> Wed, 27 Aug 2025 18:05:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-office-2021-6670.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-office-2021-6670.html
</guid><description>
Since the end of February 2021, Microsoft has announced two new versions of Office 2021 including: Office 2021 and Office LTSC. Reportedly, Office 2021 is the next version of Office 2019, promising to bring users a better experience in the new Word, Excel or PowerPoint tools.
With each office user, the Microsoft Office toolkit is essential and indispensable software in the job. Microsoft Office has undergone numerous editions from Office 2010, 2013, 2016, 2019 to Microsoft 365 developed...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Downloader 9.16.5</title><pubDate> Wed, 27 Aug 2025 18:04:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html
</guid><description>
YTD Youtube Downloader is an application that reliable and intuitive, allowing you to quickly download YouTube videos and save them to your computer. You can also convert the media files to the format desired video or extract audio streams and save separately. YTD Youtube Downloader lets you save your favorite clips of yourself from Youtube, Facebook, Vimeo and Dailymotion to your desktop. The software supports URLS from many web site hosting, multimedia and allows you to download desired...
</description></item><item><title>Download FinePrint 12.15</title><pubDate> Wed, 27 Aug 2025 18:04:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fineprint-276.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fineprint-276.html
</guid><description>
FinePrint is a software support you work in text saves paper and increases the lifespan of your printer. FinePrint is a software connected printer, you can print 4 or 8 pages file on the computer on a page of paper that still ensure the font is clear, easy to read.
With FinePrint works for you, the incidents of printing annoyances will disappear. Below are just some examples of incidents in which FinePrint can fix. Read more part of our Business for the benefit of the FinePrint in the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Lightroom 8.5.1 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Wed, 27 Aug 2025 18:03:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-photoshop-lightroom-0001-5334.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-photoshop-lightroom-0001-5334.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Photoshop Lightroom is the most professional version completely redesigned and based on a performance architecture that is better responsive to ever expanding galleries, while also featuring unrivaled processing tools with noise reduction and sharpening tools to get the best picture quality. Adobe Photoshop Lightroom gives the basic ideas of software produced by Adobe in 2002, as one of the developers and gradually improving and the features of the ImageReady software are included.
...
</description></item><item><title>Download Executor 2.0.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 27 Aug 2025 18:02:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-executor-271.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-executor-271.html
</guid><description>
Executor for windows is a software alternative premium customization features for the Windows "Run" and "Search Programs". When you press WIN + Z and provides the search results instant, as-you-type for any keywords you enter. By default, Executor will index all the Desktop and Start Menu and you can easily expand the search range by adding the folder location additional.
Executor for windows
The program comes with a list of commands built in which you can use to quickly access many...
</description></item><item><title>Download HFS: HTTP File Server (version 3) 0.57.13</title><pubDate> Wed, 27 Aug 2025 18:02:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hfs-http-file-server-11851.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hfs-http-file-server-11851.html
</guid><description>
HFS is a web file server to run on your computer. Share a folder or even a file thanks to the virtual file system. Essentially, this application turns your computer into an HTTP server and all users who want to connect and download files can do so by loading a simple website in their browser. HFS includes many configuration settings, so you can basically change each part of the application, starting with how users download files and ending with the appearance of the created website.
HFS...
</description></item><item><title>Download OneCommander Pro 3.100.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 27 Aug 2025 18:01:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-one-commander-4232.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-one-commander-4232.html
</guid><description>
One Commander is a file manager for Microsoft Windows with function improved user interface and navigation experience, system file and manipulating the files. Utilities use the tree view to sort the folder, subfolders, and files your, make sure that the current location of you always clear. It supports multiple tabs, allowing you to easily switch between them and access the folder you need.
One Commander - a filemanager for Windows
Depending on the format of the files, some files can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tiny11 24H2 Build 26100.4946</title><pubDate> Wed, 27 Aug 2025 18:00:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tiny11-8649.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tiny11-8649.html
</guid><description>
Tiny11 is a compact Windows operating system based on Windows 11 Pro 22H2, Tiny11 has everything you need for a comfortable, hassle-free computing experience. cumbersome and messy like a standard Windows installation. The operating system requires only 8GB of disk space and 2GB of RAM, and requires no TPM (Trusted Platform Module) and Secure Boot support.
The main goal of Tiny11 is to extend the reach of systems that can access Windows 11. The custom edition can run on any system...
</description></item><item><title>Download EaseUS Fixo Technician 3.8.0 Build 20250825</title><pubDate> Wed, 27 Aug 2025 18:00:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-fixo-9814.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-fixo-9814.html
</guid><description>
Video is corrupted or inaccessible after power failure and sudden blackout, whole system crash, update failure, wrong file handling or some other reason? EaseUS Fixo allows you to repair many different video file formats including MOV, MP4, M2TS, MKV, MTS, 3GP, etc. easier no matter how broken it is.
It can intelligently and intelligently repair damaged and damaged photos from computers or other external storage devices such as USB flash drives, memory cards, SD cards, digital cameras...
</description></item><item><title>Download NVIDIA App 11.0.5.245</title><pubDate> Wed, 27 Aug 2025 17:59:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nvidia-app-12646.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nvidia-app-12646.html
</guid><description>
NVIDIA App is an indispensable companion for PC gamers and creators. Make sure your PC is always updated with the latest NVIDIA drivers and technology. Optimize your games and apps with the new unified GPU control center, capture your favorite moments with powerful recording tools through in-game overlays, and explore new tools and features. Latest NVIDIA software.
The program consists of two main parts
	Game Ready Drivers: GeForce Game Ready Drivers are fine-tuned in collaboration...
</description></item><item><title>Download GiliSoft Audio Recorder Pro 13.7</title><pubDate> Wed, 27 Aug 2025 17:58:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-audio-recorder-pro-855.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-audio-recorder-pro-855.html
</guid><description>
GiliSoft Audio Recorder Pro is software perfect recorder to record audio and microphone of your computer to AAC, AC3, AIFF, AMR, AU, FLAC, M4A, M4B, M4R, MKA, MP2, MP3, OGG, RA, VOC , WAV Files or WMA files on Windows 7/8. Recording the sound that goes through your sound card is not at all a difficult task, but GiliSoft Audio Recorder Pro promises to make everything a lot easier, even for those who do not have computer knowledge advanced.
GiliSoft Audio Recorder Pro - audio recording...
</description></item><item><title>Download CapCut PC 6.9.0.2786 / 7.0.0.2832 Beta 4</title><pubDate> Wed, 27 Aug 2025 17:58:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capcut-pc-9995.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capcut-pc-9995.html
</guid><description>
CapCut PC is a simple video editing tool that you can freely use anywhere. You can create videos on your browser, desktop and laptop, or on your phone. Versatile editing, magical AI tools, team collaboration, and built-in assets. Create videos in a whole new way.
You can edit videos based on editing the timeline, in the process you can add different elements and effects to the video to give the best effect to your work. It is a simple and intuitive set of editing tools and effects that...
</description></item><item><title>Download Google Chrome 139.0.7258.155</title><pubDate> Wed, 27 Aug 2025 17:57:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-chrome-1012.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-chrome-1012.html
</guid><description>
Google Chrome web browser is the most used today. Support surf the web, listen to music, watch movies, play web game effective no jerky lag with the internet connection stable. When you are surfing the web or performing an important task, whether it is operation big or small, work or entertainment, then Chrome has the smart features and the speed you need to make, create and explore on the net.
The latest version of Google Chrome is the third 114. But we are providing for users Google...
</description></item><item><title>Download All About PDF 3.2034</title><pubDate> Wed, 27 Aug 2025 17:56:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-all-about-pdf-3617.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-all-about-pdf-3617.html
</guid><description>
All About PDF is an application that edit, merge, split PDF file effective for the office work. Besides, All About PDF also lets you convert them to other formats using the versatile app, intuitive and flexible this.
All-About-PDF is a Windows application, fast and powerful built to take advantage of multiple processor cores of the computer to handle PDF quickly. With the licensing of permanent, simple, as well as the option of volume licensing to deploy across the organization,...
</description></item><item><title>Download MiniTool ShadowMaker Business Deluxe WINPE 4.8.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 27 Aug 2025 17:56:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minitool-shadowmaker-pro-5385.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minitool-shadowmaker-pro-5385.html
</guid><description>
MiniTool ShadowMaker Pro is a program that provides easy file backup, system backup, and disk / partition backup for Windows users. It comes with clear interface and works quickly. This is an all-in-one data protection and disaster recovery solution for PC. With a backup, you can restore data in the event of a disaster, like system crash, hard drive failure, etc. None of the settings or features seem difficult to work. It also allows you to create a bootable medium to restore the system to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Zortam Mp3 Media Studio Pro 33.20</title><pubDate> Wed, 27 Aug 2025 17:55:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zortam-mp3-media-studio-pro-135.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zortam-mp3-media-studio-pro-135.html
</guid><description>
Zortam Mp3 Media Studio Pro brings you rich processing tools music includes extract and convert music from CD to Mp3 format, edit, music cards, music download....You can also create discs CD high-quality music, with Zortam Mp3 Media Studio search music files duplicated to remove them from the system, rename music files, switch back and forth between formats.
Zortam Mp3 Media Studio Pro is rated as perfect software in the processing of the MP3 files on the computer. First of all, you can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Bforartists 4.5.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 27 Aug 2025 17:55:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bforartists-7643.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bforartists-7643.html
</guid><description>
Bforartists is a complete, free and open source 3D suite for creating CG content. It gives you the full 3D art pipeline for creating game graphics, pre-rendered movies, and stills. From modeling, sculpting, texturing, design, animation, rendering, to post processing. The main goal of Bforartists is to provide a refined graphical user interface and better usability. This means a complete shift in usage philosophy away from hotkey-focused usage towards an intuitive and user-friendly...
</description></item><item><title>Download Dropbox 231.4.5770</title><pubDate> Wed, 27 Aug 2025 17:54:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dropbox-1313.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dropbox-1313.html
</guid><description>
Dropbox on taiwebs.com is free tool, the data synchronization across multiple PC become easier than never before: after installation, all what you have to do is enter your name, email address and password before opening the folder My Dropbox. If you install the software on a different computer, Dropbox will reflect the content of the online storage. So you exchange any data between the different computer is connected to Dropbox account. In addition the client is installed on the computer,...
</description></item><item><title>Download RedNotebook 2.40</title><pubDate> Wed, 27 Aug 2025 17:47:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rednotebook-2884.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rednotebook-2884.html
</guid><description>
RedNotebook is a note-taking app for free. It allows you to format, tag and search your entries. You can also add images, links and templates can customize, check the spelling of your notes and export into plain text, HTML or LaTeX. RedNotebook is free software under the GPL.
RedNotebook - Write notes, edit text
Features of RedNotebook
	Use #hashtags
	Format your text bold , italic or underline
	Insert images, files and links to the website
	Links and email addresses are recognized...
</description></item><item><title>Download Scooter Beyond Compare 5.1.4.31268</title><pubDate> Wed, 27 Aug 2025 17:46:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-scooter-beyond-compare-2649.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-scooter-beyond-compare-2649.html
</guid><description>
Scooter Beyond Compare is a powerful tool to compare quickly and easily the files and folders. This program provides you with a full report on work done so you can compare the complete data on the file, folder, folder with speed and file size, very fast and incredible, time changes on the file as well as the compared bytes Do byte this information. With the strong command of this program, you can merge the changes, synchronize files, create a report to record.
Scooter Beyond Compare -...
</description></item><item><title>Download CPUID HWMonitor Free 1.59</title><pubDate> Wed, 27 Aug 2025 17:46:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cpuid-hwmonitor-free-8486.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cpuid-hwmonitor-free-8486.html
</guid><description>
CPUID HWMonitor Free is a free system monitoring software that allows users to monitor various hardware components in their computer, such as CPU, GPU, memory memory and temperature. It can be used to monitor performance and troubleshoot problems with the system. The software is compatible with the Windows operating system and can be downloaded from the CPUID website.
Features of CPUID HWMonitor Free
	Real-time monitoring of various hardware components such as CPU, GPU, memory and...
</description></item></channel></rss>