<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 16:02:58 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 16:02:58 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Google Chrome 144.0.7559.133</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 17:03:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-chrome-1012.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-chrome-1012.html
</guid><description>
Google Chrome web browser is the most used today. Support surf the web, listen to music, watch movies, play web game effective no jerky lag with the internet connection stable. When you are surfing the web or performing an important task, whether it is operation big or small, work or entertainment, then Chrome has the smart features and the speed you need to make, create and explore on the net.
The latest version of Google Chrome is the third 114. But we are providing for users Google...
</description></item><item><title>Download CapCut PC 8.0.1.3366</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 17:03:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capcut-pc-9995.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capcut-pc-9995.html
</guid><description>
CapCut PC is a simple video editing tool that you can freely use anywhere. You can create videos on your browser, desktop and laptop, or on your phone. Versatile editing, magical AI tools, team collaboration, and built-in assets. Create videos in a whole new way.
You can edit videos based on editing the timeline, in the process you can add different elements and effects to the video to give the best effect to your work. It is a simple and intuitive set of editing tools and effects that...
</description></item><item><title>Download Find.Same.Images.OK 5.91</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 17:02:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-find-same-images-ok-113.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-find-same-images-ok-113.html
</guid><description>
Find.Same.Images.OK lets find the images identical or similar in the folder of you, even if they were to rotate, change size or change.
Just select one or more folders that you want the program to scan and it will return a list of all the duplicate images or very similar, as indicated by the percent the same and the preview is built.Then, you can select images from the list and then copy, move or delete them.
Find.Same.Images.OK
In addition, there are other options smart option allows...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mozilla Firefox 147.0.3</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 16:59:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-firefox-quantum-501.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-firefox-quantum-501.html
</guid><description>
Firefox Quantum is a web browser independently provide the tabbed browsing combined with numerous handy features like pop-up blocker, Bookmarks, direct (integrated RSS), password manager, and more. Functionality can be extended with dozens of plugins available for free (extensions).
Firefox Quantum are interface completely new, beautiful, neat, minimalistic and delicate, eats less RAM to 30% compared with the old version and solve the condition consuming capacity
Firefox can import all...
</description></item><item><title>Download GoldWave 7.04</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 16:58:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-goldwave-1577.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-goldwave-1577.html
</guid><description>
GoldWave is a sound editor comprehensive digital be most appreciated. GoldWave ideal for those who work with sound to edit CD, restore, archive, speech analysis, radio and TV, Java and web pages, games or just to entertain. You can use it to do everything from reply elaborately message to content audio CD professional, high quality.
GoldWave - edit digital audio
The work that GoldWave done:
	Play, edit, mix, and analyze audio
	Record audio from cassettes, vinyl records, radio, etc....
</description></item><item><title>Download Cockos REAPER 7.61</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 16:58:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cockos-reaper-889.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cockos-reaper-889.html
</guid><description>
Cockos REAPER is a powerful software for for windows, chp lets you record, arrange, edit, and display the audio waveform multi-track. Cockos REAPER offers an extensive feature set includes many effects and a sample project. REAPER supports ASIO, Kernel Streaming, WaveOut, and DirectSound for playback and recording. It reads the files in WAV, OGG and MP3 files and records WAV files. You can arrange any number of items in any number of tracks and use plug-in sound processing (DirectX and...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter 3.9.18 (0202)</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 16:49:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-to-mp3-converter-1744.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-to-mp3-converter-1744.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter is the software support download youtube video and convert video to mp3 format fast and most simple. MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter allows you download and convert videos from YouTube and other websites to MP3 format by pasting the YouTube URL into the application. When you paste the URL, the program will display thumbnails for videos and you have the option to customize the title information, artist and album before you begin the process of...
</description></item><item><title>Download VovSoft Text to MP3 Converter 4.4</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 16:49:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-text-to-mp3-converter-6717.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-text-to-mp3-converter-6717.html
</guid><description>
VovSoft Text to MP3 Converter is free software that easily converts your text to speech, supports e-learning, presentations, YouTube videos, and increases accessibility . Text can be exported as MP3 and WAV files. This program uses the pre-installed Microsoft SAPI Text-to-Speech (TTS) engine to generate speech.
VovSoft Text to MP3 Converter gives you options for used voice engine, as well as output audio format. Two main options give users the choice of increased quality (WAV) or a more...
</description></item><item><title>Download Dropbox 240.4.8609</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 16:48:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dropbox-1313.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dropbox-1313.html
</guid><description>
Dropbox on taiwebs.com is free tool, the data synchronization across multiple PC become easier than never before: after installation, all what you have to do is enter your name, email address and password before opening the folder My Dropbox. If you install the software on a different computer, Dropbox will reflect the content of the online storage. So you exchange any data between the different computer is connected to Dropbox account. In addition the client is installed on the computer,...
</description></item><item><title>Download dbForge Studio for Oracle Enterprise 2025.3.61</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 16:48:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbforge-studio-for-oracle-enterprise-14049.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbforge-studio-for-oracle-enterprise-14049.html
</guid><description>
dbForge Studio for Oracle is a trusted integrated development environment (IDE) for Oracle SQL developers. This database solution speeds up PL/SQL coding, synchronizes data between different Oracle servers, and automates the process of managing schema changes during development. The solution is equipped with a graphical user interface (GUI) and versatile data editing tools, making it easy to manage both internal and external data.
Key features of the studio include a PL/SQL coding...
</description></item><item><title>Download Scooter Beyond Compare 5.2.0.31866 Beta</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 16:47:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-scooter-beyond-compare-2649.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-scooter-beyond-compare-2649.html
</guid><description>
Scooter Beyond Compare is a powerful tool to compare quickly and easily the files and folders. This program provides you with a full report on work done so you can compare the complete data on the file, folder, folder with speed and file size, very fast and incredible, time changes on the file as well as the compared bytes Do byte this information. With the strong command of this program, you can merge the changes, synchronize files, create a report to record.
Scooter Beyond Compare -...
</description></item><item><title>Download Python 3.14.3</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 16:42:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-python-4355.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-python-4355.html
</guid><description>
Python is a programming language high-level for the purpose of programming multi-function, due to Guido van Rossum created and first launched in 1991. Python is designed with strong advantages is easy to read, easy to learn and easy to remember. Python is a language can form very bright, clear structure, convenient for new people to learn programming. Python fully create a dynamic and user mechanisms to allocate the memory automatically; so it is similar to Perl, Ruby, Scheme, Smalltalk,...
</description></item><item><title>Download WordPress 6.9.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 16:41:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wordpress-2340.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wordpress-2340.html
</guid><description>
WordPress is a publishing system blog written in the programming language PHP and use MySQL database. WordPress is a descendant official of b2/cafelog, developed by Michel Valdrighi. The name WordPress was suggested by Christine Selleck, a friend of the main developer Matt Mullenweg.
WordPress - open source website
Must say teeth WordPress source code is part website Blog today. Simply because the way to use it is downright simple. You just need to download this source code on, Then...
</description></item><item><title>Download Prey Basic 1.13.25</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 16:41:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-prey-5347.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-prey-5347.html
</guid><description>
Prey is free software that allows you to track and find your laptop, phone and tablet whenever stolen or missing - easily and all in one place. It's open source, lightweight, offering you full remote control, 24/7. You can quickly find out what the thief looks, what he is doing on your device and where he is actually hiding using GPS or WiFi geolocation. It's payback time.
Basically, you install a small agent in your PC or phone that will silently wait for the remote signal to wake up and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Syncovery Premium 11.12.7.161</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 16:40:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncovery-pro-enterprise-232.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncovery-pro-enterprise-232.html
</guid><description>
Syncovery Pro Enterprise is a great application used to back up data and to synchronize personal computers, servers, laptops, notepads and storage online. The software comes with support for FTP and secure FTP servers, SSH, WebDAV, Amazon S3, http, update the part file, ZIP compression, data encryption, and schedule automatic backups.
Syncovery Pro Enterprise have the ability to freely select files and folders across the whole folder hierarchy in tree view and supports email...
</description></item><item><title>Download BitRecover PST Converter Wizard 26.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 16:39:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pst-converter-wizard-01en-809.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pst-converter-wizard-01en-809.html
</guid><description>
BitRecover PST Converter Wizard software is the safe conversion of Outlook PST file to Gmail, Thunderbird, Windows Live Mail, Apple Mail and many popular file formats other than the attachments are retained. PST Converter is developed with the perfect combination between the friendliness and reliability of the user, allows to save data file PST in desired format. It securely transfers the contact to PST, task, calendar, notes, etc. without changing the initial information and the format of...
</description></item><item><title>Download QILING Deep Data Recovery 4.7.0 Build 20260201</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 16:39:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qiling-deep-data-recovery-14091.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qiling-deep-data-recovery-14091.html
</guid><description>
Mistakenly deleted, formatted drive or inaccessible RAW drive? Don't worry, Deep Data Recovery software will help you quickly scan and recover deleted and lost files. QILING Deep Data Recovery is a reliable data recovery software for Windows, designed to help users effectively recover deleted, lost or inaccessible files from various storage devices such as hard drives, USB drives, SD cards and digital cameras. The software can recover a wide range of files, including photos, videos, audio...
</description></item><item><title>Download QILING File Shredder 4.6.0 Build 20260201</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 16:38:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qiling-file-shredder-14092.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qiling-file-shredder-14092.html
</guid><description>
Permanently wipe shared drives or data, remove sensitive data easily and efficiently. File Shredder provides powerful protection for your important information and privacy. Certified data erasure algorithms ensure your data cannot be recovered by others. High-speed wiping saves your precious time, and rarely takes up system resources.
Why use QILING File Shredder to erase data:
	File Shredder: Permanently erase and remove unnecessary files from your computer after recovery
	Hard Drive...
</description></item><item><title>Download InnoExtractor Ultra 2026 v11.4.0.166</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 16:38:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-innoextractor-plus-4009.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-innoextractor-plus-4009.html
</guid><description>
InnoExtractor Plus is a handy lightweight but strong will allow you to use technology InnoUnp to easily extract the installer Inno Setup. Using this tool, you will be able to explore the content and the internal structure of installers and extract them to a folder on the local drive or on the storage device mobile without running the file setup. InnoExtractor Plus comes with graphical interface simple and user friendly, allowing you to easily open the installed just by drag and drop...
</description></item><item><title>Download QILING Fast Cache Standard / Server 3.2.2 Build 20260201</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 16:38:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qiling-fast-cache-standard-server-13700.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qiling-fast-cache-standard-server-13700.html
</guid><description>
QILING Fast Cache can improve the overall performance of the system. Temporary files are often accessed by the system or other applications, and the reading speed of RAM is much higher than that of a real hard drive, so storing frequently accessed data in RAM greatly improves the data reading speed; Additional hard drives and SSD storage media have limited read and write times, so QILING Fast Cache also improves the life of real hard drives.
Main Features
	Improve system performance:...
</description></item><item><title>Download Coder Technologies Coder 2.28.10</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 16:37:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coder-oss-enterprise-8726.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coder-oss-enterprise-8726.html
</guid><description>
Coder OSS Enterprise is a development platform that provides a complete cloud-based solution for software development, testing and deployment. It is designed to simplify the software development process by providing developers with a collaborative and streamlined environment.
Coder offloads development from local workstations to your on-premises infrastructure and public cloud. Boost developer productivity with powerful server resources and instant integration. Keep the code and data...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tier1App yCrash 3.1.4</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 16:37:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tier1app-ycrash-13868.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tier1app-ycrash-13868.html
</guid><description>
yCrash is a root cause analysis tool developed by Tier1App that helps identify the source of complex manufacturing issues. The tool is designed to quickly determine why issues like CPU spikes, memory degradation, or increased response times occur, rather than simply identifying what the problem is.
Key features and functionality of yCrash include:
	Automatic data collection and analysis The tool collects and analyzes over 18 different artifacts, including GC logs, stream backups, and...
</description></item><item><title>Download CrushFTP 11.4.1.7</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 16:36:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-crushftp-13882.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-crushftp-13882.html
</guid><description>
CrushFTP is an extremely powerful, easy-to-use solution that runs on almost any operating system: macOS 10.9+/11/12+, Win2012+, Linux, Solaris, BSD, Unix, etc! Any operating system that can run Java 8 at a minimum can run CrushFTP. It supports multiple protocols including FTP, FTPS, SFTP, HTTP, HTTPS, WebDAV, and WebDAV SSL, making it flexible for secure file transfers across a variety of environments.
Key features of CrushFTP include:
	Cross-platform compatibility: Runs on macOS,...
</description></item><item><title>Download QILING Safe Disk Standard / Server 3.1.2 Build 20260201</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 16:36:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qiling-safe-disk-standard-server-14525.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qiling-safe-disk-standard-server-14525.html
</guid><description>
QILING Safe Disk stores your confidential data in strong encryption on a drive and gives you transparent access from any application. Safe Disk is a program that allows you to create and use encrypted virtual drives. You create a container file on an existing hard drive created with a specific password. The virtual drive can then only be accessed with the correct password. Without the correct password, the files on the virtual drive are completely inaccessible. After entering the correct...
</description></item><item><title>Download Picture Window Pro 8.0.547</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 16:35:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-picture-window-pro-7452.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-picture-window-pro-7452.html
</guid><description>
Picture Window Pro is a powerful image editing tool designed for serious photographers with strict creative and quality standards. Its comprehensive set of photo editing and editing tools let you control and shape every aspect of your images.
Picture Window Pro 8 is a complete rewrite of Picture Window Pro 7. It features non-destructive image editing through a novel interface based on an image tree. It also fully supports large, high-resolution displays and can be used in dual monitor...
</description></item></channel></rss>