<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 15:46:24 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 15:46:24 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download IObit Smart Defrag Pro 11.0.0.454</title><pubDate> Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:21:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iobit-smart-defrag-pro-319.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iobit-smart-defrag-pro-319.html
</guid><description>
IObit Smart Defrag Pro is software that defragment the disk to help speed up the whole system to prevent the technical errors not desired. Based on the technology of disk defragmentation latest of IObit, and technology “boot Time disk defrag” Smart Defrag 5 is created with the ability to defragment in the world. It not only provides defragmentation, but also smart sorting your files based on using frequency, thus increasing the disk speed and the whole system for highest...
</description></item><item><title>Download Advanced SystemCare Ultimate 17.5.0.132</title><pubDate> Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:21:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-systemcare-ultimate-132.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-systemcare-ultimate-132.html
</guid><description>
Advanced SystemCare Ultimate 17: Antivirus software that also helps protect, repair, clean and optimize your PC. Based on BitDefender antivirus technology and IObit anti-malware engine, it is part of IObit antivirus project devoted to providing better and value-added services to our users.
With real-time protection against viruses, spyware and phishing attacks, powerful tuning and cleaning functions, Advanced SystemCare Ultimate provides always-on protection, Automatic and all-in-one...
</description></item><item><title>Download iTubeGo YouTube Downloader 10.6.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:20:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-itubego-youtube-downloader-3681.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-itubego-youtube-downloader-3681.html
</guid><description>
iTubeGo YouTube Downloader  is the best way to download live video from 1000+ streaming sites. iTubeGo YouTube Downloader is a powerful download tool that allows you to save video and audio for free. The output format of high speed converter is high quality MP4, MP3. Fully compatible with iPhone, iPad, iTunes, iMovie, Android Phone and more.
iTubeGo YouTube Downloader - Solution for downloading high quality Youtube video 
Features of iTubeGo YouTube Downloader
	Download videos from...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDQ Inventory 19.4.93.0 Enterprise</title><pubDate> Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:20:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdq-inventory-1468.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdq-inventory-1468.html
</guid><description>
PDQ Inventory is a software application to manage your system. This software will be able to manage your system by scanning the Windows operating system of you to provide information hardware, software, and configuration for the Windows operating system in your your tools. The tools available in this software helps you can scan the computer correctly.
In addition, the software PDQ Inventory can give you very detailed information. This software application is one of the management...
</description></item><item><title>Download Navicat Premium 17.3.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:19:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-navicat-premium-87.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-navicat-premium-87.html
</guid><description>
Navicat Premium is a developer tool database allows you to connect simultaneously with the MySQL database, MariaDB, SQL Server, Oracle, PostgreSQL and SQLite from a single application. Navicat Premium is compatible with the database cloud such as Amazon RDS, Amazon Aurora, Amazon Redshift, SQL Azure, Oracle Cloud and Google Cloud. You can quickly and easily build, manage and maintain database of your.
Features, characteristics, Navicat Premium:
Move data seamlessly
Data transfer, data...
</description></item><item><title>Download UltraSearch Professional 4.8.1.1181</title><pubDate> Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:18:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ultrasearch-professional-10252.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ultrasearch-professional-10252.html
</guid><description>
UltraSearch Professional is the professional version that helps you find your files and documents on all connected hard drives and network drives. Search by file type, document content, or file properties. Take back your valuable time and let UltraSearch do the searching for you.
UltraSearch Professional does not maintain an index stored on your hard disk. It achieves speed by working directly on the Master File Table (MFT) of NTFS partitions. So it even identifies NTFS hardlinks. That...
</description></item><item><title>Download Macrium Reflect Workstation / Server / Server Plus 8.1.8626</title><pubDate> Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:18:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-macrium-reflect-1444.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-macrium-reflect-1444.html
</guid><description>
Macrium Reflect is software backup and recovery files, image files, with big improvements in speed, simplicity and strength. The software we provide taiwebs.com 've included 3 version is Macrium Reflect Workstation / Server / Server Plus. Whole our focus is to help organizations protect critical data and business systems, without fuss and budget breaking.
Macrium Reflect - backup and restore files
The function of Macrium Reflect
	Backup tool new: image gradually increases and...
</description></item><item><title>Download PPTube 10.6.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:18:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pptube-12556.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pptube-12556.html
</guid><description>
PPTube Video Downloader allows you to download HD videos easily, from 720p, 1080p, 2K, 4K and 8K. You can save multiple videos at the same time. Just copy multiple video URLs from various websites and paste them into PPTube Downloader, then you can download multiple videos in seconds.
In addition, you can download HD videos from Instagram, TikTok, Facebook, Apple Music, Vimeo, adult websites, etc. and convert them to MP4, MP3, MOV, AAC and more than 20 other output formats. PPTube...
</description></item><item><title>Download Paprika Recipe Manager 3.3.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:17:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-paprika-recipe-manager-5584.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-paprika-recipe-manager-5584.html
</guid><description>
Paprika Recipe Manager is a simple and fun recipe management software for everyone: from aspiring chefs to professional chefs. With web entry, grocery listings and meal planners, Paprika is the perfect kitchen companion. If you love to cook, Paprika will be the most useful app you'll ever download!
Paprika is an application that helps you organize recipes, plan meals and create food lists. Using Paprika's built-in browser, you can save recipes from anywhere on the web. Want to access your...
</description></item><item><title>Download IntraWEB Ultimate 16.1.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:17:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intraweb-ultimate-2007.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intraweb-ultimate-2007.html
</guid><description>
IntraWEB Ultimate is a tool to build the website. With this tool, the developer can create the page using the same method used to build the Windows program. Because the HTML page directly from the concept design to the user's computer does not download a bit more complicated and in fact is required from web server. So, the template IntraWeb on the server and download server and displays them to the user. Things technology direction of the IntraWEB Ultimate provides part flexibility and...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDQ Deploy 19.4.93.0 Enterprise</title><pubDate> Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:16:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdq-deploy-1469.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdq-deploy-1469.html
</guid><description>
PDQ Deploy Enterprise is an application to keep the Windows PC and the programs installed on it. Software PDQ Deploy helps you to connect multiple patch or a windows app (.exe, .msi) with multiple operating systems. The deployment software can be install, delete, run script, reboot, copy the file, sliding mode, send messages, etc.
PDQ Deploy Enterprise
Features of PDQ Deploy Enterprise
	Send notifications (alerts) via email
	Run the script as popular as .vbs, .reg .bat and .ps1
	Run...
</description></item><item><title>Download Service Security Editor 7.0.4.68</title><pubDate> Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:13:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-service-security-editor-8055.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-service-security-editor-8055.html
</guid><description>
Service Security Editor is free software that allows you to effectively add/remove service permissions that restrict or allow access to your system. This tool is designed to provide an easy way for users to grant (or deny) the ability to start, stop, pause or modify any Windows Service with minimal clicks.
Service Security Editor will be an alternative to Microsoft's powerful SC and SubInACL.exe command line programs. Service Security Editor is a powerful administration tool and is...
</description></item><item><title>Download PHP 8.4.11</title><pubDate> Wed, 30 Jul 2025 18:12:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-php-1878.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-php-1878.html
</guid><description>
PHP (abbreviation regression: "P... Hypertext Preprocessor", "Personal Home Page") is a programming language script or a kind of code primarily used to develop the application write for server, open source, used for general purposes. It is very suitable with the web and can easily embed into your HTML. Due to be optimized for web applications, speed fast, compact syntax like C and Java, easy to learn and time building the product is relatively shorter compared to other languages, so PHP...
</description></item><item><title>Download Zero Install 2.27.3</title><pubDate> Wed, 30 Jul 2025 15:53:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zero-install-1632.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zero-install-1632.html
</guid><description>
Zero Install is a system, install the software distribution cross africa focus. Other features include full support for shared libraries (with the SAT for resolution dependent), share between users, and integration with the package manager original foundation. Zero Install supports both binary packages and source and works on Linux systems , OS X , Unix and Windows. It is completely open source.
Zero Install - System software installation
Zero Install also has a number of interesting...
</description></item><item><title>Download CapCut PC 6.7.0.2661 / 6.8.0.2697 Beta 4</title><pubDate> Wed, 30 Jul 2025 15:52:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capcut-pc-9995.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capcut-pc-9995.html
</guid><description>
CapCut PC is a simple video editing tool that you can freely use anywhere. You can create videos on your browser, desktop and laptop, or on your phone. Versatile editing, magical AI tools, team collaboration, and built-in assets. Create videos in a whole new way.
You can edit videos based on editing the timeline, in the process you can add different elements and effects to the video to give the best effect to your work. It is a simple and intuitive set of editing tools and effects that...
</description></item><item><title>Download GoodSync Enterprise 12.9.2.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 30 Jul 2025 15:50:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-goodsync-enterprise-163.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-goodsync-enterprise-163.html
</guid><description>
GoodSync Enterprise is a software that saves files and files easily and is reliable. It automatically analyts, synchronize and backup your email, family photos, contacts, MP3, financial documentation and other important files-between desktop computers, laptops, servers, external drives and Windows Mobile devices as well as remotely via FTP , SFTP, WebDAV and more. The GoodSync synchronized software combines bulletproof reliability with an extremely easy interface to compare, synchronize...
</description></item><item><title>Download iDownerGo Pro 10.6.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 30 Jul 2025 15:49:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idownergo-12439.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idownergo-12439.html
</guid><description>
iDownerGo is the best tool that allows users to download videos, music and playlists from more than 10,000 streaming sites. It can easily convert videos to MP4, MOV, MKV, 3GP, AAC, WAV, FLAC and other formats on PC and Mac. With this amazing program, users can enjoy their favorite media content without restrictions.
iDownerGo Features
	Download any video up to 8K resolution
	Download 1080p videos online from over 10,000 popular streaming sites easily.
	Save any video in various...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Saver Pro 10.6.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 30 Jul 2025 15:49:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-saver-6830.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-saver-6830.html
</guid><description>
YT Saver is a software that supports downloading Video, Audio, Playlist from 10,000+ websites, Convert Video to MP4, MOV, AAC, WAV and more. YT Saver is a powerful downloader that allows you to save video and audio for free. The output format of the high-speed converter is high-quality MP4, MP3. Fully compatible with iPhone, iPad, iTunes, iMovie, Android Phone and more.
Supported Input Formats:
	Video: MP4, M4V, 3GP, MPEG, DAT, AVI, ASF, WMV, VOB, MKV, FLV, 3GS, 3G2, F4V, WEBM, TS,...
</description></item><item><title>Download 4KSoftware 4K Downloader 5.16.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 30 Jul 2025 15:48:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-downloader-3858.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-downloader-3858.html
</guid><description>
4K Downloader is a Windows application small but powerful to download and convert video in 4K and 8K Ultra HD from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion and thousands of other video-based websites. It speeds up your download by up to 5 times. Consider that most smart phones, TVS, computers, and tablets all support the high definition format, don't be surprised when many users want to enjoy quality content on their device. 4K Downloader is a lightweight software designed to help you grab videos...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cascadeur 2025.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 30 Jul 2025 15:41:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cascadeur-9720.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cascadeur-9720.html
</guid><description>
Cascadeur is a standalone software for 3D keyframe animation of human figures or other characters. Never before has it been so easy and fun to create an animation from scratch or re-edit. Thanks to AI-powered tools, you can perform key poses very quickly, see the physical results immediately, and adjust the secondary movement. All while retaining full control at any point.
Cascadeur uses advanced simulation techniques and algorithms to accurately simulate the movements and interactions...
</description></item><item><title>Download Dropbox 229.4.5197</title><pubDate> Wed, 30 Jul 2025 15:41:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dropbox-1313.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dropbox-1313.html
</guid><description>
Dropbox on taiwebs.com is free tool, the data synchronization across multiple PC become easier than never before: after installation, all what you have to do is enter your name, email address and password before opening the folder My Dropbox. If you install the software on a different computer, Dropbox will reflect the content of the online storage. So you exchange any data between the different computer is connected to Dropbox account. In addition the client is installed on the computer,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Winstep Nexus 25.7</title><pubDate> Wed, 30 Jul 2025 15:40:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winstep-xtreme-447.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winstep-xtreme-447.html
</guid><description>
Winstep Nexus is software that helps you reschedule the icons of apps, prevent a disturbance on the Desktop. Winstep Nexus offers multiple features that are differentiated into different main application groups so you choose to use. Winstep Nexus has the ability to organize icons of applications, frequently used documents on a computer so that your computer will always be in a stack of blocks.
Winstep Nexus helps to enhance your productivity, software that allows you to work better and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Synapse Audio DUNE 3 3.6.4</title><pubDate> Wed, 30 Jul 2025 15:40:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-synapse-audio-dune-1030.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-synapse-audio-dune-1030.html
</guid><description>
Synapse Audio DUNE is the new technology brought the concept of unison fame to new heights. Unison is a feature classic synthesizer developed at the same time many voice when playing a note, usually up to 8. The voice that can be separated and spread in the stereo field. The new thing about DUNE is the ability to do anything with the voice, not that most, or even the phrase the voice.
Synapse Audio DUNE 3
The filter is modified in Dune 3 now has filters multi-dual mode plus effects...
</description></item><item><title>Download Alternate Password DB 3.630</title><pubDate> Wed, 30 Jul 2025 15:39:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-alternate-password-db-2723.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-alternate-password-db-2723.html
</guid><description>
Alternate Password DB is a program to securely store the password and your PIN code. With just one password, you have access to the encrypted data (BLOWFISH 256 bit). The password file can be converted into an executable file, can be transferred on a USB memory stick or other removable drive without the need to install this program.
Alternate Password DB - password storage safe
You can also configure the program locks itself after a period of time (main password will be required...
</description></item><item><title>Download Visual Studio Code 1.102.3</title><pubDate> Wed, 30 Jul 2025 15:36:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-visual-studio-code-3182.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-visual-studio-code-3182.html
</guid><description>
Visual Studio Code is the encryption tool of Microsoft has met most of the needs of the developer. Environment this encoding was introduced to compete with other products such as Sublime and Nodepad ++ . Microsoft, in its new product, has not been released in many years, has provided many features in a simple environment. In addition to the familiar with a dozen programming languages, the syntax and get to know coding language as soon as be encrypted and allows for syntax highlighting, it...
</description></item></channel></rss>