<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 13:53:28 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 13:53:28 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download HWiNFO 8.40</title><pubDate> Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:41:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hwinfo-1828.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hwinfo-1828.html
</guid><description>
HWiNFO (HWiNFO32) is a diagnostic tool and hardware information, recognizes and displays detailed information about all the hardware components of you. HWiNFO will hold the component in the tree view and provide the report easy to read for each category.
HWiNFO - Hardware Diagnostics
HWiNFO is especially useful so you don't have to install it on each computer and completely for free. Just run the direct program and you will have full information of the computer that you need. The...
</description></item><item><title>Download HWiNFO Portable 8.40</title><pubDate> Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:41:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hwinfo-portable-11340.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hwinfo-portable-11340.html
</guid><description>
HWiNFO Portable is a professional hardware information and diagnostic tool that supports the latest components, technologies and industry standards. These tools are designed to collect and present the maximum amount of information possible about computer hardware, making them suitable for users looking for driver updates, computer manufacturers, system integrators as well as technical experts. Retrieved information is presented in a logical, easy-to-understand format and can be exported...
</description></item><item><title>Download R-Wipe &amp;amp; Clean 20.0 Build 2543</title><pubDate> Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:29:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-wipe-clean-891.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-wipe-clean-891.html
</guid><description>
R-Wipe &amp;amp; Clean is software to delete junk files, unnecessary files from your computer to release the storage space and speed up your computer. In addition, R-Wipe &amp;amp; Clean also unleash the capacity of your drive and delete information invasion of privacy on different operations online and offline including your internet history and cookies, the list of downloaded files and documents were open, buffer different data, temporary files and many other items, created by the operating...
</description></item><item><title>Download DelFast 1.2 + Context Menu</title><pubDate> Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:28:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-delfast-14400.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-delfast-14400.html
</guid><description>
DelFast is a lightweight utility for Windows that instantly deletes files and folders without the delays caused by Windows Explorer's calculations and animations. It's designed to be fast, simple, and easy to carry.
Features of DelFast
	Instantly deletes files and folders
	Supports multiple selection (delete multiple items at once)
	No installer needed, just a single EXE file
	Extremely small size (approximately 188 KB)
	Minimal CPU usage
	Clean and simple user interface
	Permanent...
</description></item><item><title>Download Hasleo Data Recovery 6.8 All Editions</title><pubDate> Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:27:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hasleo-data-recovery-professional-2216.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hasleo-data-recovery-professional-2216.html
</guid><description>
Hasleo Data Recovery is a software data recovery powerful and reliable. Lost file? It does not matter, the software will solve this problem. It doesn't matter if you accidentally delete files or format the disk, or you can have trouble system. This development will allow you to recover lost files from hard drive, PC, external hard drive, USB drive, SD card, digital camera, mobile phone, music player, MP3 / MP4 and other media.
Hasleo Data Recovery Professional - data recovery, file
The...
</description></item><item><title>Download anyPDF 1.5.0.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:26:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anypdf-11943.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anypdf-11943.html
</guid><description>
AnyPDF is an integrated PDF viewer and manager as it facilitates viewing and editing of PDF files in a user-friendly manner where users can merge multiple documents, protect and compress important data, etc. This program aims to be a more or less general tool for PDF workflow. That said, it doesn't necessarily specialize in anything specific as it has a number of uses related to working with PDF files.
Features of anyPDF
	User-friendly user interface
	Convert from JPG to...
</description></item><item><title>Download reaConverter Pro 8.0.177</title><pubDate> Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:26:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html
</guid><description>
reaConverter Pro is software image processing feature with batch conversion and image editing periodically becomes simple. eaConverter also provide command line utilities allow you to process images automatically, thus helping you shorten the time for other work.
reaConverter Pro integrated powerful tool of Uber with many great features. It provides advanced solutions to process and adjust images. Management of the conversion process the base image with the latest version of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Remote Desktop Manager Enterprise 2025.3.29</title><pubDate> Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:25:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-remote-desktop-manager-enterprise-242.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-remote-desktop-manager-enterprise-242.html
</guid><description>
Remote Desktop Manager Enterprise software is the complete management of remote connections and virtual machines from a single location, at the same time access support data online and cloud storage. Remote Desktop Manager supports multiple types of connections, not only connections for the protocol connect remote computer Remote Desktop Protocol (RDP).
Remote Desktop Manager easily add, edit, delete, share, organize and find your remote connection of you quickly. Compatible with...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft Office 2021-2024 Professional Plus VL (64-bit) 2512 Build 19530.20138 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:25:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-office-2021-6670.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-office-2021-6670.html
</guid><description>
Since the end of February 2021, Microsoft has announced two new versions of Office 2021 including: Office 2021 and Office LTSC. Reportedly, Office 2021 is the next version of Office 2019, promising to bring users a better experience in the new Word, Excel or PowerPoint tools.
With each office user, the Microsoft Office toolkit is essential and indispensable software in the job. Microsoft Office has undergone numerous editions from Office 2010, 2013, 2016, 2019 to Microsoft 365 developed...
</description></item><item><title>Download Dropbox 239.4.8301</title><pubDate> Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:25:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dropbox-1313.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dropbox-1313.html
</guid><description>
Dropbox on taiwebs.com is free tool, the data synchronization across multiple PC become easier than never before: after installation, all what you have to do is enter your name, email address and password before opening the folder My Dropbox. If you install the software on a different computer, Dropbox will reflect the content of the online storage. So you exchange any data between the different computer is connected to Dropbox account. In addition the client is installed on the computer,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Pegasun System Utilities 9.3.5</title><pubDate> Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:23:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pegasun-system-utilities-10950.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pegasun-system-utilities-10950.html
</guid><description>
Pegasun System Utilities is a software suite designed to optimize and improve the performance of Windows computers. It provides various tools to clean junk files, optimize system settings, manage startup programs, and enhance overall system speed and stability. This software aims to streamline system processes, improve drive performance, and enhance overall computer performance.
System utilities provide more than 28 tools to meet almost any PC need. Whether you need to clean up your...
</description></item><item><title>Download Revive Faces 2.0.11</title><pubDate> Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:23:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-revive-faces-13762.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-revive-faces-13762.html
</guid><description>
Have you ever looked at an old photo or video and wished you could see those faces clearly again? Time, blurriness, and pixels shouldn't steal the smiles, glances, or stories of the people you love. With Revive Faces, our breakthrough AI-powered restoration software, blurry, smudged, and pixelated faces can now shine with stunning clarity—as if they were taken yesterday.
Why Restore Faces?
	See the unseen again – Our advanced AI not only sharpens images, but also recreates lost...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft Support and Recovery Assistant 17.01.3954.000</title><pubDate> Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:22:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-support-and-recovery-assistant-4821.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-support-and-recovery-assistant-4821.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft Support and Recovery Assistant is a client to enable customers of Microsoft troubleshooting and diagnosis of incidents, their relation to the application OS &amp;amp; Windows. It can help you troubleshoot, install, uninstall, activate and more. Open the app and click on the Microsoft products you need to help.
Current it can fix the problem Office, Office 365, Outlook and Windows. If it can't troubleshoot for you, it will propose the next steps and help you to contact the support...
</description></item><item><title>Download Opera One 126.0.5750.18</title><pubDate> Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:22:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-972.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-972.html
</guid><description>
Opera is a fast, safe, configurable and compliant intranet web browser, which includes both the reader and the application. The Opera browser supports web browsing, listening to music, watching high speed movies, you can open many tabs on the Opera without affecting your browsing speed. Opera now supports almost all devices and operating systems such as windows, IOS, Android, linux, MacOS ...
Opera is a beautiful interface and many interesting features, operating on both PCs and mobile,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Typora 1.12.4</title><pubDate> Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:21:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-typora-6764.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-typora-6764.html
</guid><description>
Typora gives you a seamless experience as both a reader and a writer. It removes the preview window, the mode switcher, the syntax symbols of the markup source code, and all other unnecessary distractions. Instead, it provides an actual live preview to help you focus on the content itself.
Features of Typora:
	Typora allows you to manage your files easily, providing both a file tree panel and a side panel (file list).
	Automatically view the Outline structure of your document in the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Monkeys Audio 11.91</title><pubDate> Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:21:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-monkeys-audio-949.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-monkeys-audio-949.html
</guid><description>
Monkey\'s Audio is software that compresses digital music without loss of quality. Supports high quality WAV files and CD ripping. Monkeys Audio will compress .wav tracks into .ape files to reduce their size without loss of sound quality, decompress .ape, convert files, check file integrity and manage tags.
Unlike traditional methods like MP3 and OGG, which permanently remove quality to save space, Monkey\'s Audio only creates perfect copies with the same sound quality as the originals....
</description></item><item><title>Download TunnelBear 4.17.2.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:20:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tunnelbear-4601.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tunnelbear-4601.html
</guid><description>
TunnelBear is a VPN app for the Internet connection to help you protect your identity, allow you to select the IP address that author for you to easily access other Internet services. The purpose of TunnelBear is to help you add an additional layer of security to the data communication occurs between the PC and a remote server by using the service anonymous to encrypt information. With the help of it you can navigate on the Internet without having to worry that your data can be blocked by...
</description></item><item><title>Download Advanced CSV Converter 7.89</title><pubDate> Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:20:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-csv-converter-4508.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-csv-converter-4508.html
</guid><description>
Advanced CSV Converter is a conversion tool CSV to DBF, Excel (XLS, XLSX), TXT, HTML, PRG, XML, SQL, RTF. To convert a file, the program provides an interface controlled by the wizard, guides you step by step conversion. Use the wizard, you select file input, select the format and destination folder. If necessary, you can set the filter switch according to the example and select columns you want to exclude from the process. When the conversion process is started, the program will extract...
</description></item><item><title>Download Scale Photo Up 2.0.11</title><pubDate> Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:19:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-scale-photo-up-13763.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-scale-photo-up-13763.html
</guid><description>
Are you tired of low-resolution, pixelated footage that stifles your creativity? Say goodbye to grainy memories and say hello to Scale Photo Up – groundbreaking AI software that doubles resolution, enhances detail, and smooths out imperfections in your photos and videos with stunning clarity!
Why Scale Photo Up?
	Upscale 2x – No loss of quality! – Turn blurry, low-resolution photos and videos into sharp, high-resolution masterpieces. Perfect for breathing new life into old...
</description></item><item><title>Download C64 Forever Plus Edition 11.2.3</title><pubDate> Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:19:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-c64-forever-plus-edition-2307.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-c64-forever-plus-edition-2307.html
</guid><description>
C64 Forever is the program is an emulator of Commodore strong, even comes with a set of rich game. Of course, video games have come a long way and so can you and you need more than a lifetime to undergo computer toys alone, not to mention game machines. If you, like me, are nostalgic and want to undergo these difficulties, neurological examination, patience and everything else, you need the emulator for this.
C64 Forever Plus Edition - The emulator game
External application suitable...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ocenaudio 3.17.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:18:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ocenaudio-837.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ocenaudio-837.html
</guid><description>
Ocenaudio: software for windows, this is the sound editing easy, fast and powerful. ocenaudio is a program for audio editing multi-platform, easy to use, fast and functional. This is the ideal software for those who need to edit and analyze audio files.
Ocenaudio - editor powerful audio for windows
This software is based on Ocen Framework , a powerful library developed to simplify and standardize the development of application analysis and sound processing on many platforms.
Features...
</description></item><item><title>Download Geometric Glovius Prime 6.7.0.121</title><pubDate> Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:18:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-geometric-glovius-pro-754.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-geometric-glovius-pro-754.html
</guid><description>
Geometric Glovius Pro is viewer CAD 3D modern for files CATIA, NX, STEP, IGES, Pro/ENGINEER and Creo, SolidWorks, Inventor and Solid Edge. The work of Geometric Glovius Pro is made exact measurements, cut dynamic sections, compare differences between models and export to 3D PDF, STL and Glovius Mobile.
Geometric Glovius Pro - manager, and view CAD 3D
The features of Geometric Glovius Pro
	Modern interface, simple, easy to use
	Mobile app for free for iOS &amp;amp; Android powerful...
</description></item><item><title>Download Pazu StreamGet All-In-One Video Downloader 2.9.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:18:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pazu-streamget-all-in-one-video-downloader-12037.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pazu-streamget-all-in-one-video-downloader-12037.html
</guid><description>
StreamGet All-In-One Video Downloader is the ultimate downloading solution for you. It supports downloading any movies and shows from the most popular streaming sites including Netflix, Prime Video, Disney Plus, Max, Hulu, and Apple TV Plus. The downloader is continuously updated to support more platforms in the future.
Download movies and shows from various streaming platforms to MP4/MKV on your Windows device and enjoy them anywhere you want.
Features of Pazu StreamGet All-In-One...
</description></item><item><title>Download System Utilities 1.4.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:17:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-system-utilities-10394.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-system-utilities-10394.html
</guid><description>
System Utilities as its name suggests, contains a collection of tools that can help you maintain your system easily. It can scan your drive for storage, help you quickly uninstall programs, as well as manage startup applications and clean up unnecessary data.
Features of System Utilities
	Scan and organize all the folders on your PC to create more space.
	Uninstall all programs that you do not use. Get rid of data junk on your computer.
	Determine which programs should start...
</description></item><item><title>Download TickTick Premium 8.0.0.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:17:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ticktick-premium-7770.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ticktick-premium-7770.html
</guid><description>
TickTick Premium is a task management application that helps users stay organized, it is very suitable for educators and students with many incentives. TickTick turns your Windows PC device into a flexible, easy-to-use and highly efficient office platform. Join millions of people to capture ideas, organize their lives, and do something creative every day.
Whether there are work related tasks or personal goals, TickTick is here to help you manage all your to-dos. With five different...
</description></item></channel></rss>