<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 01:37:38 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 01:37:38 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Microsoft Visual C++ 2015-2022 Redistributable 14.50.35710</title><pubDate> Sat, 18 Oct 2025 19:04:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-visual-c-4856.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-visual-c-4856.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft Visual C++ Redistributable Package contains the component run-time libraries of Visual C ++ required to run the application on a PC without installed Visual C ++. Microsoft Visual C++ or also known as MSVC development environment integrated (IDE) for the programming language C, C++, at the same time integrated tools for developing and debugging C++ source code. Microsoft Visual C++ supports the function of automatic completion of the coding and the debugging function...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Acrobat Pro DC 2025.001.20813 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Sat, 18 Oct 2025 19:04:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-001en-adobe-acrobat-pro-458.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-001en-adobe-acrobat-pro-458.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Acrobat Pro DC is a comprehensive software that helps you create and edit the PDF&amp;nbsp;document, or create form, sign, protect PDF, connect, split PDF, export PDF to various formats. The Acrobat Pro DC is the latest version of Adobe with improvements in the interface with the polished ribbon bar and the ability to create and handle pdf files as well as its male versions.
The highlight of the Acrobat Pro DC is probably the ability to connect, store documents on the cloud, you can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Any Video Downloader Pro 9.6.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 18 Oct 2025 19:03:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-video-downloader-pro-3731.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-video-downloader-pro-3731.html
</guid><description>
Any Video Downloader Pro is software support you can download video HD 720p, 1080p, 2K, 4K and 8K from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion, Vimeo, Metacafe and thousands of video sharing sites, other. It is a tool to speed up multi-threading can speed up your download faster up to 5 times. This helpful program support download at the same time. Any Video Downloader Pro lets you download multiple videos at the same time. Moreover, it allows you to pause and resume downloads if you need more...
</description></item><item><title>Download Jubler Subtitle Εditor 9.0.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 18 Oct 2025 19:02:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jubler-subtitle-editor-11148.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jubler-subtitle-editor-11148.html
</guid><description>
Jubler is a text-based subtitle editing tool. It can be used as a new subtitle authoring software or as a tool to convert, convert, edit and refine existing subtitles. It is open source under the free general public license (GNU). It is written in Java 5.0 (also known as Java 1.5.0) to be truly cross-platform. It has been tested on Linux (Intel 32 &amp;amp; 64 bit), Windows (XP and Vista) and Mac OS X (PPC and Intel).
Jubler Subtitle Editor features
	It supports Advanced SubStation,...
</description></item><item><title>Download anyPDF 1.4.4</title><pubDate> Sat, 18 Oct 2025 19:02:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anypdf-11943.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anypdf-11943.html
</guid><description>
AnyPDF is an integrated PDF viewer and manager as it facilitates viewing and editing of PDF files in a user-friendly manner where users can merge multiple documents, protect and compress important data, etc. This program aims to be a more or less general tool for PDF workflow. That said, it doesn't necessarily specialize in anything specific as it has a number of uses related to working with PDF files.
Features of anyPDF
	User-friendly user interface
	Convert from JPG to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Alfa eBooks Manager Pro / Web 9.4.1.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 18 Oct 2025 19:01:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-alfa-ebooks-manager-web-981.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-alfa-ebooks-manager-web-981.html
</guid><description>
Alfa eBooks Manager Web is a program that enables to arrange the electronic books and paper of you in a single electronic library. eBooks Manager Website will host the electronic books and print in an electronic library. Group, filter and sort books by multiple parameters. Find any book in just a second by title, author or ISBN.
Alfa eBooks Manager Web - ebook library
Alfa eBooks Manager Web provides comprehensive set of fields, including the author, category, publisher, series, ISBN,...
</description></item><item><title>Download WYSIWYG Web Builder 20.3.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 18 Oct 2025 19:01:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wysiwyg-web-builder-177.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wysiwyg-web-builder-177.html
</guid><description>
WYSIWYG Web Builder : The construction of the website from scratch using HTML code isn't a pleasant process, even when you know what you are doing. The website can be built using WYSIWYG Web Builder with using the element similar to the package published on the desktop: text and images placed in frames and tables on the page, so very little surprised when most of the efforts to make the web become a experience user-friendly than. the controls do you use to build your pages.
WYSIWYG Web...
</description></item><item><title>Download Freemake Video Converter Gold 5.0.0.18</title><pubDate> Sat, 18 Oct 2025 19:00:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-freemake-video-converter-gold-167.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-freemake-video-converter-gold-167.html
</guid><description>
Freemake Video Converter Gold is a software to help convert tail high quality videos with many different formats on many devices. Freemake Video Converter - convert video to AVI, MP4, WMV, MKV, 3GP, DVD, MP3, iPad, iPhone, PSP, Android phone. Video to MP3 just with one click! Rip and burn DVD. Convert YouTube to MP4, AVI, etc. with Freemake! Results guaranteed. Freemake Video Converter has fast conversion speed, guarantee the output quality,support create HTML5 videos have the embed code...
</description></item><item><title>Download Visual C++ Redistributable Runtimes AIO Repack 0.102.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 18 Oct 2025 19:00:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-visual-c-redistributable-runtimes-aio-repack-7825.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-visual-c-redistributable-runtimes-aio-repack-7825.html
</guid><description>
Visual C++ Redistributable Runtimes AIO Repack is a setup package that includes all the latest Microsoft Visual C++ Redistribution Runtimes without the initial setup payload.
	Built on VBCRedis_AIO_x86_x64.exe
	This process is handled by a command set of windows command, which runs hidden in the background by default.
	Before installation, the script will check and remove the existing Visual C + + runtime settings, including the original EXE or MSI setup or the older MSI package...
</description></item><item><title>Download Typora 1.12.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 18 Oct 2025 18:59:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-typora-6764.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-typora-6764.html
</guid><description>
Typora gives you a seamless experience as both a reader and a writer. It removes the preview window, the mode switcher, the syntax symbols of the markup source code, and all other unnecessary distractions. Instead, it provides an actual live preview to help you focus on the content itself.
Features of Typora:
	Typora allows you to manage your files easily, providing both a file tree panel and a side panel (file list).
	Automatically view the Outline structure of your document in the...
</description></item><item><title>Download MusConv 4.10.427 Lifetime</title><pubDate> Sat, 18 Oct 2025 18:58:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html
</guid><description>
MusConv transfers playlists, albums, followed artists and liked songs across a variety of services – Spotify, Apple Music, Amazon Music, YouTube, YouTube Music, iTunes, Deezer, Tidal, SoundCloud, Pandora and more 125 music services!
Features of MusConv Ultimate
	Transfer playlists, albums, followed artists and liked tracks between over 125 music servicesManage playlists (Delete, Merge, Split, Copy...)
	More than 125 music services supported
	Access DAILY updated music charts on...
</description></item><item><title>Download Pazu StreamGet All-In-One Video Downloader 2.8.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 18 Oct 2025 18:57:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pazu-streamget-all-in-one-video-downloader-12037.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pazu-streamget-all-in-one-video-downloader-12037.html
</guid><description>
StreamGet All-In-One Video Downloader is the ultimate downloading solution for you. It supports downloading any movies and shows from the most popular streaming sites including Netflix, Prime Video, Disney Plus, Max, Hulu, and Apple TV Plus. The downloader is continuously updated to support more platforms in the future.
Download movies and shows from various streaming platforms to MP4/MKV on your Windows device and enjoy them anywhere you want.
Features of Pazu StreamGet All-In-One...
</description></item><item><title>Download Amagicsoft Magic Data Recovery Technician 3.11.290.139</title><pubDate> Sat, 18 Oct 2025 18:57:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-amagicsoft-magic-data-recovery-technician-14112.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-amagicsoft-magic-data-recovery-technician-14112.html
</guid><description>
Amagicsoft Magic Data Recovery Technician is a data recovery software product from Amagicsoft designed to help users, even those who are not technically savvy, recover deleted, formatted or lost files from various devices and file systems. The software supports over 5,000 file types and offers dual scanning modes (Quick Scan and Advanced Scan), real-time preview of recoverable files, and is compatible with various storage media such as hard drives, memory cards, and USB flash...
</description></item><item><title>Download Streamlabs OBS 1.19.6</title><pubDate> Sat, 18 Oct 2025 18:56:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-streamlabs-obs-6531.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-streamlabs-obs-6531.html
</guid><description>
Streamlabs OBS is a free video and video game livestream. Streamlabs OBS uses the same OBS source code but is improved with a better user experience. The software is also free and provides the setup process even more easily than the OBS Studio. Thanks to a built-in editor, Streamlabs OBS allows you to create and preview your flow interface with only a few clicks. Streamlabs OBS offers you various layers of coating to customize and design your flow for a few minutes. Obviously, after you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Fast Video Cutter Joiner 6.9.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 18 Oct 2025 18:56:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fast-video-cutter-joiner-7542.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fast-video-cutter-joiner-7542.html
</guid><description>
Fast Video Cutter Joiner is a fast video cutter and joiner with an easy to use interface. It allows users to trim parts of a video quickly while maintaining the quality of the original video. It supports various formats like AVI, MPEG, MP4, WMV, 3GP, FLV...
This tool helps you to cut video files into small parts, to keep only the parts you need and remove unwanted parts like trailers and advertisements in a movie. The clips you cut can then be used for other video productions or for a...
</description></item><item><title>Download System Mechanic Pro 25.7.1.47 + Standard</title><pubDate> Sat, 18 Oct 2025 18:55:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-system-mechanic-434.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-system-mechanic-434.html
</guid><description>
System Mechanic Pro is tool cleanup and repair errors on the system and restore hard drive and operating speed window.  System Mechanic helps you to clean your entire computer system, delete the unnecessary files, detect and repair the incident occurred due to virus attack or due to mistakenly deleted system files.
System Mechanic offers many useful features such as Registry cleaning, defragmenting computer memory, protect your privacy while accessing the Internet. With programs this...
</description></item><item><title>Download Easy Gamer Utility Pro 1.3.87</title><pubDate> Sat, 18 Oct 2025 18:55:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easy-gamer-utility-pro-12381.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easy-gamer-utility-pro-12381.html
</guid><description>
Easy Gamer Utility Pro is an easy-to-use program for Windows that can do a lot on your PC to help fix gaming problems, performance problems, and general optimization! The best tool to improve your Windows gaming experience! Is your game laggy and slow? If so, you can use the built-in game accelerator in Easy Gamer Utility, which boosts system performance, makes games run smoother, and increases FPS.
Additionally, this handy utility deletes and cleans unwanted and unnecessary temporary...
</description></item><item><title>Download System Mechanic Ultimate Defense 25.7.1.47</title><pubDate> Sat, 18 Oct 2025 18:54:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-system-mechanic-ultimate-defense-1974.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-system-mechanic-ultimate-defense-1974.html
</guid><description>
System Mechanic Ultimate Defense is software provides tracking features anti browser and protect your online privacy, management, encryption and secure password protection, anti-virus certified, VB100, detect and remove malware on demand, technology, erase hard drive military grade, award-winning optimize PC, software, file recovery advanced.
Malware threats is growing fast now because of almost a million new viruses, worms, trojan horses, rootkits and other types of spyware, and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Minimal Firewall 2.5.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 18 Oct 2025 18:54:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minimal-firewall-13877.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minimal-firewall-13877.html
</guid><description>
Minimal Firewall works in conjunction with Windows Firewall to block all unknown connections by default, prompting you to create application-based rules to mitigate malware, telemetry, and data leaks. Completely eliminate applications that call home without your knowledge. Minimal Firewall provides a more secure and integrated approach by interacting directly with the native Windows Firewall, eliminating the need for risky system modifications.
Core Features
	Lockdown Mode: The core...
</description></item><item><title>Download Quick CPU 5.3.0.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 18 Oct 2025 18:54:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quick-cpu-5144.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quick-cpu-5144.html
</guid><description>
Quick CPU (Core Parking Manager v3) is an application designed to tweak and monitor the performance settings of the CPU such as Core Parking, Frequency Scaling and Turbo Boost, as well as made other adjustments. Below you will find all information about how it works, how to interpret the data and install the application and how to perform these adjustments.
Features of Quick CPU
	Performance graphs for each core. Show if the core is Active or not adjust the size for the CPU...
</description></item><item><title>Download Social Media Downloader 7.8.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 18 Oct 2025 18:53:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-socialmediaapps-facebook-video-downloader-3742.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-socialmediaapps-facebook-video-downloader-3742.html
</guid><description>
SocialVideo Downloader (formerly SocialMediaApps Facebook Video Downloader) is a Windows application to download and convert your favorite videos from Facebook and hundreds of other video sharing sites. It increases your loading speed by up to 500%, or even more! The application has a simple and intuitive user interface, its main functions and features are quite obvious to anyone. , regardless of prior experience with similar purpose tools.
&amp;nbsp;
SocialVideo Downloader
The main...
</description></item><item><title>Download Becky! Internet Mail 2.82.01</title><pubDate> Sat, 18 Oct 2025 18:53:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-becky-internet-mail-3926.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-becky-internet-mail-3926.html
</guid><description>
Becky! Internet Mail is a client E-mail features dedicated to Windows and the Internet. Since its inception in 1996, Becky! Internet Mail is constantly improving its functions to listen to user feedback and it has become one of the products email share most successful. Becky! Internet Mail is an email application that creates multiple mailboxes. You will find many features to be expected for a software E-mail Internet and a number of features will exceed your expectations. It has almost...
</description></item><item><title>Download Easy Cut Studio 6.015</title><pubDate> Sat, 18 Oct 2025 18:52:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easy-cut-studio-2620.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easy-cut-studio-2620.html
</guid><description>
Easy Cut Studio is a program that gives you a full set of functions to design, print and cut the shapes, professional, graphics, logo, sticker, inscriptions, and much more. According to the developers, the app is compatible with TrueType fonts and OpenType, as well as with the format SVG and PDF other.
Among the advantages, it is noteworthy that interface convenience, it includes a number of blocks, so you have everything in hand so that you can focus on the creation process. It comes...
</description></item><item><title>Download SQL Backup Master 8.0.991 Enterprise</title><pubDate> Sat, 18 Oct 2025 18:51:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sql-backup-master-6687.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sql-backup-master-6687.html
</guid><description>
SQL Backup Master backup your SQL Server database into any popular cloud hosting service such as Dropbox, OneDrive, Amazon S3, Microsoft Azure, Box and Google Drive. It can also backup the database to the FTP server-or a directory on your local machine, network server or storage device.
The backup of your SQL Server database to the cloud will not be complex or expensive. SQL Backup Master is born by providing an easy way to download copies of your database to one or more of the most...
</description></item><item><title>Download Steinberg Groove Agent SE 5.2.30</title><pubDate> Sat, 18 Oct 2025 18:51:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-steinberg-groove-agent-se-11161.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-steinberg-groove-agent-se-11161.html
</guid><description>
Designed for both songwriters and beat makers, Groove Agent 5 includes the best electronic and acoustic drum kits. One of the most detailed acoustic drum kits ever in Groove Agent sits alongside a variety of percussion instruments, modern electronic drums and MIDI tracks, providing an inspiring rhythm composition tool for producers of all genres , from jazz, funk and rock to Trap and EDM. Support for VST, AU and AAX plug-in formats means Groove Agent 5 can be used with almost any...
</description></item></channel></rss>