<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 19:51:02 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 19:51:02 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download UniGetUI 3.3.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Sep 2025 16:32:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-unigetui-12209.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-unigetui-12209.html
</guid><description>
UniGetUI (formerly WingetUI) is a graphical user interface for WinGet (and other package managers), a command-line package manager for Windows 10 and Windows 11 such as Winget, Scoop, Chocolatey, Pip, NPM, .NET Tool and PowerShell Gallery. It allows users to install, update and uninstall software from the package manager easily. Additionally, it provides features like backup, restore, group and update your packages and receive notifications about new updates.
With this program, you can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Quick CPU 5.2.0.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Sep 2025 16:32:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quick-cpu-5144.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quick-cpu-5144.html
</guid><description>
Quick CPU (Core Parking Manager v3) is an application designed to tweak and monitor the performance settings of the CPU such as Core Parking, Frequency Scaling and Turbo Boost, as well as made other adjustments. Below you will find all information about how it works, how to interpret the data and install the application and how to perform these adjustments.
Features of Quick CPU
	Performance graphs for each core. Show if the core is Active or not adjust the size for the CPU...
</description></item><item><title>Download IObit Uninstaller Pro 15.0.0.10</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Sep 2025 16:31:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iobit-uninstaller-pro-339.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iobit-uninstaller-pro-339.html
</guid><description>
IObit Uninstaller Pro is software to delete programs not needed easily even when Windows "Remove Programs" operation not successful. IObit Uninstaller Pro will uninstall the app Windows, browser toolbars, software packages and plug-ins added. It comes with a scan function is powerful and a tool, Force Uninstall, both of which help to easily and completely remove the app stubborn, and the excess useless, to release more disk space.
With IObit Uninstaller Pro you will have peace of mind...
</description></item><item><title>Download CPU Temp 1.8.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Sep 2025 16:30:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cpu-temp-10651.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cpu-temp-10651.html
</guid><description>
CPU Temp is a free and simple application for monitoring CPU temperature, compatible with Windows 11 or older versions of Windows OS. CPU Temp seamlessly integrates, giving you real-time insights into CPU temperature, usage, clock speed, power consumption, and other essential parameters of your processor. reason.
With an intuitive and customizable interface, CPU Temp offers over 40 different user interface themes and color schemes. You can pick and choose the UI that suits your style,...
</description></item><item><title>Download mpv player 0.40.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Sep 2025 16:30:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mpv-player-4574.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mpv-player-4574.html
</guid><description>
mpv player is a media player for free for the command line. mpv player supports multiple format media files, audio and video codecs, and subtitle types. The application can be deployed via command-line and loading videos can be done by simply drag the file into the executable of mpv. In addition, you can first open the application and then drag and drop the file input.
The player has the option control basic playback allows fast forward and jumping throughout the clip. Move on to the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Stellar Data Recovery Pro 12.3.0.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Sep 2025 16:28:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stellar-phoenix-windows-data-recovery-professional-3312.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stellar-phoenix-windows-data-recovery-professional-3312.html
</guid><description>
Stellar Phoenix Windows Data Recovery Professional is an application that reliable and comprehensive, allowing you to recover quickly and easily the files lost or deleted from internal hard drive or any media outside any other. The program provides with an intuitive interface and no clutter, help you easily get back lost data without modifying the original structure.
Stellar Phoenix Windows Data Recovery Professional - Recover lost data
Stellar Phoenix Windows Data Recovery...
</description></item><item><title>Download FanCtrl 1.7.5</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Sep 2025 16:28:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fanctrl-5779.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fanctrl-5779.html
</guid><description>
FanCtrl is software that allows you to automatically control the fan speed on your PC. FanCtrl is easy to use, although the app is best for high-end users. You can cause damage to your computer due to overheating or conflict with other processors or other monitoring software. As an independent developed application, not all motherboards are or may be supported.
The application is well positioned and is located in the system tray with the name of the motherboard, every fan and control...
</description></item><item><title>Download Seamless3d 3.037</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Sep 2025 16:28:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-seamless3d-10257.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-seamless3d-10257.html
</guid><description>
Seamless3d is one of the easiest 3D modeling and animation programs that offers artistic freedom. It is designed to be a powerful and practical way to create 3D models that will appeal to anyone who wants to create quality 3D animated content for the web. A versatile NURBS-based 3D Modeler/Animator designed for ease of use without compromising artistic freedom, allowing you to create unique models.
Features of Seamless3d
	WYSIWYG
	Undo/Redo
	Export clean, efficient files
	Dedicated...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare Recoverit 13.6.2.12</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Sep 2025 16:27:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-recoverits-374.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-recoverits-374.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare Recoverit is a data recovery software that is easily lost at a rapid rate and is used by many people. You will do what happens if one day your data is suddenly lost due to the virus or deleted it, .. Wondershare Recoverit will provide you with an environment to protect important data.
Wondershare Recoverit has all the scanning processes that are divided into multiple types, from the typical recovery of the deleted files that are deleted to the recovery of missing files due...
</description></item><item><title>Download yt-dlp 2025.09.05</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Sep 2025 16:27:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-dlp-6802.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-dlp-6802.html
</guid><description>
yt-dlp is a youtube-dl branch based on youtube-dlc currently not working. The main focus of this project is the addition of new features and patches while still updating the original project.
</description></item><item><title>Download Nitro Pro Enterprise 14.41.0.15</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Sep 2025 16:26:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nitro-pdf-pro-34.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nitro-pdf-pro-34.html
</guid><description>
Nitro Pro Enterprise create, edit and convert PDF files easily with the help of the visual program this also allows users to accurately extract text from PDF files thanks to OCR function of it. Nitro Pro is one of the software solutions, create and edit PDF most advanced, providing basically all the tools you need to help you in this area. Although it is called 'Professional', this app has been developed to target beginners and advanced users, so you won't feel too hard to use.
Direct...
</description></item><item><title>Download DesktopSnowOK 6.69</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Sep 2025 16:26:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopsnowok-1950.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopsnowok-1950.html
</guid><description>
DesktopSnowOK is an application to create snow fall effect interesting, DesktopSnowOK allows you to animate your desktop with the flakes of snow virtual. You can choose from many types of scales, configure the number of flakes (5-64) and the speed of them. The interface of DesktopSnowOK is quite simple but allows you to make more customization. At any time you can also choose to activate or deactivate DesktopSnowOK by the Activate/ Deactivate, click on Start with Windows to launch the app...
</description></item><item><title>Download BackUp Maker Pro 8.315</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Sep 2025 16:26:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-backup-maker-pro-480.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-backup-maker-pro-480.html
</guid><description>
BackUp Maker Pro is software backup, data recovery secure against hazards like virus attack, system error or due to the user mistakenly deleted data... BackUp Maker Pro security of your files regularly so that in case of emergency, data your computer you can still gain access. BackUp Maker automatically stores your data and at the same time provide intuitive operation: select your data, optionally set the automation to backup according to schedules, select the destination and immediately,...
</description></item><item><title>Download StaxRip 2.50.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Sep 2025 16:25:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-staxrip-2930.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-staxrip-2930.html
</guid><description>
StaxRip app is a comprehensive and powerful, allowing you to convert all video files DVB, DVD, or DV video into a variety of file formats. The program is open Source, meaning completely free to download and use. StaxRip can support many video formats such as x264, MPEG-4, DivX, XviD, MPEG-2 and many other formats. The format sounds different also be supported, including MP2 / MPA, AAC, WAV, Ogg Vorbis, MP3, AC3, DTS and other formats. Moreover, the program also supports a variety of...
</description></item><item><title>Download VovSoft Webcam Capture 3.4</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Sep 2025 16:25:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-webcam-capture-4683.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-webcam-capture-4683.html
</guid><description>
VovSoft Webcam Capture is a solution very simple software allows you to track video webcam of yourself from the user interface, minimalist reasonable. It offers a number of photo effects and can help you modify the properties of your webcam. You can click on the Start button and here you go. You can easily change the webcam device of software. Webcam Capture is a Windows native applications.
VovSoft Webcam Capture only requires DirectX 9 was installed in Windows XP SP2 and above. You...
</description></item><item><title>Download Stellar Data Recovery Technician 12.3.0.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Sep 2025 16:24:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stellar-data-recovery-technician-3561.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stellar-data-recovery-technician-3561.html
</guid><description>
Stellar Data Recovery Technician is a other version helps you to recover lost data like files, photos, videos, emails and many other things from hard drive Windows storage media and RAID arrays. Technicians data recovery of Stellar smart detection parameters RAID key and rebuild the RAID virtual to recover data from the RAID 0 array, RAID 5 and RAID 6 faulty or damaged.
Software Stellar Data Recovery Technician provides advanced functions for recovering data from servers, RAID 0, 5 and 6...
</description></item><item><title>Download KeyScrambler Premium 3.18.0.5 + Professional</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Sep 2025 16:24:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-keyscrambler-premium-professional-143.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-keyscrambler-premium-professional-143.html
</guid><description>
KeyScrambler Premium / Professional allows users to search for and remove the malicious program, the spy program on the computer system. This program support users to handle a number of spy programs send user information to the server by way thoroughly remove them from the system.
KeyScrambler Premium Key key encryption real-time encryption key, every key you type deep in the Windows. It protects the personal information of you against all malware keylog already know and not know on...
</description></item><item><title>Download FileOptimizer 17.10</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Sep 2025 16:23:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fileoptimizer-2994.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fileoptimizer-2994.html
</guid><description>
FileOptimizer is a free software user support compress multiple file formats on a computer, reducing the capacity to easily share or store that still does not affect the original quality of the file. FileOptimizer will optimize the file size with no data loss supports BMP, DIB, DLL, BPL, DRV, LZL, SYS, CHM, CHS, CHW, DOC, DOT, FPX, MDB, MDT, MIX, MPD, MPP, MPT, MSI, MSP, MST, ONE, OST, PPS, PPT, PUB, PUZ STICKYNOTES, SNT THUMBS, DB, VSD, VST, VSS, XL, XLC, XLM, XLS, XLW, XSF, XSN, EXE,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Nitro Pro 14.41.0.15 Retail</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Sep 2025 16:22:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nitro-pro-379.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nitro-pro-379.html
</guid><description>
Nitro Pro is software that provides features to create, edit and convert PDF files or share PDF files standard.  This is a simple software, easy to understand and intuitive to use so you can work more efficiently. Nitro Pro you can share your files with others, regardless of whether they are using the platform or device, and Nitro Pro helps convert easily.
Nitro Pro convert one or multiple files into PDF with just one or two clicks. Re-use and re-use content based on the PDF with higher...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDF24 PDF Creator 11.28.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Sep 2025 16:21:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf24-pdf-creator-926.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf24-pdf-creator-926.html
</guid><description>
PDF24 PDF Creator is a printer driver application that lets you convert any document or image can be printed into PDF format. With any application that supports printing any user can also create a PDF file of the document through the virtual printer PDF24. Virtual printer can also save the file under format image files other than PDF such as PNG, JPEG, BMP, TIFF, and PSD. After printing, a help section of the program that pops up allows the user to view, save, send, edit that...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ambiera CopperCube Professional 6.7.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Sep 2025 16:21:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ambiera-coppercube-professional-853.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ambiera-coppercube-professional-853.html
</guid><description>
Ambiera CopperCube Professional is the editor to create applications, games and website 3D. Create 3D models, set camera controls, material.. Ambiera CopperCube create everything from the view simple model to the full 3D game. You can do all this without programming.
Ambiera CopperCube Professional - Create apps, build 3D scenes
CopperCube is an editor tool complete 3D includes all the features you need to create games for multiple platforms. And it's very lightweight: the Whole...
</description></item><item><title>Download Stellar Toolkit for Data Recovery 12.3.0.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Sep 2025 16:21:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stellar-toolkit-for-data-recovery-3330.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stellar-toolkit-for-data-recovery-3330.html
</guid><description>
Stellar Toolkit for Data Recovery is recovery software lost data or can't access, can restore the file buffer is not full or corrupt, and the Windows operating system, Mac and Linux. Sometimes the data on the hard drive can be deleted due to a system error or malfunction. In such cases, use a recovery software can strongly increase the possibility of data recovery and save your important data from the risk of permanently deleted.
Stellar Toolkit for Data Recovery - recover lost...
</description></item><item><title>Download Power-user for PowerPoint and Excel 1.7.51.150</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Sep 2025 16:20:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-power-user-for-powerpoint-and-excel-522.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-power-user-for-powerpoint-and-excel-522.html
</guid><description>
Power-user for PowerPoint and Excel is a utility providing you with a library of templates, icons, charts, maps and diagrams for spreadsheet and presentation. With Power-user for PowerPoint and Excel, you will attract the attention of your audience with stunning graphics will certainly impress.
Power-user comes with a collection of 2,000 icons to illustrate your slides. The icons are vector shapes so you can resize them without distortion and color back as you with. With Power-user, you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Monkeys Audio 11.42</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Sep 2025 16:19:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-monkeys-audio-949.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-monkeys-audio-949.html
</guid><description>
Monkey\'s Audio is software that compresses digital music without loss of quality. Supports high quality WAV files and CD ripping. Monkeys Audio will compress .wav tracks into .ape files to reduce their size without loss of sound quality, decompress .ape, convert files, check file integrity and manage tags.
Unlike traditional methods like MP3 and OGG, which permanently remove quality to save space, Monkey\'s Audio only creates perfect copies with the same sound quality as the originals....
</description></item><item><title>Download Ortmann Pixel Art Designer 7.8.1.822</title><pubDate> Sat, 06 Sep 2025 16:19:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ortmann-pixel-art-designer-12404.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ortmann-pixel-art-designer-12404.html
</guid><description>
With the new software ORTMANN Pixel Art Designer©, you can create Diamond Painting® patterns based on your own photos. Also for other techniques, such as:
	Diamond Painting
	Artkal Bügelperle
	Hama Bügelperlen
	MiniSteck
	Lego Mosaik
	as well as any other mosaic technique.
Load your favorites. photo, for example a photo of your pet or a beautiful vacation memory - and convert it into a diamond painting pattern with just a few mouse clicks!
</description></item></channel></rss>