<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 13:47:57 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 13:47:57 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download ProShot 8.32.3 build 539</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 16:18:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-proshot-8195.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-proshot-8195.html
</guid><description>
ProShot is a camera app for Android devices that offers advanced manual controls for photography enthusiasts. It allows users to manually adjust settings such as shutter speed, ISO, white balance, and focus. It also offers a level of integration, a powerful time-lapse mode, and many other features for advanced photography. It's designed for advanced users who want more control over their photos than the default camera app offers.
Camera features of ProShot
	Auto, Program, Manual and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Chat AI - AI Chatbot Assistant v228.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 16:18:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-chat-ai-ai-chatbot-assistant-11260.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-chat-ai-ai-chatbot-assistant-11260.html
</guid><description>
AI Chatbot is a smart artificial intelligence interactive application that brings a unique and convenient experience to users. With AI Chatbot, you can communicate and ask questions directly with a powerful AI system that helps you find information, answer questions, and even provide solutions to complex problems.
Main features of Chatbot AI include
	Natural conversation: Chatbot AI uses advanced natural language technology to understand and respond to your questions and requests...
</description></item><item><title>Download Weather &amp;amp; Radar USA - Pro 2025.24</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 16:18:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-weather-radar-usa-pro-8391.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-weather-radar-usa-pro-8391.html
</guid><description>
Weather &amp;amp; Radar USA is a mobile application that provides users with real-time weather information and forecasts for locations in the United States. The app includes many features such as current weather conditions, hourly and daily forecasts, radar and satellite images, and severe weather alerts. It also includes many customizable settings, such as the ability to set up multiple locations and receive notifications about specific weather conditions.
Features of Weather &amp;amp; Radar...
</description></item><item><title>Download Bass Booster &amp;amp; Equalizer PRO 1.9.5</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 16:17:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-bass-booster-equalizer-pro-10057.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-bass-booster-equalizer-pro-10057.html
</guid><description>
This is the premium version of Bass Booster &amp;amp; Equalizer. Enjoy an ad-free experience, premium features, and priority support of Bass Booster &amp;amp; Equalizer! Improve the sound quality of your Android device with Bass Boost, Volume Boost, Virtualizer and Equalizer. Make your music and videos sound like never before. Bass Booster and Volume Booster allow you to adjust sound effect levels so you get the most out of the Music, Audio or Video coming from your device.
Features of Bass...
</description></item><item><title>Download MIUI Hidden Settings Activity 1.6.12</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 16:17:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-miui-hidden-settings-activity-8889.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-miui-hidden-settings-activity-8889.html
</guid><description>
MIUI hidden settings app is a launcher that works to find and explore all hidden options for mi phones (Miui Rom like Xiaomi Poco, redmi,...) newer operating system, MIUI 10, 11, 12 and also for Android like Samsung, LG, ...
MI Hidden Settings shows all installed settings, allowing you to reveal, unlock and change settings, find and display system and hardware information or discover new features . it uses the system package name of this setting and searches for it in internally...
</description></item><item><title>Download Running Tracker App – FITAPP 8.9.5</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 16:17:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-fitapp-track-my-run-running-8392.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-fitapp-track-my-run-running-8392.html
</guid><description>
FITAPP Track My Run &amp;amp; Running is a fitness tracking mobile application that allows users to track and analyze their running activities. It often includes features like GPS tracking, allowing users to track their route, distance, speed, and time. It also includes many tools for analyzing performance, such as graphs and charts that display data such as heart rate, calories burned, and elevation.
FITAPP will also help you lose weight, count calories, maintain your target weight or...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sygic GPS Navigation &amp;amp; Maps 25.6.1-2487</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 16:16:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sygic-gps-navigation-maps-8606.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sygic-gps-navigation-maps-8606.html
</guid><description>
Sygic GPS Navigation &amp;amp; Maps is the most downloaded GPS navigation app in the world, trusted by more than 200 million drivers. Offline 3D maps stored on your phone for GPS navigation without an internet connection. We update our maps for free multiple times each year so you can always rely on Sygic GPS Navigation.
Navigate anywhere, even without an Internet connection
	Offline maps of all the countries in the world, from TomTom and other providers
	Free map updates several times...
</description></item><item><title>Download Solid Explorer File Manager 3.2.1 beta</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 16:16:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-solid-explorer-file-manager-8924.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-solid-explorer-file-manager-8924.html
</guid><description>
Solid Explorer is a file management application inspired by old file management applications. Solid Explorer is a popular file management app for Android devices that allows users to manage and organize their files and folders in an intuitive and user-friendly interface. It offers many features that make it stand out from other file management apps.
Solid Explorer allows you to navigate to files stored on your device and automatically organize them into collections. You can view,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Weather &amp;amp; Widget - Weawow 7.0.5</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 16:16:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-weather-widget-weawow-8870.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-weather-widget-weawow-8870.html
</guid><description>
Weawow is a beautiful and highly accurate weather forecast application. You can also sell your photos at the Weawow marketplace. Weawow is a comprehensive and user-friendly weather app and widget that provides users with accurate and reliable weather information and forecasts as well as a host of other features and functions. This is a useful tool for those who want to stay up to date with the latest forecasts and weather conditions, whether for personal or professional purposes.
Weawow...
</description></item><item><title>Download All-In-One Calculator 3.2.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 16:15:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-all-in-one-calculator-9092.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-all-in-one-calculator-9092.html
</guid><description>
All-In-One Calculator is a simple, clean and easy-to-use calculator with a full set of tools for everyday life, such as a unit converter, currency converter, percentage calculator and more. From simple or complex calculations, to unit and currency conversions, percentages, ratios, area, volume, etc. it does it all. And it does it!
Features of All-In-One Calculator
Main Calculator
	Simple or Scientific Layout
	40 Light or Dark (AMOLED) Themes
	Editable Input &amp;amp; Cursor
	Copy &amp;amp;...
</description></item><item><title>Download XAPK Installer 4.6.7</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 16:15:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-xapk-installer-14218.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-xapk-installer-14218.html
</guid><description>
Is there an easier way to install apk apps on your device? This all-in-one xapk installer for Android will help you! Our app will help you download and install files seamlessly from apkpure and other sources. No need to search for folders, unzip packages, or use manual methods.
Although this is an apk installer for Android, it is also a full-fledged xapk installer to satisfy all users' requirements for an xapk file downloader. Our tool recognizes both .apk and .xapk files in just a few...
</description></item><item><title>Download IPTV Pro 9.1.12</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 16:15:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-iptv-pro-9093.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-iptv-pro-9093.html
</guid><description>
IPTV Pro is an Android application that allows you to watch live TV channels and movies on your Android device. It provides access to many channels from around the world, including sports, news, movies, and entertainment channels. IPTV Pro supports both M3U and XSPF playlists, and allows you to add your own playlists.
IPTV Pro Features
	Supports M3U and XSPF playlists
	Playlist history
	Play a multicast stream using a UDP proxy (the proxy needs to be installed in your LAN)
	Grid, list...
</description></item><item><title>Download KMPlayer Plus (Divx Codec) 35.11.251</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 16:14:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-kmplayer-plus-divx-codec-8720.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-kmplayer-plus-divx-codec-8720.html
</guid><description>
KMPlayer Plus with DivX codec is also available for Android devices, providing a powerful media player that supports many video and audio formats. These features include ad-free playback, cloud storage support, and high-resolution video playback support.
With support for DivX, KMPlayer Plus for Android allows users to watch high-quality DivX encoded videos on their mobile devices without the need for additional codecs or software. This is a convenient feature for users who want to watch...
</description></item><item><title>Download QuickEdit Text Editor Pro 1.12.2 build 256</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 16:14:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-quickedit-text-editor-pro-9059.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-quickedit-text-editor-pro-9059.html
</guid><description>
QuickEdit is a fast, stable and full-featured text editor for Android devices. It has been optimized for both phones and tablets. This app is designed to provide a variety of features and tools that make editing and formatting text on mobile devices as easy and efficient as possible.
QuickEdit Text Editor Pro Features
	Advanced notepad application with many improvements.
	Code editor and syntax highlighting for over 40 languages ​​(C++, C#, Java, XML, Javascript, Markdown, PHP,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Podcast Republic - Podcast app 25.11.21R</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 16:13:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-podcast-republic-podcast-app-8131.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-podcast-republic-podcast-app-8131.html
</guid><description>
Podcast Republic is a podcast app that allows users to discover, download and listen to podcasts on their mobile devices. Podcast Republic is a top quality Podcast App on Android with 4+ million downloads, 76k+ authentic reviews, 600k+ podcasts, and 40+ million episodes worldwide. It offers features like automatic downloading, variable playback speed, and the ability to create and manage playlists. Podcast Republic also supports Android Auto and Chromecast, so you can listen to podcasts...
</description></item><item><title>Download Battery Guru: Battery Info 2.4.3.2 build 643</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 16:13:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-battery-guru-battery-health-8651.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-battery-guru-battery-health-8651.html
</guid><description>
Battery Guru displays battery usage information, measures battery capacity (mAh), shows estimates, and helps you change your charging habits with helpful tips to extend battery life and increase battery life up 200%.
Features of Battery Guru for Android
	Batteries have a limited lifespan, each time you charge your device, the battery wears out, reducing its total (design) capacity.
	Now you can reduce wear and tear, spend less time tethering your device to the charger, and get the...
</description></item><item><title>Download WiFi Mouse Pro 5.6.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 16:13:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wifi-mouse-pro-8925.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wifi-mouse-pro-8925.html
</guid><description>
Convert your phone into a wireless mouse, keyboard and trackpad for your computer, it allows you to control your PC/Mac/Linux easily via local network connection. Media Controller, Presentation Controller and Remote File Explorer are all included in this controller app.
Now you can relax on the sofa and control movies or games in the comfort of your own home, replacing your broken mouse and keyboard with this app.
Features of WiFi Mouse Pro
	Fully simulated mouse
	Built-in support...
</description></item><item><title>Download CamSam PLUS 3.9.8 build 141</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 16:13:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-camsam-plus-11110.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-camsam-plus-11110.html
</guid><description>
Camsam Plus the Speed ​​and Red Light Camera Warning System! With Camsam Plus You Receive Editorially Verified Speedcam Alerts in Real Time. More than 5 million participants worldwide report Daily on Newly Discovered Speedcams.
Overview of Functions
	Real Time Alerts of Mobile Radar Traps
	More than 60,000 Fixed Speedcams Worldwide from SCDB.Info
	Directional alerts for all fixed speedcams
	speed camera map
	Automatic Updates Every 5 Minutes
	Visual and Acoustic...
</description></item><item><title>Download Fake GPS 5.8.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 16:12:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-fake-gps-8178.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-fake-gps-8178.html
</guid><description>
Fake GPS is an app "Fake GPS" is a type of app that allows users to spoof their device's GPS location, making it appear to be somewhere other than their actual location. Surname. These types of apps are often used for a variety of reasons, such as for testing location-based apps, hiding one's location from certain apps or websites, or for use in mobile experiences. virtual reality or augmented reality experience.
The following are required to ensure the application runs smoothly:
	You...
</description></item><item><title>Download AR Ruler App: Tape Measure Cam 3.1.6</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 16:12:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ar-ruler-app-tape-measure-cam-8721.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ar-ruler-app-tape-measure-cam-8721.html
</guid><description>
AR Ruler app is a mobile app that uses augmented reality (AR) technology to measure distances, angles, and sizes of objects in real-world environments. This app works by using the device's camera and sensors to create a virtual 3D representation of a real-life environment.
The AR Ruler app uses augmented reality (AR) technology to measure the real world using your smartphone's camera. Target the detected plane and start using the AR
tape measure tool
Features of AR Ruler...
</description></item><item><title>Download Acode - code editor | FOSS 1.11.7 build 966</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 16:12:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-acode-code-editor-foss-8264.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-acode-code-editor-foss-8264.html
</guid><description>
Acode is a free and open source code editing application for Android devices. It allows users to edit and code on their mobile devices and supports multiple programming languages ​​and file formats. This is a useful tool for programmers and developers who need to work with code on the go or away from their primary development environment.
You can use this editor to edit HTML, JavaScript, text. You can create a website, run it in your browser, and view errors or logs in the console....
</description></item><item><title>Download Genius Scan Enterprise 7.33.3 build 7068</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 16:11:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-genius-scan-enterprise-8561.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-genius-scan-enterprise-8561.html
</guid><description>
Genius Scan Enterprise: Quickly scan your paper documents on the go and export them as multi-page PDF files. Place any document in front of your device's camera: our scanner app automatically recognizes the paper on the background, crops it and cleans the result. You get sharp, easy-to-read scans. Batch scanning allows you to scan dozens of pages in just a few seconds. Powerful tools help you organize, share or archive your documents.
Features of Genius Scan Enterprise for...
</description></item><item><title>Download iLMeteo: weather forecast 2.72.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 16:11:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ilmeteo-weather-forecast-13328.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ilmeteo-weather-forecast-13328.html
</guid><description>
iLMeteo is a reliable and accurate weather forecast application, thanks to the Nowcasting technique, perfect for planning and enjoying your day, without being surprised by sudden weather changes. Thanks to the new metheograms and webcams, detailed information on sea, wind, air quality, radar and custom widgets, the iLMeteo app will give you all the information you are looking for and you will never be surprised by weather changes.
iLMeteo Features
	Weather forecast for the whole...
</description></item><item><title>Download Smart AudioBook Player 11.6.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 16:11:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-smart-audiobook-player-8181.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-smart-audiobook-player-8181.html
</guid><description>
Smart AudioBook Player is a type of application that allows users to listen to audiobooks on their mobile devices. This app is designed to improve the listening experience by providing features such as automatic bookmarking, adjustable playback speed, and sleep timer. The program is specially designed to play audio books. Let's say you have audiobooks and have copied them to your phone.
Smart AudioBook Player Features
	Supports Chromecast.
	Control playback speed.
	Categorize books...
</description></item><item><title>Download Learn Coding/Programming: Mimo 6.14</title><pubDate> Thu, 27 Nov 2025 16:11:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-learn-codingprogramming-mimo-11634.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-learn-codingprogramming-mimo-11634.html
</guid><description>
Code in Python, JavaScript, HTML, CSS or SQL and start your career in Technology in 5 minutes a day! Whether you're an aspiring developer or just starting your journey Code in HTML, JavaScript, or other programming languages, the Mimo programming and coding app is designed to make learning to code accessible, engaging, and effective. Learn to code in these languages popular programming languages ​​like Python, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, SQL, etc. With Mimo coding app, you can learn...
</description></item></channel></rss>