<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:41:24 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:41:24 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Ultracopier 3.0.1.3</title><pubDate> Wed, 26 Nov 2025 01:07:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-supercopier-2121.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-supercopier-2121.html
</guid><description>
SuperCopier is a replacement for advanced copy command Windows standard. Supercopier support pause and resume the copy operation is ongoing, install copy speed can adjust, automatically rename the old file, and more.
You can view a detailed list of queue copy and optionally move files up or down in the list, add additional files and also can delete or ignore the category when needed. This can be especially useful when you copy large number of files.
Supercopier - copy...
</description></item><item><title>Download LDPlayer 9.1.82.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 22:32:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ldplayer-2331.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ldplayer-2331.html
</guid><description>
LDPlayer is an Android emulator that allows users to play games and run applications on Windows computers. LDPlayer supports heavy gaming, running chat applications, editing photos, videos, and many other Android applications. LDPlayer is compatible with Android 5.1 and above, supporting multitasking for an experience that is not inferior to that of using on Mobile.
Installation is a simple and quick process that does not require any special attention from you, there are more. settings,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Office Timeline Plus 13.05.00.00 Expert / Pro / Pro+ Edition</title><pubDate> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 22:30:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-timeline-2106.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-timeline-2106.html
</guid><description>
Office Timeline is an add-on very useful and powerful software for Microsoft PowerPoint. With add-ons, you can create PowerPoint documents look more beautiful. With add-ons, you can add the time Line on the project by yourself. Application time for the composition and different segments of the document, your PowerPoint will not only increase the beauty for your work, but also for customers and your manager. The people who created this product is also believe that add-ons this is the only...
</description></item><item><title>Download Apowersoft Video Download Capture 6.6.2.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 22:29:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-apowersoft-video-download-capture-1556.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-apowersoft-video-download-capture-1556.html
</guid><description>
Apowersoft Video Download Capture is a comprehensive tool with advanced technologies for media streaming to choice cost-effective to download videos from YouTube, Dailymotion, Vimeo, Yahoo Screen and Hulu, as well as millions of other websites. Apowersoft Video Download Capture is your download video powerful and effective this can download and save videos, movies, tv episodes and music videos online. It also has the switch function, supports convert any video to MP4, AVI, MKV, WMV and the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ashampoo PDF Pro 5.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 22:29:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-pdf-business-272.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-pdf-business-272.html
</guid><description>
Ashampoo PDF Pro and Ashampoo PDF Business software is responsible for managing the file PDF offers you the tool effective and flexible when working with data Files PDF. Ashampoo PDF Business full support, such as viewing and creating PDF files, particular emphasis was placed on editing documents as simple as editing text in a word processor of your favorites.
Ashampoo PDF Business
Ashampoo PDF Business can convert your documents into popular formats such as Word, fill in the form with...
</description></item><item><title>Download TeamViewer QuickSupport 15.72.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 22:28:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-teamviewer-quicksupport-1933.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-teamviewer-quicksupport-1933.html
</guid><description>
A different version of TeamViewer is TeamViewer QuickSupport is a solution easy to use allows you to share your desktop with a users TeamViewer other to receive technical support or other support. All what you need to do is run the TeamViewer QuickSupport and provides for the remote user ID and your password to grant access to the computer to your desk. Only people you trust can connect to your computer and access password will automatically change after each session.
The software also...
</description></item><item><title>Download CoolUtils PDF Combine Pro 4.2.0.153/104</title><pubDate> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 22:28:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-pdf-combine-pro-580.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-pdf-combine-pro-580.html
</guid><description>
CoolUtils PDF Combine Pro  is software that helps you combine  PDF, DOC, TXT, DOCX, HTML, XLS, images  h (TIFF, JPEG, PNG) and  email  as a  PDF  file. With PDF Combine Pro it is easier than ever to combine documents into one PDF file. Now you don't have to use some programs and converters to get a PDF. Everything for PDF Combine Pro to do for you.
Office, fax, email files - get combined PDF in seconds for personal use, commercial needs, electronic discovery, or manufacturing.  PDF...
</description></item><item><title>Download Classroom Spy Professional 5.4.12</title><pubDate> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 22:27:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-classroom-spy-professional-916.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-classroom-spy-professional-916.html
</guid><description>
Classroom Spy Professional is a software classroom management effective. Manage and track activities of all the computers of students remotely. Plus, you can share your screen with the activity record of the student, the computer controls for performance, limit the use of the Internet, the application blocks and more.
Classroom Spy Professional - software classroom management
The main features of Classroom Spy Professional
	Display live images of the remote computer.
	You can control...
</description></item><item><title>Download AnyTrans for iOS 8.9.13.20251125</title><pubDate> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 22:27:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anytrans-for-ios-755.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anytrans-for-ios-755.html
</guid><description>
AnyTrans for iOS is content manager essential fully managed iPhone, Android and content of your cloud. Including all mobile devices, all cloud drives from your iPhone, iPad, iPod touch to phones and tablets. From local disk to cloud storage. AnyTrans has protected them all, providing you convenient management for all data and your files, regardless of whether they are stored where.
AnyTrans is the one stop solution to meet all the management needs of your data. For the first time, you can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Waterfox 6.6.5.1 / 2022.11</title><pubDate> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 22:27:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-waterfox-114.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-waterfox-114.html
</guid><description>
Waterfox is a 64-bit version of the foundation Firefox was built and the compiler Intel is optimized for speed and performance on Windows systems.Waterfox does not add any additional features or bling, in fact, it will automatically import all the gadgets and install is have of you, so you will feel like at home when you run it the first time.All the add-on your Firefox will work with Waterfox, however, only support the plug-in more 64-bit, is includes Adobe Flash, Oracle Java and...
</description></item><item><title>Download ExamDiff Pro Master Edition 16.0.1.14</title><pubDate> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 22:26:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-examdiff-pro-master-312.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-examdiff-pro-master-312.html
</guid><description>
ExamDiff Pro Master is a tool to compare files and folders intuitive and easy to use, intuitive and easy to use for Windows. ExamDiff Pro Master has unique features distinguishes ExamDiff Pro with the program compare other. ExamDiff Pro Master to help perform reviews of code and share other reports with your colleagues and compare local website with FTP server by plug-ins more integrated.
ExamDiff Pro Master can create a snapshot folder for comparison and storage in the future, compare...
</description></item><item><title>Download TeamViewer 15.72.3 + Portable</title><pubDate> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 22:25:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-teamviewer-528.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-teamviewer-528.html
</guid><description>
TeamViewer is software that functions to connect and control the remote computer, the ability to connect with any system anywhere from all over the place. This is a support tool users is very convenient. TeamViewer to help users control remote computer becomes much more simple, help you interact and collaborate with others in the exchange and share of information, instruction manual, application software or fix the computer.
TeamViewer as a revolution of computer science. when you have...
</description></item><item><title>Download EverNote 10.164.2.24280</title><pubDate> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 22:25:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-evernote-3261.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-evernote-3261.html
</guid><description>
EverNote is the all in one tool allows you to track notes, todo items, memos, outlines, excerpts, websites, ideas and other things and automatically synchronize them between multiple computers and mobile devices (iPhone, Android, etc.). You can choose to sort their notes into categories, password protect them, export them to XML and more. EverNote supports a number of pattern notes allow you to add to-do list, spreadsheet like Excel to calculate costs (automatic sum), notes, phone, contact...
</description></item><item><title>Download CleverGet 24.0.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 22:25:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cleverget-8570.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cleverget-8570.html
</guid><description>
CleverGet is a download manager to download 8K Videos, Live Streaming and even paid services from 1000+ websites like YouTube, Facebook, Twitter, Twitch.tv, HBO Max, Netflix, Amazon, Disney+, Hulu, HBO Max, U-NEXT, and more In addition, you can also use it to download high quality audio, download lossless 320 kbps video and audio 8K and 320 kbps are new popular formats for high quality video and audio , and CleverGet is almost the only tool that allows downloading 8K video and audio at...
</description></item><item><title>Download AIMP 5.40 Build 2700 + Portable</title><pubDate> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 22:24:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aimp-1302.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aimp-1302.html
</guid><description>
AIMP is a free audio with support for large number of formats and playlists. It works with multiple playlists immediately, allows creation of bookmarks and also has the playback queue.
AIMP - audio player
Features of AIMP
	Clear sound, technology of re-creating fundamentally different from Winamp and WMP
	The balance sensitivity
	Maximum functions from minimal resource
	Minimum consumption of system resources
	Multi-language support
	Support the audio format
	Adjust the hot keys for...
</description></item><item><title>Download DroidKit 2.3.7.20251125</title><pubDate> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 22:24:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-droidkit-6578.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-droidkit-6578.html
</guid><description>
DroidKit is data recovery software for your mobile device, it will quickly scan your phone memory and save photos, WhatsApp chats and files, messages Messages, contacts and more essential data up to 13 categories, covering almost everything you need every day. All Android phones and tablets are supported. Without rooting your device. No tech skills required. No need to wait many days. You can get back what you've lost with just a few simple clicks, instantly.
Besides, DroidKit also has...
</description></item><item><title>Download Software Ideas Modeler Ultimate 15.16</title><pubDate> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 22:23:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-software-ideas-modeler-ultimate-10388.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-software-ideas-modeler-ultimate-10388.html
</guid><description>
Software Ideas Modeler Ultimate is a feature-rich CASE tool that can help you design software using various modeling tools and schematic notations. It will help you create a UML model, ERD designer, diagram generator, wireframing tool or BPMN editor.
Features of Software Ideas Modeler Ultimate
	Tools for UML diagrams, class diagrams, block diagrams, data flow diagrams, and other tools help you design your software or its key parts accurately.
	Handle user requests...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adlice Protect (formerly RogueKiller) 16.5.2.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 22:23:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rogueKiller-171.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rogueKiller-171.html
</guid><description>
RogueKiller is a tool anti-malware independent can assist advanced users with the removal of a number of difficulties in the removal of malware, in security software rogue special.
The program can terminate processes, malware has to know to you can delete them manually or use the tool clear of the Tuesday to complete the work. RogueKiller can also restore HOSTS file as well as your DNS settings and Proxy, which is often modified by rogue applications.
RogueKiller
When you run...
</description></item><item><title>Download FBackup 9.9.999</title><pubDate> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 22:22:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fbackup-1834.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fbackup-1834.html
</guid><description>
FBackup enables you to backup files and important folders on the hard drive locally or outside (not memory card, USB drive) or network drive. You can create multiple backup sets and schedule them to run automatically at the times defined in advance. The backups can be compressed into a ZIP file to be stored or reproduced in copy form files standard.
Modern interface
The program interface is quite easy to use, FBackup supports multi-language and provided the free utility, can also be...
</description></item><item><title>Download PhoneRescue for iOS 4.3.1.20251125</title><pubDate> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 22:22:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-phonerescue-for-ios-2851.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-phonerescue-for-ios-2851.html
</guid><description>
PhoneRescue for iOS is the solution to restore lost data of iOS devices such as iPhone, iPad with the ability to work quickly find back all the data on the device such as music, videos, photos, call logs, contacts, or even sms. With PhoneRescue is that you don't need to connect iPhone device with the computer directly, the software works through the index and account, now you can completely assured when using data on the iPhone, by all user's data are lost, you can restore back...
</description></item><item><title>Download Brickaizer 8.0.4.7</title><pubDate> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 22:22:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-brickaizer-3680.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-brickaizer-3680.html
</guid><description>
Brickaizer+ is a tool quite interesting to help create the mosaic unique. Software Brickaizer have the ability to create the perfect color match every color combination and size can. A number of tools mix color high precision is used, including color schemes, colour - and black and white, and tool joint color Mosaizer XV. Even from a close distance, can see beautiful pictures, don't need to walk 5 meters to get rid of the markings do not match.
Brickaizer+ - Create mosaic...
</description></item><item><title>Download Bforartists 5.0.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 16:55:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bforartists-7643.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bforartists-7643.html
</guid><description>
Bforartists is a complete, free and open source 3D suite for creating CG content. It gives you the full 3D art pipeline for creating game graphics, pre-rendered movies, and stills. From modeling, sculpting, texturing, design, animation, rendering, to post processing. The main goal of Bforartists is to provide a refined graphical user interface and better usability. This means a complete shift in usage philosophy away from hotkey-focused usage towards an intuitive and user-friendly...
</description></item><item><title>Download KeepMouseSpeedOK 3.48</title><pubDate> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 16:54:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-keepmousespeedok-2762.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-keepmousespeedok-2762.html
</guid><description>
KeepMouseSpeedOK is a simple app for those who often change the mouse speed and are looking for ways to do this from the system tray icon instead of mouse settings Windows. In addition to changing the cursor speed, the program also can lock the speed setting to ensure that the application of the Tuesday not changed. If you need access tot he full the mouse settings, a shortcut is provided in the tray icon and the file menu.
KeepMouseSpeedOK - control mouse speed
Program is suitable...
</description></item><item><title>Download CyberLink PhotoDirector Ultra 2026 v17.0.1124.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 16:53:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-photodirector-ultra-129.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-photodirector-ultra-129.html
</guid><description>
Cyberlink PhotoDirector Ultra is known to be photo editing tools and videos with the effect is extremely rich, help you to change the style for the individual images or the videos of his favorite. This software integrated the 3D engine helps to speed up Video processing, which allows accessing the repository effect online and extract the Videos into the movies 3D Bru-ray, 3D AVCHD.
Cyberlink PhotoDirector Ultra to offer users a more professional tool to handle their images, remove...
</description></item><item><title>Download Rhinoceros 8.25.25328.11001</title><pubDate> Tue, 25 Nov 2025 16:52:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rhinoceros-179.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rhinoceros-179.html
</guid><description>
Rhinoceros is design software 3D easy to learn, easy to use and has range of application in various industries. Rhinoceros (or Rhino, Rhino3D) is a graphics software CAD and 3D developed by Robert McNeel &amp;amp; Associates, a private company established in the year 1980. Rhinoceros is developed according to the algorithm NURBS mathematical model, algorithm, focus on the correct presentation of curves and surfaces mathematics in computer graphics (in contrast to the application polygon...
</description></item></channel></rss>