<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 17:43:19 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 17:43:19 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Dynamic Wallpaper Enginer for macOS 23.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 29 Jul 2025 16:52:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/mac/download-dynamic-wallpaper-enginer-macos-13314.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/mac/download-dynamic-wallpaper-enginer-macos-13314.html
</guid><description>
Dynamic Wallpaper Engine allows you to use dynamic wallpapers on your desktop/screensaver. It provides thousands of dynamic wallpapers in the Workshop while taking up as little system resources as possible.
Key Features
	Over 4,000 high-quality dynamic wallpapers, updated regularly.
	Search dynamic wallpapers by keyword. Categories include 4K Ultra HD, Anime, Nature, Pets, Games, Beauty, Movies, AI Art, etc.
	Multiple playback modes: Single Loop, Playlist Loop, Shuffle.
	Support...
</description></item><item><title>Download Permute for macOS 3.13.5 (2859)</title><pubDate> Tue, 29 Jul 2025 16:51:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/mac/download-permute-macos-13427.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/mac/download-permute-macos-13427.html
</guid><description>
Video, audio, and image files come in many different shapes and sizes, but sometimes you need a specific format because your iPad or DVD player won't play it. That's what Permute is all about, easily converting your media files to a variety of formats.
Key Features
	Easy to Use: Built from the ground up, Permute is the perfect example of what a Mac app should be. With a beautiful interface and simple drag &amp;amp; drop, no complicated options.
	Permute is designed to be incredibly fast....
</description></item><item><title>Download Boxy SVG for macOS 4.74.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 29 Jul 2025 16:51:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/mac/download-boxy-svg-macos-12937.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/mac/download-boxy-svg-macos-12937.html
</guid><description>
The goal of the Boxy SVG project is to create the best SVG editor for non-technical users as well as for professional designers and developers. SVG is the standard format for storing vector graphics such as icons, banners, charts, and illustrations.
Features of Boxy SVG for macOS
	Clean and intuitive user interface inspired by Inkscape, Sketch, and Adobe Illustrator
	Extensive support for editing object geometry on canvas, transforming, drawing, and other properties
	Save to SVG and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Allavsoft Video Downloader Converter for macOS 3.28.2.9336</title><pubDate> Tue, 29 Jul 2025 16:51:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/mac/download-allavsoft-video-downloader-converter-macos-12939.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/mac/download-allavsoft-video-downloader-converter-macos-12939.html
</guid><description>
This powerful video downloader supports downloading movies, music videos, playlists, sports videos, lectures and more from free video sharing sites like Facebook, Dailymotion, eHow and more than 100 video sharing sites.
Besides downloading videos in original format, Allavsoft also features one-click downloading and converting downloaded videos download to popular video formats like MP4, AVI, WMV, MOV, MPEG-1, MPEG-2, VOB, ASF, RMVB, DV, TS, Apple ProRes, WebM, FLV, OGV, etc.
Features...
</description></item><item><title>Download MouseBoost Pro for macOS 3.8.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 29 Jul 2025 16:51:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/mac/download-mouseboost-pro-macos-13024.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/mac/download-mouseboost-pro-macos-13024.html
</guid><description>
MouseBoost Pro integrates more than 30 kinds of small tools, the operation is very simple, just right-click, you can activate any kind of function you want, greatly improving work efficiency. You can create any file type you want, open any APP you want, organize it yourself, fully customize it!
Features of MouseBoost Pro for Mac
	All menus support custom arrangement.
	Quickly create any commonly used file type and support custom creation of many different file types you want.
	Quickly...
</description></item><item><title>Download iBarcoder for macOS 3.16.11</title><pubDate> Tue, 29 Jul 2025 16:50:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/mac/download-ibarcoder-macos-13539.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/mac/download-ibarcoder-macos-13539.html
</guid><description>
iBarcoder is a professional barcode generator for Mac, allowing to create any number of individual or sequential barcodes, print them into multi-color barcode labels in your own style, in any size or shape, or export them as graphic image files in common vector and raster image formats.
iBarcoder helps you design and print barcode labels, stickers, tags on your Mac in just a few steps. Use our Mac barcode software to generate barcodes of over 40 1-D and 2-D barcode symbologies...
</description></item><item><title>Download EdgeView for macOS 5.1.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 29 Jul 2025 16:50:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/mac/download-edgeview-macos-13433.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/mac/download-edgeview-macos-13433.html
</guid><description>
EdgeView is a fast image viewer with an elegant user interface. EdgeView is developed and designed for modern MacOS. It can open various image files such as JPEG, PNG, TIFF, BMP and RAW files of DSLR, EPS and PDF, AI (Adobe Illustrator). Can open image files in archive directly without extracting.
With EdgeView you can:
	Users can open files, rename files, delete files from EdgeView file browser. Also can access SMB/AFP/FTP network drives.
	Users can quickly navigate images using...
</description></item><item><title>Download Path Finder for macOS 2197</title><pubDate> Tue, 29 Jul 2025 16:50:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/mac/download-path-finder-macos-13698.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/mac/download-path-finder-macos-13698.html
</guid><description>
Path Finder makes you a master of file management. Take full control of your file system. Save your time: compare and sync folders, view hidden files, use Dual Pane and full keyboard navigation to browse your file system.
Work the way you want: extreme customization lets you access most tools in a variety of ways to fit your workflow. Works seamlessly with other platforms: leave no hidden .DS_Store files on non-Mac drives, securely and completely erase files with powerful wipe from any...
</description></item><item><title>Download SponsorBlock for YouTube for macOS 5.14.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 29 Jul 2025 16:49:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/mac/download-sponsorblock-for-youtube-macos-12941.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/mac/download-sponsorblock-for-youtube-macos-12941.html
</guid><description>
SponsorBlock for YouTube on macOS is a popular browser extension designed to skip sponsored segments, intros, outros, subscription prompts, and other unwanted parts of YouTube videos. It allows you to skip sponsors, intros, outros, subscription prompts, and other annoying parts of YouTube videos. SponsorBlock is a community-contributed browser extension that allows anyone to submit the start and end times of sponsored segments and other segments of YouTube videos.
What's...
</description></item><item><title>Download Dropzone 4 Pro for macOS 4.80.64</title><pubDate> Tue, 29 Jul 2025 16:49:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/mac/download-dropzone-pro-macos-13227.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/mac/download-dropzone-pro-macos-13227.html
</guid><description>
Dropzone is a Mac app that redefines the drag and drop experience, speeds up file transfers, simplifies app launches, and seamlessly integrates with multiple services to optimize your workflow and increase your productivity. It makes copying and moving files, opening apps, and sharing files with multiple services faster and easier. Dropzone is a unique and amazing app, unlike anything you have ever used before.
Dropzone comes with a powerful scripting API and with a little programming...
</description></item><item><title>Download Multitouch for macOS 1.34</title><pubDate> Tue, 29 Jul 2025 16:49:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/mac/download-multitouch-macos-13432.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/mac/download-multitouch-macos-13432.html
</guid><description>
Multitouch lets you bind a custom action to a specific magic trackpad or magic mouse gesture. For example, a three-finger tap can perform a paste command. Improve your workflow by performing keyboard shortcuts, controlling browser tabs, performing a middle click, and more.
Some popular gestures include:
	Click and Tap: Tap with one finger to click; two-finger tap to right-click.
	Scroll: Swipe two fingers up/down/left/right to scroll documents and web pages.
	Zoom: Pinch open or...
</description></item><item><title>Download TechSmith Snagit for macOS 2024.4.5</title><pubDate> Tue, 29 Jul 2025 16:49:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/mac/download-techsmith-snagit-macos-13431.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/mac/download-techsmith-snagit-macos-13431.html
</guid><description>
TechSmith Snagit is a powerful screen capture and recording tool that makes collecting and sharing information easier than ever. With intuitive editing features and access to a template library, anyone can turn simple captures into professional-quality images, GIFs, and videos.
Key Features
	Capture your screen and camera at the same time.
	Edit captures with tools to redact sensitive information, rearrange objects, and draw directly on the screen.
	Create professional-quality images,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Rectangle Pro for macOS 3.0.57</title><pubDate> Tue, 29 Jul 2025 16:48:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/mac/download-rectangle-pro-macos-12934.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/mac/download-rectangle-pro-macos-12934.html
</guid><description>
Rectangle Pro allows users to arrange windows into various positions on the screen, including quarters, halves, and thirds, using keyboard shortcuts or the drag-and-drop function. The window tossing feature allows users to quickly move and resize windows by holding the adjustment key and moving the cursor in specific directions. It offers eight different window sizes and positions, similar to a compass asterisk.
Features of Rectangle Pro for macOS
	Put windows in the right place. More...
</description></item><item><title>Download PullTube for macOS 1.8.5.75</title><pubDate> Tue, 29 Jul 2025 16:48:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/mac/download-pulltube-macos-13311.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/mac/download-pulltube-macos-13311.html
</guid><description>
A beautiful online video downloader for your Mac. PullTube offers a streamlined workflow for fast video downloading, offers control over output quality, and lets you extract audio to MP3 or M4A files. Save videos from Youtube, TikTok, Twitch, Facebook, Vimeo, Instagram, Bilibili, Soundcloud and more.
PullTube app can handle videos of any length or size and you can track the download progress in the main window of the app. The utility also integrates with Notification Center to send...
</description></item><item><title>Download Downie for macOS 4.10.4</title><pubDate> Tue, 29 Jul 2025 16:48:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/mac/download-downie-001-1660.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/mac/download-downie-001-1660.html
</guid><description>
Downie is a software that supports high quality video download from the Internet to support more than 1,000 different websites for MacOS (including YouTube, Vimeo, etc.) and this number is growing rapidly. Downie Support specific websites by the country, it is localized into many different languages. If your language is missing, please contact us we can give you a free license to exchange for the translation.
Downie - Support to download videos from web for macOS
The main features of...
</description></item><item><title>Download SiteSucker for macOS 5.7.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 29 Jul 2025 16:47:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/mac/download-sitesucker-macos-13715.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/mac/download-sitesucker-macos-13715.html
</guid><description>
SiteSucker is a Macintosh application that automatically downloads websites from the Internet. It does this by asynchronously copying the website's pages, images, PDFs, stylesheets, and other files to your local hard drive, replicating the website's directory structure.
SiteSucker can be used to create local copies of websites. By default, SiteSucker "localizes" the files it downloads, allowing you to browse the site offline, but it can also download sites without modification.
Key...
</description></item><item><title>Download ChatBox: AI Chat Bot Assistant 1.66.7</title><pubDate> Tue, 29 Jul 2025 16:45:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-chatbox-ai-chat-bot-assistant-12995.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-chatbox-ai-chat-bot-assistant-12995.html
</guid><description>
ChatBox is an advanced AI chat application and your virtual assistant built on the most advanced AI chat models. Designed to seamlessly integrate into your daily life, this AI chatbot uses advanced machine learning to improve productivity and provide instant solutions. Whether you're looking for help with a task or need answers to complex questions, your AI chatbot will leverage the latest advances in AI chat to help.
Some Highlights
	ChatBox leverages the latest AI technology to...
</description></item><item><title>Download LINE Camera - Photo editor 17.4.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 29 Jul 2025 16:44:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-line-camera-photo-editor-8219.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-line-camera-photo-editor-8219.html
</guid><description>
LINE Camera - Photo editor is a photo editing application that allows users to enhance and personalize their photos with a variety of filters, stickers and frames.
Some features of the LINE Camera apk app include:
	Camera filters: LINE Camera offers a variety of camera filters that can be applied to photos in real time, allowing users to see the effects before taking a photo.
	Stickers and frames: The app includes a large library of stickers and frames that can be added to photos to...
</description></item><item><title>Download DiskDigger Pro file recovery 1.0-pro-2025-07-28</title><pubDate> Tue, 29 Jul 2025 16:44:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-diskdigger-pro-file-recovery-13674.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-diskdigger-pro-file-recovery-13674.html
</guid><description>
DiskDigger Pro (for rooted devices!) can recover and restore lost photos, documents, videos, music and more from your memory card or internal memory (see supported file types below). Whether you accidentally deleted a file or even reformatted your memory card, DiskDigger's powerful data recovery features can find your lost files and let you recover them.
You can upload recovered files directly to Google Drive, Dropbox, or send them via email. The app also allows you to upload files to...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDF editor &amp;amp; PDF converter pro 9.0 build 106</title><pubDate> Tue, 29 Jul 2025 16:44:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pdf-editor-pdf-converter-pro-9852.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pdf-editor-pdf-converter-pro-9852.html
</guid><description>
PDF Converter &amp;amp; PDF Editor is a very comprehensive tool to perform various operations on pdf files
	Convert Word files to PDF: Now you can convert doc files to pdf files.
	Convert images to PDF files: Convert your jpg to PDF. Click image from camera or select an image from gallery and convert it.
	Website to PDF: Convert html website to PDF and save all articles/news reports to read later.
	Merge pdf: Combine pdf documents into a single document.
	Split documents: Is the file too...
</description></item><item><title>Download Folder Player Pro 5.35 build 349</title><pubDate> Tue, 29 Jul 2025 16:43:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-folder-player-pro-8330.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-folder-player-pro-8330.html
</guid><description>
Folder Player Pro is a mobile music player application available for Android devices. It allows users to play and organize their music files by folders, instead of just by artist or album. This app is perfect for users who have a lot of music files on their device and want to listen to them in a more organized way.
Features of Folder Player Pro APK
	Ability to play music files by folder, making it easy to find and listen to specific songs or albums
	Supports many audio file formats,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Business Calendar 2 Pro 2.52.9 build 252900</title><pubDate> Tue, 29 Jul 2025 16:43:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-business-calendar-8433.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-business-calendar-8433.html
</guid><description>
Business Calendar 2 Pro is the premium version of our popular calendar app. It provides a great overview of your appointments, is easy to use, and gives you powerful tools to plan and schedule your events and tasks.
Features of Business Calendar
Your personal organizer
	calendar, planner and tasks in one app
	6 clearly designed main views: month, week, day, agenda, year and tasks
	popup with live event details in month view
	flexible daily and weekly planning that can be adjusted...
</description></item><item><title>Download Magnifier Plus with Flashlight 4.8.10</title><pubDate> Tue, 29 Jul 2025 16:42:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-magnifier-plus-with-flashlight-8494.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-magnifier-plus-with-flashlight-8494.html
</guid><description>
Are you tired of trying to read labels with small fonts? Now you can use your Android device as the perfect digital magnifier! No need to use a magnifying glass to read small labels - this app lets you see text large and clearly. The magnifier has on-screen zoom and illumination controls for easy operation. You can also use the flash as a light to get a brighter image, and the negative mode inverts the colors so you can see this differently when they're hard to see.
Features of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Smart Launcher 6 ‧ Home Screen 6.5 build 0361</title><pubDate> Tue, 29 Jul 2025 16:42:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-smart-launcher-8412.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-smart-launcher-8412.html
</guid><description>
Smart Launcher is a mobile app that provides users with a customized home screen and app launcher on their Android devices. It includes features like minimalist interface, automatic app sorting, and gesture controls. The app also includes many customizable settings, such as the ability to change the theme, icon size, and screen layout, as well as the ability to create custom categories for the app.
Smart Launcher Features
	Ambient theme: Smart launcher automatically changes theme...
</description></item><item><title>Download OTT Navigator IPTV 1.7.3.2 Beta</title><pubDate> Tue, 29 Jul 2025 16:42:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ott-navigator-iptv-11547.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ott-navigator-iptv-11547.html
</guid><description>
Watch your provider's IPTV on any device (phone, tablet, TV, TV-box). It serves as a platform to watchIPTV unlimited channels. Developed by SIA Scillarium Studio, it works well with your chosen provider's playlists on any available device such as smartphone, tablet, TV or TV-box.
Main features:
Live streaming
	watch live TV
	automatically group favorite channels and categories
	start playing last channel at launch
	timeshift support for providers with repositories
	picture-in-picture...
</description></item></channel></rss>