<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 23:41:33 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 23:41:33 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Mp3Tag 3.31</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 23:51:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mp3tag-150.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mp3tag-150.html
</guid><description>
Mp3tag is a powerful tool and easy to use to edit ID3 tags and OGG comments about the files MP3 - and Ogg Vorbis. It can rename files based on the tag information, replace characters or words from tags and filenames. Help users create and add the tag information for MP3 files to manage the information that is reasonable.
The program supports lookup database freedb online for the selected files, allowing you to automatically gather tag information appropriate for the files or CD selection....
</description></item><item><title>Download EaseUS ClipAce (ScreenShot) 1.5.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 23:50:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-screenshot-7937.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-screenshot-7937.html
</guid><description>
Capture everything on your screen easily through this tool, EaseUS ScreenShot provides users with a powerful set of screen capture tools to meet all their needs. The app is easy to start and use, and it does exactly what you'd expect: it helps you take screenshots without much effort.
You can capture the entire screen or just an area of ​​it. To help improve usability, double-pressing the Alt key automatically captures the full screen, while pressing Ctrl twice will let you select...
</description></item><item><title>Download Stablebit Scanner 2.6.13.4088</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 23:49:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stablebit-scanner-5563.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stablebit-scanner-5563.html
</guid><description>
Stablebit Scanner is the software that scans all your hard drives, ensuring that every precious bit remains readable. It allows you to easily connect to any other copy of it running on your LAN. Rest assured that the Stablebit Scanner is completely safe using the standard Windows Kerberos Authentication. In addition to making sure every bit on your hard drive is readable, the scanner will automatically check the integrity of your file system and notify you as soon as any problems are...
</description></item><item><title>Download Foxit PDF Editor Pro Portable 2025.2.0.33028 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 23:48:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-foxit-pdf-editor-pro-portable-3495.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-foxit-pdf-editor-pro-portable-3495.html
</guid><description>
Foxit is almost the first company to develop software to edit the PDF directly and professionally in a new way. The development of this product, known as Foxit PhantomPDF, is currently growing company and are adding more features every day. And today we give you version Foxit PhantomPDF Business Portable activated full-featured and completely free.
Foxit PhantomPDF Business Portable - mobile Version support create and edit PDF documents
The professional features that this software...
</description></item><item><title>Download StableBit CloudDrive 1.2.13.1839</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 23:48:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stablebit-clouddrive-7738.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stablebit-clouddrive-7738.html
</guid><description>
StableBit CloudDrive is a software that helps mount cloud drives on Windows, It supports a lot of cloud storage providers such as: Amazon S3, Backblaze B2, Box, Dropbox, FTP, Google Cloud Storage, Google Drive, Microsoft Azure, OneDrive for Business, Rackspace...
Features of StableBit CloudDrive
	Cloud storage helps keep your data safer, and it's also cheaper to store than buying a hard drive and storing data on it.
	Your data is instantly encrypted as soon as it is written to your...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDF Anti-Copy Pro Portable 2.6.2.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 23:47:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-anti-copy-pro-portable-4486.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-anti-copy-pro-portable-4486.html
</guid><description>
PDF Anti-Copy Pro Portable is a reliable application and easy to use allows you to protect your PDF documents from being copied or converted to other formats. The program will clear all the rights for the processing of your PDF files. PDF Anti-Copy Pro Portable very easy to use, requires no complicated settings and allows you to delete the right material with just a few simple steps. The interface of the program is intuitive and allows you to easily access all the tools and features...
</description></item><item><title>Download StableBit DrivePool 2.3.13.1687</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 23:46:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stablebit-drivepool-7739.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stablebit-drivepool-7739.html
</guid><description>
StableBit DrivePool is a modern disk merge application with file cloning, it combines multiple physical hard drives into one large virtual drive to store everything in NTFS files (or ReFS) standard. Allows you to specify any folder as the cloned folder. In the event of a drive failure, your duplicate files are safe.
Easily select the disk to be used to store files in any directory. Speed ​​up your team by placing performance-sensitive files on SSDs. Combining StableBit DrivePool...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare Filmora Portable 14.5.20.12999</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 23:46:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-filmora-portable-02en-3752.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-filmora-portable-02en-3752.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare Filmora Portable a simple editor video professional, with this software, you can turn those precious moments into a gorgeous movie, and share it everywhere. Use the edit Filmora to express the creativity and great results your. With the edit this movie, you can add video, music, animation, graphic effects and different filters. Moreover, with Wondershare Filmora Portable you can export videos to various popular video formats and various mobile devices to share and enjoy broader...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ashampoo Burning Studio 26.0.3</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 23:45:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-burning-studio-266.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-burning-studio-266.html
</guid><description>
Ashampoo Burning Studio 19 recording files, movies and music to any disc CD, DVD, or Blu-ray any. It's easy, fast and secure! Record data, create audio CDS, create backups, or create your own movie - the possibilities are endless! Even the senior project as a DVD video with the menu and the scene selection screen is only a few minutes. Get the total solution for the drive recorder of you!
Ashampoo Burning Studio
Features Ashampoo Burning Studio
	Fast, clear and powerful - now with...
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 7.1.5</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 23:45:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-11-7760.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-11-7760.html
</guid><description>
TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 is a program that allows users to discover hidden settings in Windows 11. This application is specially designed for Windows 11, groups many registry settings and distribute them from the easy and secure user interface. With TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 you can move the Windows taskbar to the top and resize the taskbar by editing the registry value. With any application that modifies the registry, we recommend that you have a backup copy...
</description></item><item><title>Download AudioRealism ABL3 v3.3.4.4</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 23:45:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-audiorealism-abl-2335.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-audiorealism-abl-2335.html
</guid><description>
AudioRealism ABL (ABL3) is the next generation of the plug-in simulation 303 is appreciated by us. ABL3 is a re-design complete from the start and has been developed in the last few years with the goal of creating the simulation realistic as possible. With a workflow is intuitive and streamlined, we hope ABL3 will set a new benchmark in software 303.
AudioRealism ABL - plug simulation 303 bassline
Features of AudioRealism ABL
	Improved massively simulation tool 303
	Storage sync...
</description></item><item><title>Download App Builder 2025.22</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 23:44:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-app-builder-241.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-app-builder-241.html
</guid><description>
App Builder is a software application developer to help create and design apps, HTML5, web app, web app PWA on both platforms mobile and desktop. App Builder is professional software supports users to create the program HTML5 without writing code. It is very easy to use, suitable with all users who lack of professional knowledge in the field of programming and application design.
App Builder brings to 22 different themes that users can use to design for your app. You can choose 1 or a...
</description></item><item><title>Download AudioRealism ReDominator 1.5.2.4</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 23:44:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-audiorealism-redominator-9769.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-audiorealism-redominator-9769.html
</guid><description>
AudioRealism ReDominator is an emulation of the classic Hoover Synth, a polyphonic DCO (digitally controlled oscillator) synth from 1986. AJ-1/ 2 became popular in the technical and frenetic scene of the early 90s, especially thanks to the classic Hoover sound (which ReDominator accurately emulates). But beyond those niche sounds, there's a versatile synthesizer with bass, accompaniment, lead, organ, and so much more just waiting to be discovered!
Features of AudioRealism...
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 7.1.5</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 23:43:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-10-7759.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-10-7759.html
</guid><description>
TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 is a utility that allows users to discover hidden settings in Windows 10. This application is specially designed for Windows 10, groups many registry settings and provide them from an easy and secure user interface. With TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 you can move the Windows taskbar to the top and resize the taskbar by editing the registry value. With any application that modifies the registry, we recommend that you have a backup copy to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Applied Acoustics Systems Lounge Lizard EP-5 v5.0.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 23:43:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-applied-acoustics-systems-lounge-lizard-ep-4-3059.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-applied-acoustics-systems-lounge-lizard-ep-4-3059.html
</guid><description>
Be simulated according to the electric pianos classic great, Applied Acoustics Systems Lounge Lizard EP-4 is the dream of keyboard players. You not only get the whole arsenal of piano, but also get the real-time control for most aspects of each instrument. We are talking about physical models allows you to adjust the hardness of the hammer, the noise of the shock absorbers, color and decay, etc. The result is not comparable with the realism and warmth of it. Don't solve any electric piano...
</description></item><item><title>Download AudioRealism ADM1x 1.6.1.6</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 23:41:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-audiorealism-adm1x-11483.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-audiorealism-adm1x-11483.html
</guid><description>
AudioRealism ADM1x is a combination of three classic drum machines (808, 909 and 606) using virtual analog emulation and sample player in one plug-in. The ADM emulates three classic drum machines from that era rolled into one, combined with a 32-step internal sequencer and sample control (PCF) effects.
ADM contains 25 drum generators, each carefully modeled after classic analog circuitry, and 4 PCM players, for a total of 34 sounds (some generators have two sounds). Certain sounds have...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wise Folder Hider Pro 5.0.9.239</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 19:57:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wise-folder-hider-432.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wise-folder-hider-432.html
</guid><description>
Wise Folder Hider is software file protection allows users to encrypt, put a password, hide file on the hard drive.  Wise Folder Hider will is perfect software to protect data files on your system. When using this software you complete peace of mind with important files by themselves do not leak out, and anyone who uses your computer also can't know these hidden files that of you.
Wise Folder Hider offers users the ability to hide files, folders on the hard drive so that other people...
</description></item><item><title>Download EaseUS BitWiper Pro 2.2.1 Build 2508141316</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 19:56:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-bitwiper-pro-11594.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-bitwiper-pro-11594.html
</guid><description>
EaseUS BitWiper Pro is an application that helps users delete data securely and completely unrecoverable. Designed with a simple and easy-to-use interface, this is a useful tool for erasing especially important data before selling, reusing or exchanging electronic devices.
	A secure tool to erase sensitive data from your Windows hard drive.
	Permanently delete files, entire disk or an individual partition.
	Save time with this high-speed data destruction software.
	Providing erasing...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare UniConverter Portable 16.5.9.323</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 19:56:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-uniconverter-portable-12162.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-uniconverter-portable-12162.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare UniConverter Portable - a portable version (unofficial), formerly known as Wondershare Video Converter Ultimate, is a comprehensive media conversion software developed by Wondershare. It offers a wide range of features to convert, edit and enhance multimedia files. Convert, download, compress, edit, record videos in 1000 formats and do more.
With this comprehensive program, you can customize your home movies through advanced editing features and get professional work in...
</description></item><item><title>Download Apowersoft Video Download Capture 6.6.0.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 19:55:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-apowersoft-video-download-capture-1556.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-apowersoft-video-download-capture-1556.html
</guid><description>
Apowersoft Video Download Capture is a comprehensive tool with advanced technologies for media streaming to choice cost-effective to download videos from YouTube, Dailymotion, Vimeo, Yahoo Screen and Hulu, as well as millions of other websites. Apowersoft Video Download Capture is your download video powerful and effective this can download and save videos, movies, tv episodes and music videos online. It also has the switch function, supports convert any video to MP4, AVI, MKV, WMV and the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Lazesoft Windows Recovery 5.0.1.1 Unlimited / Professional / Server Edition</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 19:54:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lazesoft-windows-recovery-6247.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lazesoft-windows-recovery-6247.html
</guid><description>
Lazesoft Windows Recovery  is a software that Fixes all Windows startup problems and problems including boot error, virus infection, blue / black screen etc. Lazesoft Windows Recovery provides home and business users complete solutions to troubleshoot boot-up problems, retrieve valuable files, Partition Recovery, and more. With its easy-to-use interface, you can use Lazesoft Windows Recovery to fix boot problems yourself without reinstalling your Windows. No technical background is...
</description></item><item><title>Download Reg Organizer Portable 9.80</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 19:54:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reg-organizer-portable-3534.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reg-organizer-portable-3534.html
</guid><description>
Reg Organizer Portable is a software solution that allows you to enhance the operational capabilities of the computer by cleaning and defragmenting the key registry of Windows, uninstall the program little or no need to use fix a bug in the system. Review ability to optimize the registry, Reg Organizer Portable feature support automatically shutdown computer after complete the task. In process handling and cleaning systems, you will not be able to open, disposal the manipulate on other...
</description></item><item><title>Download MedCalc 23.3.5</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 19:53:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-medcalc-1536.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-medcalc-1536.html
</guid><description>
MedCalc is a statistical software for biomedical research can analyze many performance curve system with a set of rich functionality, chart types and advanced module. MedCalc was designed to meet the needs and requirements of the study nature and aims to analyze the statistical calculations of the project. This software provides the tools and means essential to analyze the characteristic curve of the system (ROC), drawing data and perform the statistical calculations.
MedCalc -...
</description></item><item><title>Download Lazesoft Disk Image and Clone Professional 5.0.1.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 19:53:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lazesoft-disk-image-and-clone-professional-6487.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lazesoft-disk-image-and-clone-professional-6487.html
</guid><description>
Lazesoft Disk Image and Clone is the software that replices your hard disk, backup or restoring your hard disk when offline is easy and safe. Lazesoft Disk Image and Clone can be used for backup, hard disk upgrades or disk replication purposes. With Lazesoft Disk Image and Clone, copy/copy the entire disc including Windows, program, file, and personal settings to the new disk/partition in just a few clicks. Never need to reinstall Windows and programs.
Features of Lazesoft Disk Image...
</description></item><item><title>Download Lazesoft Disk Image and Clone Server 5.0.1.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 19:53:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lazesoft-disk-image-and-clone-server-6488.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lazesoft-disk-image-and-clone-server-6488.html
</guid><description>
Lazesoft Disk Image and Clone  is a software that copies your entire hard disk, backs up or restores your hard disk offline easily and safely. Lazesoft Disk Image and Clone can be used for backup, hard disk upgrade or disk cloning purposes. With Lazesoft Disk Image and Clone, Copy / copy entire disk including Windows, programs, files and personal settings to new disk / partition in just a few clicks. Never need to reinstall Windows and programs.
Features of Lazesoft Disk Image and...
</description></item></channel></rss>