<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 17:43:31 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 17:43:31 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download MusConv 4.10.436 Lifetime</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Dec 2025 16:52:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html
</guid><description>
MusConv transfers playlists, albums, followed artists and liked songs across a variety of services – Spotify, Apple Music, Amazon Music, YouTube, YouTube Music, iTunes, Deezer, Tidal, SoundCloud, Pandora and more 125 music services!
Features of MusConv Ultimate
	Transfer playlists, albums, followed artists and liked tracks between over 125 music servicesManage playlists (Delete, Merge, Split, Copy...)
	More than 125 music services supported
	Access DAILY updated music charts on...
</description></item><item><title>Download NWinfo 1.5.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Dec 2025 16:52:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nwinfo-12590.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nwinfo-12590.html
</guid><description>
NWinfo is a Win32 program that allows you to obtain system and hardware information. It displays essential information about CPU, memory, disk, network, and even system operating details. Because it's portable, you can carry NWinfo on a USB stick and use it on any Windows machine, making it a useful tool for both tech enthusiasts and troubleshooters.
Features of NWinfo
	Get detailed information about SMBIOS, CPUID, S.M.A.R.T., PCI, EDID, etc.
	Supports export in JSON, YAML and LUA...
</description></item><item><title>Download OnlyOffice Desktop Editors 9.2.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Dec 2025 16:52:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-onlyoffice-7488.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-onlyoffice-7488.html
</guid><description>
OnlyOffice is a free office suite that can open documents, presentations, and spreadsheets in different tabs of the same window, providing interoperability Compatible with the most popular file formats. With an attractive intuitive interface and intuitive controls, OnlyOffice allows users to open documents, spreadsheets and presentations, or create new ones from scratch. It comes with support for the most common file formats, even those native to Microsoft's office suite. Moreover, it can...
</description></item><item><title>Download XRECODE3 1.175 Final</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Dec 2025 16:51:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xrecode-iii-2915.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xrecode-iii-2915.html
</guid><description>
"Xrecode II" is the switch and grab the audio allows you to convert from mp2, mp3, ac3, aiff, wma, amr, ogg, ape, flac, cue, mpc, wv, tak, mid, cue, m4b, tta, wav, dts , wav (rf64), m4a, mp4, ra, shn, rm, avi, aac, mpg, vob, mka, mkv, flv, Mov, swf, ofr, divx, wmv, spx, mp3, m4v, 3gp, m2v, 3g2, m4v, m2ts, ts, adts, tak, xm, mod, it, s3m, alac, umx, mtm, mlp to m4a, ape, flac, mp4 (using NeroAAC), raw, ogg, wav, wav (rf64) , wma, mpc, WavPack, mp2, ofr, Speex, ac3, tak, aiff, snd, Shorten...
</description></item><item><title>Download Brickaizer 8.0.4.7</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Dec 2025 16:50:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-brickaizer-3680.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-brickaizer-3680.html
</guid><description>
Brickaizer+ is a tool quite interesting to help create the mosaic unique. Software Brickaizer have the ability to create the perfect color match every color combination and size can. A number of tools mix color high precision is used, including color schemes, colour - and black and white, and tool joint color Mosaizer XV. Even from a close distance, can see beautiful pictures, don't need to walk 5 meters to get rid of the markings do not match.
Brickaizer+ - Create mosaic...
</description></item><item><title>Download Revo Registry Cleaner Free 2.0.5 + Portable</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Dec 2025 16:50:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-revo-registry-cleaner-free-12717.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-revo-registry-cleaner-free-12717.html
</guid><description>
Revo Registry Cleaner Free is a powerful tool designed to clean, tune and optimize the Windows Registry. Explore the powerful Registry Cleaner with over 15 scanning categories to find and remove invalid and unnecessary Registry entries. Customize your cleaning routine with custom key inclusions/exclusions and 4 different deep scan modes.
In addition, it also supports custom backups for user-specified keys as well as full Registry backups providing peace of mind as they ensure the safety...
</description></item><item><title>Download FreeFileSync 14.6</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Dec 2025 16:49:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-freefilesync-2447.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-freefilesync-2447.html
</guid><description>
FreeFileSync is a program open source and free to be used to sync files. It's available on Windows, Linux and OS X. The project is supported by donations. Donors get a few extra features like the automatic updates, synchronize, parallel, mobile version and install silent.
FreeFileSync - sync data
Features of FreeFileSync
	Detect moved and renamed files and folders
	Copy the file locked (Volume Shadow Copy Service)
	Detect conflicts and propagate delete
	Compare binary
	Full support...
</description></item><item><title>Download HTTP Toolkit 1.24.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Dec 2025 16:49:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-http-toolkit-6246.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-http-toolkit-6246.html
</guid><description>
HTTP Toolkit is software that provides the ability to automatically block HTTP and HTTPS traffic from most client applications, including web browsers such as Chrome and Firefox, most CLI tools and auxiliary languages such as Node.js, Python, Ruby etc. You can browse through traffic by marking the content type, status, and source or search by URL, status, and title to find important notifications.
You can check the URL, status, title, and content of each request or feedback, along with...
</description></item><item><title>Download TapinRadio Pro 2.16.14</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Dec 2025 16:49:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tapinradio-pro-735.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tapinradio-pro-735.html
</guid><description>
TapinRadio Pro is a professional software used to listen to the radio there are many channels to choose from and continuously updated. TapinRadio supports most of the formats internet radio - mp3, wma, ogg, aac. This is a powerful tool for you to capture information in the world and in country in the fastest and simplest.
TapinRadio Pro - Listen To The Radio
Features of TapinRadio Pro
	A lot of stations to choose from
	Supports most of the formats internet radio - mp3, wma, vorbis...
</description></item><item><title>Download Python 3.14.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Dec 2025 16:48:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-python-4355.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-python-4355.html
</guid><description>
Python is a programming language high-level for the purpose of programming multi-function, due to Guido van Rossum created and first launched in 1991. Python is designed with strong advantages is easy to read, easy to learn and easy to remember. Python is a language can form very bright, clear structure, convenient for new people to learn programming. Python fully create a dynamic and user mechanisms to allocate the memory automatically; so it is similar to Perl, Ruby, Scheme, Smalltalk,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Softwarenetz Invoice Rechnung 11.26</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Dec 2025 16:48:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-softwarenetz-invoice-5588.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-softwarenetz-invoice-5588.html
</guid><description>
Softwarenetz Invoice is a useful program for self-employed, freelancers and small companies who are in need of a simple and user-friendly program for invoicing. The invoice program contains the complete address / customer database. You can see at a glance all invoices, payments and reminders for a particular customer. The memo field gives you the opportunity to enter customer specific information. Importing existing client from csv file is also included.
You can print your invoice on your...
</description></item><item><title>Download DBF Viewer 2000 v8.92</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Dec 2025 16:47:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbf-viewer-2000-7869.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbf-viewer-2000-7869.html
</guid><description>
DBF Viewer 2000 is a fast, efficient solution for viewing and editing all types of DBF files. It can handle files from dBase, Visual dBase, Foxpro, Visual FoxPro and Clipper, just to name a few, with performance that easily rivals expensive professional database utilities. DBF Viewer 2000 is extremely fast, does any task, just one simple query and cleanup copy to export data at lightning speed.
With DBF Editor's simple, dynamically generated visual dialogs, you can easily view the...
</description></item><item><title>Download BrightVPN 1.572.298</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Dec 2025 16:47:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-brightvpn-8960.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-brightvpn-8960.html
</guid><description>
BrightVPN is a virtual private network (VPN) service that provides users with a private and secure internet browsing experience. The service uses encryption and tunneling protocols to protect users' online activities and personal data from being intercepted or tracked by third parties.
BrightVPN frees you from restrictions or censorship by unblocking any website from 150+ countries, connecting you to the Internet for free from anywhere. In addition, Bright VPN protects your internet...
</description></item><item><title>Download Monkeys Audio 11.89</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Dec 2025 16:46:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-monkeys-audio-949.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-monkeys-audio-949.html
</guid><description>
Monkey\'s Audio is software that compresses digital music without loss of quality. Supports high quality WAV files and CD ripping. Monkeys Audio will compress .wav tracks into .ape files to reduce their size without loss of sound quality, decompress .ape, convert files, check file integrity and manage tags.
Unlike traditional methods like MP3 and OGG, which permanently remove quality to save space, Monkey\'s Audio only creates perfect copies with the same sound quality as the originals....
</description></item><item><title>Download MapInfo Pro 2023.2.231</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Dec 2025 16:46:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mapinfo-pro-1872.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mapinfo-pro-1872.html
</guid><description>
MapInfo Pro is the software helps the business analysts and GIS experts get new insights about their markets, by sharing the map and the rich information to improve decision-making strategies. MapInfo Pro is an application that analyzes geography and mapping strong provider of space solutions geography. MapInfo Pro help you presented the results his business in a new way, more intuitive. It clearly demonstrates the relationship between geography and data, thanks to the map and detailed...
</description></item><item><title>Download LastPass Password Manager 5.3.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Dec 2025 16:45:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lastpass-269.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lastpass-269.html
</guid><description>
LastPass is a free software to help manage passwords allows you to store all the login information of your site in a warehouse password cross-platform compatibility only. Instead of remember the user name and personal password, you only need to remember the main password to open the lock the password of his safe.
LastPass
LastPass can automatically fill in the login box for all the account website is your hosting. Whenever you log into a website has stored your vault, the program will...
</description></item><item><title>Download MSI Center 2.0.63.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Dec 2025 16:45:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-msi-center-12314.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-msi-center-12314.html
</guid><description>
The AI ​​era of computing: MSI laptops are equipped with MSI's exclusive AI technology capable of providing completely new smart features. The AI ​​revolution has arrived on MSI laptops. MSI AI Engine automatically recognizes various user situations, triggering appropriate adjustments in performance, sound effects, display modes and keyboard backlighting. Users do not need to make manual adjustments to achieve optimal situations.
MSI Center combines all of MSI's exclusive...
</description></item><item><title>Download Operant Peak Spectroscopy 4.00.538</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Dec 2025 16:45:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-operant-peak-spectroscopy-7976.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-operant-peak-spectroscopy-7976.html
</guid><description>
Operant Peak Spectroscopy for Spectroscopy reads and converts over 60 spectral file formats. It includes library search, spectrum manipulation and many other functions. Mid IR, Near IR, FTIR, Raman, Fluorescence, LIBS, XRF, UV-VIS, Raman and EELS.
Features of Operant Peak Spectroscopy
	Peak can read data from more than 70 spectral file types.
	Convert files in bulk from closed proprietary formats.
	Peak is used worldwide in industry, education, government and military
	Peak has a...
</description></item><item><title>Download SAPIEN PrimalScript 2025 v8.1.222</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Dec 2025 16:44:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sapien-primalscript-6923.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sapien-primalscript-6923.html
</guid><description>
PrimalScript is the next generation of our industry-leading Universal Script Environment. As a system, database or network administrator, web developer, or end-user developer, you need to work with multiple technologies, languages, and file formats at the same time. The ribbon interface of PrimalScript has been carefully designed to provide almost all the functions you use every day on the Home tab. Create scenario templates based on your requirements and business needs to drive faster...
</description></item><item><title>Download SAPIEN PowerShell Studio 2025 v5.9.262</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Dec 2025 16:44:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sapien-powershell-studio-7201.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sapien-powershell-studio-7201.html
</guid><description>
PowerShell Studio is the premier editing and tooling environment for PowerShell. Create graphical tools using PowerShell with an easy-to-use GUI designer. Eliminates the need to manually write hundreds of lines of code. Use PowerShell Studio's built-in templates and wired controls to create advanced GUIs quickly. Create a PowerShell script module in minutes with PowerShell Studio. Easily convert your existing functions into a deliverable module. PowerShell Studio has a powerful editor...
</description></item><item><title>Download Disk Pulse Ultimate 17.5.24 + Enterprise + Pro</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Dec 2025 16:43:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-disk-pulse-ultimate-1465.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-disk-pulse-ultimate-1465.html
</guid><description>
Disk Pulse Ultimate is a monitoring solution change disk real-time allows one to monitor one or more disks or directories, save reports and statistics monitoring disk changes, the change is detected to the SQL database focus, execute custom commands and send E-Mail notifications when unauthorized changes are detected in the file system important.
Disk Pulse Ultimate - Monitor disc change
DiskPulse provides the ability for users to start / stop the monitoring operation disc change,...
</description></item><item><title>Download ValhallaDSP Bundle 2025.12</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Dec 2025 16:43:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-valhalladsp-bundle-10899.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-valhalladsp-bundle-10899.html
</guid><description>
Valhalla DSP has built a strong reputation in the audio industry for delivering cutting-edge solutions and impressive performance. ValhallaDSP Bundle includes many powerful tools, making it one of the top choices for creating unique and high-quality sounds in music and audio projects.
Audio plugins include:
	FreqEcho v1.2.0 - free freqshifter delay
	Delay v3.0.5 - tape/BBD/digital/pitch delay
	Plate v1.6.3 - classic plate reverb
	Room v2.0.5 - true stereo algorithmic reverb
	Shimmer...
</description></item><item><title>Download Argente System Repair 1.0.3.9</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Dec 2025 16:43:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-argente-system-repair-13813.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-argente-system-repair-13813.html
</guid><description>
Argente System Repair is a lightweight utility designed to diagnose and fix common Windows system problems. It scans your system to identify errors in operating system components, file systems, installation files, and other system components, and then applies targeted fixes to resolve these problems. The tool provides different scan modes, including simple scan, recommended scan, and custom scan, allowing users to customize the repair process according to their needs.
System Repair...
</description></item><item><title>Download VLC Media Player 3.0.22</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 22:43:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vlc-media-player-63.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vlc-media-player-63.html
</guid><description>
VLC Media Player is a multimedia player supporting many audio formats and video (MPEG-1, MPEG-2, MPEG-4, DivX, mp3, ogg, etc.) without the need for additional codecs , as well as DVDS, VCDS, and various streaming protocols different online.It also comes with a server, streaming allows you to stream media in unicast or multicast from your network.
VLC Media Player 
VLC Media Player provides a simple interface, with simple buttons control the playback standard and make the most of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Zero Install 2.28.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 22:42:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zero-install-1632.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zero-install-1632.html
</guid><description>
Zero Install is a system, install the software distribution cross africa focus. Other features include full support for shared libraries (with the SAT for resolution dependent), share between users, and integration with the package manager original foundation. Zero Install supports both binary packages and source and works on Linux systems , OS X , Unix and Windows. It is completely open source.
Zero Install - System software installation
Zero Install also has a number of interesting...
</description></item></channel></rss>