<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 01:43:23 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 01:43:23 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Clementine Music Player 1.4.1-59</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 23:12:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-clementine-4762.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-clementine-4762.html
</guid><description>
Clementine is a tools multi-platform software which allows you to listen to music from hard drive, library, audio CDS or the Internet, as well as manage it, edit the card and see the lyrics. Clementine is inspired by Amarok 1.4, focusing on a easy to use interface for searching and playing your music.
Clementine also allows you can view track information such as length, bit rate, sample rate, size, file type, number of times played and your ranking, as well as complete the card...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Downloader 10.0.10</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 23:11:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html
</guid><description>
YTD Youtube Downloader is an application that reliable and intuitive, allowing you to quickly download YouTube videos and save them to your computer. You can also convert the media files to the format desired video or extract audio streams and save separately. YTD Youtube Downloader lets you save your favorite clips of yourself from Youtube, Facebook, Vimeo and Dailymotion to your desktop. The software supports URLS from many web site hosting, multimedia and allows you to download desired...
</description></item><item><title>Download Foxit PDF Editor Pro 14.0.2.33402 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 23:10:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-foxit-pdf-editor-pro-13375.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-foxit-pdf-editor-pro-13375.html
</guid><description>
Foxit PDF Editor Pro is a professional PDF editing software designed for personal and business users who need advanced capabilities to create, edit, secure and manage PDF documents. This Foxit software can combine, split or repackage multiple PDF files. Documents can be merged or split based on page numbers, page layout or bookmarks. Additionally, this Suite can batch convert existing documents into one or more PDF files.
Features of Foxit PDF Editor Pro 
Advanced PDF editing with...
</description></item><item><title>Download Kotato All Video Downloader Pro 10.0.7</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 23:10:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kotato-all-video-downloader-pro-5228.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kotato-all-video-downloader-pro-5228.html
</guid><description>
Kotato All Video Downloader Pro is a Windows application professional to download and convert your favorite videos from the video sharing website. It speeds up your downloads up to 5 times! Kotato All Video Downloader Pro can download videos from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion and hundreds of video sharing sites, other. After downloading, you will be able to play them smoother on your PC or your mobile device, even when you don't have Internet access.
The main features of Kotato All...
</description></item><item><title>Download Agisoft Metashape Professional 2.3.0 Build 21778</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 23:09:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-agisoft-metashape-professional-1731.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-agisoft-metashape-professional-1731.html
</guid><description>
Agisoft Metashape (formerly PhotoScan) is a software product independently perform image processing and digital data creation, 3D space used in GIS applications, material cultural heritage and the production visual effects as well as the indirect measurement of the different subjects scale. Technical digital photography is deployed wisely is applied with the method of computer vision led to the system processor, smart auto, on the one hand, can be managed by a new person in the field of...
</description></item><item><title>Download FX Math Tools Manifest 25.12.10</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 23:09:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fx-draw-tools-multidocs-8814.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fx-draw-tools-multidocs-8814.html
</guid><description>
MultiDocs is a new way to create self-modifying Word documents. MultiDocs' amazing new document reproduction features allow you to create reproducible tests and quizzes in minutes. Get new numbers, new diagrams and even brand new solutions! MultiDocs combines the power of Word with two leading products: FX Draw and FX Equation in a new and exciting way.
Features of FX Draw Tools MultiDocs
	Create multiple documents: The software allows users to create multiple math and evaluation...
</description></item><item><title>Download VovSoft Duplicate File Finder 2.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 23:08:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-duplicate-file-finder-6639.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-duplicate-file-finder-6639.html
</guid><description>
VovSoft Duplicate File Finder is a tool to find duplicate files on your computer. It can scan file name, file size or file content (using SHA-1 algorithm).
You may have hundreds of photos, videos, music files, or documents that you've lost track of. You're running out of disk space on your PC, but organizing your files can seem overwhelming because there are so many of them.
This utility will help you locate and remove useless file duplicates to free up disk space and better organize...
</description></item><item><title>Download FX Science Tools Manifest 25.12.10</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 23:08:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fx-science-tools-3744.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fx-science-tools-3744.html
</guid><description>
FX Science Tools provided to teachers of chemistry and physics the effective means to create equations and chemical structures. Just type and create. FX Chem FX Chem makes writing chemical equations become simple. You just type and FX Chem know enough about chemistry to put all the components of the equation at the right point. FX Chem can even create the chemical equations for nuclear - a very difficult thing in the Word. FX ChemSturation FX ChemSturation made the organic structure, what...
</description></item><item><title>Download Display Driver Uninstaller (DDU) 18.1.4.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 17:30:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-display-driver-uninstaller-1999.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-display-driver-uninstaller-1999.html
</guid><description>
Display Driver Uninstaller (DDU) help to easily completely remove the packages and drivers graphics cards AMD, NVIDIA and Intel from your system without leaving any rest whatsoever. Display Driver Uninstaller will automatically detect your current GPU and allows you to delete drivers, registry and files related only by the click of a button. It will also prevent Windows automatically re-install drivers when you reboot your computer, leaving you a drivers graphics common until you install...
</description></item><item><title>Download Foxit PDF Editor Pro 2025.3.0.35737 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 17:29:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-foxit-pdf-editor-pro-162.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-foxit-pdf-editor-pro-162.html
</guid><description>
Foxit PDF Editor Pro (formerly Foxit PhantomPDF Business) is a PDF toolkit dedicated to the creation of professional PDF documents and forms. You can do that for tasks such as personal document development, working group collaboration, company model design. Manufacturing the company's collateral, completing the agreements, applying the signature number or document storage.
Foxit PDF Editor Pro is the perfect solution for family/family offices, small and medium enterprises and large...
</description></item><item><title>Download Balabolka 2.15.0.910</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 17:28:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-balaboka-142.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-balaboka-142.html
</guid><description>
Balabolka is a text-to-speech (TTS) program. It can read text on your screen in a human-like voice. You can use Balabolka to listen to text from a variety of file formats, convert text to spoken audio files, and adjust speech parameters such as speed and pitch. It is often used for accessibility purposes, helping people who have difficulty reading or multi-tasking by listening to text while doing other activities. Balabolka supports multiple languages and uses different TTS engines,...
</description></item><item><title>Download R-Wipe &amp;amp; Clean 20.0 Build 2539</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 17:28:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-wipe-clean-891.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-wipe-clean-891.html
</guid><description>
R-Wipe &amp;amp; Clean is software to delete junk files, unnecessary files from your computer to release the storage space and speed up your computer. In addition, R-Wipe &amp;amp; Clean also unleash the capacity of your drive and delete information invasion of privacy on different operations online and offline including your internet history and cookies, the list of downloaded files and documents were open, buffer different data, temporary files and many other items, created by the operating...
</description></item><item><title>Download CapCut PC 7.7.0.3143</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 17:27:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capcut-pc-9995.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capcut-pc-9995.html
</guid><description>
CapCut PC is a simple video editing tool that you can freely use anywhere. You can create videos on your browser, desktop and laptop, or on your phone. Versatile editing, magical AI tools, team collaboration, and built-in assets. Create videos in a whole new way.
You can edit videos based on editing the timeline, in the process you can add different elements and effects to the video to give the best effect to your work. It is a simple and intuitive set of editing tools and effects that...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wipe Pro 2025.15</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 17:26:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wipe-pro-710.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wipe-pro-710.html
</guid><description>
Wipe Pro is software that helps clean up litter, increase in hard drive space besides also protect your privacy on the Internet, it removes records about personal activity on the computer. You will be able to delete browser history and the cache, the file index.dat, registry, files, cookies, internet history, auto complete, temporary internet files and many other items. This program also delete all activities other individuals that you made when using the PC and regardless of which...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cockos REAPER 7.56</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 17:26:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cockos-reaper-889.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cockos-reaper-889.html
</guid><description>
Cockos REAPER is a powerful software for for windows, chp lets you record, arrange, edit, and display the audio waveform multi-track. Cockos REAPER offers an extensive feature set includes many effects and a sample project. REAPER supports ASIO, Kernel Streaming, WaveOut, and DirectSound for playback and recording. It reads the files in WAV, OGG and MP3 files and records WAV files. You can arrange any number of items in any number of tracks and use plug-in sound processing (DirectX and...
</description></item><item><title>Download OBS Studio 32.0.4</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 17:25:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-open-broadcaster-software-2451.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-open-broadcaster-software-2451.html
</guid><description>
Open Broadcaster Software is abbreviated as OBS is a program to detect the type of multimedia content to the internet. It is worth noting that a simple interface and the presence of a good tool. You can adjust the quality of the audio and video before starting the broadcast, you can specify the URL, choose the resolution of the screen, etc. With strong desire, videos which you found can be saved to your hard drive.
Open Broadcaster Software - LiveStream on PC
The basic features of Open...
</description></item><item><title>Download XRECODE3 1.176</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 17:24:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xrecode-iii-2915.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xrecode-iii-2915.html
</guid><description>
"Xrecode II" is the switch and grab the audio allows you to convert from mp2, mp3, ac3, aiff, wma, amr, ogg, ape, flac, cue, mpc, wv, tak, mid, cue, m4b, tta, wav, dts , wav (rf64), m4a, mp4, ra, shn, rm, avi, aac, mpg, vob, mka, mkv, flv, Mov, swf, ofr, divx, wmv, spx, mp3, m4v, 3gp, m2v, 3g2, m4v, m2ts, ts, adts, tak, xm, mod, it, s3m, alac, umx, mtm, mlp to m4a, ape, flac, mp4 (using NeroAAC), raw, ogg, wav, wav (rf64) , wma, mpc, WavPack, mp2, ofr, Speex, ac3, tak, aiff, snd, Shorten...
</description></item><item><title>Download Quick Clipboard Editor 3.1.2.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 17:23:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quick-clipboard-editor-9421.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quick-clipboard-editor-9421.html
</guid><description>
Quick Clipboard Editor is free software that provides direct access to the text stored in your clipboard, allowing you to quickly modify it to meet your needs. meet your needs before pasting the text into the app you want. It allows you to quickly retrieve previous clips from your clipboard history, find and replace specific words or phrases, insert new content into each line, trim unwanted pieces of text, keep or remove lines or characters based on different criteria, arrange text using...
</description></item><item><title>Download reaConverter Pro 8.0.169</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 17:23:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html
</guid><description>
reaConverter Pro is software image processing feature with batch conversion and image editing periodically becomes simple. eaConverter also provide command line utilities allow you to process images automatically, thus helping you shorten the time for other work.
reaConverter Pro integrated powerful tool of Uber with many great features. It provides advanced solutions to process and adjust images. Management of the conversion process the base image with the latest version of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Windows Memory Cleaner 3.0.8</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 17:22:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-memory-cleaner-9959.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-memory-cleaner-9959.html
</guid><description>
Sometimes programs don't release the memory they used, making the computer slow, but you don't want to restart the system to get the used memory back. This is where you use Windows Memory Cleaner to clean up memory so you can continue working without having to restart Windows.
How to clean RAM of Windows Memory Cleaner
	Clean Combined Page List Removes blocks from the combined page list. Valid only when site merge is enabled.
	Clean Modified Page List Clears memory from the Modified...
</description></item><item><title>Download WhatsApp 2.2549.4.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 17:22:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-whatsapp-61.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-whatsapp-61.html
</guid><description>
WhatsApp is an extension for the app WhatsApp mobile allows you to send and receive messages from the comfort of desktop your.Just install WhatsApp on your pc and scan the QR code from the mobile application WhatsApp and all the chats and your contacts will be able to access from your computer to your desk.
WhatsApp - Send and receive messages for free
Moreover, they will be automatically synced to all your conversations on your computer also available on your phone.The Windows version...
</description></item><item><title>Download Bitwig Studio 6.0 Beta 8</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 17:21:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bitwig-studio-3626.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bitwig-studio-3626.html
</guid><description>
Find new standard in the process of individual work. Bitwig Studio excite you good control over his music, give you access to all features of your production. Streamline course creation of you and quickly develop your ideas into the songs, compositions and music full.
Bitwig Studio - Create your own music
Arrange and record, perform and improvise, or do all at the same time. Choose among the many records displayed. Design your sound with the equipment container commitment. Mixing the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tomabo MP4 Downloader Pro 6.0.8</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 17:21:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tomabo-mp4-downloader-pro-3602.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tomabo-mp4-downloader-pro-3602.html
</guid><description>
Tomabo MP4 Downloader Pro is the app designed exclusively for Windows users to help them download videos from the Internet. In addition, it also increase download speeds by up to 500%, or even more. Tomabo MP4 Downloader Pro, interface design, simple, well-organized, beautifully. Here, users can view a list of videos has download with gravatar, URL, quality, duration and size of them. Software allows download video series at the same time, at the same time, support create a list of clips...
</description></item><item><title>Download VovSoft Serial Port Monitor 2.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 17:21:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-serial-port-monitor-7140.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-serial-port-monitor-7140.html
</guid><description>
VovSoft Serial Port Monitor is a tool to analyze computer COM port communication data traffic. You can receive/read data from any COM port and transfer/send data to any COM port. You can change connection parameters such as baud rate, parity, data bit and stop bit. Can send text periodically, you can change sending interval in milliseconds. The "Clear", "Save to file" and "Copy to clipboard" buttons can be used. You can also set the font and background color using the menu.
You can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mikey Audio FlipCraft 1.1.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 17:20:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mikey-audio-flipcraft-14256.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mikey-audio-flipcraft-14256.html
</guid><description>
FlipCraft is an advanced sample cutting plugin designed to empower producers, beatmakers, and sound designers with unprecedented control, flexibility, and speed. Starting today, users can download a free trial and experience FlipCraft's advanced features firsthand. FlipCraft takes sample processing to the next level. With intuitive controls and powerful built-in technology.
Features of FlipCraft
	View and interact with high-resolution, zoomable waveforms
	Apply advanced stem...
</description></item></channel></rss>