<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 13:40:18 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 13:40:18 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download PowerISO 9.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 25 Oct 2025 00:42:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-poweriso-337.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-poweriso-337.html
</guid><description>
PowerISO is software extract, burn, create, edit, compress, encrypt, split, convert ISO files and mount ISO file on the virtual drive. Besides, PowerISO supports rip CDS securely, handle many different partitions as well as the ability to create a USB drive boot for Windows XP/Vista and 7. The special thing is the files compressed can be used directly without decompressing.
PowerISO - Create virtual drives
Features PowerISO
	PowerISO view, edit, delete content files in the iso...
</description></item><item><title>Download VideoProc Converter AI 8.4</title><pubDate> Sat, 25 Oct 2025 00:42:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-videoproc-2473.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-videoproc-2473.html
</guid><description>
VideoProc (an improved version of WinX HD Video Converter Deluxe) - processing software the most powerful video designed to edit, cut, crop, merge, adjust, convert and compress (4K) video with full Hardware Acceleration. Is the heir to be improved a lot, VideoProc integrated conversion / compression video UHD, the download at videos (YouTube) with the video editor, gives you the power to control optimal for every video file much music, SD, HD and 4K on your PC. With technology hardware...
</description></item><item><title>Download Nitro Pro Enterprise 14.41.1.4</title><pubDate> Sat, 25 Oct 2025 00:41:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nitro-pdf-pro-34.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nitro-pdf-pro-34.html
</guid><description>
Nitro Pro Enterprise create, edit and convert PDF files easily with the help of the visual program this also allows users to accurately extract text from PDF files thanks to OCR function of it. Nitro Pro is one of the software solutions, create and edit PDF most advanced, providing basically all the tools you need to help you in this area. Although it is called 'Professional', this app has been developed to target beginners and advanced users, so you won't feel too hard to use.
Direct...
</description></item><item><title>Download ActivePresenter Pro 10.1.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 25 Oct 2025 00:41:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-activepresenter-pro-598.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-activepresenter-pro-598.html
</guid><description>
ActivePresenter Pro is a solution to create a video screencast, development, manuals, documents and training presentations interactive. With the full editing features, ActivePresenter allows you to edit audio / video adjust interface content and specify the script branching with ease and efficiency. HTML5 support latest web standards and ability to integrate with management Systems, learning content created with ActivePresenter can be sent virtually to any device and any...
</description></item><item><title>Download Blank And Secure 8.21</title><pubDate> Sat, 25 Oct 2025 00:40:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blank-and-secure-2934.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blank-and-secure-2934.html
</guid><description>
Blank And Secure is a application lightweight and portable allows you to completely erase your sensitive data without possibility to restore. This add-on accomplish this by overwriting your files with zeros (0) before you delete them. This method is also called "zeroing data / drives". You should know that once completed, the complete data can't be recovered, so you should only use this tool if you want to permanently delete your files.
Blank And Secure - Delete data permanently
Blank...
</description></item><item><title>Download reaConverter Pro 8.0.148</title><pubDate> Sat, 25 Oct 2025 00:40:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html
</guid><description>
reaConverter Pro is software image processing feature with batch conversion and image editing periodically becomes simple. eaConverter also provide command line utilities allow you to process images automatically, thus helping you shorten the time for other work.
reaConverter Pro integrated powerful tool of Uber with many great features. It provides advanced solutions to process and adjust images. Management of the conversion process the base image with the latest version of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Reg Organizer 9.89</title><pubDate> Sat, 25 Oct 2025 00:40:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reg-organizer-1595.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reg-organizer-1595.html
</guid><description>
Reg Organizer is a software to scan and clean your registry windows register errors and help optimize performance computer system. Reg Organizer is a software subscription, professional, and professional, and any way that the Windows registry are necessary and therefore, the overall performance of Windows improves, there is this software.
Reg Organizer - registry Cleaning and pc optimization
The main features of Reg Organizer
	Cleaning the registry of the lock is not valid and not...
</description></item><item><title>Download Winxvideo AI 4.4.0.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 25 Oct 2025 00:39:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winxvideo-ai-10981.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winxvideo-ai-10981.html
</guid><description>
Winxvideo AI is an innovative video editing app that leverages the power of artificial intelligence to provide users with advanced video editing capabilities. With advanced features and a user-friendly interface, Winxvideo AI is designed to streamline the video editing process and empower creators to create professional-quality videos.
Winxvideo AI meets all your audio/video conversion needs and compresses your 4K/8K footage from GB to MB without compromising on quality, powered by...
</description></item><item><title>Download Efficient Elements for presentations 4.4.5600.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 25 Oct 2025 00:38:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-efficient-elements-for-presentations-7748.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-efficient-elements-for-presentations-7748.html
</guid><description>
Efficient Elements for presentations is an add-in for Microsoft PowerPoint for creating professional-looking presentations in your corporate design. Automatic program slides. Comprehensive Slide Library. Format and Align with one click. Check out the powerful corporate design. Interactive Harvey Shadows, Traffic Lights,… Map of All Countries in the World that you can edit in Excel.
Features of Efficient Elements for presentations
	Calculate time intervals or pages...
</description></item><item><title>Download Nitro Pro 14.41.1.4 Retail</title><pubDate> Sat, 25 Oct 2025 00:38:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nitro-pro-379.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nitro-pro-379.html
</guid><description>
Nitro Pro is software that provides features to create, edit and convert PDF files or share PDF files standard.  This is a simple software, easy to understand and intuitive to use so you can work more efficiently. Nitro Pro you can share your files with others, regardless of whether they are using the platform or device, and Nitro Pro helps convert easily.
Nitro Pro convert one or multiple files into PDF with just one or two clicks. Re-use and re-use content based on the PDF with higher...
</description></item><item><title>Download MaxCut Business Edition 2.9.5.8</title><pubDate> Sat, 25 Oct 2025 00:31:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-maxcut-business-edition-3912.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-maxcut-business-edition-3912.html
</guid><description>
MaxCut Business Edition is a software to create cutting diagrams, accurate, and cost estimate for the wood industry, cabinets and metal,.. You enter the size and material, MaxCut will do the rest! Produce optimized cutting diagrams, create estimates, orders, and labels - it's just a click. Run the application MaxCut Business Edition brings a pretty clean interface and slick quickly get you up and running. Most space represents the editing area, with the main function are stored cleverly in...
</description></item><item><title>Download MultiMonitorTool 2.21</title><pubDate> Sat, 25 Oct 2025 00:31:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-multimonitortool-2533.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-multimonitortool-2533.html
</guid><description>
MultiMonitorTool offers some useful actions for those who have your desktop computer, they are extended across multiple screens. You can turn on / off the selected screen, change resolution or screen orientation, move windows from screen to another screen, etc.
MultiMonitorTool - Configuring Multiple Screens
You can save and load the configuration screen and also automate any action of the screen by using the command-line arguments from a file bundle.
</description></item><item><title>Download AndreaMosaic 3.54.5</title><pubDate> Sat, 25 Oct 2025 00:31:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-andreamosaic-1684.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-andreamosaic-1684.html
</guid><description>
AndreaMosaic is a other tool allows you to transform photos into mosaics created from collection of photos of you. The manner of operation of the program is very simple, but it does not always give you the results you are looking for. The user must choose the image collection you want to use to create the mosaic and the photo will be converted on AndreaMosaic.
&amp;nbsp;
AndreaMosaic allows you to configure a number of options, such as width the last of the mosaic, the number of images on...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinMute 2.5.3.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 25 Oct 2025 00:30:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winmute-7446.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winmute-7446.html
</guid><description>
WinMute can automatically mute all audio devices on your PC when:
	you lock your PC.
	screensaver turns on.
	screen off
	you are logged out
	Your PC is off
	Your PC goes to sleep
	Your PC is connected to a specific wireless network
This is useful, for example, if you are away from your desk and don't want to disturb your co-workers with random sounds or music from your computer, or don't want music coming from your speakers , the next time you turn on your computer during a...
</description></item><item><title>Download Exif Pilot 6.28.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 25 Oct 2025 00:30:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-exif-pilot-3900.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-exif-pilot-3900.html
</guid><description>
Exif Pilot is a tool that small and simple will help you to easily edit the EXIF data contained in digital photos of you. Using this tool, you will be able to view and manage multiple types of data, such as IPTC, EXIF, GPS, XMP, etc. the program also allows you to create data EXIF, IPTC and GPS. The new card also can be added to your photo. Exif Pilot allows you to import and export data, IPTC and EXIF from / to files, MS Excel, CSV and XML. The program allows you to add, delete and edit...
</description></item><item><title>Download ActivePresenter Professional 10.1.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 25 Oct 2025 00:29:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-activepresenter-professional-895.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-activepresenter-professional-895.html
</guid><description>
ActivePresenter Professional is a professional software to create video screencast, development, instructions for use, documents, and presentations, interactive training. In addition, ActivePresenter allows you to edit audio / video adjust interface content and specify the script branching with ease and efficiency. HTML5 support latest web standards and ability to integrate with management systems, learning content created with activepresenter can be delivered to virtually any device and...
</description></item><item><title>Download LosslessCut 3.66.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 25 Oct 2025 00:29:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-losslesscut-1789.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-losslesscut-1789.html
</guid><description>
LosslessCut is the video editor to trim and cut video without loss of quality. Just download the video file and use seal cutter start / stop to only the part you want to cut. Click the crop icon and the highlighted part will be exported to the file new video without any decoding or encoding whatsoever. LosslessCut using ffmpeg (included) to carry all the heavy stuff.
LosslessCut - Cut and edit videos
LosslessCut based on Chromium and uses the video player HTML5, so not all formats are...
</description></item><item><title>Download Draftable Desktop 25.10.200</title><pubDate> Sat, 25 Oct 2025 00:28:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-draftable-desktop-3749.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-draftable-desktop-3749.html
</guid><description>
Draftable Desktop is comparison tool documents the fastest. Compare over 300 pages in a few seconds. Draftable Desktop 2.0 is now available - faster and stronger than ever! See all the changes in your documents, locally and online. Take your work to the next level. Compare secret and private do not use the internet and your documents never leave your computer. Specifically, Draftable Desktop compatible with .xls, .xlsx, .xlsxm. With Office 2013, 2016 or 365, you can compare text in...
</description></item><item><title>Download FTPGetter Professional 5.97.0.293</title><pubDate> Sat, 25 Oct 2025 00:27:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ftpgetter-professional-1550.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ftpgetter-professional-1550.html
</guid><description>
FTPGetter Professional is software that automates the uploading and downloading of files, allowing scheduling file transfer between your computer with the FTP server and SFTP remote. If you often access FTP / SFTP to sync files between local computer and remote PC, to update your website or upload images, webcam, FTPGetter will save you lots of time and effort.
FTPGetter Professional comes with emulator terminal integration, allowing you to connect and execute commands on remote server...
</description></item><item><title>Download PentaLogix CAMMaster 11.24.67</title><pubDate> Sat, 25 Oct 2025 00:27:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pentalogix-cammaster-5559.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pentalogix-cammaster-5559.html
</guid><description>
CAMMaster Designer is CAM software of choice by the Designer for the most demanding jobs. Experience the industry's best CAD companion to get your work done. The disinfection process is fast with all the features available in this package. Exploiting Netlist and DRC sets industry standards. Basically, CamMaster provides many functions depending on the relevant needs of the user. It also provides nearly five free technical support. Furthermore, net list comparison and class comparison make...
</description></item><item><title>Download Code VBA 11.0.0.24</title><pubDate> Sat, 25 Oct 2025 00:26:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-code-vba-7207.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-code-vba-7207.html
</guid><description>
Code VBA allows professional software developers and MS Office users to write VBA code faster and take less time to search for online solutions. Find and insert VBA for Excel, Access and Word according to the application object model. The tool annotation explains what classes and procedures perform and grant direct access (F1) to the relevant documentation on Office MSDN online. In addition, the VBA code creator supports the writing of larger code blocks.
Features of Code VBA:
	The...
</description></item><item><title>Download DBF Recovery 4.58</title><pubDate> Sat, 25 Oct 2025 00:26:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbf-recovery-7931.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbf-recovery-7931.html
</guid><description>
DBF Recovery is software that gives users the ability to restore a damaged database back to its original condition without the expertise required to complete that task. It fixes headers and data structures in an automated process that doesn't involve user interaction. With DBF Recovery, you will truly have a lean, honest DBF repair machine without any functionality.
Features of DBF Recovery
	Quick and simple to use DBF file repair software.
	Repair almost any DBF...
</description></item><item><title>Download Certificate Manager 18.35</title><pubDate> Sat, 25 Oct 2025 00:25:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-certificate-manager-13958.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-certificate-manager-13958.html
</guid><description>
Certificate Manager provides an in-depth overview of your current certificates, allowing you to easily access detailed information. It also provides functions for both exporting existing certificates and importing new certificates, enhancing your certificate management capabilities.
Application certificates are often overlooked by most users until problems arise during application installation. For the average end user, there is little reason to focus on application certificates....
</description></item><item><title>Download System Info 18.35</title><pubDate> Sat, 25 Oct 2025 00:25:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-system-info-11391.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-system-info-11391.html
</guid><description>
System Info is a simple piece of software that displays various information about your system, including its hardware, operating system, and more. Having everything presented in a single interface, where you can copy and share that data elsewhere, can finally become convenient for regular users. That's what System Information does: it gives you various data about your system, including hardware specifications, operating system, network, and more. without installation.
This application...
</description></item><item><title>Download Edge Remover 18.35</title><pubDate> Sat, 25 Oct 2025 00:25:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-edge-remover-7689.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-edge-remover-7689.html
</guid><description>
Edge Remover is our mini user interfaceless tool to permanently remove Microsoft Edge from your system. Easily remove Microsoft Edge browser from your system, with just one click, with this simple, no UI app.
Features of Edge Remover
	Remove MSEdge and its components
	Prevent reinstalling MSEdge on your system
Requirements:
Operating System: Microsoft Windows 7 or later
Framework: Microsoft .NET Framework 4.0
</description></item></channel></rss>