<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 17:35:40 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 17:35:40 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Display Driver Uninstaller (DDU) 18.1.4.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 17:30:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-display-driver-uninstaller-1999.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-display-driver-uninstaller-1999.html
</guid><description>
Display Driver Uninstaller (DDU) help to easily completely remove the packages and drivers graphics cards AMD, NVIDIA and Intel from your system without leaving any rest whatsoever. Display Driver Uninstaller will automatically detect your current GPU and allows you to delete drivers, registry and files related only by the click of a button. It will also prevent Windows automatically re-install drivers when you reboot your computer, leaving you a drivers graphics common until you install...
</description></item><item><title>Download Foxit PDF Editor Pro 2025.3.0.35737 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 17:29:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-foxit-pdf-editor-pro-162.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-foxit-pdf-editor-pro-162.html
</guid><description>
Foxit PDF Editor Pro (formerly Foxit PhantomPDF Business) is a PDF toolkit dedicated to the creation of professional PDF documents and forms. You can do that for tasks such as personal document development, working group collaboration, company model design. Manufacturing the company's collateral, completing the agreements, applying the signature number or document storage.
Foxit PDF Editor Pro is the perfect solution for family/family offices, small and medium enterprises and large...
</description></item><item><title>Download Balabolka 2.15.0.910</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 17:28:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-balaboka-142.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-balaboka-142.html
</guid><description>
Balabolka is a text-to-speech (TTS) program. It can read text on your screen in a human-like voice. You can use Balabolka to listen to text from a variety of file formats, convert text to spoken audio files, and adjust speech parameters such as speed and pitch. It is often used for accessibility purposes, helping people who have difficulty reading or multi-tasking by listening to text while doing other activities. Balabolka supports multiple languages and uses different TTS engines,...
</description></item><item><title>Download R-Wipe &amp;amp; Clean 20.0 Build 2539</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 17:28:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-wipe-clean-891.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-wipe-clean-891.html
</guid><description>
R-Wipe &amp;amp; Clean is software to delete junk files, unnecessary files from your computer to release the storage space and speed up your computer. In addition, R-Wipe &amp;amp; Clean also unleash the capacity of your drive and delete information invasion of privacy on different operations online and offline including your internet history and cookies, the list of downloaded files and documents were open, buffer different data, temporary files and many other items, created by the operating...
</description></item><item><title>Download CapCut PC 7.7.0.3143</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 17:27:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capcut-pc-9995.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capcut-pc-9995.html
</guid><description>
CapCut PC is a simple video editing tool that you can freely use anywhere. You can create videos on your browser, desktop and laptop, or on your phone. Versatile editing, magical AI tools, team collaboration, and built-in assets. Create videos in a whole new way.
You can edit videos based on editing the timeline, in the process you can add different elements and effects to the video to give the best effect to your work. It is a simple and intuitive set of editing tools and effects that...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wipe Pro 2025.15</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 17:26:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wipe-pro-710.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wipe-pro-710.html
</guid><description>
Wipe Pro is software that helps clean up litter, increase in hard drive space besides also protect your privacy on the Internet, it removes records about personal activity on the computer. You will be able to delete browser history and the cache, the file index.dat, registry, files, cookies, internet history, auto complete, temporary internet files and many other items. This program also delete all activities other individuals that you made when using the PC and regardless of which...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cockos REAPER 7.56</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 17:26:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cockos-reaper-889.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cockos-reaper-889.html
</guid><description>
Cockos REAPER is a powerful software for for windows, chp lets you record, arrange, edit, and display the audio waveform multi-track. Cockos REAPER offers an extensive feature set includes many effects and a sample project. REAPER supports ASIO, Kernel Streaming, WaveOut, and DirectSound for playback and recording. It reads the files in WAV, OGG and MP3 files and records WAV files. You can arrange any number of items in any number of tracks and use plug-in sound processing (DirectX and...
</description></item><item><title>Download OBS Studio 32.0.4</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 17:25:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-open-broadcaster-software-2451.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-open-broadcaster-software-2451.html
</guid><description>
Open Broadcaster Software is abbreviated as OBS is a program to detect the type of multimedia content to the internet. It is worth noting that a simple interface and the presence of a good tool. You can adjust the quality of the audio and video before starting the broadcast, you can specify the URL, choose the resolution of the screen, etc. With strong desire, videos which you found can be saved to your hard drive.
Open Broadcaster Software - LiveStream on PC
The basic features of Open...
</description></item><item><title>Download XRECODE3 1.176</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 17:24:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xrecode-iii-2915.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xrecode-iii-2915.html
</guid><description>
"Xrecode II" is the switch and grab the audio allows you to convert from mp2, mp3, ac3, aiff, wma, amr, ogg, ape, flac, cue, mpc, wv, tak, mid, cue, m4b, tta, wav, dts , wav (rf64), m4a, mp4, ra, shn, rm, avi, aac, mpg, vob, mka, mkv, flv, Mov, swf, ofr, divx, wmv, spx, mp3, m4v, 3gp, m2v, 3g2, m4v, m2ts, ts, adts, tak, xm, mod, it, s3m, alac, umx, mtm, mlp to m4a, ape, flac, mp4 (using NeroAAC), raw, ogg, wav, wav (rf64) , wma, mpc, WavPack, mp2, ofr, Speex, ac3, tak, aiff, snd, Shorten...
</description></item><item><title>Download Quick Clipboard Editor 3.1.2.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 17:23:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quick-clipboard-editor-9421.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quick-clipboard-editor-9421.html
</guid><description>
Quick Clipboard Editor is free software that provides direct access to the text stored in your clipboard, allowing you to quickly modify it to meet your needs. meet your needs before pasting the text into the app you want. It allows you to quickly retrieve previous clips from your clipboard history, find and replace specific words or phrases, insert new content into each line, trim unwanted pieces of text, keep or remove lines or characters based on different criteria, arrange text using...
</description></item><item><title>Download reaConverter Pro 8.0.169</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 17:23:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html
</guid><description>
reaConverter Pro is software image processing feature with batch conversion and image editing periodically becomes simple. eaConverter also provide command line utilities allow you to process images automatically, thus helping you shorten the time for other work.
reaConverter Pro integrated powerful tool of Uber with many great features. It provides advanced solutions to process and adjust images. Management of the conversion process the base image with the latest version of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Windows Memory Cleaner 3.0.8</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 17:22:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-memory-cleaner-9959.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-memory-cleaner-9959.html
</guid><description>
Sometimes programs don't release the memory they used, making the computer slow, but you don't want to restart the system to get the used memory back. This is where you use Windows Memory Cleaner to clean up memory so you can continue working without having to restart Windows.
How to clean RAM of Windows Memory Cleaner
	Clean Combined Page List Removes blocks from the combined page list. Valid only when site merge is enabled.
	Clean Modified Page List Clears memory from the Modified...
</description></item><item><title>Download WhatsApp 2.2549.4.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 17:22:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-whatsapp-61.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-whatsapp-61.html
</guid><description>
WhatsApp is an extension for the app WhatsApp mobile allows you to send and receive messages from the comfort of desktop your.Just install WhatsApp on your pc and scan the QR code from the mobile application WhatsApp and all the chats and your contacts will be able to access from your computer to your desk.
WhatsApp - Send and receive messages for free
Moreover, they will be automatically synced to all your conversations on your computer also available on your phone.The Windows version...
</description></item><item><title>Download Bitwig Studio 6.0 Beta 8</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 17:21:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bitwig-studio-3626.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bitwig-studio-3626.html
</guid><description>
Find new standard in the process of individual work. Bitwig Studio excite you good control over his music, give you access to all features of your production. Streamline course creation of you and quickly develop your ideas into the songs, compositions and music full.
Bitwig Studio - Create your own music
Arrange and record, perform and improvise, or do all at the same time. Choose among the many records displayed. Design your sound with the equipment container commitment. Mixing the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tomabo MP4 Downloader Pro 6.0.8</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 17:21:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tomabo-mp4-downloader-pro-3602.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tomabo-mp4-downloader-pro-3602.html
</guid><description>
Tomabo MP4 Downloader Pro is the app designed exclusively for Windows users to help them download videos from the Internet. In addition, it also increase download speeds by up to 500%, or even more. Tomabo MP4 Downloader Pro, interface design, simple, well-organized, beautifully. Here, users can view a list of videos has download with gravatar, URL, quality, duration and size of them. Software allows download video series at the same time, at the same time, support create a list of clips...
</description></item><item><title>Download VovSoft Serial Port Monitor 2.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 17:21:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-serial-port-monitor-7140.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-serial-port-monitor-7140.html
</guid><description>
VovSoft Serial Port Monitor is a tool to analyze computer COM port communication data traffic. You can receive/read data from any COM port and transfer/send data to any COM port. You can change connection parameters such as baud rate, parity, data bit and stop bit. Can send text periodically, you can change sending interval in milliseconds. The "Clear", "Save to file" and "Copy to clipboard" buttons can be used. You can also set the font and background color using the menu.
You can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mikey Audio FlipCraft 1.1.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 17:20:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mikey-audio-flipcraft-14256.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mikey-audio-flipcraft-14256.html
</guid><description>
FlipCraft is an advanced sample cutting plugin designed to empower producers, beatmakers, and sound designers with unprecedented control, flexibility, and speed. Starting today, users can download a free trial and experience FlipCraft's advanced features firsthand. FlipCraft takes sample processing to the next level. With intuitive controls and powerful built-in technology.
Features of FlipCraft
	View and interact with high-resolution, zoomable waveforms
	Apply advanced stem...
</description></item><item><title>Download PVS-Studio 7.40.101088.2089</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 17:20:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pvs-studio-1480.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pvs-studio-1480.html
</guid><description>
PVS-Studio is software that performs static code analysis and generate a report to help programmers find and fix bugs. PVS-Studio implements a series of check code, it is also useful to search the prints wrong error and Copy-Paste. Examples of such errors: V501, V517, V522, V523, V3001.
The main value of static analysis is in regular use, hence the error is identified and corrected at the earliest stages. There's no point of wasting 50 hours to search for a fault can be found with static...
</description></item><item><title>Download PentaLogix ViewMate Pro 11.24.72</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 17:19:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pentalogix-viewmate-pro-1008.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pentalogix-viewmate-pro-1008.html
</guid><description>
PentaLogix ViewMate Pro is software to view, edit and convert files from DXF to other formats such as Gerber. When using ViewMate Pro, with the DFM smart, you can check the data view there are mass violations or not. And not just a class once! Many violations, laminated with results quickly and accurately. The system provides an error report in ASCII, and in addition, create a file Gerber to help edit the file plot quickly.
PentaLogix ViewMate Pro - View and convert DXF
ViewMate Pro,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Danil Pristupov Fork 2.15.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 17:19:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fork-6879.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fork-6879.html
</guid><description>
Fork is a great Git client app that allows you to keep tabs on every file line so you can know who is the last person to make changes. The simple and intuitive design of this app helps the management of all of your warehouses much easier. The Fork interface is extremely friendly to users. There is a long list of repositories, branches, origins, tags and archives on the left side of the screen.
With Fork, you can also search and open any of the repositories quickly, from the top of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Audija KickDrum 2.7.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 17:18:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-audija-kickdrum-14117.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-audija-kickdrum-14117.html
</guid><description>
Audija KickDrum is a highly accurate kick drum synthesizer plugin, designed for electronic music producers looking for maximum control and versatility in their bass drum sounds. It features a three-dimensional wavetable engine, detailed harmonic editing, and extensive routing options, making it far superior to a typical drum plugin.
KickDrum Features
	Combine a precise sine oscillator—with a fixed zero-crossing point—and a flexible sampler to layer and analyze kick sounds.
	Shape...
</description></item><item><title>Download WSL Distro Manager 1.10.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 17:08:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wsl-distro-manager-10290.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wsl-distro-manager-10290.html
</guid><description>
WSL Distro Manager is a free and open source application that provides a graphical user-friendly interface for managing Windows Subsystem for Linux (WSL) distributions. . With WSL Distro Manager you can easily install, install, org update, backup and restore WSL distributions, as well as configure installation and launch them with just one click. WSL Distro Manager also offers a number of additional features to enhance your WSL experience, offering limits such as sharing distributions...
</description></item><item><title>Download Picture Window Pro 8.0.540</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 17:07:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-picture-window-pro-7452.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-picture-window-pro-7452.html
</guid><description>
Picture Window Pro is a powerful image editing tool designed for serious photographers with strict creative and quality standards. Its comprehensive set of photo editing and editing tools let you control and shape every aspect of your images.
Picture Window Pro 8 is a complete rewrite of Picture Window Pro 7. It features non-destructive image editing through a novel interface based on an image tree. It also fully supports large, high-resolution displays and can be used in dual monitor...
</description></item><item><title>Download Digital Compass 18.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 16:37:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-digital-compass-13590.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-digital-compass-13590.html
</guid><description>
This app is a smart compass with high accuracy and a great tool for outdoor activities. This compass app allows you to easily determine the direction you are facing. This app is built using the device's gyroscope, accelerometer, magnetometer, gravity sensor to determine the direction. Make sure your device has an accelerometer and magnetometer sensor or it will not work.
Features
	Show current location (longitude, latitude, address)
	Show altitude
	Show magnetic field strength
	Show...
</description></item><item><title>Download All PDF Editor &amp;amp; Reader | Xodo 10.10.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 14 Dec 2025 16:37:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-xodo-pdf-reader-editor-8451.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-xodo-pdf-reader-editor-8451.html
</guid><description>
Xodo PDF Reader &amp;amp; Editor is a mobile application for reading and editing PDF documents on Android and iOS devices. The app allows users to view, annotate, and edit PDF files using a variety of tools, including highlighting, underlining, and adding notes. With Xodo, you can read, annotate, sign, and share PDFs and fill out PDF forms, all while syncing with Google Drive, Dropbox, and OneDrive.
Xodo PDF Reader &amp;amp; Editor Features
	PDF Viewer: Application that allows users to view...
</description></item></channel></rss>