<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:31:49 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:31:49 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Power-user for PowerPoint and Excel 1.7.73.270</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:31:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-power-user-for-powerpoint-and-excel-522.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-power-user-for-powerpoint-and-excel-522.html
</guid><description>
Power-user for PowerPoint and Excel is a utility providing you with a library of templates, icons, charts, maps and diagrams for spreadsheet and presentation. With Power-user for PowerPoint and Excel, you will attract the attention of your audience with stunning graphics will certainly impress.
Power-user comes with a collection of 2,000 icons to illustrate your slides. The icons are vector shapes so you can resize them without distortion and color back as you with. With Power-user, you...
</description></item><item><title>Download EaseUS Data Recovery Wizard Professional WinPE 20.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:30:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-data-recovery-wizard-winpe-4379.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-data-recovery-wizard-winpe-4379.html
</guid><description>
EaseUS Data Recovery Wizard WinPE - recovery software best data to restore data deleted, formatted or lost from PC, laptop or mobile device easily and quickly. Help get back the lost files or deleted photos, music, sounds, emails, etc. from hard drive, memory card, USB, digital cameras, mobile devices, and other storage media. Program recover data this recover files lost or deleted 100% safe from losing cases different data on different devices without overwriting original data.
EaseUS...
</description></item><item><title>Download Room Arranger 10.3.4.743</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:30:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-room-arranger-3779.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-room-arranger-3779.html
</guid><description>
Room Arranger is a 3D application lets you easily plan for the room, office or his apartment just a few mouse clicks. The application comes with a simple interface will significantly simplify your work. You can draw many kinds of objects and items to create furniture of your own. This app also includes a library of object rich.
Software Room Arranger enables you to view your project in 3D form. You can also upload the 3D scene interact on your blog or your website. The application uses...
</description></item><item><title>Download Coolmuster Word to PDF Converter 2.7.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:29:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-word-to-pdf-converter-4839.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-word-to-pdf-converter-4839.html
</guid><description>
Coolmuster Word to PDF Converter is a reliable app and simple and help users to quickly convert Word documents to PDF for easy management and share. After conversion Word documents to PDF format, you will easily transfer files between your computer with other apps without encountering problems connecting, how.
Now when using this software, you will be very surprised to see conversion results. PDF file is still retaining all contents, text, images, layout and original formatting in the...
</description></item><item><title>Download MyLanViewer Enterprise 6.7.5</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:29:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mylanviewer-enterprise-1274.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mylanviewer-enterprise-1274.html
</guid><description>
MyLanViewer is a program for scanning IP address, Netbios and LAN / Network powerful for Windows tool whois and traceroute, remote shutdown and process management Wake On LAN (WOL), scan and monitor wireless networks. This app will help you find all IP addresses, MAC addresses and shared folders of computers on the network wired or wireless (Wi-Fi).
MyLanViewer Enterprise - Scan IP address LAN/Network
The program scans network and displays the computer network in your window, friends...
</description></item><item><title>Download Coolmuster PDF Password Remover 2.3.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:28:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-pdf-password-remover-4203.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-pdf-password-remover-4203.html
</guid><description>
Coolmuster PDF Password Remover is software password unlock PDF files protected Click people like to use password to protect copyright PDF of their work out of copying, printing, editing or stealing by others. So, sometimes you need to delete password from PDF to edit, copy, or share. Under this situation, Coolmuster PDF Password Remover can be an ideal assistant to you can remove password as you like.
Coolmuster PDF Password Remover - Remove password protected PDF
Forget the PDF...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinShift Forge 0.7.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:27:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winshift-forge-14401.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winshift-forge-14401.html
</guid><description>
What is WinShift Forge?
WinShift Forge is a lightweight utility built to enhance the performance of Windows 11. WinShift Forge allows you to easily remove them, free up space, and speed up your system. WinShift Forge lets you instantly refresh your computer screen by customizing the most important icons. No more fumbling through complex system settings—easily take direct control of the core Windows visuals and make your PC truly your own.
Key Features:
Personalize Your PC
	Replace...
</description></item><item><title>Download Coolmuster PDF Locker 2.6.4</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:27:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-pdf-locker-9592.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-pdf-locker-9592.html
</guid><description>
Coolmuster PDF Locker is a software program designed to secure and protect PDF documents by adding password encryption and various access restrictions. It provides features that help you control and manage the security of your PDF files. Discover the importance of password protecting your PDF files to keep your valuable data safe and secure. Protect your documents and keep sensitive information private as you please with this PDF encryption software now.
Discover three levels of strong...
</description></item><item><title>Download Coolmuster PDF to Word Converter 2.3.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:26:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-pdf-to-word-converter-4838.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-pdf-to-word-converter-4838.html
</guid><description>
Coolmuster PDF to Word Converter is simple tool to help you convert PDF files to Word. Microsoft Word is a file format ideal, allows users to edit, change and share with your friends without encountering any restrictions. So, if you want to edit PDF files on Mac, then try converting it to Word format to edit better. Coolmuster PDF to Word Converter will help all Mac users to quickly export Adobe to Word docx.
Now, with Coolmuster PDF to Word Converter, users can perfectly peace of mind...
</description></item><item><title>Download Coolmuster ePub Converter 2.3.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:26:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-epub-converter-4201.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-epub-converter-4201.html
</guid><description>
Coolmuster ePub Converter is software to convert the file format common to documents ePub. you probably already know is ePub, as a format of electronic books popular, widely supported by most all devices for reading electronic books popular. So, have you ever wondered about converting other files to ePub format to read on your device read your ebooks while you go out? An idea not bad, right? Just download the software Coolmuster ePub Converter, all conversion from files to ePub simple the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Syncovery Premium 11.12.6.160</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:25:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncovery-pro-enterprise-232.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncovery-pro-enterprise-232.html
</guid><description>
Syncovery Pro Enterprise is a great application used to back up data and to synchronize personal computers, servers, laptops, notepads and storage online. The software comes with support for FTP and secure FTP servers, SSH, WebDAV, Amazon S3, http, update the part file, ZIP compression, data encryption, and schedule automatic backups.
Syncovery Pro Enterprise have the ability to freely select files and folders across the whole folder hierarchy in tree view and supports email...
</description></item><item><title>Download SonarQube Data Center Edition 2026.1.0.119033 MultiOS</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:25:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sonarqube-data-center-edition-8059.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sonarqube-data-center-edition-8059.html
</guid><description>
SonarQube empowers all developers to write cleaner and safer code. Join the Open Community of over 200,000 developer groups. SonarQube provides reports on duplicate code, coding standards, unit testing, code coverage, code complexity, comments, bugs, and security recommendations.
Features of SonarQube
	Detect complex bugs to prevent undefined behavior from affecting end users.
	Fix your apps' vulnerabilities and learn about AppSec along the way with Secure Hotspot.
	Make sure your...
</description></item><item><title>Download Coolmuster PDF Creator Pro 2.7.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:24:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-pdf-creator-pro-4200.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-pdf-creator-pro-4200.html
</guid><description>
Coolmuster PDF Creator Pro is a tool to create PDF files of your own easily and manage the different files on the computer and convert all the file similar or related into a PDF file large. With Coolmuster PDF Creator Pro you can create your own PDF from 4 different formats so you can share and manage files on computer more effectively. You can create PDF files from 7 major formats, including Microsoft Word (.docx), Text (.txt), image (.jpg, .png, .gif, .bmp, etc.), MOBI (.mobi .prc),...
</description></item><item><title>Download Coolmuster PDF Merger 3.2.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:24:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-pdf-merger-9590.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-pdf-merger-9590.html
</guid><description>
Coolmuster PDF Merger is a relatively simple tool that can get the job done without requiring much effort on your part. It has a modern interface where users can add documents they want to merge, which this tool can combine within seconds. Merge PDF files easily with Coolmuster PDF Merger, a reliable and eco-friendly PDF combiner. Attractive interface and intuitive instructions make merging easy.
Merge PDFs and images easily while preserving the original quality. Enjoy a seamless...
</description></item><item><title>Download TeamViewer 15.74.4 + Portable</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:23:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-teamviewer-528.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-teamviewer-528.html
</guid><description>
TeamViewer is software that functions to connect and control the remote computer, the ability to connect with any system anywhere from all over the place. This is a support tool users is very convenient. TeamViewer to help users control remote computer becomes much more simple, help you interact and collaborate with others in the exchange and share of information, instruction manual, application software or fix the computer.
TeamViewer as a revolution of computer science. when you have...
</description></item><item><title>Download Coolmuster PDF to ePub Converter 2.5.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:17:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-pdf-to-epub-converter-9596.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-pdf-to-epub-converter-9596.html
</guid><description>
Coolmuster PDF to ePub Converter is a software tool that allows you to convert PDF documents to ePub format. ePub is a widely supported e-book format that can be read on a variety of devices, including e-readers, tablets, and smartphones. With this converter you can convert your PDF files to ePub format for better readability and compatibility on different devices and platforms.
Also, Coolmuster PDF to ePub Converter's built-in PDF preview function allows you to preview all PDF content...
</description></item><item><title>Download Coolmuster PDF Converter Pro 2.3.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:16:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-pdf-converter-pro-4204.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-pdf-converter-pro-4204.html
</guid><description>
Coolmuster PDF Converter Pro is the app to convert PDF to different formats for editing You want to edit PDF files without Adobe Acrobat Pro professional? You can try Coolmuster PDF Converter Pro to convert PDF files to different formats 7 to edit and share as you like. A conversion tool PDF good will support the output formats are different and have high conversion speed, quality loss, etc. Coolmuster PDF Converter Pro is a powerful program, is the desktop application for PDF...
</description></item><item><title>Download HFS: HTTP File Server (version 3) 3.0.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:16:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hfs-http-file-server-11851.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hfs-http-file-server-11851.html
</guid><description>
HFS is a web file server to run on your computer. Share a folder or even a file thanks to the virtual file system. Essentially, this application turns your computer into an HTTP server and all users who want to connect and download files can do so by loading a simple website in their browser. HFS includes many configuration settings, so you can basically change each part of the application, starting with how users download files and ending with the appearance of the created website.
HFS...
</description></item><item><title>Download Talking Translator - Languages 3.6.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:14:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-talking-translator-9776.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-talking-translator-9776.html
</guid><description>
With the instant translation feature, the Talking Translator application will help you communicate in any multilingual environment such as when traveling, going on business trips, meeting buyers or just simple conversations. You can translate into more than 100 languages ​​with just this one app: Talking Translator! You don't know how to read sentences? Nothing! Talking Translator provides handwritten text translation.
Supports more than 100 languages ​​including English,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Centi PRO - Currency Converter 8.0.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:13:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-centi-pro-currency-converter-9377.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-centi-pro-currency-converter-9377.html
</guid><description>
Centi is a simple and fast currency converter, providing up-to-date exchange rate information for over 170 currencies and countries. It has a beautiful interface for quick access to the conversions you need. Centi Money Converter is great for traveling abroad or for monitoring foreign markets.
Centi PRO Features - Currency Converter
	Convert over 170 currencies and exchange rates
	Utilities
	Create custom currency (price, name, country, flag, symbol and code)
	Download data only when...
</description></item><item><title>Download Bluelight Filter for Eye Care 6.6.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:13:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-bluelight-filter-for-eye-care-8192.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-bluelight-filter-for-eye-care-8192.html
</guid><description>
Blue light from smartphones or tablets causes eye strain and makes it difficult to sleep at night. This app adjusts your screen color to reduce blue light and relax your eyes, helping you sleep better.
Features of Blue Light Filter for Eye Care
	Free screen filter app to protect your eyes
	Screen filter with natural colors
	Easy operation
	Turn on or off quickly and easily
	Automatic start
	Eye care on your smartphone or tablet
	This app works on most smartphones like Samsung Galaxy,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Net Signal Pro: WiFi &amp;amp; 5G Meter 4.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:13:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-net-signal-pro-wifi-5g-meter-9658.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-net-signal-pro-wifi-5g-meter-9658.html
</guid><description>
This app is a useful tool that allows you to check your WiFi Signal Strength and Mobile Signal Strength anywhere using your mobile device. It helps to find areas with good WiFi or cellular connectivity to set up smart home devices. View mobile signal 2G, 3G, 4G, 5G, network carrier, sim operator, phone type, network type, network strength in dBm, IP address,...
Features of Net Signal Pro: WiFi &amp;amp; 5G Meter
	Mobile signal information
	WiFi signal information
	Accurate Wi-Fi and...
</description></item><item><title>Download CALCU Stylish Basic Calculator 4.7.14</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:13:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-stylish-calculator-calcu-8716.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-stylish-calculator-calcu-8716.html
</guid><description>
Express your style with a computer made just for you. Choose a stylish, colorful theme to brighten your day while you calculate with ease. CALCU™ is easy to use for everyday calculations, with all the scientific capabilities you need for work and school at a swipe. And for your most demanding needs, CALCU™ lets you add or remove the functions and constants you need to create the perfect calculator you designed for you.
Features of Fashion Calculator - CALCU
	Try our new Material...
</description></item><item><title>Download Image Size - Photo Resizer 10.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:12:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-image-size-photo-resizer-12071.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-image-size-photo-resizer-12071.html
</guid><description>
This app allows you to resize images to any size you like (with limitations), quickly and easily. It is actually a resizing application. You can specify the output format using one of the following four measurement units: pixels, millimeters, centimeters, inches. To maintain aspect ratio, simply tap the chain icon between the width and height input fields. Image Dimensions gives you the option to save, email, print, or share the final image.
Main features:
	Resize photos or images...
</description></item><item><title>Download Email Aqua Mail - Fast, Secure 1.57.0 build 105700601</title><pubDate> Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:12:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-email-aqua-mail-fast-secure-8329.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-email-aqua-mail-fast-secure-8329.html
</guid><description>
Aqua Mail is the right app for all your email needs! Whether it's a work or personal email, a company exchange server, or even a rarely used secondary account, Aqua Mail lets you easily access all your emails from one complete app. edit.
No complicated setup required, just enter your email and password and you're done. With flexibility and diverse customization options, Aqua Mail's goal is to reflect the needs of modern users and provide a platform that anyone can tailor to their needs...
</description></item></channel></rss>