<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 15:35:14 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 15:35:14 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download NetSpeedTray 1.1.4 + Portable</title><pubDate> Sat, 23 Aug 2025 18:05:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-netspeedtray-14068.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-netspeedtray-14068.html
</guid><description>
NetSpeedTray is a lightweight, open source network monitor for Windows that displays upload/download speeds directly on the Taskbar with a native look and feel.
Designed to blend seamlessly with Windows 10/11 user interface. Includes intelligent detection of light and dark themes on the taskbar to ensure text is always visible. Sits quietly in the system tray without hogging resources. Features "Dynamic Update Rate" that automatically reduces update frequency when the network is idle to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Minimal Firewall 2.1.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 23 Aug 2025 18:04:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minimal-firewall-13877.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minimal-firewall-13877.html
</guid><description>
Minimal Firewall works in conjunction with Windows Firewall to block all unknown connections by default, prompting you to create application-based rules to mitigate malware, telemetry, and data leaks. Completely eliminate applications that call home without your knowledge. Minimal Firewall provides a more secure and integrated approach by interacting directly with the native Windows Firewall, eliminating the need for risky system modifications.
Core Features
	Lockdown Mode: The core...
</description></item><item><title>Download MEmu Android Emulator 9.2.7</title><pubDate> Sat, 23 Aug 2025 18:03:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-memu-2975.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-memu-2975.html
</guid><description>
MEmu or also known as Android Emulator is the Android emulator light and free, allowing Windows users to enjoy Android experience the original on the computer and device Microsoft their. This app provides outstanding performance, allowing you to play on PC a series of games designed to run on Android devices. This app allows you to play the game favorite Android on larger screens, to bring you a better gaming experience.
MEmu - Android emulator, lightweight and free
Software MEmu also...
</description></item><item><title>Download Q-Dir 12.33</title><pubDate> Sat, 23 Aug 2025 18:01:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-q-dir-348.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-q-dir-348.html
</guid><description>
Q-Dir is software to manage the entire file and folder on the computer, allowing to see file in same time 4 different positions (viewport quadro) while still maintaining all the standard features of the Explorer.
It also provides a variety of management features, additional files included the filter file color-coding, layouts and columns can be customized, quick access to file and folder favorites and more.
Other features of Q-Dir , including directory listings (.txt, .doc .html .csv),...
</description></item><item><title>Download Disk Drill Enterprise 6.0.1054.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 23 Aug 2025 18:00:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-disk-drill-enterprise-6875.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-disk-drill-enterprise-6875.html
</guid><description>
Disk Drill Enterprise is software that allows you to recover files from hard drives and USB devices, external hard drives, memory cards, iPhone and iPad, drive formats like NTFS, FAT, exFAT, HFS + Mac drive, EXT2/3/4. The software provides fast scan and deep scan mode, depending on the user's needs, to save time and achieve the highest efficiency.
Features of Disk Drill Enterprise
	Users simply need one click to activate Disk Drill.
	Support to scan the entire drive and rejoin lost...
</description></item><item><title>Download Chaos V-Ray 7.1.2 Build 7.10.02 for SketchUp 2021 - 2025</title><pubDate> Sat, 23 Aug 2025 18:00:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vray-for-sketchup-3936.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vray-for-sketchup-3936.html
</guid><description>
V-Ray Next for SketchUp is the tool of Chaos Group for Windows PC, this is a lighting tool and as a professional for architects &amp;amp; designers.V-Ray Next for SketchUp allows you to export everything and everything - from the design models to the 3D scene details most of you. Use V-Ray for SketchUp, you can also have access to over 600 documents actual photo, drag and drop. V-Ray Next for SketchUp is very easy to use and brings great results. You can use it to create everything - from 3D...
</description></item><item><title>Download NxFilter 4.7.3.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 23 Aug 2025 17:59:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nxfilter-50.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nxfilter-50.html
</guid><description>
NxFilter is a server filter DNS have the ability to filter Internet traffic based on domain names and content types. In addition, it can use check package DNS to protect your network from malware and botnet activity.
NxFilter is installed on a single computer, where it acts as a proxy server, DNS. To route Internet traffic through NxFilter, you will need to change the DNS settings on all the machines that you want to protect to use the IP address of the individual NxFilter (instead of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Quick Clipboard Editor 3.1.1.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 23 Aug 2025 17:58:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quick-clipboard-editor-9421.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quick-clipboard-editor-9421.html
</guid><description>
Quick Clipboard Editor is free software that provides direct access to the text stored in your clipboard, allowing you to quickly modify it to meet your needs. meet your needs before pasting the text into the app you want. It allows you to quickly retrieve previous clips from your clipboard history, find and replace specific words or phrases, insert new content into each line, trim unwanted pieces of text, keep or remove lines or characters based on different criteria, arrange text using...
</description></item><item><title>Download Chaos Corona 13.1 for 3ds Max 2016 - 2026</title><pubDate> Sat, 23 Aug 2025 17:58:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chaos-corona-2986.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chaos-corona-2986.html
</guid><description>
Corona Renderer is the name of the plug-in technique and dedicated powerful, but have high functionality for Autodesk software 3ds Max. Plug before you is a standalone application known to the CLI. In addition, users can use this tool to promote their business on software Maxon Cinema 4D is also used. The manufacturers of this product believe that working with this tool is very simple and in fact you only need to press the activities rendered. With this tool easier than ever can do the...
</description></item><item><title>Download GoodSync Enterprise 12.9.7.7</title><pubDate> Sat, 23 Aug 2025 17:57:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-goodsync-enterprise-163.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-goodsync-enterprise-163.html
</guid><description>
GoodSync Enterprise is a software that saves files and files easily and is reliable. It automatically analyts, synchronize and backup your email, family photos, contacts, MP3, financial documentation and other important files-between desktop computers, laptops, servers, external drives and Windows Mobile devices as well as remotely via FTP , SFTP, WebDAV and more. The GoodSync synchronized software combines bulletproof reliability with an extremely easy interface to compare, synchronize...
</description></item><item><title>Download PingPlotter Professional 5.25.16.9082</title><pubDate> Sat, 23 Aug 2025 17:55:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pingplotter-professional-4090.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pingplotter-professional-4090.html
</guid><description>
PingPlotter Professional is monitoring software network graphics, drawing graphs latency and data packet loss for maximum hundreds of targets at the same time. It includes everything in PingPlotter Standard, plus tools to monitor multi-targets, communicating with other systems, and collect data remotely. PingPlotter Professional is accessed through interface like web browser. PingPlotter Pro check out hundreds of targets at the same time. Summary chart available to the organization goals...
</description></item><item><title>Download CLO Standalone OnlineAuth 2025.1.126</title><pubDate> Sat, 23 Aug 2025 17:55:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-clo-standalone-2806.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-clo-standalone-2806.html
</guid><description>
CLO Standalone is a powerful software to design 3D clothes and outfits. Nowadays, computer plays a prominent role in the industry and the different industries use a variety of techniques and computer techniques to increase the quality and quantity of their products. In the garment industry, it is important to design new templates for clothing to meet the needs of customers and diversify. Aware of this demand, programmers and software companies have launched many products to help the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Chaos V-Ray 7.1.2 Build 7.10.02 for Rhinoceros 7-9</title><pubDate> Sat, 23 Aug 2025 17:54:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-v-ray-next-for-rhino-1285.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-v-ray-next-for-rhino-1285.html
</guid><description>
V-Ray Next For Rhino is an extension a very powerful and handy for Rhino can be used to improve the process output. V-Ray Next allows you to achieve much achievement in Rhino than ever. It's faster to showcase your designs in the best light of them. And a variety of new tools to help manage and display the sight of you much easier.
V-Ray Next For Rhino
V-Ray Next in for Rhino comes with some speed on the table. Optimize performance, speed up the production up to 50% off. The shader...
</description></item><item><title>Download Starry Night Pro Plus 8.1.1.2094</title><pubDate> Sat, 23 Aug 2025 17:52:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-starry-night-pro-plus-1953.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-starry-night-pro-plus-1953.html
</guid><description>
Starry Night Pro Plus 8 is astronomical software for those who love to explore the universe, the stars, the planet in the milky way, a way sharp. Application has been refitted inside and out to best meet the needs of amateur astronomers, modern! With a database of gorgeous new object, integrated with the cloud service, and tons of new smart features, Starry Night 8 sets you up for success more than ever! Discover a new object, updates, 36.000, be cross-reference database built from the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Power-user Premium 1.7.49.136</title><pubDate> Sat, 23 Aug 2025 17:52:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-power-user-premium-3149.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-power-user-premium-3149.html
</guid><description>
Power-user is a plugin for software, Microsoft Excel, PowerPoint and Word help you to provide more visual content so you can create the spreadsheet attractive. It contains templates, icons, tables, drawings and charts, modern, professional, allows you to build professional looking documents. You can add custom content to your project just by a click of the mouse and surprise clients and colleagues with your skills on Excel, PowerPoint and Word.
Power-user Premium - Plugin Excel,...
</description></item><item><title>Download HE - Hardware Read and Write Utility 1.25.08.23</title><pubDate> Sat, 23 Aug 2025 17:52:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-he-hardware-read-and-write-utility-4287.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-he-hardware-read-and-write-utility-4287.html
</guid><description>
HE - Hardware Read and Write Utility is a powerful utility intended for hardware engineer, engineer, BIOS developer, driver, engineer, QA engineers, performance test engineers, diagnostic, etc., this utility access almost all the computer hardware, including PCI (PCI Express), index / Data, PCI, memory, index memory / Data space I / O, Index I / O / Data, Super I / O, DIMM SPD, CPU The registers MSR, screen, SMART, physical area of the hard drive identification data, ATA, dump tables ACPI...
</description></item><item><title>Download Chaos Corona 13.1 for Cinema 4D R17 - 2025</title><pubDate> Sat, 23 Aug 2025 17:51:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-corona-renderer-for-cinema-4d-6499.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-corona-renderer-for-cinema-4d-6499.html
</guid><description>
Corona Renderer  is the name of a powerful, but highly functional engineering and dedicated plug-in for Autodesk 3ds Max software. Plug in before you are a known CLI standalone application. In addition, users can use this tool to advertise their business on Maxon Cinema 4D software which is also used. The manufacturers of this product firmly believe that working with this tool is very simple, and in fact you just need to hit render the rendering operations. With this tool it's easier...
</description></item><item><title>Download Geometric NestingWorks 2025 SP1 for SolidWorks 2024-2026</title><pubDate> Sat, 23 Aug 2025 17:50:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-geometric-nestingworks-1070.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-geometric-nestingworks-1070.html
</guid><description>
Geometric NestingWorks software promote technology, 3D true form NESTLib® top in the industry - is known by the application developer nested throughout the world is one of the library cage shape automatically the fastest and most full-featured existing in the industry. With NESTINGWorks, product designers can effectively optimize the layout sheetstock - including specifications for employing grain direction paper - so they can produce the maximum number of parts from a single piece of...
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 7.1.6</title><pubDate> Sat, 23 Aug 2025 17:49:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-11-7760.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-11-7760.html
</guid><description>
TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 is a program that allows users to discover hidden settings in Windows 11. This application is specially designed for Windows 11, groups many registry settings and distribute them from the easy and secure user interface. With TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 you can move the Windows taskbar to the top and resize the taskbar by editing the registry value. With any application that modifies the registry, we recommend that you have a backup copy...
</description></item><item><title>Download yt-dlp 2025.08.22</title><pubDate> Sat, 23 Aug 2025 17:49:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-dlp-6802.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-dlp-6802.html
</guid><description>
yt-dlp is a youtube-dl branch based on youtube-dlc currently not working. The main focus of this project is the addition of new features and patches while still updating the original project.
</description></item><item><title>Download Power-user for PowerPoint and Excel 1.7.49.136</title><pubDate> Sat, 23 Aug 2025 17:48:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-power-user-for-powerpoint-and-excel-522.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-power-user-for-powerpoint-and-excel-522.html
</guid><description>
Power-user for PowerPoint and Excel is a utility providing you with a library of templates, icons, charts, maps and diagrams for spreadsheet and presentation. With Power-user for PowerPoint and Excel, you will attract the attention of your audience with stunning graphics will certainly impress.
Power-user comes with a collection of 2,000 icons to illustrate your slides. The icons are vector shapes so you can resize them without distortion and color back as you with. With Power-user, you...
</description></item><item><title>Download QOwnNotes 25.8.6</title><pubDate> Sat, 23 Aug 2025 17:48:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qownnotes-3178.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qownnotes-3178.html
</guid><description>
QOwnNotes is notes bookmark file simple text (GPL) open source application for GNU / Linux , Mac OS X and Windows of Patrizio Bekerle ( pbek on GitHub and IRC) (optional) activity along with the notes application of ownCloud or Nextcloud. QOwnNote store your notes as plain text files and can be synchronized with synchronization function file of ownCloud / Nextcloud. You can also use other apps like Syncthing or Dropbox . Just write out your thoughts as they appear, and edit them if...
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 7.1.6</title><pubDate> Sat, 23 Aug 2025 17:47:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-10-7759.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-10-7759.html
</guid><description>
TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 is a utility that allows users to discover hidden settings in Windows 10. This application is specially designed for Windows 10, groups many registry settings and provide them from an easy and secure user interface. With TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 you can move the Windows taskbar to the top and resize the taskbar by editing the registry value. With any application that modifies the registry, we recommend that you have a backup copy to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Notepad3 6.25.822.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 23 Aug 2025 17:47:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-notepad3-2157.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-notepad3-2157.html
</guid><description>
Notepad3 is a program for editing text open source for Microsoft Windows, released under the software license BSD. Software is written by Florian Balmer using the editing component Scintilla, and is in wide release starting on march 4, 2004. Balmer construction Notepad2 according to Microsoft Notepad: small, fast, used to be.
Notepad3 - edit Text
Moreover, Notepad3 has the following features: folding code, coupling, frame, indentation, auto completion of words, convert character...
</description></item><item><title>Download CAMWorks 2025 SP3 for SolidWorks 2024-2025</title><pubDate> Sat, 23 Aug 2025 17:46:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-camworks-2110.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-camworks-2110.html
</guid><description>
GbometryPLM pleased to announce the availability of CAMWorks 2019 SP3.0, is a solution programming CAM modern automation creating the toolpath in SOLIDWORKS. Power supply for CAMIDWORKS ORANGE, now have a links seamless link for all the requirements and convenience of the user to SOLIDWORKS.
CAMWorks is the solution production computer assistance (CAM) fully integrated first to be designed exclusively for operation in SOLIDWORKS and is the first solution provider based on knowledge,...
</description></item></channel></rss>