<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 01:44:46 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 01:44:46 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Blender 4.5.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 21 Aug 2025 00:45:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blender-3017.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blender-3017.html
</guid><description>
Blender has a tool that new and very powerful, whose name is Ciking provides the ability to display extremely impressive and extremely realistic.
Features of Blender
	- Feature button support complete
	- The ball exactly on the physical side, SSS and translucency
	- Support languages open for coding the ball unique
Blender - The software-rendered optical
Tool output integration provides:
	- The GPU and CPU
	- Preview options view real-time
	- Support light HDR
	- The license...
</description></item><item><title>Download Polarr Photo Editor Pro 5.11.11</title><pubDate> Thu, 21 Aug 2025 00:44:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-polarr-photo-editor-pro-3761.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-polarr-photo-editor-pro-3761.html
</guid><description>
Polarr Photo Editor Pro offers advanced tools automatically advanced and sophisticated filters to edit all the details in your photo. The professional photographer will look forward to the support layer, curve tool, adjust locally, our and more. Polarr Photo Editor Pro provides everything you need and more with the easiest way to date that still gives you professional look that you are trying to achieve, all for free.
Polarr Photo Editor Pro - image editing tools advanced
The features...
</description></item><item><title>Download LibreOffice 25.8.0 / 7.6.7</title><pubDate> Thu, 21 Aug 2025 00:44:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-libreoffice-391.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-libreoffice-391.html
</guid><description>
LibreOffice is editor free for office similar to MS Office and OpenOffice includes word processor, spreadsheet application, presentation tool, database and design diagrams. Here is the app code open source, multi-feature, to offer users many tools to draft documents and handle the office documents efficiently.
The program can open or import most Microsoft Office formats popular, including .doc .ppt and .csv as well as many document formats other. LibreOffice is a tool to be more user...
</description></item><item><title>Download Free YouTube Download 4.4.37.820 Premium</title><pubDate> Thu, 21 Aug 2025 00:43:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-download-1177.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-download-1177.html
</guid><description>
Free YouTube Download Premium is the most popular application to download videos from YouTube. The program was released in 2006 and regularly updated since then. Use the program to download and convert YouTube videos to view offline anytime.
Free YouTube Download - added Support to download youtube
Download more videos! Save whole playlists and YouTube channels, videos from a playlist individually (history, video be favorite, favourites, Watch later), videos from many different...
</description></item><item><title>Download LibreWolf 142.0-1</title><pubDate> Thu, 21 Aug 2025 00:42:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-librewolf-11967.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-librewolf-11967.html
</guid><description>
LibreWolf is a customized and independent version of Firefox, with the main goals being user privacy, security and freedom. LibreWolf is designed to provide increased protection against tracking and fingerprinting techniques and includes a number of security enhancements. This is achieved through our security and privacy oriented settings and patches. LibreWolf also aims to remove all telemetry, data collection and annoyances, as well as disable anti-free features like DRM.
LibreWolf...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare Recoverit 13.6.0.14</title><pubDate> Thu, 21 Aug 2025 00:42:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-recoverits-374.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-recoverits-374.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare Recoverit is a data recovery software that is easily lost at a rapid rate and is used by many people. You will do what happens if one day your data is suddenly lost due to the virus or deleted it, .. Wondershare Recoverit will provide you with an environment to protect important data.
Wondershare Recoverit has all the scanning processes that are divided into multiple types, from the typical recovery of the deleted files that are deleted to the recovery of missing files due...
</description></item><item><title>Download AnyTrans for iOS 8.9.12.20250820</title><pubDate> Thu, 21 Aug 2025 00:41:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anytrans-for-ios-755.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anytrans-for-ios-755.html
</guid><description>
AnyTrans for iOS is content manager essential fully managed iPhone, Android and content of your cloud. Including all mobile devices, all cloud drives from your iPhone, iPad, iPod touch to phones and tablets. From local disk to cloud storage. AnyTrans has protected them all, providing you convenient management for all data and your files, regardless of whether they are stored where.
AnyTrans is the one stop solution to meet all the management needs of your data. For the first time, you can...
</description></item><item><title>Download System Utilities 1.3.5.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 21 Aug 2025 00:41:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-system-utilities-10394.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-system-utilities-10394.html
</guid><description>
System Utilities as its name suggests, contains a collection of tools that can help you maintain your system easily. It can scan your drive for storage, help you quickly uninstall programs, as well as manage startup applications and clean up unnecessary data.
Features of System Utilities
	Scan and organize all the folders on your PC to create more space.
	Uninstall all programs that you do not use. Get rid of data junk on your computer.
	Determine which programs should start...
</description></item><item><title>Download Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium 4.4.37.820</title><pubDate> Thu, 21 Aug 2025 00:39:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-to-mp3-converter-premium-844.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-to-mp3-converter-premium-844.html
</guid><description>
Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium version is a software used to convert YouTube to MP3, extract audio from playlists YouTube, show listings, charts, video responses, channels, favorites of the user. With Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium, you can download and convert playlists, channels, stream original tv series and get them into iTunes at the same time.
Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium - convert YouTube to MP3
Features Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium from the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare Repairit 6.5.13.6</title><pubDate> Thu, 21 Aug 2025 00:39:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-recoverit-video-repair-3889.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-recoverit-video-repair-3889.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare Recoverit Video Repair is a reliable application that helps you fix the broken video, Wondershare Recoverit Video Repair supports file formats MP4, MOV, M4V, M2TS, MKV, MTS, 3GP, AVI and FLV is corrupt and broken. Great service we provide. It fixes the video that there is corruption in the process of shooting, when done, file transfer, while editing, convert.
Wondershare Recoverit Video Repair - video repair broken
Features of Wondershare Recoverit Video Repair
	Repair...
</description></item><item><title>Download KMPlayer (KMP) 2025.7.28.15 x64 / 4.2.3.24 x86</title><pubDate> Thu, 21 Aug 2025 00:38:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kmplayer-kmp-902.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kmplayer-kmp-902.html
</guid><description>
KMPlayer (KMP) is software watch movies listen to music multi-function for video enthusiasts. KMPlayer development is many types of the format different. KMPlayer has improved on sound quality, images when listening to music and watching movies, the playback speed of video is faster, more codec player is added to the software video decoder is optimized.
KMPlayer also supports a variety of audio formats and video and offers a the interface can be customized with the preview coverflow and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Advanced Driver Updater 4.6.1086.7222</title><pubDate> Thu, 21 Aug 2025 00:36:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-driver-updater-1170.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-driver-updater-1170.html
</guid><description>
Advanced Driver Updater is software that automatically check, download and install the Driver for the fastest computer with the software always be updated with the latest. Advanced Driver Updater will help your system will always have the latest drivers and you will no longer have to make search for driver updates manually. Outdated drivers can slow your PC or even cause errors. Drivers for video cards are particularly prone to this. A program is clearly structured to provide access to...
</description></item><item><title>Download QILING Disk Master Professional 8.5</title><pubDate> Thu, 21 Aug 2025 00:36:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qiling-disk-master-professional-4826.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qiling-disk-master-professional-4826.html
</guid><description>
QILING Disk Master provides powerful tools recover lost data and restore the broken system in few minutes. There is software to restore data &amp;amp; backup systems, reliable and advanced system for desktop and laptops at homes and businesses. It allows the user to perform the operation backup service and backup the entire / difference / increase in comprehensive.
The features of QILING Disk Master
	Backup and system protection (image)
	Backup and restore files
	Compressed file...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mp3Tag 3.31a</title><pubDate> Thu, 21 Aug 2025 00:36:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mp3tag-150.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mp3tag-150.html
</guid><description>
Mp3tag is a powerful tool and easy to use to edit ID3 tags and OGG comments about the files MP3 - and Ogg Vorbis. It can rename files based on the tag information, replace characters or words from tags and filenames. Help users create and add the tag information for MP3 files to manage the information that is reasonable.
The program supports lookup database freedb online for the selected files, allowing you to automatically gather tag information appropriate for the files or CD selection....
</description></item><item><title>Download DroidKit 2.3.6.20250820</title><pubDate> Thu, 21 Aug 2025 00:35:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-droidkit-6578.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-droidkit-6578.html
</guid><description>
DroidKit is data recovery software for your mobile device, it will quickly scan your phone memory and save photos, WhatsApp chats and files, messages Messages, contacts and more essential data up to 13 categories, covering almost everything you need every day. All Android phones and tablets are supported. Without rooting your device. No tech skills required. No need to wait many days. You can get back what you've lost with just a few simple clicks, instantly.
Besides, DroidKit also has...
</description></item><item><title>Download GLview (OpenGL Extensions Viewer) 7.4.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 21 Aug 2025 00:35:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opengl-extension-viewer-3468.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opengl-extension-viewer-3468.html
</guid><description>
OpenGL Extensions Viewer is a reliable software that displays useful information about the accelerated OpenGL current 3D API and 3D Vulkan new. This program displays the vendor name, the version implemented, the name renderer and extension of the accelerated OpenGL 3D current.
OpenGL Extensions Viewer - Display detailed information graphics
This software utility analyzes the hardware and software of your PC and give you detailed information about the renderers such as DirectX version ,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Prevent Restore Pro 2025 v111</title><pubDate> Thu, 21 Aug 2025 00:33:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-prevent-restore-pro-1473.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-prevent-restore-pro-1473.html
</guid><description>
Prevent Restore Pro is software prevent restore files deleted in any drive: external hard drives and hard drives mounted in hard drive, SSD, Flash drives, except CD-ROM and CD-RW. The software uses many security algorithms can be used to get data.Our program includes some of the most reliable and accepted as standard.
Prevent Restore Pro - Prevent restore files deleted
The features of Prevent Restore Pro
Mode to clean up quickly
	In this mode, the program will not overwrite the free...
</description></item><item><title>Download GraphPad Prism 10.6.0.890</title><pubDate> Thu, 21 Aug 2025 00:32:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-graphpad-prism-3726.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-graphpad-prism-3726.html
</guid><description>
GraphPad Prism is one of the software products statistics released by a private company whose name is GraphPad. This software has the ability to draw all the chart types 3D and also be used to solve the statistical problems. In general, this software is designed to solve the problems of science and commerce. GraphPad Prism provides users the ability to solve statistical problems difficult and most difficult with the right speed.
GraphPad Prism - software statistics
Although GraphPad...
</description></item><item><title>Download QILING Disk Master Technician 8.5</title><pubDate> Thu, 21 Aug 2025 00:31:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qiling-disk-master-technician-4828.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qiling-disk-master-technician-4828.html
</guid><description>
QILING Disk Master Technician is the complete tool to simplify the management partition and move the OS and software backup &amp;amp; recovery for IT admins, technicians and consultants. With simple interface and easy to use, anyone, even users with no technical, can protect all business data important in the last few minutes to ensure business continuity without the need to have experts. In addition, It also support to check the health of the hard disk, edit questions startup permanently...
</description></item><item><title>Download Personal Backup 6.4.1.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 21 Aug 2025 00:31:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-personal-backup-1117.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-personal-backup-1117.html
</guid><description>
Personal Backup is software to backup data on computer hard drive professional with the ability to copy data on the hard drive and save any folder. Personal Backup is the most optimal solutions to ensure safety for data on avoid computer viruses, malicious code, intrusion and data loss because you can restore lost data at any time if it has to be backed up and stored on the folder of the computer.
Personal Backup - backup computer data
Features of Personal Backup
	Backup cross data...
</description></item><item><title>Download Aiseesoft FoneLab for Android 6.0.6</title><pubDate> Thu, 21 Aug 2025 00:31:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aiseesoft-fonelab-for-android-3929.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aiseesoft-fonelab-for-android-3929.html
</guid><description>
Aiseesoft FoneLab for Android is one of the software Android data recovery best. Aiseesoft FoneLab for Android is recovery software data great for Android users that helps you recover text messages, deleted messages, attached, lost, contacts lost, call history and Photos, Photo, Videos, Music, documents on Android phone, tablet and your SD card. Regardless of whether you lost files due to mistakenly deletion, root, upgrade, format the memory card, attack of virus or due to you crashing,...
</description></item><item><title>Download QILING Disk Master Server 8.5</title><pubDate> Thu, 21 Aug 2025 00:30:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qiling-disk-master-server-4827.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qiling-disk-master-server-4827.html
</guid><description>
QILING Disk Master Server support, backup, data recovery, along with many attractive features other. QILING Disk Master Server data recovery &amp;amp; backup system reliable and advanced system for desktop and laptops at homes and businesses. It allows the user to perform the operation backup service and backup the entire / difference / increase in comprehensive for your server.
QILING Disk Master Server support to fully recover, the content is not deformed in comparison with document,...
</description></item><item><title>Download XMPlay 4.0.0.19</title><pubDate> Thu, 21 Aug 2025 00:29:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xmplay-2666.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xmplay-2666.html
</guid><description>
XMPlay is an audio player software free for Windows. Originally released in 1998, it created the difference compared with the competitors by providing a special copy authentication of the audio file track. XMPlay is an audio player, supporting audio formats OGG / MP3 / MP2 / MP1 / WMA / AAC / MP4 / WAV / AIFF / CDA / MO3 / IT / XM / S3M / MTM / MOD / UMX, PLS / M3U / ASX / playlist WAX / CUE and ZIP archives. Download more audio file formats, and file storage is also supported via...
</description></item><item><title>Download Atlantis Word Processor 4.4.6.5</title><pubDate> Thu, 21 Aug 2025 00:28:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-atlantis-word-processor-585.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-atlantis-word-processor-585.html
</guid><description>
Atlantis Word Processor is a word processor app with features format, standard text, autocorrect, and spell check.  Atlantis is a word processor in accordance with most of the tasks handled daily text. The interface is very easy to use and offers the toolbars, hotkeys and sound effects thanh can customize (can turn off). It includes a clip library for quick access to the text or images used regular preview, font format and many other features aimed at improving the process of your...
</description></item><item><title>Download QuickSoundSwitcher 1.7.3</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 23:20:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quicksoundswitcher-14033.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quicksoundswitcher-14033.html
</guid><description>
QuickSoundSwitcher is a lightweight, open-source Windows utility designed to quickly and easily manage audio input and output devices. It allows users to switch between multiple audio devices (e.g. speakers, headphones, microphones) and control the volume directly from the system tray without navigating to complex Windows settings.
The program also provides an application volume mixer, allowing for volume adjustment and muting for individual programs. This tool is especially useful for...
</description></item></channel></rss>