<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 16:09:10 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 16:09:10 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Google Chrome 143.0.7499.193</title><pubDate> Thu, 08 Jan 2026 18:13:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-chrome-1012.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-chrome-1012.html
</guid><description>
Google Chrome web browser is the most used today. Support surf the web, listen to music, watch movies, play web game effective no jerky lag with the internet connection stable. When you are surfing the web or performing an important task, whether it is operation big or small, work or entertainment, then Chrome has the smart features and the speed you need to make, create and explore on the net.
The latest version of Google Chrome is the third 114. But we are providing for users Google...
</description></item><item><title>Download CPU-Z 2.18</title><pubDate> Thu, 08 Jan 2026 18:10:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cpu-z-2240.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cpu-z-2240.html
</guid><description>
A wonderful development has been updated, in a simple way, can display technical information about the computer, your personal nature it will operate in Windows operating systems from version 98 to latest version 7. After starting, you can see the specifications of different sets of processing center, you can find out full data on the video card and motherboard, I forgot to add about RAM, download CPU-Z from our project in full news.
CPU-Z - Check CPU hardware
After installing, launch...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDF-XChange Pro 10.8.2.407</title><pubDate> Thu, 08 Jan 2026 18:07:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-xchange-editor-pro-3422.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-xchange-editor-pro-3422.html
</guid><description>
PDF-XChange Editor Pro is an application to manipulate and create PDF versatile, offering a wide range of useful features and powerful will help you to easily work with PDF files. This application is very flexible and allows you to easily create and modify PDF files. PDF-XChange Editor Pro provides a powerful set of tools and flexibility to work with PDF files, such as editor PDF-XChange new, utilities series, OFFice2PDF and the Addin tool Bar allows you to easily convert multiple file...
</description></item><item><title>Download IObit Driver Booster Pro 13.2.0.184</title><pubDate> Thu, 08 Jan 2026 18:06:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iobit-driver-booster-102.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iobit-driver-booster-102.html
</guid><description>
IObit Driver Booster Pro is the starting step to avoid hardware errors, the loss of the system and hidden security vulneruses. To update the regular driver is also an effective way to enhance your overall computer performance and maximize your gaming experience. While this process can be dangerous and frustrating if done manually. IObit Driver Booster Pro is introduced to download and update the driver for you automatically with only one click. Based on the cloud library, IObit Driver...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDF-XChange Editor Plus 10.8.2.407</title><pubDate> Thu, 08 Jan 2026 18:06:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-xchange-editor-plus-645.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-xchange-editor-plus-645.html
</guid><description>
PDF-XChange Editor Plus is the editor, PDF viewer, compact, fast with many features, add-ons, professional. When using the PDF-XChange Editor Plus, easy for users to create, view, edit, annotate, OCR and digital signing PDF files, plus much more.
PDF-XChange Editor is a PDF editing full-featured. With the help of it, you can edit, fix, add, or delete text easily. Graphics can also be moved, resized or removed.
Features PDF-XChange Editor Plus
Edit documents
	Use a variety of editing...
</description></item><item><title>Download Media Player Classic Home Cinema 2.6.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 08 Jan 2026 18:05:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-media-player-classic-home-cinema-2839.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-media-player-classic-home-cinema-2839.html
</guid><description>
Media Player Classic Home Cinema is a multimedia compact for Microsoft Windows 32 bit and 64 bit. MPC mimics the interface of Windows Media Player 6.4, but provides most options and features available in the modern means. Media Player Classic Home Cinema for free 100% no advertising, so you can directly access content and enjoy media playback without being distracted.
With Media Player Classic Home, you can now change the design a multimedia of the custom toolbar. There is a range to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Aperty 1.5.0 (1438)</title><pubDate> Thu, 08 Jan 2026 18:04:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aperty-12574.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aperty-12574.html
</guid><description>
Aperty is a dedicated portrait editing software developed by Skylum, designed to simplify the editing process for professional photographers. It offers a wide range of features to enhance portrait photography while reducing post-processing time.
Why Aperty?
Aperty is a photo editing tool for professional portrait photographers who want to reduce post-processing time without sacrificing quality and client satisfaction.
Features of Aperty
	Automatic Editing: Optimize your editing...
</description></item><item><title>Download XYplorer (32 Bit) 27.20.0900</title><pubDate> Thu, 08 Jan 2026 18:04:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-portable-12066.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-portable-12066.html
</guid><description>
XYplorer Portable is a file management software application that provides a comprehensive set of features for organizing and managing files and folders on your computer. This is a portable version of XYplorer that you can run directly from a portable storage device, such as a USB drive, without installation.
XYplorer Portable Features
	File Management: XYplorer Portable provides a two-window interface, allowing you to view and work with two folders at the same time. It provides easy...
</description></item><item><title>Download XRECODE3 1.177</title><pubDate> Thu, 08 Jan 2026 18:03:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xrecode-iii-2915.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xrecode-iii-2915.html
</guid><description>
"Xrecode II" is the switch and grab the audio allows you to convert from mp2, mp3, ac3, aiff, wma, amr, ogg, ape, flac, cue, mpc, wv, tak, mid, cue, m4b, tta, wav, dts , wav (rf64), m4a, mp4, ra, shn, rm, avi, aac, mpg, vob, mka, mkv, flv, Mov, swf, ofr, divx, wmv, spx, mp3, m4v, 3gp, m2v, 3g2, m4v, m2ts, ts, adts, tak, xm, mod, it, s3m, alac, umx, mtm, mlp to m4a, ape, flac, mp4 (using NeroAAC), raw, ogg, wav, wav (rf64) , wma, mpc, WavPack, mp2, ofr, Speex, ac3, tak, aiff, snd, Shorten...
</description></item><item><title>Download NxFilter 4.7.4.3</title><pubDate> Thu, 08 Jan 2026 18:02:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nxfilter-50.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nxfilter-50.html
</guid><description>
NxFilter is a server filter DNS have the ability to filter Internet traffic based on domain names and content types. In addition, it can use check package DNS to protect your network from malware and botnet activity.
NxFilter is installed on a single computer, where it acts as a proxy server, DNS. To route Internet traffic through NxFilter, you will need to change the DNS settings on all the machines that you want to protect to use the IP address of the individual NxFilter (instead of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Amagicsoft Magic Data Recovery Technician 3.12.6.147</title><pubDate> Thu, 08 Jan 2026 18:01:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-amagicsoft-magic-data-recovery-technician-14112.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-amagicsoft-magic-data-recovery-technician-14112.html
</guid><description>
Amagicsoft Magic Data Recovery Technician is a data recovery software product from Amagicsoft designed to help users, even those who are not technically savvy, recover deleted, formatted or lost files from various devices and file systems. The software supports over 5,000 file types and offers dual scanning modes (Quick Scan and Advanced Scan), real-time preview of recoverable files, and is compatible with various storage media such as hard drives, memory cards, and USB flash...
</description></item><item><title>Download QILING Disk Master Professional 8.7</title><pubDate> Thu, 08 Jan 2026 18:01:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qiling-disk-master-professional-4826.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qiling-disk-master-professional-4826.html
</guid><description>
QILING Disk Master provides powerful tools recover lost data and restore the broken system in few minutes. There is software to restore data &amp;amp; backup systems, reliable and advanced system for desktop and laptops at homes and businesses. It allows the user to perform the operation backup service and backup the entire / difference / increase in comprehensive.
The features of QILING Disk Master
	Backup and system protection (image)
	Backup and restore files
	Compressed file...
</description></item><item><title>Download K-Lite Codec Pack Full 19.4.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 08 Jan 2026 18:01:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-115.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-115.html
</guid><description>
K Lite Codec Pack Full brings pc users an optimal solution for watching movies, listening to music, support most popular format today by using collection codec rich. This software also allows you to refine the quality of videos and music to enjoy, create a list of music and video to comfortable enjoy.
Prompt to software, listen to music, watch movies, currently, part, user will prompt to programs like VLC or KMP ... With VLC, it was too familiar with users, not just watch videos, listen...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wise Care 365 Pro 7.3.3.720 Beta</title><pubDate> Thu, 08 Jan 2026 18:01:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wise-care-365-pro-106.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wise-care-365-pro-106.html
</guid><description>
Wise Care 365 pro is a package of utilities registry, disk, and other systems important for your PC. Easy to use and effective, Wise Care 365 is the best solution to improve the performance of your computer. Get Wise Care 365 and your computer will never run slow again!
Wise Care 365 pro is what?
Wise Care 365 Pro
	Check PC a clicks
	Pc cleaning &amp;amp; speed up
	Inventory hardware
	Protecting your privacy
	Protect real-time system
	Silent mode
	Boot speed faster
	Freeing up disk...
</description></item><item><title>Download High-Logic FontCreator Professional 15.0.0.3042</title><pubDate> Thu, 08 Jan 2026 18:00:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-high-logic-fontcreator-professional-1533.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-high-logic-fontcreator-professional-1533.html
</guid><description>
High-Logic FontCreator Professional allows you to create and edit TrueType fonts and OpenType. It has the powerful drawing tools that typographers and graphic designers require, and an intuitive interface that allows beginners to become productive immediately.
When you create or open a font, FontCreator displays an overview of all available characters. You can only add the characters missing, or select an existing character, and modify its appearance. You can import (scanned) signature...
</description></item><item><title>Download K-Lite Codec Pack Mega 19.4.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 08 Jan 2026 17:59:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-mega-3202.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-mega-3202.html
</guid><description>
K-Lite Mega Codec Pack is a collection of components needed for audio playback and the video in the player DirectShow like Windows Media Player, Media Center, and Media Player Classic. This is the latest beta version, Pack Codec K-Lite latest stable. The Mega variant is the biggest of the four variants of the codec pack. It provides everything you need to play all audio and video files. In addition, it also contains some codecs ACM / VFW can be used by the application coding / video...
</description></item><item><title>Download QILING Disk Master Technician WinPE 8.7</title><pubDate> Thu, 08 Jan 2026 17:58:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qiling-disk-master-technician-winpe-4831.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qiling-disk-master-technician-winpe-4831.html
</guid><description>
QILING Disk Master Technician WinPE is programs backup and restore data on WinPE for programmers and administrators, QILING Disk Master Technician WinPE meet all the needs to recover data your lost and restore the broken system in few minutes. There is software to restore data &amp;amp; backup systems, reliable and advanced system for desktop and laptops at homes and businesses. It allows the user to perform the operation backup service and backup the entire / difference / increase in...
</description></item><item><title>Download Universal USB Installer 2.0.3.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 08 Jan 2026 17:58:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-universal-usb-installer-3140.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-universal-usb-installer-3140.html
</guid><description>
Universal USB Installer is a software to create a USB Linux that will give you the ability to choose from a large selection of Linux distributions to create bootable USB Flash Drives. the software is intuitive and easy to use, allowing you to simply choose a distribution Live Linux, your flash drive and the ISO file and make USB drive bootable with just a single mouse click. When the task finishes, you will get USB Flash Drive ready to accommodate Linux distributions have chosen. This...
</description></item><item><title>Download TrayStatus Pro 5.1.3</title><pubDate> Thu, 08 Jan 2026 17:57:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-traystatus-pro-1597.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-traystatus-pro-1597.html
</guid><description>
TrayStatus Pro is professional software to help display the status of the keys Caps Lock, Num Lock, Scroll Lock, Kana, Alt, Ctrl, Shift in the system tray. In addition, the software TrayStatus this Pro also displays CPU, memory or operation of the hard drive or use performance counters to track things like the queue length, disk, network activity, requires IIS and more.
TrayStatus Pro - Show keyboard status and parameters of the computer
The features and functions TrayStatus...
</description></item><item><title>Download QILING Disk Master Technician 8.7</title><pubDate> Thu, 08 Jan 2026 17:56:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qiling-disk-master-technician-4828.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qiling-disk-master-technician-4828.html
</guid><description>
QILING Disk Master Technician is the complete tool to simplify the management partition and move the OS and software backup &amp;amp; recovery for IT admins, technicians and consultants. With simple interface and easy to use, anyone, even users with no technical, can protect all business data important in the last few minutes to ensure business continuity without the need to have experts. In addition, It also support to check the health of the hard disk, edit questions startup permanently...
</description></item><item><title>Download QILING Disk Master Server 8.7</title><pubDate> Thu, 08 Jan 2026 17:56:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qiling-disk-master-server-4827.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qiling-disk-master-server-4827.html
</guid><description>
QILING Disk Master Server support, backup, data recovery, along with many attractive features other. QILING Disk Master Server data recovery &amp;amp; backup system reliable and advanced system for desktop and laptops at homes and businesses. It allows the user to perform the operation backup service and backup the entire / difference / increase in comprehensive for your server.
QILING Disk Master Server support to fully recover, the content is not deformed in comparison with document,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Stardock Start11 2.6.0.1 Beta</title><pubDate> Thu, 08 Jan 2026 17:56:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stardock-start11-7029.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stardock-start11-7029.html
</guid><description>
Start11 is an application capable of customizing the Start Menu and Taskbar on Windows 11 and Windows 10. This is an application that allows users to customize Windows 11 to suit their preferences. his personal. Start11 will help you bring the new Start Menu of Windows 11 to Windows 10. And vice versa, Start11 also helps you to bring the Start Menu of Windows 10 to Windows 11.
Start11 also helps users bring some functions of Windows 10 to Windows 11 through customizing the Taskbar such...
</description></item><item><title>Download DirPrintOK 7.51</title><pubDate> Thu, 08 Jan 2026 17:21:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dirprintok-2073.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dirprintok-2073.html
</guid><description>
DirPrintOK allows you to print and save the contents of the folder and / or entire folder structures. You can browse the directory with Explorer-like interface and arbitrary filter folder contents by file extensions or matching the wildcard. You can also right-click to exclude files or folders selected from the printed version.
&amp;nbsp;
Folder contents can be grouped by path, date, size or file extension and you can customize the data columns to be included in the printed book. Very easy...
</description></item><item><title>Download Brave Browser 1.85.120</title><pubDate> Thu, 08 Jan 2026 17:21:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-brave-browser-2874.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-brave-browser-2874.html
</guid><description>
Brave Browser is a browser based on Chromium, the basic principle is that operation fast and privacy of users. The program can block pop-up windows and other ads, plus it blocked the mechanism for monitoring the online activities of your. Therefore, you can purchase and safely browse the website you are interested in without having to worry about the fact that your activity will be monitored and then you will be shown the necessary advertising or service provider of parties...
</description></item><item><title>Download Double Commander 1.1.32</title><pubDate> Thu, 08 Jan 2026 17:15:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-double-commander-7801.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-double-commander-7801.html
</guid><description>
Double Commander is an open source file manager with two panels side by side. The idea is based on Total Commander but with new and different features. Double Commander has multi-rename tool, tabbed interface, custom columns, internal text editor, built-in file viewer, archive support (ZIP, RAR), extensive search functionality, configurable button bar, file activity logging, plug-in support and more.
Features of Double Commander
	Internal text editor (F4) with syntax...
</description></item></channel></rss>