<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 23:42:49 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 23:42:49 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download CalendarTask (formerly DesktopCal) 3.26.262.8332</title><pubDate> Sat, 03 Jan 2026 00:05:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopcal-1831.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopcal-1831.html
</guid><description>
CalendarTask (formerly DesktopCal) is a simple desktop calendar that blends into your desktop without blocking access to your desktop icons. You can double-click on a date to quickly add notes and also jump to specific dates in the past or future.
CalendarTask - Computer calendar
CalendarTask can use your current wallpaper or loop through images from your folder and update your desktop every few minutes. The program helps you make appointments, make plans... Not only that, the Screen...
</description></item><item><title>Download ImageGlass 9.4.1.15</title><pubDate> Sat, 03 Jan 2026 00:04:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-imageglass-4396.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-imageglass-4396.html
</guid><description>
ImageGlass is a software free image viewer open source. With a beautiful interface, simple and works in a gentle way is the advantages first thing that users notice in ImageGlass. Software ImageGlass is also a tool that helps users to view photos with support for many popular formats, including animations GIF, image transparent PNG. Imageglass allows users to view photos in zoom mode and zoom very flexible and easy. With this utility, you can browse the photo series with the same Zoom...
</description></item><item><title>Download HFS: HTTP File Server (version 3) 3.0.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 03 Jan 2026 00:03:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hfs-http-file-server-11851.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hfs-http-file-server-11851.html
</guid><description>
HFS is a web file server to run on your computer. Share a folder or even a file thanks to the virtual file system. Essentially, this application turns your computer into an HTTP server and all users who want to connect and download files can do so by loading a simple website in their browser. HFS includes many configuration settings, so you can basically change each part of the application, starting with how users download files and ending with the appearance of the created website.
HFS...
</description></item><item><title>Download KiCad 9.0.7</title><pubDate> Sat, 03 Jan 2026 00:03:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kicad-10384.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kicad-10384.html
</guid><description>
KiCad is a unique software product that allows you to open, create and develop electronic circuits for subsequent visualization of printed circuit board designs in interactive views . It allows you to develop complex circuit diagrams using an electronic components database and test signal integrity. It includes free applications, facilities, templates, and open libraries.
Using KiCad, users will be able to create truly professional printed circuit board layouts, beautifully designed...
</description></item><item><title>Download ArmorTools Professional / Home 26.0.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 02 Jan 2026 23:46:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-armortools-7726.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-armortools-7726.html
</guid><description>
ArmorTools is a set of tools that extend the capabilities of the MS Windows operating system in the field of security and protection of user confidential information. ArmorTools allows you to create secure virtual disks encrypted with AES128/AES256 algorithms, encrypting files and folder contents using any file as a password.
ArmorTools erases the user's work traces on the computer, deletes the history of accessing websites, deletes confidential information without the possibility of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Advanced SystemCare Pro Portable 19.1.0.176</title><pubDate> Fri, 02 Jan 2026 23:46:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-systemcare-pro-portable-8964.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-systemcare-pro-portable-8964.html
</guid><description>
Advanced SystemCare Pro Portable (a portable version) is system optimization and maintenance software developed by IObit. It is designed to help users improve the performance and speed of their Windows computers by cleaning junk files, optimizing system settings, and fixing various system errors.
It specializes in ONE-Click solutions to detect, clean, repair, speed up and ultimately protect PC. With new system technology, Advanced SystemCare Pro lets you run your computer faster....
</description></item><item><title>Download O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro 22.1.231 / Server</title><pubDate> Fri, 02 Jan 2026 23:45:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-diskimage-pro-218.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-diskimage-pro-218.html
</guid><description>
O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro is software backup data comprehensive and effective is provided to protect the data of the computer system, it creates images for individual drives or the entire system that still does not affect your system.
O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro allows the user to backup the entire computer or drive, the and files whenever you want even while the computer is being used. Or can use O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro to create a copy chinh sac of computer disk drives, can be used instead of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download ButterScroll 1.3.4</title><pubDate> Fri, 02 Jan 2026 23:45:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-butterscroll-13824.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-butterscroll-13824.html
</guid><description>
Smooth scrolling on Windows just got better. Smooth scrolling for Windows is what ButterScroll is all about. It improves the way your mouse scrolls using customizable speed and ease settings.
Smooth scrolling for all types of mice.
ButterScroll improves your everyday scrolling experience with smooth scrolling precision, customizable controls, and a satisfying feel across all your Windows apps — from browsers to spreadsheets.
ButterScroll Features
	Easy to set up and use
	Smooth,...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinToUSB Enterprise Portable 10.4</title><pubDate> Fri, 02 Jan 2026 23:44:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wintousb-portable-11910.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wintousb-portable-11910.html
</guid><description>
WinToUSB Portable (Windows To USB) is a handy tool that allows you to install and run a fully functional Windows operating system on an external hard drive, USB flash drive or Thunderbolt drive. It has a user-friendly interface that makes it easy for users to install and run Windows on a USB drive. It is suitable for both beginners and advanced users.
It's easy and effective, in just 3 steps and a few minutes you can create your first Windows 11/10/8/7 or portable Windows Server...
</description></item><item><title>Download FTPGetter Professional 5.97.0.297</title><pubDate> Fri, 02 Jan 2026 23:44:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ftpgetter-professional-1550.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ftpgetter-professional-1550.html
</guid><description>
FTPGetter Professional is software that automates the uploading and downloading of files, allowing scheduling file transfer between your computer with the FTP server and SFTP remote. If you often access FTP / SFTP to sync files between local computer and remote PC, to update your website or upload images, webcam, FTPGetter will save you lots of time and effort.
FTPGetter Professional comes with emulator terminal integration, allowing you to connect and execute commands on remote server...
</description></item><item><title>Download VovSoft Collect URL 4.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 02 Jan 2026 23:43:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-collect-url-7395.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-collect-url-7395.html
</guid><description>
VovSoft Collect URL is an internet scanner like a search engine bot. Starting from the URL the user entered, it lists all the links on the URL. Then it recursively scans all the links in the list. Users can limit URL Crawl to only one domain name. The file extension ignore list can be edited. Connection and response timeout values ​​are editable. Additionally, the user can change the user agent value for HTTP and HTTPS connections.
Features of VovSoft Collect URL
	Scan the...
</description></item><item><title>Download foobar2000 2.25.5</title><pubDate> Fri, 02 Jan 2026 23:43:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-foobar2000-1812.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-foobar2000-1812.html
</guid><description>
foobar2000 is the media player for media formats MP3, WAV, OGG and other formats multimedia other. It has no bells and whistles, however, under the hood, the program offers quite many features, including format, title and layout of the interface can be customized, convert WAV, Equalizer, Resampler, note cards, MP3, playlists, music album, CD, drag / drop and more. It also includes all the standard features like shuffle, random play, etc.
foobar2000 - The media player
foobar2000 running...
</description></item><item><title>Download Glary Utilities Pro Portable 6.36.0.40</title><pubDate> Fri, 02 Jan 2026 23:42:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-utilities-pro-portable-3500.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-utilities-pro-portable-3500.html
</guid><description>
Glary Utilities Pro Portable is a program that provides you with the necessary options to clean and maintain your PC system. The software's interface consists of a small window, simple to use. Newbies shouldn't have any problems getting around the program. So you can scan for problems revolving around incorrect registry entries, dangerous startup entries, invalid shortcuts, Internet history and traces, temporary files, spyware and adware.
Glary Utilities Pro Portable - Optimize and...
</description></item><item><title>Download DeskSoft EarthView 7.14.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 02 Jan 2026 23:42:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desksoft-earthview-184.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desksoft-earthview-184.html
</guid><description>
With software DeskSoft EarthView you can easily create wallpapers to your computer or select screen saver of your favorite. the program can change day and night, the clouds will also change according to weather conditions current on one or another part of the earth, you can see the lights of the city.
Features of DeskSoft EarthView can be interesting, because of DeskSoft EarthView support for day and night, you can view atmospheric phenomena, light city can see, the cloud is displayed,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Reg Organizer 9.90 Beta 1</title><pubDate> Fri, 02 Jan 2026 23:41:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reg-organizer-1595.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reg-organizer-1595.html
</guid><description>
Reg Organizer is a software to scan and clean your registry windows register errors and help optimize performance computer system. Reg Organizer is a software subscription, professional, and professional, and any way that the Windows registry are necessary and therefore, the overall performance of Windows improves, there is this software.
Reg Organizer - registry Cleaning and pc optimization
The main features of Reg Organizer
	Cleaning the registry of the lock is not valid and not...
</description></item><item><title>Download gSyncit 5.8.42</title><pubDate> Fri, 02 Jan 2026 23:41:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gsyncit-2290.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gsyncit-2290.html
</guid><description>
gSyncit allows syncing calendar, contacts, notes and tasks of Outlook with the Google account, Toodledo, Todoist, Pocket Informant Online, Evernote, Simplenote, Nozbe of you. It also supports syncing Calendar and contacts with iCloud, AOL, Yahoo! many other services that support CardDAV and CalDav access.
gSyncit - application support for Microsoft Outlook
gSyncit is a program, a add-ons powerful for Outlook email application, it easily integrates with the Microsoft's solution to work...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Downloader 10.1.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 02 Jan 2026 23:40:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html
</guid><description>
YTD Youtube Downloader is an application that reliable and intuitive, allowing you to quickly download YouTube videos and save them to your computer. You can also convert the media files to the format desired video or extract audio streams and save separately. YTD Youtube Downloader lets you save your favorite clips of yourself from Youtube, Facebook, Vimeo and Dailymotion to your desktop. The software supports URLS from many web site hosting, multimedia and allows you to download desired...
</description></item><item><title>Download XtraTools Pro 26.0.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 02 Jan 2026 23:34:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xtratools-pro-7168.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xtratools-pro-7168.html
</guid><description>
XtraTools Pro is a universal tool for MS Windows system optimization that takes care of all aspects of your computer like optimizing the registry and removing unnecessary program to establish network connection and increase RAM speed. It is a compact tool with an intuitive interface that gives you complete control over the boot process, memory monitoring and a huge set of system settings that control your computer. The current version of the software provides the following tools: Folder...
</description></item><item><title>Download EarthTime 6.31.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 02 Jan 2026 23:34:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-earthtime-185.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-earthtime-185.html
</guid><description>
EarthTime is software that displays the time and date local time of any place in the world. This application has database integration good for 3000 city, users can manually add, download at EarthTime if you want to. EarthTime allows you to install for the time zone and current local time.EarthTime displays the Earth according to the view night and day, you can view the map in full screen mode.
EarthTime
The feature on EarthTime
	EarthTime allows users to interact with visualization...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT-DL 12.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 02 Jan 2026 23:33:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-dl-5876.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-dl-5876.html
</guid><description>
YT-DL is a small program to download videos from YouTube and other video sites. Our goal is to make the program as simple as its name.
The features of YT-DL
	Download the video from YouTube and other video sites
	Increase download speed up to 400%
	Download multiple videos at the same time
	Pause and continue to download at any time
	Preview video content while downloading
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Geek YTDL Pro 12.1.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 02 Jan 2026 23:33:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-geek-ytdl-pro-9895.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-geek-ytdl-pro-9895.html
</guid><description>
YT Geek YTDL Pro is software that helps users easily download videos from YouTube and hundreds of other video sites. It is very easy to use, just paste the video URL and you can download the video while keeping the original quality. Not only videos on Youtube, users can download any video from social networking sites like Facebook, Vimeo, Myspace video,...
Features of YT Geek YTDL Pro
	Download videos from YouTube and other video sites.
	Increase download speed up to 400%.
	Download...
</description></item><item><title>Download HoRNet Corrosion 1.1.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 02 Jan 2026 23:33:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hornet-corrosion-13061.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hornet-corrosion-13061.html
</guid><description>
HoRNet Corrosion is an audio effects plugin designed primarily as a ring modulator, adding roughness, distortion and creative modulation to the sound. It works by modulating the input audio signal with a synthetic waveform (white noise, sine, sawtooth, square) or an external audio source, creating a cross modulation distortion that enriches and distorts the original sound. This makes it suitable for adding character to bass, synth sounds, drum loops, etc.
Key features include:
	Ring...
</description></item><item><title>Download FileViewPro Gold Edition 1.9.8.23</title><pubDate> Fri, 02 Jan 2026 20:38:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fileviewpro-gold-edition-14431.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fileviewpro-gold-edition-14431.html
</guid><description>
FileViewPro is an easy-to-use solution that allows you to open hundreds of different file types with just ONE program. Open any document, watch any video, listen to any song, view any photo, or open any other file type you want.
FileViewPro Program Features
	Watch any video, any format such as .avi, .flv, .3gp and many more formats
	Listen to any audio file such as .m4a, .flac, .wmv and many other formats
	View your photos and images in .jpg, .bmp, .tif and many other formats
	Simply...
</description></item><item><title>Download BitRecover PDF Merge Wizard 4.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 02 Jan 2026 20:31:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bitrecover-pdf-merge-wizard-14430.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bitrecover-pdf-merge-wizard-14430.html
</guid><description>
If you frequently work with PDF documents, you might consider using specialized tools for certain related tasks, such as editing files or managing them more easily. BitRecover PDF Merge Wizard is one of the applications mentioned above that can help you combine multiple PDF files from your computer into a single PDF file with little effort.
The PDF merging software has a built-in feature to combine multiple password-protected PDF files without any problems. This service will first...
</description></item><item><title>Download Free Download Manager 6.32.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 02 Jan 2026 16:54:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-download-manager-3105.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-download-manager-3105.html
</guid><description>
Free Download Manager is free application download manager, Free Download Manager will significantly increase downloads by splitting the files into several smaller parts and then downloads at the same time. Speed your download will be significantly increased. Manager download free can also continue to download at broken or not responding, so you don't need start downloading from the beginning after occasionally interrupted.
Free Download Manager - Manage and speed up downloads
You can...
</description></item></channel></rss>