<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 18:00:53 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 18:00:53 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download VirtualBox 7.2.6.172322</title><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jan 2026 16:09:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-virtualbox-285.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-virtualbox-285.html
</guid><description>
VirtualBox is a virtualization software open source allows you to run one or more operating system in a virtual machine while running Windows. It is used for purposes such as experience app or try to play the game new in a safe environment, do not affect the main operating system of you. With this software, users will better control multiple virtual machines at the same time.
VirtualBox - Create virtual drive allows running multiple operating systems at the same time
The program comes...
</description></item><item><title>Download Office Timeline Plus 13.22.00.00 Expert / Pro / Pro+ Edition</title><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jan 2026 16:08:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-timeline-2106.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-timeline-2106.html
</guid><description>
Office Timeline is an add-on very useful and powerful software for Microsoft PowerPoint. With add-ons, you can create PowerPoint documents look more beautiful. With add-ons, you can add the time Line on the project by yourself. Application time for the composition and different segments of the document, your PowerPoint will not only increase the beauty for your work, but also for customers and your manager. The people who created this product is also believe that add-ons this is the only...
</description></item><item><title>Download Active UNERASER Ultimate 26.0.6</title><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jan 2026 16:07:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-active-uneraser-ultimate-2635.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-active-uneraser-ultimate-2635.html
</guid><description>
Active UNERASER Ultimate is a powerful program and effectively allow you to recover files, folder and partition accidentally deleted. You can install it and work from the boot disk. Active UNERASER Ultimate works with the file system such as NTFS, FAT, HFS +, Unix UFS, etc. the interface is quite convenience, minimal installation, it easily works in general, I hope the program will be useful.
Active UNERASER Ultimate - Restore permissions for specific and partition the drive
The basic...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mozilla Thunderbird 147.0.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jan 2026 16:01:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thunderbird-1788.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thunderbird-1788.html
</guid><description>
Thunderbird is an email program full featured with controls spam integration, mail filter, address book, news groups and more. It provides a clean interface and easy to use (customizable). Thunderbird also provides the security features such as S / MIME, digital signing, message encryption, support for certificates and security devices.
Before using this feature, you should review the settings IMAP, SMTP, and SSL/TLS his. Now, what all you need to do is provide your name, email address,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Perfectly Clear WorkBench 5.0.1.3063</title><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jan 2026 16:00:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfectly-clear-workbench-6892.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfectly-clear-workbench-6892.html
</guid><description>
Perfectly Clear Workbench is an application that uses image editing libraries Perfectly Clear by Athentech and is provided to demonstrate the capabilities of the Perfectly Clear processing libraries, which recognize faces and allow quick export of processing settings for use.
One of the key features in Workbench is the ability to "export to API" when saving a Preset. This allows you to make image edits in Workbench and adjust the settings to suit your editing style and needs. You can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Directory List and Print Pro 4.40</title><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jan 2026 16:00:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-list-and-print-pro-481.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-list-and-print-pro-481.html
</guid><description>
Directory List and Print Pro is software that provides function lists and support printing content, quick, simple. In addition, the file list can be formatted, filtered, saved to several file formats and also further processed (delete / copy / move files). By copying to the clipboard the list can be exported into other programs or opened directly in Word and Excel.
The features Directory List and Print basic
	Choose the folders listed in a tree structure.
	Select the folder by...
</description></item><item><title>Download reaConverter Pro 8.0.188</title><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jan 2026 15:59:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html
</guid><description>
reaConverter Pro is software image processing feature with batch conversion and image editing periodically becomes simple. eaConverter also provide command line utilities allow you to process images automatically, thus helping you shorten the time for other work.
reaConverter Pro integrated powerful tool of Uber with many great features. It provides advanced solutions to process and adjust images. Management of the conversion process the base image with the latest version of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Free YouTube Download 4.5.2.117 Premium</title><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jan 2026 15:54:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-download-1177.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-download-1177.html
</guid><description>
Free YouTube Download Premium is the most popular application to download videos from YouTube. The program was released in 2006 and regularly updated since then. Use the program to download and convert YouTube videos to view offline anytime.
Free YouTube Download - added Support to download youtube
Download more videos! Save whole playlists and YouTube channels, videos from a playlist individually (history, video be favorite, favourites, Watch later), videos from many different...
</description></item><item><title>Download Atlantis Word Processor 5.0.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jan 2026 15:54:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-atlantis-word-processor-585.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-atlantis-word-processor-585.html
</guid><description>
Atlantis Word Processor is a word processor app with features format, standard text, autocorrect, and spell check.  Atlantis is a word processor in accordance with most of the tasks handled daily text. The interface is very easy to use and offers the toolbars, hotkeys and sound effects thanh can customize (can turn off). It includes a clip library for quick access to the text or images used regular preview, font format and many other features aimed at improving the process of your...
</description></item><item><title>Download Stardock Start11 2.6.0.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jan 2026 15:48:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stardock-start11-7029.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stardock-start11-7029.html
</guid><description>
Start11 is an application capable of customizing the Start Menu and Taskbar on Windows 11 and Windows 10. This is an application that allows users to customize Windows 11 to suit their preferences. his personal. Start11 will help you bring the new Start Menu of Windows 11 to Windows 10. And vice versa, Start11 also helps you to bring the Start Menu of Windows 10 to Windows 11.
Start11 also helps users bring some functions of Windows 10 to Windows 11 through customizing the Taskbar such...
</description></item><item><title>Download Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium 4.5.2.117</title><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jan 2026 15:48:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-to-mp3-converter-premium-844.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-to-mp3-converter-premium-844.html
</guid><description>
Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium version is a software used to convert YouTube to MP3, extract audio from playlists YouTube, show listings, charts, video responses, channels, favorites of the user. With Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium, you can download and convert playlists, channels, stream original tv series and get them into iTunes at the same time.
Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium - convert YouTube to MP3
Features Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium from the...
</description></item><item><title>Download ExamDiff Pro Master Edition 16.0.1.21</title><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jan 2026 15:47:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-examdiff-pro-master-312.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-examdiff-pro-master-312.html
</guid><description>
ExamDiff Pro Master is a tool to compare files and folders intuitive and easy to use, intuitive and easy to use for Windows. ExamDiff Pro Master has unique features distinguishes ExamDiff Pro with the program compare other. ExamDiff Pro Master to help perform reviews of code and share other reports with your colleagues and compare local website with FTP server by plug-ins more integrated.
ExamDiff Pro Master can create a snapshot folder for comparison and storage in the future, compare...
</description></item><item><title>Download O&amp;amp;O Defrag Server 30.5.1215</title><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jan 2026 15:46:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-defrag-server-2521.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-defrag-server-2521.html
</guid><description>
O&amp;amp;O Defrag Server professional software has the ability to defragment the hard disk and can work with the file system different from FAT / 32 to NTFS / 5, and support for the different arrays Volume / Stripe Sets. You can also set the schedule which O &amp;amp; O Defrag will be booted and perform a number of manipulation certain. Regular defragmentation of the disk partition optimized performance of your computer. The user interface is very easy to use. It has a ribbon bar displays all the...
</description></item><item><title>Download O&amp;amp;O Defrag Pro 30.5.1215</title><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jan 2026 15:46:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-o-o-defrag-pro-149.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-o-o-defrag-pro-149.html
</guid><description>
O&amp;amp;O Defrag Pro is the professional software has the ability to defragment the hard disk and can work with the file system different from FAT / 32 to NTFS / 5, and support for the different arrays Volume / Stripe Sets. You can also set the schedule which O &amp;amp; O Defrag will be booted and perform a number of manipulation certain. Regular defragmentation of the disk partition optimized performance of your computer. The user interface is very easy to use. It has a ribbon bar displays all...
</description></item><item><title>Download eDocPrinter PDF Pro 10.64 Build 10648</title><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jan 2026 15:46:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-edocprinter-pdf-pro-3915.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-edocprinter-pdf-pro-3915.html
</guid><description>
eDocPrinter PDF Pro is an application to create PDF files from applications in Windows 2000, Windows XP and above. eDocPrinter PDF Pro works as a printer under windows environment, hence users can print from any application window using the device printing GDI. Extremely easy to work with this tool, because it installs on your system as a virtual printer and lets you convert documents to PDF in an easy way. eDocPrinter PDF Pro comes with advanced functions that can meet the requirements of...
</description></item><item><title>Download OkMap Desktop 19.3.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jan 2026 15:45:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-okmap-desktop-581.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-okmap-desktop-581.html
</guid><description>
OkMap Desktop is interactive software working on the computer with web maps or digital maps bought or scanned. OkMap can also import a data vector from the most common formats and data DEM related to information height.
Through the map you can organize your path by creating waypoints , routesand tracks on the screen your computer, and upload this data to your GPS . OkMap set data high speedautomatic and estimated moving time . Furthermore OkMap provides you also have autorouting and...
</description></item><item><title>Download PCSX2 2.6.3</title><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jan 2026 15:45:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pcsx2-4470.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pcsx2-4470.html
</guid><description>
PCSX2 is a software application copy your Playstation 2, allowing you to play the game on your computer. As a gaming machine, virtual PCSX2 can overcome the hardware limitations to bring you these important advantages such as the ability to use the memory card is not limited to save games, screen resolution, custom, game cheats, save game is loading at any time during your game - play, the ability to tom to use any controller compatible Windows operating system and HD recordings of your...
</description></item><item><title>Download XRECODE3 1.178</title><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jan 2026 15:44:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xrecode-iii-2915.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xrecode-iii-2915.html
</guid><description>
"Xrecode II" is the switch and grab the audio allows you to convert from mp2, mp3, ac3, aiff, wma, amr, ogg, ape, flac, cue, mpc, wv, tak, mid, cue, m4b, tta, wav, dts , wav (rf64), m4a, mp4, ra, shn, rm, avi, aac, mpg, vob, mka, mkv, flv, Mov, swf, ofr, divx, wmv, spx, mp3, m4v, 3gp, m2v, 3g2, m4v, m2ts, ts, adts, tak, xm, mod, it, s3m, alac, umx, mtm, mlp to m4a, ape, flac, mp4 (using NeroAAC), raw, ogg, wav, wav (rf64) , wma, mpc, WavPack, mp2, ofr, Speex, ac3, tak, aiff, snd, Shorten...
</description></item><item><title>Download ASCOMP Easy Slideshow Professional 2.100</title><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jan 2026 15:38:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ascomp-easy-slideshow-professional-13811.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ascomp-easy-slideshow-professional-13811.html
</guid><description>
ASCOMP Easy Slideshow Professional is a user-friendly Windows software designed to quickly create stunning slideshow videos from your photos. Ideal for both beginners and professionals, the software offers an intuitive drag-and-drop interface for arranging images, setting display durations, and adding individual subtitles or captions for personalization.
Key features include:
	Over 200 built-in transition effects such as soft fades, dynamic zooms, and creative animations for changing...
</description></item><item><title>Download Google Drive (Backup and Sync) 120.0.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jan 2026 15:30:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-drive-6751.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-drive-6751.html
</guid><description>
Using Google Drive is a great way to store your files safely in secure data centers, where your files will not be lost. Even if your computer, phone or tablet is broken, the files you store in the Google Drive are safe. Download photos, videos, documents, and other files that are important to you up to Google Drive. Continue with the memory up to 15GB. Free. Google Drive helps you access your file faster by recognizing the objects in your image and text in the scanned documents.
Easy to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft Activation Scripts 3.10</title><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jan 2026 15:17:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-activation-scripts-5390.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-activation-scripts-5390.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft Activation Scripts is an open source Windows and Office activation tool that features online HWID, Ohook, KMS38 and KMS activation methods, along with advanced troubleshooting functionality.
Activation methods
			Trigger type
			Supported products
			Activation time
			HWID
			Windows 10-11
			Permanent
			Ohook
			Office
			Permanent
			KMS38
			Windows 10-11, Server
			Until 2038
			Online KMS
			Windows / Office
			180 days (with...
</description></item><item><title>Download NX Auto Clicker 2.2.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jan 2026 13:05:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nx-auto-clicker-14546.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nx-auto-clicker-14546.html
</guid><description>
NX Auto Clicker is an all-in-one solution for gamers and professional users who need speed, accuracy, and reliability. Whether you need ultra-fast auto-clicker software for your favorite sandbox games, or a smart keyboard macro for repetitive office tasks, NX delivers professional performance in a modern, clean interface.
Why choose NX Auto Clicker?
Unlike basic clicker software, NX combines Mouse Automation and Keyboard Macros into a single, lightweight application. It has a...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinOptimizer Std 6.7.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jan 2026 12:58:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winoptimizer-std-14545.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winoptimizer-std-14545.html
</guid><description>
WinOptimizer Std is a comprehensive suite of utilities designed to help you optimize every aspect of your computer's operating system and web browser, especially for Windows 10 and 11.
The software includes several tools:
	System Information: Displays important information about the hardware, software, and network configuration of your device.
	RAM Freeing: Increases system performance with the RAM Freeing module.
	Extract Windows icons: Allows you to easily extract and convert...
</description></item><item><title>Download PFA Color Suite 6.5.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jan 2026 12:52:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pfa-color-suite-14544.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pfa-color-suite-14544.html
</guid><description>
PFA Color Suite is a versatile cinematic color grading plugin (OpenFX) designed primarily for DaVinci Resolve, integrating many color grading tools into a single interface. You apply one plugin as a single effect instead of having to build long and complex button trees for each shot in Resolve. It's geared towards cinematic color grading for feature films, commercials, and YouTube content, including for non-professional color grading users.
Core tools included
	Film splitter...
</description></item><item><title>Download MASTER EC3 Steel Connections 15.2.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jan 2026 12:43:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-master-ec3-steel-connections-14543.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-master-ec3-steel-connections-14543.html
</guid><description>
BIMware MASTER EC3 Steel Connections software is used to design and verify the load-bearing capacity of typical steel structure connections. The verification of connections is carried out according to the recommendations of EUROCODE 3 (EN 1993-1-8, EN 1993-1-1) with the possibility of considering the national annexes of the following countries: the United Kingdom, France, and Poland.
Key Features
	Performs steel connection calculations based on geometry, bolts, and internal...
</description></item></channel></rss>