<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 17:47:13 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 17:47:13 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Urban VPN 4.0.6</title><pubDate> Mon, 12 Jan 2026 17:59:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-urban-vpn-7155.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-urban-vpn-7155.html
</guid><description>
Urban VPN is a subsidiary of Urban Cyber ​​Security and the creators of one of the world's most trusted and free virtual private networks. VPN Browser Extension Gives You Quick and Easy Activation &amp;amp; Unlimited bandwidth! Urban VPN helps you keep your device activities safe and private. Protect your device from harmful ads and protect your device from malware and other security holes when using public Wi-Fi connections. With Urban VPN, you can safely surf the web without fear of...
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 7.7.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 12 Jan 2026 17:58:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-11-7760.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-11-7760.html
</guid><description>
TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 is a program that allows users to discover hidden settings in Windows 11. This application is specially designed for Windows 11, groups many registry settings and distribute them from the easy and secure user interface. With TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 you can move the Windows taskbar to the top and resize the taskbar by editing the registry value. With any application that modifies the registry, we recommend that you have a backup copy...
</description></item><item><title>Download FX Science Tools Manifest 26.01.10</title><pubDate> Mon, 12 Jan 2026 17:58:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fx-science-tools-3744.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fx-science-tools-3744.html
</guid><description>
FX Science Tools provided to teachers of chemistry and physics the effective means to create equations and chemical structures. Just type and create. FX Chem FX Chem makes writing chemical equations become simple. You just type and FX Chem know enough about chemistry to put all the components of the equation at the right point. FX Chem can even create the chemical equations for nuclear - a very difficult thing in the Word. FX ChemSturation FX ChemSturation made the organic structure, what...
</description></item><item><title>Download FX Math Tools Manifest 26.01.10</title><pubDate> Mon, 12 Jan 2026 17:57:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fx-draw-tools-multidocs-8814.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fx-draw-tools-multidocs-8814.html
</guid><description>
MultiDocs is a new way to create self-modifying Word documents. MultiDocs' amazing new document reproduction features allow you to create reproducible tests and quizzes in minutes. Get new numbers, new diagrams and even brand new solutions! MultiDocs combines the power of Word with two leading products: FX Draw and FX Equation in a new and exciting way.
Features of FX Draw Tools MultiDocs
	Create multiple documents: The software allows users to create multiple math and evaluation...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinPE 11-10-8 Sergei Strelec 2026.01.11</title><pubDate> Mon, 12 Jan 2026 17:57:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winpe-10-8-sergei-strelec-8027.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winpe-10-8-sergei-strelec-8027.html
</guid><description>
WinPE 11-10-8 Sergei Strelec is a Windows 11, 10 and 8 PE boot disk for computer maintenance, hard disks and partitions, disk and partition backup and restore, computer diagnostics, data recovery, installation Windows.
Assembly components include:
	WinPE 11 x64
	WinPE 10 x64
	WinPE 10 x86
	WinPE 8 x86
	WinPE 8 x86 (Native)
System Requirements:
1. RAM 1 GB or more
2. PC can boot from CD/DVD or USB drive.
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 7.7.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 12 Jan 2026 17:56:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-10-7759.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-10-7759.html
</guid><description>
TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 is a utility that allows users to discover hidden settings in Windows 10. This application is specially designed for Windows 10, groups many registry settings and provide them from an easy and secure user interface. With TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 you can move the Windows taskbar to the top and resize the taskbar by editing the registry value. With any application that modifies the registry, we recommend that you have a backup copy to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Artweaver Plus 8.1.2.3675</title><pubDate> Mon, 12 Jan 2026 17:55:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-artweaver-plus-1324.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-artweaver-plus-1324.html
</guid><description>
Artweaver Plus is a software graphics editor with many functions fundamental to advanced and supports many different formats. Artweaver Plus works with image files in formats BMP, GIF, JPEG, JPG, JPE, PCX, PNG, TGA, VDA, ICB, VST, TIF, TIFF and AWD. Out of the possibilities of it, you can do outstanding work with layers, import and export graphic in different formats.
Artweaver Plus - editing software graphics
Artweaver Plus owner interface very similar to Photoshop , so users very...
</description></item><item><title>Download TidyWindow 3.8.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 12 Jan 2026 17:55:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tidywindow-14454.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tidywindow-14454.html
</guid><description>
TidyWindow is a Windows desktop assistant that automates developer PC setup, cleanup, diagnostics, software package installation, registry tweaking, and driver updates—powered by a WPF interface and robust PowerShell 7 automation capabilities in the background.
Key Features
	Essentials Repair Center (docs/essentials.md): Queues selected automation tasks Filter for network, Defender, printing, and Windows Update issues. Each task supports preview run, sequential execution, restore...
</description></item><item><title>Download Directory Opus Pro 13.20.3 Beta</title><pubDate> Mon, 12 Jan 2026 17:54:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-opus-pro-779.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-opus-pro-779.html
</guid><description>
Directory Opus Pro is a software replacement for Explorer with traditional strength and function more than any manager other files. Directory Opus Pro full support for high DPI screen (for example 4K and 5K) with the rename dialog is redesigned, with new features. Besides being a recording macro only allows you to perform mass renaming complex that don't need regular expressions. In addition, Directory Opus Pro also enhances the ability to script.Better handling of renaming recursive and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Hasleo Data Recovery WinPE 6.8 Technician Edition</title><pubDate> Mon, 12 Jan 2026 17:54:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hasleo-data-recovery-winpe-12320.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hasleo-data-recovery-winpe-12320.html
</guid><description>
Hasleo Data Recovery WinPE is an emergency disc that includes a WindowsPE bootable ISO file for CD/DVD or USB drive. It is professional data recovery software for Windows 11/10/8/7/XP and Windows Server, Hasleo Data Recovery can help you recover deleted or lost files from hard drive, SSD, external hard drive, USB flash drive, SD card and other storage devices easily and quickly, this software supports any data loss situations, such as accidental file deletion, files disappearing from the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wordaizer Pro 6.0.0.197</title><pubDate> Mon, 12 Jan 2026 17:53:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wordaizer-pro-7052.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wordaizer-pro-7052.html
</guid><description>
Wordaizer Pro is an efficient program that helps you create an image and add words with a specific shape. Wordaizer Pro allows you to create a word cloud, which can be easily customized from a number of different perspectives. Alternatively, you can create your own shapes or by uploading JPG, BMP, PNG, ICO, EMF or WMF files. In addition, the text can be customized, from font type, size, color, all caps, etc.
Wordaizer Pro can help you create a video, showing how the shape of a word...
</description></item><item><title>Download NTFS Permissions Reporter Enterprise 5.0.629.0 All Editions</title><pubDate> Mon, 12 Jan 2026 17:53:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ntfs-permissions-reporter-enterprise-6370.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ntfs-permissions-reporter-enterprise-6370.html
</guid><description>
System administrators are constantly required to check user rights for specific files and folders. This is often a time-consuming work, with multiple NTFS classes and repetitive adjustments over time creating a security maze. NTFS Permissions Reporter Enterprise allows you to confirm the security status of the entire file system quickly and efficiently. All have multiple export formats, command line support, integration scheduling, advanced filtration, and more.
Features of NTFS...
</description></item><item><title>Download LibreCAD 2.2.1.3</title><pubDate> Mon, 12 Jan 2026 17:47:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-librecad-4571.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-librecad-4571.html
</guid><description>
LibreCAD is a 2D CAD application and the most comprehensive that users can download and install absolutely for free. Now there is a huge community of users who love LibreCAD around the world, this tool has been localized into over 20 languages and supports most major operating systems, including Microsoft Windows, Mac OS X and Linux (Debian, Ubuntu, Fedora, Mandriva, Suse...).
The features of LibreCAD
	App is completely free - users do not need to worry about copyright issues or...
</description></item><item><title>Download Telegram for Desktop 6.4.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 12 Jan 2026 17:46:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-telegram-3376.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-telegram-3376.html
</guid><description>
Telegram is an instant messaging service and voice over IP services on the cloud platform. Client application Telegram is available for Android, iOS, Windows Phone, Windows NT, macOS, and Linux. Users can send messages and exchange photos, videos, stickers, audio and files of any kind.
Telegram - Messaging and free phone calls
Telegram seamless sync across all your devices and can be used on desktop, tablet and phone. You can send unlimited amount of messages, photos, videos and files...
</description></item><item><title>Download Monkfish XML Software XML Blueprint 22.20260111</title><pubDate> Mon, 12 Jan 2026 17:45:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-monkfish-xml-software-xml-blueprint-12529.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-monkfish-xml-software-xml-blueprint-12529.html
</guid><description>
The intelligent XML editor in XMLBlueprint fully supports DTD, Relax NG, Schematron, XSD, XSLT (1.0, 2.0, 3.0) and XPath (1.0, 2.0, 3.1). The unique combination of relevant features and an affordable price for both professional and home users makes this a smart choice for all your XML-related work. With XMLBlueprint you can edit and validate very large XML files (1GByte or more). With an intuitive user interface, XMLBlueprint makes XML editing quick and easy. XMLBlueprint is the best...
</description></item><item><title>Download Filezo 6.0.13</title><pubDate> Mon, 12 Jan 2026 17:44:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-filezo-14317.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-filezo-14317.html
</guid><description>
Filezo instantly finds any file, folder or application on your Windows PC at lightning speed. Just type a few keys and launch! That's it! Filezo's smart search feature ensures meaningful and clean results. It makes your computing life more enjoyable by eliminating boring clicks. Saves a lot of time and effort!
	Quickly access any document, folder or program on Windows in less than 5 seconds! Whether it's on your local hard drive, cloud drive or network drive.
	Tag files and folders to...
</description></item><item><title>Download MultiEcuScan 5.3R1</title><pubDate> Mon, 12 Jan 2026 17:44:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-multiecuscan-7863.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-multiecuscan-7863.html
</guid><description>
MultiEcuScan is a dealer-grade diagnostic tool for most Fiat, Alfa Romeo and Lancia models and also for some Jeep, Chrysler, Dodge and Suzuki models. To use the software, you need an interface. The following interfaces are currently supported by the software: KL (also known as VagCom 409), ELM327 (1.3 or later), OBDKey 1.40, OBDLink, ELM Scan 5, CANtieCAR.
Features of MultiEcuScan
	Read and clear error codes
	Live sensor data
	Live data graphical view
	Check actuator
	Reset /...
</description></item><item><title>Download Round-Robin Mailer 36.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 12 Jan 2026 17:44:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-round-robin-mailer-4433.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-round-robin-mailer-4433.html
</guid><description>
Round-Robin Mailer is software, manage your calendar, send email and redirect or forward multiple messages at the same time to the contact selected with the help of this software supports the protocols POP3 and IMAP4. Round-Robin Mailer is an application that comes with the solution for this problem, by allowing you to automatically read and forward every email to any number of contacts. In addition, it also allows you to use any type of email service to do so, regardless of whether you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Checkbook for Excel 7.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 12 Jan 2026 17:43:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-checkbook-for-excel-6353.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-checkbook-for-excel-6353.html
</guid><description>
Checkbook for Excel is a really easy-to-use checkbook app that can help alleviate the cost of tracking costs, deposits, service fees, and other details of keeping a cheque on money. Checkbook for Excel makes sure you remember actually entering the data, especially the ATM withdrawones. You can also separate the category designation, which is particularly useful if you want to track the costs of child care that may be due to tax.
Checkbook for Excel is a fully feature software...
</description></item><item><title>Download Intel Chipset Device Software 10.1.20398.8776</title><pubDate> Mon, 12 Jan 2026 17:33:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intel-chipset-device-software-9117.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intel-chipset-device-software-9117.html
</guid><description>
Intel Chipset Device Software (INF Update Utility) is a driver package that installs Windows INF files and other system files used by Intel Chipset components to manage and control control various functions of the motherboard. This software is essential for the normal operation of the computer system, as it ensures that the chipset components communicate effectively with the operating system and other hardware devices.
Intel Chipset Device Software provides support for various Intel...
</description></item><item><title>Download Super Quick Settings Pro 7.6</title><pubDate> Mon, 12 Jan 2026 17:31:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-super-quick-settings-pro-9007.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-super-quick-settings-pro-9007.html
</guid><description>
Super Quick Setting Pro is an app designed for Android devices that provides a customizable quick settings panel for easy access to settings and used apps. use regularly. This app allows you to create your own custom dashboard with the settings you love, such as WiFi, Bluetooth, screen brightness, etc.
With Super Quick Settings Pro, you can quickly turn settings on or off, adjust screen brightness, and launch apps with just a few taps. The app offers plenty of customization options,...
</description></item><item><title>Download PhotoDirector: AI Photo Editor 20.9.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 12 Jan 2026 17:31:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-photodirector-photo-editor-8144.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-photodirector-photo-editor-8144.html
</guid><description>
PhotoDirector is a photo editing app for Android devices that allows you to edit and enhance your photos with a variety of tools and effects. With PhotoDirector, you can adjust your photo's color and lighting, remove blemishes and other imperfections, and apply filters to give your photos a unique look. You can also use PhotoDirector to create photo collages and slideshows, add text and stickers to photos, and share your edited photos on social networks or through other sharing...
</description></item><item><title>Download Netmonitor: 5G, Cell &amp;amp; WiFi 1.28.1 build 440</title><pubDate> Mon, 12 Jan 2026 17:30:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-netmonitor-cell-wifi-11660.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-netmonitor-cell-wifi-11660.html
</guid><description>
With Netmonitor, you can clearly know the strength of mobile and WiFi signals, and find out which corner of your office or home has the best reception. Netmonitor displays advanced 2G/3G/4G/5G (NSA and SA) mobile network information and helps you see the status of the mobile network by collecting data about cell towers. Also detects aggregate carriers (called LTE-Advanced).
Troubleshooting tools for voice and data service quality, RF (Telecommunication) optimization, and technical work...
</description></item><item><title>Download Video Player All Format 1.3.2.2.112</title><pubDate> Mon, 12 Jan 2026 17:30:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-video-player-all-format-10984.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-video-player-all-format-10984.html
</guid><description>
The best Video Player All Format for Android with subtitle support. Listen to music with high quality equalizer. Browse and play songs by genre, album, artist, song and folder.
Features of Video Player All Format
	Select multiple files by pressing and holding.
	Hardware acceleration.
	Video player supports all video formats, including MP4, M4V, AVI, MOV, 3GP, FLV, WMV, RMVB, TS, etc.
	Video queue with reordering.
	Supports subtitles with subtitle delay adjustment.
	Find duplicate...
</description></item><item><title>Download Lockscreen Widgets and Drawer 3.1.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 12 Jan 2026 17:30:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-lockscreen-widgets-and-drawer-8656.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-lockscreen-widgets-and-drawer-8656.html
</guid><description>
Widgets and drawers on the lock screen: A long time ago, Android introduced a feature that allowed you to display certain widgets on the lock screen. For some reason, this useful feature was removed with the release of Android 5.0 Lollipop, limiting widgets to the home screen only. While some manufacturers, such as Samsung, have brought back limited versions of lock screen widgets, you're usually limited to the widgets the manufacturer has created for you. Well, not anymore! Lock screen...
</description></item></channel></rss>