<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 13:45:29 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 13:45:29 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Weather Live 7.8.6 build 395</title><pubDate> Sun, 17 Aug 2025 16:40:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-weather-live-8465.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-weather-live-8465.html
</guid><description>
Weather Live is a weather forecast app for Android devices that provides users with current weather conditions, hourly and daily forecasts, and severe weather warnings. The app has a user-friendly interface that displays weather information in an easy-to-read format. Get live weather forecast, storm radar, current temperature, rain intensity, wind speed, severe weather alerts, rain and snow warnings – all in one with Weather Live.
Live Weather Features
	Weather forecast for many...
</description></item><item><title>Download Easy Notes - Note Taking Apps 1.3.21.0811</title><pubDate> Sun, 17 Aug 2025 16:40:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-easy-notes-notebook-notepad-8388.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-easy-notes-notebook-notepad-8388.html
</guid><description>
Easy Notes - Great note taking app, Notepad, Notebook, Free Notes is a free easy to use note taking app for notes app. With this easy notebook and notepad app, take quick notes with colorful backgrounds and checklists to organize notes and tasks easily. Use this aesthetic note taker and note taker to add photos or audio to your notes. Easy Notes is a useful notebook and note-taking app for taking notes and organizing work.
Features of Easy Notes - Notebook, Notepad
	Free Notepad and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cast to TV+ Chromecast Roku TV 12.262</title><pubDate> Sun, 17 Aug 2025 16:40:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-cast-to-tv-chromecast-roku-tv-10801.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-cast-to-tv-chromecast-roku-tv-10801.html
</guid><description>
Transfer videos, music, photos...or watch on your phone. Smart TVs with integrated DLNA include: LG TVs, TCL, Phillips, Sony Bravia, Samsung, Sharp, Panasonic and many other brands. Please check your TV's user manual. Any web browser: can send video to web browsers such as Chrome, Firefox, Amazon Silk, TV browser or PlayStation 4.
Features &amp;amp; Limitations of some streaming receivers
Screen mirroring
	Screen mirroring is only available on newer Android devices.
Roku Streaming...
</description></item><item><title>Download SD Maid 2/SE - System Cleaner 1.4.16-beta0</title><pubDate> Sun, 17 Aug 2025 16:39:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sd-maid-2se-system-cleaner-10472.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sd-maid-2se-system-cleaner-10472.html
</guid><description>
SD Maid 2/SE - System Cleaner is a reliable helper for your Android, keeping the device clean &amp;amp; orderly. SD Maid SE has optional features that use the AccessibilityService API to automate tedious actions. Using the AccessibilityService API, SD Maid SE can click buttons for you to perform cross-app operations, for example, clear cache. SD Maid SE does not use the AccessibilityService API to collect information.
No one is perfect and neither is Android
	Apps you deleted will leave...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sleep Cycle: Sleep Tracker 4.25.31-production</title><pubDate> Sun, 17 Aug 2025 16:39:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sleep-cycle-sleep-tracker-8151.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sleep-cycle-sleep-tracker-8151.html
</guid><description>
Sleep cycle: A sleep tracker is a mobile app that uses sensors on your phone to track your sleep patterns and wake you at the optimal time in your sleep cycle. The app analyzes your sleep patterns and wakes you up in 30-minute intervals when you are in light sleep, which is the natural waking phase of your sleep cycle. This helps you feel more rested and refreshed when you wake up. Sleep cycle: Sleep tracker also includes features like a sleep diary, snore tracker, and sleep notes,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sectograph. Day &amp;amp; Time planner 5.39</title><pubDate> Sun, 17 Aug 2025 16:39:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sectograph-day-time-planner-8322.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sectograph-day-time-planner-8322.html
</guid><description>
Sectograph is a day and time planning app available for Android devices as an APK file. It is a calendar and scheduling app that allows users to plan and organize their day, view upcoming events and appointments, and set reminders. The app also includes many customization options, such as the ability to change the color scheme and background image. Additionally, it has a built-in time tracking feature, allowing users to track time spent on various activities.
Sectograph features. Day...
</description></item><item><title>Download All-In-One Calculator 3.1.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 17 Aug 2025 16:38:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-all-in-one-calculator-9092.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-all-in-one-calculator-9092.html
</guid><description>
All-In-One Calculator is a simple, clean and easy-to-use calculator with a full set of tools for everyday life, such as a unit converter, currency converter, percentage calculator and more. From simple or complex calculations, to unit and currency conversions, percentages, ratios, area, volume, etc. it does it all. And it does it!
Features of All-In-One Calculator
Main Calculator
	Simple or Scientific Layout
	40 Light or Dark (AMOLED) Themes
	Editable Input &amp;amp; Cursor
	Copy &amp;amp;...
</description></item><item><title>Download Everyday | Calendar Widget 18.8.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 17 Aug 2025 16:37:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-everyday-calendar-widget-8422.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-everyday-calendar-widget-8422.html
</guid><description>
Daily is a widget to check calendar information from the home screen. It is highly customizable with a dynamic theme engine to match your style. Try exploring its other features.
Everyday Features | Calendar Widget
	A utility to check events.
	A utility for the things that matter most.
	A utility to navigate through different dates.
	Calendar First Date Number of Days # Empty Days
	Event number Event indicator Shows events and more.
	Dynamic theme engine is background aware to avoid...
</description></item><item><title>Download PeakFinder 4.8.53</title><pubDate> Sun, 17 Aug 2025 16:37:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-peakfinder-10050.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-peakfinder-10050.html
</guid><description>
Explore more mountains than any other climber! PeakFinder AR makes it possible… and shows the names of all the mountains and peaks with a 360° panoramic display. This functionality is completely offline - and worldwide! PeakFinder knows more than 650,000 mountain peaks - from Mount Everest to that little hill on the corner.
PeakFinder Features
	Works offline and worldwide
	Includes more than 650,000 peak names
	Install the camera image using a panoramic drawing *
	Display real-time...
</description></item><item><title>Download eWeather HDF - weather app 9.1.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 17 Aug 2025 16:36:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-eweather-hdf-weather-app-11121.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-eweather-hdf-weather-app-11121.html
</guid><description>
The weather forecast is highly accurate thanks to the use of data from two independent weather agencies. eWeather HD is the Android app with the most information about the weather and your environment. It includes weather forecasts and current weather from various weather providers, NOAA radar, weather alerts, latest earthquakes, geomagnetic storm forecast, pressure change indicator, calendar wind, lunar and solar, road visibility and METAR, etc.
Annual archived data on air and sea...
</description></item><item><title>Download AR Plan 3D Tape Measure, Ruler 4.10.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 17 Aug 2025 16:36:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ar-plan-3d-tape-measure-ruler-8786.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ar-plan-3d-tape-measure-ruler-8786.html
</guid><description>
AR Floorplan 3D – Innovative measurement application, augmented reality (AR, lidar scanner) for quick room measurement. AR camera sensor technology allows placing virtual tape measure on real surface, making the process of measuring and creating 3D floor plan much easier and faster. Using the device's camera sensor - sketch a house, draw a blueprint, build a design.
With the AR Plan 3D ruler app, you can
	Measure the perimeter and height of a room in Metric or Imperial units (cm, m,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Web Video Cast | Browser to TV 5.12.6 build 5604</title><pubDate> Sun, 17 Aug 2025 16:35:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-web-video-cast-browser-to-tv-8372.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-web-video-cast-browser-to-tv-8372.html
</guid><description>
Web Video Cast allows you to watch TV videos from your favorite websites including movies, TV shows, live news, sports and IPTV. It also allows you to stream local videos stored on your phone. Image and audio files are also supported. Subtitles are detected on the website, you can also use your own subtitles or you can use the built-in search feature of OpenSubtitles.org.
Web Video Caster supports the most popular streaming devices, allowing your TV to stream video directly from the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Your Calendar Widget 1.67.3</title><pubDate> Sun, 17 Aug 2025 16:35:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-your-calendar-widget-8141.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-your-calendar-widget-8141.html
</guid><description>
Your Calendar Widget is an app that provides a customizable calendar widget for Android devices. The app allows users to view their upcoming events and appointments directly from their device's home screen. It shows your upcoming events. You can easily configure and adjust the widget according to your needs. Each widget has its own configuration. This allows you to have several widgets with different display and calendar settings.
Features of Your Calendar Widget
	Widgets can be used...
</description></item><item><title>Download IObit Driver Booster Pro Portable 12.6.0.620</title><pubDate> Sat, 16 Aug 2025 23:38:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iobit-driver-booster-pro-portable-4169.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iobit-driver-booster-pro-portable-4169.html
</guid><description>
IObit Driver Booster Pro Portable is a portable version developed with IObit's most advanced driver update technology, which automatically identifies and scans for outdated, downloaded drivers and install the correct update for you with just one click, saving you a lot of time. In addition, IObit Driver Booster Pro Portable is specially developed to enhance drivers for better gaming performance and ensure better computer performance by improving update security with Restore, Uninstall...
</description></item><item><title>Download Topaz Video AI Pro 7.1.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 16 Aug 2025 23:38:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-video-enhance-ai-3733.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-video-enhance-ai-3733.html
</guid><description>
Topaz Video Enhance AI is a tool to increase video quality with this great technology ONE. Topaz Video Enhance WHO wide open your video to resolutions up to 8K with the details and consistency of motion. Until the present, there is no way to re-create a perfect high resolution video from the footage is low resolution. From the family film to SD low quality to DVD quality and more than that, Video Enhance WHO will convert your video into the footage is upgrade clear with resolutions up to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Remote Desktop Manager Enterprise 2025.2.26</title><pubDate> Sat, 16 Aug 2025 23:37:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-remote-desktop-manager-enterprise-242.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-remote-desktop-manager-enterprise-242.html
</guid><description>
Remote Desktop Manager Enterprise software is the complete management of remote connections and virtual machines from a single location, at the same time access support data online and cloud storage. Remote Desktop Manager supports multiple types of connections, not only connections for the protocol connect remote computer Remote Desktop Protocol (RDP).
Remote Desktop Manager easily add, edit, delete, share, organize and find your remote connection of you quickly. Compatible with...
</description></item><item><title>Download Glary Utilities Pro Portable 6.29.0.33</title><pubDate> Sat, 16 Aug 2025 23:36:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-utilities-pro-portable-3500.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-utilities-pro-portable-3500.html
</guid><description>
Glary Utilities Pro Portable is a program that provides you with the necessary options to clean and maintain your PC system. The software's interface consists of a small window, simple to use. Newbies shouldn't have any problems getting around the program. So you can scan for problems revolving around incorrect registry entries, dangerous startup entries, invalid shortcuts, Internet history and traces, temporary files, spyware and adware.
Glary Utilities Pro Portable - Optimize and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Duplicate File Finder Professional 2025 v405</title><pubDate> Sat, 16 Aug 2025 23:35:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-duplicate-file-finder-professional-4425.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-duplicate-file-finder-professional-4425.html
</guid><description>
Duplicate File Finder Professional is a compact application helps you quickly find and remove files duplicate on the computer. With Duplicate File Finder Professional you can choose any folder on the hard drive or use the folder standard user and our app will analyze the deep content of the selected folder to copy. It will take only a few seconds. The files will be compared by the hash algorithm MD5, which means they will be compared by content, not by name. Then, use our convenient...
</description></item><item><title>Download O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro 21.1.183 / Server</title><pubDate> Sat, 16 Aug 2025 23:28:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-diskimage-pro-218.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-diskimage-pro-218.html
</guid><description>
O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro is software backup data comprehensive and effective is provided to protect the data of the computer system, it creates images for individual drives or the entire system that still does not affect your system.
O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro allows the user to backup the entire computer or drive, the and files whenever you want even while the computer is being used. Or can use O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro to create a copy chinh sac of computer disk drives, can be used instead of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download VCap Downloader Pro 0.1.35.6662</title><pubDate> Sat, 16 Aug 2025 23:27:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vcap-downloader-pro-8474.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vcap-downloader-pro-8474.html
</guid><description>
VCap Downloader Pro (VCapDL) is a popular piece of software that allows you to record video and audio from websites on the internet. The interface of the software is similar to a normal browser, making it easy for users to get used to and work with this software. User just need to copy video url from favorite browser and convert it to VCap Downloader Pro. It will capture the video and make the quality available for download. You can also extract the audio track from any video and convert...
</description></item><item><title>Download MOTU Digital Performer 11.35.100361</title><pubDate> Sat, 16 Aug 2025 23:27:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-motu-digital-performer-1514.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-motu-digital-performer-1514.html
</guid><description>
MOTU Digital Performer is processor plug-ins, exciting new, a synth, strong and much improved workflow title new upgrade this big. Let's arouse your creativity, then tweak the distribution of you - all in a workflow alone. DP version 10 offers new exciting features such as short window, and Stretch Audio, plus hundreds of virtual instruments included and dozens of process improvement work according to the requirements of users DP.
MOTU Digital Performer - tools audio editing
MOTU...
</description></item><item><title>Download Robin YouTube Video Downloader Pro 6.15.7</title><pubDate> Sat, 16 Aug 2025 23:26:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-video-downloader-pro-2828.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-video-downloader-pro-2828.html
</guid><description>
YouTube Video Downloader Pro is a Windows application professional to download and convert videos from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion and thousands of video sharing sites, other. It accelerates your download up to 5 times. YouTube Video Downloader Pro allows you to download multiple videos at the same time. It also allows you to pause, resume and cancel a download at any time.
YouTube Video Downloader Pro - Download online videos on social networks
Features of YouTube Video Downloader...
</description></item><item><title>Download IntraWEB Ultimate 16.1.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 16 Aug 2025 23:21:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intraweb-ultimate-2007.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intraweb-ultimate-2007.html
</guid><description>
IntraWEB Ultimate is a tool to build the website. With this tool, the developer can create the page using the same method used to build the Windows program. Because the HTML page directly from the concept design to the user's computer does not download a bit more complicated and in fact is required from web server. So, the template IntraWeb on the server and download server and displays them to the user. Things technology direction of the IntraWEB Ultimate provides part flexibility and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Muziza YouTube Downloader Converter 8.11.6</title><pubDate> Sat, 16 Aug 2025 23:21:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-muziza-youtube-downloader-converter-3972.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-muziza-youtube-downloader-converter-3972.html
</guid><description>
Muziza YouTube Downloader Converter is a tool to create conditions for an attractive interface and many features to help you to download video clips from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion, Instagram and other sites. Muziza YouTube Downloader Converter can also download the video UHD 8K, 5K, 4K, QHD 2K, HD 1080p and 720p from YouTube. The app allows you download only audio stream from YouTube and save as MP3. You don't need to download the entire video file.
Muziza YouTube Downloader...
</description></item><item><title>Download PACETEQ OneTiming 1.10.144</title><pubDate> Sat, 16 Aug 2025 23:20:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-paceteq-onetiming-12731.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-paceteq-onetiming-12731.html
</guid><description>
OneTiming integrates all important data sources, including all major timing protocols, GPS feeds, Race Control Messages, weather data and video feeds. The optimal balance of performance and durability is designed to be the benchmark for dynamic and complex racing environments.
Key Features of OneTiming
	Data Integration: OneTiming seamlessly combines information from multiple channels, including timekeeping, telemetry, weather data, and audio/video feeds. This integration supports all...
</description></item></channel></rss>