<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 15:40:04 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 15:40:04 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download foobar2000 2.25</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Sep 2025 17:16:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-foobar2000-1812.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-foobar2000-1812.html
</guid><description>
foobar2000 is the media player for media formats MP3, WAV, OGG and other formats multimedia other. It has no bells and whistles, however, under the hood, the program offers quite many features, including format, title and layout of the interface can be customized, convert WAV, Equalizer, Resampler, note cards, MP3, playlists, music album, CD, drag / drop and more. It also includes all the standard features like shuffle, random play, etc.
foobar2000 - The media player
foobar2000 running...
</description></item><item><title>Download ImageMagick 7.1.2-3</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Sep 2025 17:15:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-imagemagick-1319.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-imagemagick-1319.html
</guid><description>
ImageMagick is software image processing command line to create, edit, compose, or convert bitmap images. ImageMagick is completely free for users and you easily download it on taiwebs.com. Typical functions most of software is able to read and write images in many formats (over 100) including DPX, EXR, GIF, JPEG, JPEG-2000, PDF, PhotoCD, PNG, Postcript, SVG, and TIFF.
ImageMagick - image Processing
The Windows version of ImageMagick is installed. Just click on the appropriate version...
</description></item><item><title>Download 3uTools 3.28.012</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Sep 2025 17:07:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-3utools-4336.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-3utools-4336.html
</guid><description>
3uTools is tool data management and file iOS the most effective. 3uTools help easily manage the apps, photos, music, ringtones, video files and other multimedia. Watch full the different status of iOS devices, including activating, unlocking, status, pin lock and iCloud, as well as detailed information about iOS &amp;amp; iDevice. 3uTools can automate the hardware available for iOS devices. iOS flashing in normal mode, DFU mode and recovery mode are supported. Unlocking with a click of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download BrightVPN 1.566.436</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Sep 2025 17:06:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-brightvpn-8960.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-brightvpn-8960.html
</guid><description>
BrightVPN is a virtual private network (VPN) service that provides users with a private and secure internet browsing experience. The service uses encryption and tunneling protocols to protect users' online activities and personal data from being intercepted or tracked by third parties.
BrightVPN frees you from restrictions or censorship by unblocking any website from 150+ countries, connecting you to the Internet for free from anywhere. In addition, Bright VPN protects your internet...
</description></item><item><title>Download Syncthing 2.0.4</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Sep 2025 17:05:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncthing-2115.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncthing-2115.html
</guid><description>
Syncthing is synchronization service, cloud and open and non-focus allows you to share and sync files with other computers and gives you full control how to share your data and who can access it. Syncthing does not store your data in any other place, there is no server side Tuesday how to join. In addition, all the communication is secured by TLS and every button is determined by the certificate the strength of the encryption. Only computers that have explicitly allowed can connect with...
</description></item><item><title>Download Free YouTube Download 4.4.37.827 Premium</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Sep 2025 17:04:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-download-1177.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-download-1177.html
</guid><description>
Free YouTube Download Premium is the most popular application to download videos from YouTube. The program was released in 2006 and regularly updated since then. Use the program to download and convert YouTube videos to view offline anytime.
Free YouTube Download - added Support to download youtube
Download more videos! Save whole playlists and YouTube channels, videos from a playlist individually (history, video be favorite, favourites, Watch later), videos from many different...
</description></item><item><title>Download HE - Hardware Read and Write Utility 1.25.09.02</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Sep 2025 17:03:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-he-hardware-read-and-write-utility-4287.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-he-hardware-read-and-write-utility-4287.html
</guid><description>
HE - Hardware Read and Write Utility is a powerful utility intended for hardware engineer, engineer, BIOS developer, driver, engineer, QA engineers, performance test engineers, diagnostic, etc., this utility access almost all the computer hardware, including PCI (PCI Express), index / Data, PCI, memory, index memory / Data space I / O, Index I / O / Data, Super I / O, DIMM SPD, CPU The registers MSR, screen, SMART, physical area of the hard drive identification data, ATA, dump tables ACPI...
</description></item><item><title>Download Monkeys Audio 11.41</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Sep 2025 17:03:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-monkeys-audio-949.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-monkeys-audio-949.html
</guid><description>
Monkey\'s Audio is software that compresses digital music without loss of quality. Supports high quality WAV files and CD ripping. Monkeys Audio will compress .wav tracks into .ape files to reduce their size without loss of sound quality, decompress .ape, convert files, check file integrity and manage tags.
Unlike traditional methods like MP3 and OGG, which permanently remove quality to save space, Monkey\'s Audio only creates perfect copies with the same sound quality as the originals....
</description></item><item><title>Download Dashcam Viewer Plus 4.0.7</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Sep 2025 17:03:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dashcam-viewer-531.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dashcam-viewer-531.html
</guid><description>
Dashcam Viewer is a software application for viewing movies, GPS data and sensor data recorded by dashcam or a camera. Dashcam Viewer supports more than 100 camera models. The video dashcam of you on the main screen while viewing speed, distance, position, bearing capacity and updated data shock sensor on your car on the chart, display data and maps.
The main features Dashcam Viewer
	Export format of your GPS to the popular file formats such as Google Earth KML files and exchange GPS...
</description></item><item><title>Download AntiPlagiarism.NET 4.147</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Sep 2025 17:02:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-antiplagiarismnet-2457.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-antiplagiarismnet-2457.html
</guid><description>
AntiPlagiarism NET is software to check the originality of some given text, most people find a section of text on the Internet, often the search engines quickly put out the answer to this question. Sometimes the results can be wrong, because not all results are accurate, a hundred percent. Fortunately, there are other solutions to the problem, for example, AntiPlagiarism.NET it can help you determine the originality of some given text. Application to operate correctly, you need to install...
</description></item><item><title>Download LeoCAD 25.09</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Sep 2025 17:02:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-leocad-7929.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-leocad-7929.html
</guid><description>
LeoCAD is a CAD program for creating virtual LEGO models. LeoCAD has an intuitive interface designed to allow beginner users to create new models without having to spend too much time learning the application. At the same time, it has a rich feature set that allows experienced users to build models using more advanced techniques.
LeoCAD is fully compatible with the LDraw Standard and related tools, and it reads and writes LDR and MPD files so you can share and download models from the...
</description></item><item><title>Download ExamDiff Pro Master Edition 16.0.1.9</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Sep 2025 17:01:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-examdiff-pro-master-312.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-examdiff-pro-master-312.html
</guid><description>
ExamDiff Pro Master is a tool to compare files and folders intuitive and easy to use, intuitive and easy to use for Windows. ExamDiff Pro Master has unique features distinguishes ExamDiff Pro with the program compare other. ExamDiff Pro Master to help perform reviews of code and share other reports with your colleagues and compare local website with FTP server by plug-ins more integrated.
ExamDiff Pro Master can create a snapshot folder for comparison and storage in the future, compare...
</description></item><item><title>Download Gilisoft DRM Protection 8.8.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Sep 2025 17:01:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-video-drm-protection-5260.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-video-drm-protection-5260.html
</guid><description>
Gilisoft Video DRM Protection is software that helps you can protect your videos and the E-Learning content to another by secure, encrypted the files, your content and distribute them to the target audience authorized of you. Very easy to make video / sound / pictures of you can't see are for anyone except those you allow. Gilisoft Video DRM Protection can encrypt and pack video &amp;amp; codec &amp;amp; player into exe.
Gilisoft Video DRM Protection can easily encode almost any kind of Video...
</description></item><item><title>Download HTTP Toolkit 1.22.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Sep 2025 17:00:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-http-toolkit-6246.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-http-toolkit-6246.html
</guid><description>
HTTP Toolkit is software that provides the ability to automatically block HTTP and HTTPS traffic from most client applications, including web browsers such as Chrome and Firefox, most CLI tools and auxiliary languages such as Node.js, Python, Ruby etc. You can browse through traffic by marking the content type, status, and source or search by URL, status, and title to find important notifications.
You can check the URL, status, title, and content of each request or feedback, along with...
</description></item><item><title>Download MassTube 2026 v21.0.1.162 Ultra</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Sep 2025 17:00:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-masstube-plus-461.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-masstube-plus-461.html
</guid><description>
MassTube Plus is a small utility used to download the favorite videos of you on youtube on your computer. This is a software compact, has a simple design with few options to download videos fastest. The you complete peace of mind because the software is easy to use, built exclusively for a single goal: to retrieve the video file from YouTube, so it doesn't pack the other useful features such as search engine integrated and a download audio file.
MassTube can work with multiple output...
</description></item><item><title>Download lessmsi 2.8.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Sep 2025 16:59:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lessmsi-12392.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lessmsi-12392.html
</guid><description>
Lessmsi (Less MSIerables) is a free and portable application that allows users to view and extract the contents of MSI files.
How does it work? Files with the .msi extension are not as widely used as their .exe cousins, but both contain programs for Windows. The main difference between them is that the latter does not always come with an installer, while it comes standard with the former. However, there will be cases where you just need to view or want to extract specific content from...
</description></item><item><title>Download Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium 4.4.37.827</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Sep 2025 16:59:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-to-mp3-converter-premium-844.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-to-mp3-converter-premium-844.html
</guid><description>
Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium version is a software used to convert YouTube to MP3, extract audio from playlists YouTube, show listings, charts, video responses, channels, favorites of the user. With Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium, you can download and convert playlists, channels, stream original tv series and get them into iTunes at the same time.
Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium - convert YouTube to MP3
Features Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium from the...
</description></item><item><title>Download QOwnNotes 25.9.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Sep 2025 16:58:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qownnotes-3178.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qownnotes-3178.html
</guid><description>
QOwnNotes is notes bookmark file simple text (GPL) open source application for GNU / Linux , Mac OS X and Windows of Patrizio Bekerle ( pbek on GitHub and IRC) (optional) activity along with the notes application of ownCloud or Nextcloud. QOwnNote store your notes as plain text files and can be synchronized with synchronization function file of ownCloud / Nextcloud. You can also use other apps like Syncthing or Dropbox . Just write out your thoughts as they appear, and edit them if...
</description></item><item><title>Download Trellix Stinger (McAfee Stinger) 13.0.0.449</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Sep 2025 16:58:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mcafee-stinger-202.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mcafee-stinger-202.html
</guid><description>
McAfee Stinger is a free utility that functions to scan, check and remove the hazards and obstacles as virus or malware for Windows, whether they are hiding deep into the system.
In addition, due to the ability to search for the correct folder, or the data at risk contains viruses to scan instead you have to remove a long time waiting for antivirus software to scan all system on your computer. Thus speed of work of the McAfee Stinger faster and somewhat more accurate.
Themselves McAfee...
</description></item><item><title>Download MyLanViewer Enterprise 6.5.7</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Sep 2025 16:57:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mylanviewer-enterprise-1274.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mylanviewer-enterprise-1274.html
</guid><description>
MyLanViewer is a program for scanning IP address, Netbios and LAN / Network powerful for Windows tool whois and traceroute, remote shutdown and process management Wake On LAN (WOL), scan and monitor wireless networks. This app will help you find all IP addresses, MAC addresses and shared folders of computers on the network wired or wireless (Wi-Fi).
MyLanViewer Enterprise - Scan IP address LAN/Network
The program scans network and displays the computer network in your window, friends...
</description></item><item><title>Download Secret Video Downloader 0.9.9</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Sep 2025 16:57:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secret-video-downloader-13775.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secret-video-downloader-13775.html
</guid><description>
Secret Video Downloader is a free application designed to facilitate easy video downloading from various websites. It leverages the yt-dlp command line program to efficiently grab video content, allowing users to save videos in the highest quality available without complicated installation or configuration. The tool has a minimalist interface focused on simplicity: the user pastes the video URL into the built-in browser, clicks the Download button, and the video is added to the download...
</description></item><item><title>Download Privacy Eraser Free 6.22.0 Build 5360</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Sep 2025 16:56:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-privacy-eraser-free-9160.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-privacy-eraser-free-9160.html
</guid><description>
Privacy Eraser is a software tool that helps protect user privacy by securely erasing or deleting unwanted data from their computer or device. This tool is designed to delete browsing history, cookies, cache, temporary files and other sensitive information that may be stored on the computer.
Privacy Eraser can be used to clear browsing history of popular web browsers such as Google Chrome, Mozilla Firefox and Microsoft Edge. It can also clear the history and cache of other applications,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Disk Pulse Ultimate 17.2.26 + Enterprise + Pro</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Sep 2025 16:56:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-disk-pulse-ultimate-1465.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-disk-pulse-ultimate-1465.html
</guid><description>
Disk Pulse Ultimate is a monitoring solution change disk real-time allows one to monitor one or more disks or directories, save reports and statistics monitoring disk changes, the change is detected to the SQL database focus, execute custom commands and send E-Mail notifications when unauthorized changes are detected in the file system important.
Disk Pulse Ultimate - Monitor disc change
DiskPulse provides the ability for users to start / stop the monitoring operation disc change,...
</description></item><item><title>Download MobiPDF: PDF Editor &amp;amp; Scanner 11.9.267317</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Sep 2025 16:54:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pdf-extra-scan-edit-sign-8390.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pdf-extra-scan-edit-sign-8390.html
</guid><description>
PDF Extra PDF Editor &amp;amp; Scanner is a mobile application that allows users to create, edit and sign PDF documents on their Android or iOS devices. It includes many tools and features that make it easy to work with PDF files, including scanning, editing, and signing. This application also allows users to combine multiple PDF files into a single document and export PDF files in various file formats, such as JPEG, PNG, and Microsoft Word.
Features of PDF Extra PDF Editor &amp;amp;...
</description></item><item><title>Download CCleaner – Phone Cleaner 25.17.0 build 800011244</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Sep 2025 16:54:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ccleaner-pro-for-android-3428.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ccleaner-pro-for-android-3428.html
</guid><description>
CCleaner is a system cleaning and optimization tool for Android devices. CCleaner for Android allows users to delete unnecessary files, such as temporary files and caches, as well as identify and uninstall applications that are taking up too much space on the device. It also includes a task kill to close running applications and free up memory. This can help free up storage space and improve device performance. In addition, CCleaner for Android also has a security feature that allows you...
</description></item></channel></rss>