<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 12:44:36 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 12:44:36 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Download video no watermark 1.51.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:44:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-download-video-no-watermark-13999.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-download-video-no-watermark-13999.html
</guid><description>
Want to download videos without watermark? Try Video Downloader for TT No Watermark (Pinterest Video Downloader)! You can freely set live wallpaper and ringtone by downloading your favorite music or videos! Download any videos and music you like on TT and watch them offline. Fast and Easy!
Highlight Features
	Video Downloader for TT (Pinterest Video Downloader): No need to log in.
	Set live wallpaper and ringtone is simple and free.
	Download Pinterest mp4 videos, Download CapCut...
</description></item><item><title>Download aCalendar+ Calendar &amp;amp; Tasks 2.9.6 build 2009600</title><pubDate> Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:44:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-acalendar-calendar-tasks-9857.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-acalendar-calendar-tasks-9857.html
</guid><description>
aCalendar+ Calendar &amp;amp; Tasks is a popular calendar and task manager app for Android devices. It is developed by Tapir Apps GmbH and acts as an enhanced version of the free aCalendar app. aCalendar+ offers a variety of features and customization options to help users stay organized and manage their schedules and tasks effectively.
Features of aCalendar+ Calendar &amp;amp; Tasks Tasks
	intuitive navigation with smooth transitions
	day, week, month and year views
	full screen...
</description></item><item><title>Download Password Safe and Manager 9.1.0 build 901001</title><pubDate> Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:43:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-password-safe-and-manager-8210.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-password-safe-and-manager-8210.html
</guid><description>
Password Safe and Manager is a password management application for Android devices. The app also includes features like login autofill, a password generator, and a built-in browser to access your account directly from the app. It's a great way to securely store and manage your login information and other sensitive information.
Summary of essential functions
	securely store passwords, access data, etc.
	classify your entries in Password Security
	access via a single master...
</description></item><item><title>Download Running Tracker App – FITAPP 8.10.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:43:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-fitapp-track-my-run-running-8392.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-fitapp-track-my-run-running-8392.html
</guid><description>
FITAPP Track My Run &amp;amp; Running is a fitness tracking mobile application that allows users to track and analyze their running activities. It often includes features like GPS tracking, allowing users to track their route, distance, speed, and time. It also includes many tools for analyzing performance, such as graphs and charts that display data such as heart rate, calories burned, and elevation.
FITAPP will also help you lose weight, count calories, maintain your target weight or...
</description></item><item><title>Download Digital Clock &amp;amp; Weather Widget 6.9.18.674</title><pubDate> Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:43:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-digital-clock-weather-widget-11659.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-digital-clock-weather-widget-11659.html
</guid><description>
Digital Clock &amp;amp; Weather Widget application is a multifunctional application that helps users track time and weather information easily and conveniently. With a modern and easy-to-use interface, this application will be a great assistant for users in managing time and preparing for daily activities.
Outstanding features of the Digital Clock &amp;amp; Weather Widget application include:
	Digital clock display: Users can easily see the current hour, minute and second on their phone...
</description></item><item><title>Download Stoxy PRO - Stock Market Live 7.0.3</title><pubDate> Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:42:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-stoxy-pro-stock-market-live-9366.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-stoxy-pro-stock-market-live-9366.html
</guid><description>
Stoxy Pro: Easily Follow Your Stocks, Indices, Futures From The US, EU, and Asian Markets. View Stocks Quotes and Daily Performance In Customizable Portfolios, Tap Any Ticker To See An Interactive Chart and Detailed Information. Read the Latest Investment and Business News from Top Publications Around The World.
Features of Stoxy PRO - Stock Market Live
	Stay on top of the changing us and global stocks markets. Get Real-time Stock Quotes and Prices: Apple Inc. (Aapl), Alphabet Inc....
</description></item><item><title>Download BeSoccer - Soccer Live Score 6.1.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:42:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-besoccer-soccer-live-score-8800.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-besoccer-soccer-live-score-8800.html
</guid><description>
All the football in the world at the click of a button. BeSoccer is the best live soccer app with soccer news, results and statistics. We cover over 10,000 competitions: you'll be able to follow all the matches live, receive goal notifications, line-ups, news, signings and today's televised matches . Explore the best database in the world of football with all the statistics about your team, favorite players around the world, comparisons, team form and the latest transfer rumours.&amp;lt;...
</description></item><item><title>Download Podcast &amp;amp; Radio - Castmix 5.9.11</title><pubDate> Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:42:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-podcast-player-castmix-9313.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-podcast-player-castmix-9313.html
</guid><description>
Subscribe to podcasts you love, play the latest episodes from your favorite podcasts, discover recommendations, browse unlimited podcast categories. CastMix allows you to manage Podcast episodes, live radio, audiobooks and RSS feeds! Everything in a single app.
Features of Castmix for Android
Podcast
	Search podcasts by name or keyword;
	Browse podcasts by category;
	Subscribe to your favorite podcasts;
	Import from OPML file/URL;
	Listen to podcasts offline;
	Share a podcast or...
</description></item><item><title>Download Peak – Brain Games &amp;amp; Training 4.30.6</title><pubDate> Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:41:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-peak-brain-games-training-8236.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-peak-brain-games-training-8236.html
</guid><description>
Peak is a brain training application aimed at improving cognitive abilities and brain activity. It has many games and exercises designed to target different areas of the brain such as memory, attention, problem solving and more. It only takes 10 minutes a day to complete a brain training exercise. And, with 45 brain games for adults and new brain training exercises every day, there's always a fun challenge waiting for you.
Some features of the application include:
	Daily brain...
</description></item><item><title>Download Onkyo HF Player 2.14.4</title><pubDate> Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:40:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-onkyo-hf-player-12073.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-onkyo-hf-player-12073.html
</guid><description>
Get more control over how the music sounds on your Android device with our touch-adjustable linear phase FIR equalizer, providing 16,384 distinct HD equalizer bands without loss sound quality. Create and save your own EQ presets or choose optimized filters created by professional musicians. HF Player for Android also enables playback of High-Resolution Audio formats including FLAC, 192 kHz/24-bit WAV and DSD at no additional charge.
Features:
	Updated user interface
	Lyrics are...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare Recoverit 14.0.18.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 11 Feb 2026 21:07:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-recoverits-374.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-recoverits-374.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare Recoverit is a data recovery software that is easily lost at a rapid rate and is used by many people. You will do what happens if one day your data is suddenly lost due to the virus or deleted it, .. Wondershare Recoverit will provide you with an environment to protect important data.
Wondershare Recoverit has all the scanning processes that are divided into multiple types, from the typical recovery of the deleted files that are deleted to the recovery of missing files due...
</description></item><item><title>Download CalendarTask (formerly DesktopCal) 3.26.267.8501</title><pubDate> Wed, 11 Feb 2026 21:06:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopcal-1831.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopcal-1831.html
</guid><description>
CalendarTask (formerly DesktopCal) is a simple desktop calendar that blends into your desktop without blocking access to your desktop icons. You can double-click on a date to quickly add notes and also jump to specific dates in the past or future.
CalendarTask - Computer calendar
CalendarTask can use your current wallpaper or loop through images from your folder and update your desktop every few minutes. The program helps you make appointments, make plans... Not only that, the Screen...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Illustrator 2026 v30.2.1.1 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Wed, 11 Feb 2026 21:06:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-illustrator-0024-749.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-illustrator-0024-749.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Illustrator is a powerful vector graphics editor developed by Adobe Inc., first released in 1987. It is primarily used by graphic designers, illustrators, and artists to create high-quality illustrations, logos, icons, and digital artwork. Unlike raster graphics editors like Adobe Photoshop, which manipulate images pixel by pixel, Illustrator uses mathematical formulas to create vector graphics. This allows designs to be scaled infinitely without losing quality, making it ideal for...
</description></item><item><title>Download Perfectly Clear WorkBench 5.0.2.3093</title><pubDate> Wed, 11 Feb 2026 21:05:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfectly-clear-workbench-6892.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfectly-clear-workbench-6892.html
</guid><description>
Perfectly Clear Workbench is an application that uses image editing libraries Perfectly Clear by Athentech and is provided to demonstrate the capabilities of the Perfectly Clear processing libraries, which recognize faces and allow quick export of processing settings for use.
One of the key features in Workbench is the ability to "export to API" when saving a Preset. This allows you to make image edits in Workbench and adjust the settings to suit your editing style and needs. You can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Google Chrome 145.0.7632.46</title><pubDate> Wed, 11 Feb 2026 21:05:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-chrome-1012.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-chrome-1012.html
</guid><description>
Google Chrome web browser is the most used today. Support surf the web, listen to music, watch movies, play web game effective no jerky lag with the internet connection stable. When you are surfing the web or performing an important task, whether it is operation big or small, work or entertainment, then Chrome has the smart features and the speed you need to make, create and explore on the net.
The latest version of Google Chrome is the third 114. But we are providing for users Google...
</description></item><item><title>Download RawDigger 1.4.10.845</title><pubDate> Wed, 11 Feb 2026 21:04:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rawdigger-3593.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rawdigger-3593.html
</guid><description>
RawDigger is a tool to visualize and examine raw data true as the camera has recorded. In essence, it is a type of microscope allows you to delve into the raw data. RawDigger does not change the raw data in any way. RawDigger is not a transition rough. Instead, it allows you to see the data that will be used by convertors rough.
RawDigger - Check the raw data the camera recorded
The features of RawDigger
	RawDigger displays a chart of the raw data, differs greatly from the chart and...
</description></item><item><title>Download MEmu Android Emulator 9.3.2.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 11 Feb 2026 21:04:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-memu-2975.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-memu-2975.html
</guid><description>
MEmu or also known as Android Emulator is the Android emulator light and free, allowing Windows users to enjoy Android experience the original on the computer and device Microsoft their. This app provides outstanding performance, allowing you to play on PC a series of games designed to run on Android devices. This app allows you to play the game favorite Android on larger screens, to bring you a better gaming experience.
MEmu - Android emulator, lightweight and free
Software MEmu also...
</description></item><item><title>Download System Mechanic Pro 26.0.1.81 + Standard</title><pubDate> Wed, 11 Feb 2026 21:04:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-system-mechanic-434.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-system-mechanic-434.html
</guid><description>
System Mechanic Pro is tool cleanup and repair errors on the system and restore hard drive and operating speed window.  System Mechanic helps you to clean your entire computer system, delete the unnecessary files, detect and repair the incident occurred due to virus attack or due to mistakenly deleted system files.
System Mechanic offers many useful features such as Registry cleaning, defragmenting computer memory, protect your privacy while accessing the Internet. With programs this...
</description></item><item><title>Download System Mechanic Ultimate Defense 26.0.1.81</title><pubDate> Wed, 11 Feb 2026 21:03:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-system-mechanic-ultimate-defense-1974.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-system-mechanic-ultimate-defense-1974.html
</guid><description>
System Mechanic Ultimate Defense is software provides tracking features anti browser and protect your online privacy, management, encryption and secure password protection, anti-virus certified, VB100, detect and remove malware on demand, technology, erase hard drive military grade, award-winning optimize PC, software, file recovery advanced.
Malware threats is growing fast now because of almost a million new viruses, worms, trojan horses, rootkits and other types of spyware, and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Able2Extract Professional 21.0.4.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 11 Feb 2026 21:02:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-able2extract-professional-3133.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-able2extract-professional-3133.html
</guid><description>
Able2Extract Professional is a PDF conversion only on the market to help increase efficiency, productivity PDF of you on Windows. Convert PDF format to Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Publisher, AutoCAD and CSV. Get photo create perfect PDF with the optional enhanced security and quickly modify text and page PDF. Fill in, edit and create the PDF form can be filled right in the Able2Extract or insert the order number on long PDF documents. All the tasks are performed in a user interface smooth...
</description></item><item><title>Download FX Math Tools Manifest 26.02.11</title><pubDate> Wed, 11 Feb 2026 21:02:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fx-draw-tools-multidocs-8814.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fx-draw-tools-multidocs-8814.html
</guid><description>
MultiDocs is a new way to create self-modifying Word documents. MultiDocs' amazing new document reproduction features allow you to create reproducible tests and quizzes in minutes. Get new numbers, new diagrams and even brand new solutions! MultiDocs combines the power of Word with two leading products: FX Draw and FX Equation in a new and exciting way.
Features of FX Draw Tools MultiDocs
	Create multiple documents: The software allows users to create multiple math and evaluation...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cutting Optimization Pro 5.18.20</title><pubDate> Wed, 11 Feb 2026 21:01:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cutting-optimization-pro-6573.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cutting-optimization-pro-6573.html
</guid><description>
Cutting Optimization Pro is a cutting software used to obtain the optimal cut layout for one-dimensional (1D) and two-dimensional (2D) pieces. The software also allows you to define and process complex products, such as desks, tables, cabinets, cabinets, bookshelves... Cutting Optimization Pro can be used to cut rectangular panels made of glass, wood, metal, plastic or any other material used in industrial applications.
Features of Cutting Optimization Pro
	Optimize 1D and 2D in the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft Office Pro Plus - Online Installer 3.3.11</title><pubDate> Wed, 11 Feb 2026 21:01:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-office-professional-plus-online-installer-7661.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-office-professional-plus-online-installer-7661.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft Office 2021 Professional Plus x86-x64 - Online Installer is a small script that helps users to download and install Microsoft Office 2021 Professional Plus including all updates directly from Microsoft CDN Server.
The version of Office 2021 downloaded and installed on your computer will include the following programs: Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Outlook, OneNote, Publisher, Access, Visio, Project, ProofingTools, OneDrive Desktop.
Usage:
Unzip the downloaded ZIP Archive...
</description></item><item><title>Download VSave 3.0.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 11 Feb 2026 21:00:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vsave-14404.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vsave-14404.html
</guid><description>
VSave is a video saving and editing app that lets you download videos from cloud storage services, import videos from your camera or library, and convert or edit video formats and attributes. It's compatible with major platforms including YouTube, NicoNico, Apple Music, Spotify, TikTok, Twitter, and other video, audio, and social media websites. It supports downloading playlists, shows, channels, individual songs, and entire albums. Save content permanently in high quality without data...
</description></item><item><title>Download EdrawMax Portable 15.1.4.1481 Ultimate</title><pubDate> Wed, 11 Feb 2026 21:00:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-edraw-max-portable-4301.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-edraw-max-portable-4301.html
</guid><description>
Edraw Max Portable is software that diagrams all in one, helping simplify the creation of professional looking diagrams, organizational chart, network diagrams, business presentations, building plans, mind mapping, illustration, science, fashion designs, UML diagrams, workflows, program structure diagrams, web design diagrams, electrical engineering, map orientation, diagram database and much more.
Edraw Max Portable - mapping professional
With the large library is drawing available...
</description></item></channel></rss>