<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 11:33:59 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 11:33:59 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Daemon Tools Lite 12.3.0.2361</title><pubDate> Sat, 11 Oct 2025 13:17:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-daemon-tools-lite-3391.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-daemon-tools-lite-3391.html
</guid><description>
DAEMON Tools Lite is based on two key features, simulation of virtual disks and building the file disk image as iso. DAEMON Tools Lite can emulate up to 4 virtual drives, DVD, CD or Blu-ray on your computer. The virtual units will be present in your system the same as the unit. After you select the virtual drive you want, you will choose a disc image (nrg, iso, mdf, bin, cue, etc.) that you want to mount. Visit My Computer at the device have The mobile storage and you will find the disk...
</description></item><item><title>Download Executor 2.1.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 11 Oct 2025 13:12:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-executor-271.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-executor-271.html
</guid><description>
Executor for windows is a software alternative premium customization features for the Windows "Run" and "Search Programs". When you press WIN + Z and provides the search results instant, as-you-type for any keywords you enter. By default, Executor will index all the Desktop and Start Menu and you can easily expand the search range by adding the folder location additional.
Executor for windows
The program comes with a list of commands built in which you can use to quickly access many...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Substance 3D Stager 3.1.5 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Sat, 11 Oct 2025 13:12:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-substance-3d-stager-6624.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-substance-3d-stager-6624.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Substance 3D Stager is a professional staging tool for designing and rendering scenes. Import content, arrange your scene, apply materials and textures, adjust both image-based and physical lighting, save the camera with different resolutions, and render realistic images , all in Stager!
Substance 3D Stager allows you to make creative decisions in context. Tweak and adjust your compositions in real time. Build your realistic 3D scenes with smart tools quickly and efficiently. With...
</description></item><item><title>Download lessmsi 2.10.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 11 Oct 2025 13:11:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lessmsi-12392.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lessmsi-12392.html
</guid><description>
Lessmsi (Less MSIerables) is a free and portable application that allows users to view and extract the contents of MSI files.
How does it work? Files with the .msi extension are not as widely used as their .exe cousins, but both contain programs for Windows. The main difference between them is that the latter does not always come with an installer, while it comes standard with the former. However, there will be cases where you just need to view or want to extract specific content from...
</description></item><item><title>Download Steinberg Dorico Pro 6.1.10</title><pubDate> Sat, 11 Oct 2025 13:11:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-steinberg-dorico-4929.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-steinberg-dorico-4929.html
</guid><description>
Steinberg Dorico help you write musical notation, automatically generated results are printed with exceptional quality - and playback with realism spectacular. Steinberg Dorico easy enough for anyone to learn, but there are hundreds of symbols, features, options and advanced audio to satisfy even the most demanding professionals.
With the user interface itself is streamlined, students and those less experienced in recording scores can be composed and arranged straight into Dorico, help...
</description></item><item><title>Download Telegram for Desktop 6.2.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 11 Oct 2025 13:10:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-telegram-3376.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-telegram-3376.html
</guid><description>
Telegram is an instant messaging service and voice over IP services on the cloud platform. Client application Telegram is available for Android, iOS, Windows Phone, Windows NT, macOS, and Linux. Users can send messages and exchange photos, videos, stickers, audio and files of any kind.
Telegram - Messaging and free phone calls
Telegram seamless sync across all your devices and can be used on desktop, tablet and phone. You can send unlimited amount of messages, photos, videos and files...
</description></item><item><title>Download The Dude 7.20.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 11 Oct 2025 13:10:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-the-dude-3238.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-the-dude-3238.html
</guid><description>
The Dude is a new application by MikroTik which can dramatically improve the way you manage your network environment. It will automatically scan all devices in the subnet is specified, draw and layout a map of your networks, monitor services of your devices and alert you in case some service has problems.is a new application by MikroTik which can dramatically improve the way you manage your network environment. It will automatically scan all devices in the subnet is specified, draw and...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinPaletter 1.0.9.7</title><pubDate> Sat, 11 Oct 2025 13:09:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winpaletter-7537.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winpaletter-7537.html
</guid><description>
WinPaletter lets you color the accents of Windows 10 and 11 without restrictions thanks to an easy-to-use interface. Personalizing your Windows PC made easy with WinPaletter; it gives you the ability to change almost every aspect of how your screen appears. The interface is modern and lists color change options for title bars, accents and more.
WinPaletter makes changing the color of Windows elements as simple as possible. You can also save your mix to a theme file. You can have...
</description></item><item><title>Download ARES Commander 2026.2 SP2 Build 26.2.1.3150</title><pubDate> Sat, 11 Oct 2025 13:09:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ares-commander-4235.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ares-commander-4235.html
</guid><description>
ARES Commander is professional software to help you create and modify DWG drawings in 2D and 3D on your computer. Take advantage of features drafting and design that you expect for the file DWG its with the cost savings significantly. ARES Commander bring your productivity to new heights with productivity tools, smart and a special concept: the Trinity of CAD. ARES Commander offers interface and feel familiar, intuitive for any user CAD have any experience. More than one solution...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tomabo MP4 Downloader Pro 5.8.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 11 Oct 2025 13:08:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tomabo-mp4-downloader-pro-3602.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tomabo-mp4-downloader-pro-3602.html
</guid><description>
Tomabo MP4 Downloader Pro is the app designed exclusively for Windows users to help them download videos from the Internet. In addition, it also increase download speeds by up to 500%, or even more. Tomabo MP4 Downloader Pro, interface design, simple, well-organized, beautifully. Here, users can view a list of videos has download with gravatar, URL, quality, duration and size of them. Software allows download video series at the same time, at the same time, support create a list of clips...
</description></item><item><title>Download Foxmail 7.2.25.489</title><pubDate> Sat, 11 Oct 2025 13:08:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-foxmail-2142.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-foxmail-2142.html
</guid><description>
Foxmail is free software that functions to manage email, such as automatic check mail and new email notifications. Foxmail new looks fresh clean and brings clarity to the entire experience. You know good design when you use it. Foxmail new looks fresh clean and brings clarity to the entire experience. You know good design when you use it.
Foxmail - Email Management
Use the notepad function Foxmail, you can record while working, easily organize information useful. Foxmail will keep all...
</description></item><item><title>Download O&amp;amp;O Defrag Pro 30.0.1058</title><pubDate> Sat, 11 Oct 2025 13:07:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-o-o-defrag-pro-149.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-o-o-defrag-pro-149.html
</guid><description>
O&amp;amp;O Defrag Pro is the professional software has the ability to defragment the hard disk and can work with the file system different from FAT / 32 to NTFS / 5, and support for the different arrays Volume / Stripe Sets. You can also set the schedule which O &amp;amp; O Defrag will be booted and perform a number of manipulation certain. Regular defragmentation of the disk partition optimized performance of your computer. The user interface is very easy to use. It has a ribbon bar displays all...
</description></item><item><title>Download Desktop.Calendar.Tray.OK 4.44</title><pubDate> Sat, 11 Oct 2025 13:07:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopcalendartrayok-2837.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopcalendartrayok-2837.html
</guid><description>
Desktop.Calendar.Tray.OK is one of the alternatives they can choose to use instead of the calendar app Windows. A plus point of the Desktop.CalWiki.Tray.OK is it possible to calculate the difference in the number of days between selected date and current date. In other words, only by clicking on a specific date, users can find out the number of weeks and days until that date. This feature is useful when you schedule appointments and meetings.
Desktop.Calendar.Tray.OK - the calendar App...
</description></item><item><title>Download DM Disk Editor and Data Recovery (DMDE) 4.4.0.828</title><pubDate> Sat, 11 Oct 2025 13:07:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dm-disk-editor-and-data-recovery-9139.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dm-disk-editor-and-data-recovery-9139.html
</guid><description>
DM Disk Editor and Data Recovery (abbreviated as DMDE) is a great program for searching, editing and recovering data on disk. This software is used to search, edit and recover data on disk. File system: FAT12/16, FAT32, NTFS. OS: Windows 9x/ME/2K/XP/Vista, Console versions for DOS, Linux. Direct disk access under DOS.
DMDE has many freeware features such as a disk editor, a simple partition manager (i.e. allowing partition recovery), a disk image and clone tool, a RAID creator and...
</description></item><item><title>Download O&amp;amp;O Defrag Server 30.0.1058</title><pubDate> Sat, 11 Oct 2025 13:07:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-defrag-server-2521.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-defrag-server-2521.html
</guid><description>
O&amp;amp;O Defrag Server professional software has the ability to defragment the hard disk and can work with the file system different from FAT / 32 to NTFS / 5, and support for the different arrays Volume / Stripe Sets. You can also set the schedule which O &amp;amp; O Defrag will be booted and perform a number of manipulation certain. Regular defragmentation of the disk partition optimized performance of your computer. The user interface is very easy to use. It has a ribbon bar displays all the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tray Radio 14.0.5.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 11 Oct 2025 13:06:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tray-radio-3135.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tray-radio-3135.html
</guid><description>
Tray Radio is a small radio running in the system tray and provides quick access to many international radio. You can right-click on the tray icon to select radio stations by country or quickly launch the radio favorite by only one click. Tray Radio can be used to record the current playback and saved as MP3 files on your hard drive.
Tray Radio - Listen to live Radio
&amp;nbsp;
Other features include a media player integrated to play the file locally to your preferred stations, the hot...
</description></item><item><title>Download Jailer 16.9.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 11 Oct 2025 13:01:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jailer-3196.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jailer-3196.html
</guid><description>
Jailer is a tool to reset the database, schema and browse data. It the sets of continuous, intact reference from the database relations. It removes outdated data without violating integrity. Theory is that force majeure DBMS (using JDBC), platform-independent and tạobộ data DbUnit , XML has hierarchical structure and SQL-DML is arranged in the link structure.
Jailer - Installed back to the database
Database Jailer is growing both in scale and complexity to meet the growing needs of...
</description></item><item><title>Download MultiPar 1.3.3.5 beta</title><pubDate> Sat, 11 Oct 2025 12:55:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-multipar-12575.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-multipar-12575.html
</guid><description>
MultiPar provides multi-functional file and folder protection and more. It will perform file verification, error correction, error detection and recovery to protect your files and folders from deletion, downloading, copying, software and hardware errors, virus infections, tampering Malicious and all kinds of other data corruption can make your day. You can also create an Archive that can be used to check file integrity or to recover damaged documents.
Features of MultiPar
	Friendly,...
</description></item><item><title>Download THR DeBleed 1.1.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 11 Oct 2025 12:54:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thr-debleed-11867.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thr-debleed-11867.html
</guid><description>
deBleed is not a traditional noise gate! It was designed from the ground up to effectively eliminate cymbal bleed while still allowing Kicks, Snares and Toms to resonate without affecting their tone.
Why use deBleed?
Other methods to remove cymbal hum have always relied on the use of high-cut filters, but this significantly affects the tone of the snare and even the kick because they remove so much higher frequencies which are an integral part of those components (especially...
</description></item><item><title>Download TGRMN Software VVEngine Server Premium 3.0.3002</title><pubDate> Sat, 11 Oct 2025 10:03:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tgrmn-software-vvengine-server-premium-14221.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tgrmn-software-vvengine-server-premium-14221.html
</guid><description>
What is VVEngine?
VVEngine is an advanced profile scheduler for ViceVersa PRO. It is developed by TGRMN Software, the company behind ViceVersa PRO. VVEngine works seamlessly with ViceVersa PRO. It is specially designed to run all your profiles automatically.
Advanced Scheduler for ViceVersa
VVEngine makes managing and scheduling multiple profiles very easy. Each profile can be scheduled separately and profiles can be grouped into categories.
Simplified user interface via standard Web...
</description></item><item><title>Download NTCL Soft Enhanced section views creation Plus 1.1.6.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 11 Oct 2025 10:00:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ntcl-soft-enhanced-section-views-creation-plus-14220.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ntcl-soft-enhanced-section-views-creation-plus-14220.html
</guid><description>
This application is designed for individual section views, allowing for detailed control and precise layout, ideal for creating plot-ready sheets and addressing common issues associated with large blank areas on drawings. Creating section views in Autodesk® Civil 3D® is complex with many parameters. This application will help to simplify the task of viewing cross-sections by using individual cross-section views and adds the following features…
	The Bandset title of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Visual Studio Code 1.105.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 10 Oct 2025 17:05:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-visual-studio-code-3182.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-visual-studio-code-3182.html
</guid><description>
Visual Studio Code is the encryption tool of Microsoft has met most of the needs of the developer. Environment this encoding was introduced to compete with other products such as Sublime and Nodepad ++ . Microsoft, in its new product, has not been released in many years, has provided many features in a simple environment. In addition to the familiar with a dozen programming languages, the syntax and get to know coding language as soon as be encrypted and allows for syntax highlighting, it...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ant Download Manager Pro 2.16.0 Build 91579</title><pubDate> Fri, 10 Oct 2025 17:05:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ant-download-manager-pro-137.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ant-download-manager-pro-137.html
</guid><description>
Ant Download Manager Pro is software support download has the same features as IDM, even it has many prominent features, more user friendly more and have speed download data incredible. Ant Download Manager is a Internet content downloader quickly with support download at video! Function: fully Integrated with the web browsers most popular: Internet Explorer 8+, Mozilla Firefox 32 +, Google Chrome 31+ and the copies of them (Pale Moon, Opera, Vivaldi, Slimjet, ComodoDragon, etc.). you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Google Chrome 141.0.7390.77</title><pubDate> Fri, 10 Oct 2025 17:04:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-chrome-1012.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-chrome-1012.html
</guid><description>
Google Chrome web browser is the most used today. Support surf the web, listen to music, watch movies, play web game effective no jerky lag with the internet connection stable. When you are surfing the web or performing an important task, whether it is operation big or small, work or entertainment, then Chrome has the smart features and the speed you need to make, create and explore on the net.
The latest version of Google Chrome is the third 114. But we are providing for users Google...
</description></item><item><title>Download ON1 Photo RAW MAX 2026 v20.0.4.17586</title><pubDate> Fri, 10 Oct 2025 17:03:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-on1-photo-raw-max-10717.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-on1-photo-raw-max-10717.html
</guid><description>
ON1 Photo RAW MAX 2024 is powerful photo editing software that provides photographers with many tools and features to enhance and edit their images. With a user-friendly interface, it offers advanced editing capabilities, including non-destructive editing, AI-powered adjustments, and precise control over color and tone. It also supports raw files from over 800 cameras and works with JPEG, TIF, PSD, PSB, PNG and DNG files. Additionally, it also includes photo organization tools to manage...
</description></item></channel></rss>