<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 15:43:08 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 15:43:08 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Internet Download Manager (IDM) 6.42 Build 56</title><pubDate> Wed, 26 Nov 2025 16:03:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-inetnet-download-manager-161.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-inetnet-download-manager-161.html
</guid><description>
Internet Download Manager is the download acceleration software, the best download support now, it can help you speed up the download up to five times, continue and schedule downloads. The latest version of IDM adds the compatibility of Windows 10 and Windows 11, it has supported all current popular browsers such as Internet Explorer, Mozilla Firefox, Opera, Google Chrome, ..
Download IDM with the latest version on taiwebs.com making it easy to download and manage your downloaded files...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ant Download Manager Pro 2.16.3 Build 92038</title><pubDate> Wed, 26 Nov 2025 16:02:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ant-download-manager-pro-137.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ant-download-manager-pro-137.html
</guid><description>
Ant Download Manager Pro is software support download has the same features as IDM, even it has many prominent features, more user friendly more and have speed download data incredible. Ant Download Manager is a Internet content downloader quickly with support download at video! Function: fully Integrated with the web browsers most popular: Internet Explorer 8+, Mozilla Firefox 32 +, Google Chrome 31+ and the copies of them (Pale Moon, Opera, Vivaldi, Slimjet, ComodoDragon, etc.). you...
</description></item><item><title>Download IDM Retail 6.42 Build 56</title><pubDate> Wed, 26 Nov 2025 16:02:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-internet-download-manager-retail-3609.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-internet-download-manager-retail-3609.html
</guid><description>
IDM - Internet Download Manager Retail is a reliable utility and high efficiency will help you to increase your download speed and manage download at better. The program allows you to easily schedule, pause and resume downloads with a single click. Moreover, the application provides error resilience robust and can restart the download at the interrupted or broken. You can restore the download is interrupted due to network problems, lost connections, unexpected power outages, computer...
</description></item><item><title>Download StartAllBack 3.9.18.5341</title><pubDate> Wed, 26 Nov 2025 16:01:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-startallback-6857.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-startallback-6857.html
</guid><description>
With the official release of Windows 11, chances are that most of you want to try it out. As the name suggests, StartAllBack is a small, lightweight tool that can help you enjoy the power of the new operating system while keeping the look and feel, especially because main work area, desktop of Windows 7, Windows 10 as taskbars and start menu styles.
StartAllBack is specially designed for Windows 11 and will not work on any older operating systems. If you want to get the start menu back...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube Downloader 3.9.18 (2411)</title><pubDate> Wed, 26 Nov 2025 16:00:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube Downloader  is a dedicated software that helps users  downloading youtube videos  Favorites on PC for offline viewing. With MediaHuman YouTube  Downloader  you can download videos from youtube website to your computer with  fast speed , with special software development technology that automatically receives videos from Websites, in addition to the ability to download videos from software websites, can convert downloaded video formats to various formats for the purpose...
</description></item><item><title>Download Supremo 4.11.6.2934</title><pubDate> Wed, 26 Nov 2025 16:00:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-supremo-2334.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-supremo-2334.html
</guid><description>
Supremo is a powerful solution, simple and full for control the desktop remotely. It allows you to control a remote PC or host a meeting in seconds. Interface Supremo with USilio control Panel , computer management.
Supremo - control your computer remotely
Features of Supremo
	Supremo include a file single executable very light and does not require installation. It's fast and author to the test.
	Supremo encrypting data stream with AES-256 algorithm and interface with USilio control...
</description></item><item><title>Download Typora 1.12.4</title><pubDate> Wed, 26 Nov 2025 15:59:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-typora-6764.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-typora-6764.html
</guid><description>
Typora gives you a seamless experience as both a reader and a writer. It removes the preview window, the mode switcher, the syntax symbols of the markup source code, and all other unnecessary distractions. Instead, it provides an actual live preview to help you focus on the content itself.
Features of Typora:
	Typora allows you to manage your files easily, providing both a file tree panel and a side panel (file list).
	Automatically view the Outline structure of your document in the...
</description></item><item><title>Download R-Studio 9.5 Build 191645 Network / Technician</title><pubDate> Wed, 26 Nov 2025 15:59:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-studio-1415.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-studio-1415.html
</guid><description>
R-Studio is a group of software data recovery and data recovery powerful and effective. -STUDIO is the solution to recover most comprehensive data for the file restored from the variants NTFS, NTFS5, ReFS, FAT12 / 16/32, exFAT, HFS / HFS + (Macintosh), Little and Big Endian of UFS1 / UFS2 (FreeBSD / OpenBSD / NetBSD / Solaris) and Ext2 / Ext3 / Ext4 partition FS (Linux).
R-Studio is also used to recover file raw (scan known file types) for the file system is damaged or not determined. It...
</description></item><item><title>Download XYplorer (32 Bit) 27.20.0700</title><pubDate> Wed, 26 Nov 2025 15:58:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-portable-12066.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-portable-12066.html
</guid><description>
XYplorer Portable is a file management software application that provides a comprehensive set of features for organizing and managing files and folders on your computer. This is a portable version of XYplorer that you can run directly from a portable storage device, such as a USB drive, without installation.
XYplorer Portable Features
	File Management: XYplorer Portable provides a two-window interface, allowing you to view and work with two folders at the same time. It provides easy...
</description></item><item><title>Download Free YouTube Download 4.4.45.1124 Premium</title><pubDate> Wed, 26 Nov 2025 15:58:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-download-1177.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-download-1177.html
</guid><description>
Free YouTube Download Premium is the most popular application to download videos from YouTube. The program was released in 2006 and regularly updated since then. Use the program to download and convert YouTube videos to view offline anytime.
Free YouTube Download - added Support to download youtube
Download more videos! Save whole playlists and YouTube channels, videos from a playlist individually (history, video be favorite, favourites, Watch later), videos from many different...
</description></item><item><title>Download O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Premium 22.0.1122</title><pubDate> Wed, 26 Nov 2025 15:57:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-diskimage-server-4547.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-diskimage-server-4547.html
</guid><description>
O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Server is software that is specially designed for use in enterprise environments, the software allows users to backup all the files you want and keep them safe from any incident or disaster computer. O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Server comes with a variety of easy to use utility that allows users to backup entire partitions of the specific files from their PC, as well as recover the version previous data of them, all from a simple interface.
O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Server - data...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter 3.9.18 (2411)</title><pubDate> Wed, 26 Nov 2025 15:56:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-to-mp3-converter-1744.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-to-mp3-converter-1744.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter is the software support download youtube video and convert video to mp3 format fast and most simple. MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter allows you download and convert videos from YouTube and other websites to MP3 format by pasting the YouTube URL into the application. When you paste the URL, the program will display thumbnails for videos and you have the option to customize the title information, artist and album before you begin the process of...
</description></item><item><title>Download XYplorer 28.00.0800 Beta</title><pubDate> Wed, 26 Nov 2025 15:56:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-533.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-533.html
</guid><description>
XYplorer - File Manager for Windows is software that supports users to manage files on the Window quickly and to arrange the folder tidy. XYplorer features tabbed browsing, search, files, powerful, preview, flexible, highly customizable interface, dual frame options and a variety of unique ways to automate effective tasks often repeat. It's fast, lightweight, and portable.
Features XYplorer
	XYplorer is a file manager mobile. It does not require any settings, store all configuration...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tenorshare 4DDiG Windows Backup 1.1.0.22</title><pubDate> Wed, 26 Nov 2025 15:55:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tenorshare-4ddig-windows-backup-14219.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tenorshare-4ddig-windows-backup-14219.html
</guid><description>
Backup files, partitions, or computers to computers or external devices. Full system backup to keep your system safe. Restore a specific partition from a full backup to save time. Task management console for easy backup.
Backup data with just one click
	PC backup: Delete, overwrite, corruption, or sudden crash can cause data loss. To keep your data safe, easily create a backup of your files, partitions, drives, or system with 4DDiG Windows Backup. Create a backup task, choose what you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Dassault Systemes DraftSight Enterprise Plus 2026 SP0</title><pubDate> Wed, 26 Nov 2025 15:55:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-draftsight-enterprise-plus-4057.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-draftsight-enterprise-plus-4057.html
</guid><description>
DraftSight Enterprise Plus solution is a 2D and 3D CAD feature-rich for architects, engineers and suppliers of construction services, as well as user professional CAD designers, educators and hobbyists. Options, options and tools consistent with the needs and specific interests of you. Freedom of design is really lets you work the way you want to work. It is the ability to easily switch from 2D sketch to 3D models and back to optimize and maximize the design.
DraftSight Enterprise Plus...
</description></item><item><title>Download Fast Video Cutter Joiner 6.9.3</title><pubDate> Wed, 26 Nov 2025 15:54:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fast-video-cutter-joiner-7542.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fast-video-cutter-joiner-7542.html
</guid><description>
Fast Video Cutter Joiner is a fast video cutter and joiner with an easy to use interface. It allows users to trim parts of a video quickly while maintaining the quality of the original video. It supports various formats like AVI, MPEG, MP4, WMV, 3GP, FLV...
This tool helps you to cut video files into small parts, to keep only the parts you need and remove unwanted parts like trailers and advertisements in a movie. The clips you cut can then be used for other video productions or for a...
</description></item><item><title>Download PilotEdit Pro 20.5.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 26 Nov 2025 15:54:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pilotedit-979.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pilotedit-979.html
</guid><description>
PilotEdit is software edit the textfile to help you execute scripts, extract strings and edit large files. PilotEdit is the editing file will help you search and replace multi-line text, edit files, FTP or even download and upload files and folders FTP. With edit file PilotEdit becomes easier.
PilotEdit - edit text files
PilotEdit is a hex-editor and advanced text support opening files larger than 4GB. It provides syntax to customize and highlight keywords, advanced search and replace...
</description></item><item><title>Download Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium 4.4.45.1124</title><pubDate> Wed, 26 Nov 2025 15:53:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-to-mp3-converter-premium-844.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-to-mp3-converter-premium-844.html
</guid><description>
Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium version is a software used to convert YouTube to MP3, extract audio from playlists YouTube, show listings, charts, video responses, channels, favorites of the user. With Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium, you can download and convert playlists, channels, stream original tv series and get them into iTunes at the same time.
Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium - convert YouTube to MP3
Features Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium from the...
</description></item><item><title>Download DMSoft DBConvert for Access and SQLite 1.1.9</title><pubDate> Wed, 26 Nov 2025 15:53:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dmsoft-dbconvert-for-access-and-sqlite-11362.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dmsoft-dbconvert-for-access-and-sqlite-11362.html
</guid><description>
DMSoft DBConvert for Access and SQLite provides solutions that support conversion from SQLite to Microsoft Access databases (.mdb or .accdb format) and synchronization between them in any combination. It's full of features that make moving and syncing work as quick and easy as possible.
Main features:
	Supported linked tables
	SQLite version 3.0 and above is supported
	MS Access Working Group
	Speed ​​conversion with Batch and Quantize features
	Query access to MS SQL, MySQL and...
</description></item><item><title>Download reaConverter Pro 8.0.160</title><pubDate> Wed, 26 Nov 2025 15:53:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html
</guid><description>
reaConverter Pro is software image processing feature with batch conversion and image editing periodically becomes simple. eaConverter also provide command line utilities allow you to process images automatically, thus helping you shorten the time for other work.
reaConverter Pro integrated powerful tool of Uber with many great features. It provides advanced solutions to process and adjust images. Management of the conversion process the base image with the latest version of...
</description></item><item><title>Download R-Studio Agent 9.5 Build 1696</title><pubDate> Wed, 26 Nov 2025 15:52:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-studio-agent-7164.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-studio-agent-7164.html
</guid><description>
R-Studio Agent is a handy and reliable utility that works in conjunction with R-Studio and creates remote connections over the network to recover files. The principle of R-Studio Agent is simple: it runs on the computer from which you want to recover files, while R-Studio is deployed on another computer and performs the actual recovery.
R-Studio Agent is installed on the computer that needs to recover files over the network. It can be installed remotely on a computer running...
</description></item><item><title>Download Executor 2.1.9</title><pubDate> Wed, 26 Nov 2025 15:52:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-executor-271.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-executor-271.html
</guid><description>
Executor for windows is a software alternative premium customization features for the Windows "Run" and "Search Programs". When you press WIN + Z and provides the search results instant, as-you-type for any keywords you enter. By default, Executor will index all the Desktop and Start Menu and you can easily expand the search range by adding the folder location additional.
Executor for windows
The program comes with a list of commands built in which you can use to quickly access many...
</description></item><item><title>Download ChromeCookiesView 1.85</title><pubDate> Wed, 26 Nov 2025 15:51:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chromecookiesview-2341.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chromecookiesview-2341.html
</guid><description>
ChromeCookiesView is an alternative to the view cookies internal standard of Google Chrome browser Web. it displays the list of all cookies stored by Google Chrome browser Web and allows you to easily delete cookies unwanted. It also allows you export the cookies into text / csv / html / xml. For each cookie, the following information is displayed: host Name, Path, Name, value, Secure (Yes / No) Cookies only HTTP (Yes / No), Time last accessed, Time created, Time...
</description></item><item><title>Download DMSoft DBSync for Access and MSSQL 4.2.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 26 Nov 2025 15:51:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dmsoft-dbsync-for-access-and-mssql-11361.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dmsoft-dbsync-for-access-and-mssql-11361.html
</guid><description>
DMSoft DBSync for Access and MSSQL is a powerful cross database migration tool to increase the size and synchronize Access x86/x64 data with MS SQL Server. It performs database conversion from Access 32/64 versions to Microsoft SQL Server/Windows Azure SQL Database and vice versa. Other move combinations are also supported. This tool provides direct conversion but when you need to overcome firewalls, MS SQL Dump files can be created. DBConvert software can automatically convert MS Access...
</description></item><item><title>Download Abelssoft SendMe (Send2Phone) 2025 v7.0 Build 3</title><pubDate> Wed, 26 Nov 2025 15:50:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-abelssoft-send2phone-2198.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-abelssoft-send2phone-2198.html
</guid><description>
Abelssoft Send2Phone is a program that allows you to send files from personal computer to phone your mobile, you can now easily share links, images, any files from PC to mobile or vice versa. Traffic will be encrypted using AES-256, so the authors assure you that you should not worry about blocking data, but I won't believe in a hundred percent. Thanks to the user interface simple, clear and pleasant. you can send the file just by a click of the mouse, the software can be integrated into...
</description></item></channel></rss>