<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 20:00:47 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 20:00:47 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download IObit Uninstaller Pro 15.0.0.4</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 21:02:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iobit-uninstaller-pro-339.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iobit-uninstaller-pro-339.html
</guid><description>
IObit Uninstaller Pro is software to delete programs not needed easily even when Windows "Remove Programs" operation not successful. IObit Uninstaller Pro will uninstall the app Windows, browser toolbars, software packages and plug-ins added. It comes with a scan function is powerful and a tool, Force Uninstall, both of which help to easily and completely remove the app stubborn, and the excess useless, to release more disk space.
With IObit Uninstaller Pro you will have peace of mind...
</description></item><item><title>Download CCleaner Pro 6.39.11548 / Business / Technician</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 21:01:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ccleaner-pro-57.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ccleaner-pro-57.html
</guid><description>
CCleaner Pro - Help your computer faster, more secure and more reliable
CCleaner Pro by Piriform is a program quick and easy to use help your computer faster, more secure and more reliable. CCleaner delete cookies, temporary files and many data do not use other clog the operating system of you. This frees up disk space value lets your system run quickly over. Deleting this data also protects your anonymity you mean you can browse online more securely. The built in Registry Cleaner fixes...
</description></item><item><title>Download CCleaner Professional Plus 6.39</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 21:00:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ccleaner-professional-plus-5532.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ccleaner-professional-plus-5532.html
</guid><description>
CCleaner Professional Plus is a collection of the latest program versions from Piriform Software, unified in a common envelope, that will help you make your computer faster, safer and more functional. Its dynamic stability and security. CCleaner Professional Plus: a 4 in 1 product that includes all Professional versions of CCleaner, Defraggler, Recuva and Speccy! With our patented technology products, you can regain full control of your PC and keep it working like new: make it faster and...
</description></item><item><title>Download ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro 15.25.0820</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 21:00:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-videotube-downloader-pro-1276.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-videotube-downloader-pro-1276.html
</guid><description>
ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro is the professional version support download videos and playlists from YouTube, videos from Dailymotion, BBC iPlayer, ITV Player, ABC,  FOX,CBS.com Vimeo, Prosieben, Metacafe, Blip.tv CBC.ca many more video sites. After the video is downloaded, you can convert them to the formats compatible with iPad, iPhone, iPod, MPEG-4, H. 264, MP3, AC3.
ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro - Download videos on Youtube
This is one of the software download the most...
</description></item><item><title>Download EASEUS Partition Master Professional Edition 19.9.0 Build 202508180953</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 21:00:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-partition-master-professional-edition-3459.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-partition-master-professional-edition-3459.html
</guid><description>
EASEUS Partition Master Professional Edition is a utility software powerful and full will help you to better manage hard drives and partitions by yourself. This application includes three main functions, such as Program instructions for copying disk and partition, manager partition and wizard restore partition. Moreover, the program allows you to create CD or DVD that can boot, to help you recover the system in case of no boot.
EASEUS Partition Master Professional Edition is the most...
</description></item><item><title>Download Joyoshare VidiKit 3.0.0.66</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 20:59:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-joyoshare-vidikit-6345.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-joyoshare-vidikit-6345.html
</guid><description>
Joyoshare VidiKit is software that helps users to switch, cut and put videos easily and quickly. You can record the screen and audio from online video sites. Powerful editing tools for creating blur, subtitles, cropping and more. Cutting the videos is easily specified with precision to every millisecond and provides the most possible way to serve the different needs of the user.
Features of Joyoshare VidiKit
	Convert, cut and merge videos easily and fast
	Record screen and audio from...
</description></item><item><title>Download Assimilate Scratch 9.8.1187</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 20:59:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-assimilate-scratch-2812.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-assimilate-scratch-2812.html
</guid><description>
Assimilate Scratch is a program that is designed to handle digital images in the film, as well as a great tool for digital post-production. This software combines many useful tools, then you and the ability to re-create documents and coordinate work, edit, perform color correction and digital layout, you can maintain and tweak it all in a user interface only. This way you can combine all of your efforts and increase your productivity. Have support to work with project resolution up to...
</description></item><item><title>Download doPDF 11.9.503</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 20:58:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dopdf-923.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dopdf-923.html
</guid><description>
doPDF is software that converts any printable document how to PDF format. doPDF acts as a virtual printer for PDF documents. The program installs as a printer driver virtual and can be accessed from any application which supports printing.
doPDF which allows users to create PDF documents by choosing "Print" from any application and with only a single operation, you can convert your document such as Microsoft Excel, Word, PowerPoint or the email and the address of your favorite websites to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Security Task Manager 3.1d</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 20:58:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-security-task-manager-493.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-security-task-manager-493.html
</guid><description>
Security Task Manager is management software task program window for you to know the performance is the use of the software. Security Task Manager provides ratings, risk, security, process description, file path, chart, CPU usage, start time, hidden functions embedded. The software also lets you know the ability to the process is the spyware potential malware, Trojan or keylogger.
Security Task Manager also delete traces of Internet activity and your computer, stop monitoring keyboard...
</description></item><item><title>Download EASEUS Partition Master WinPE Edition 19.9.0 Build 202508180953</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 20:57:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-partition-master-winpe-edition-3460.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-partition-master-winpe-edition-3460.html
</guid><description>
EASEUS Partition Master WinPE Edition is a version plugins help you to create a disk partition on WinPE for you to easily recover hard drive partition computer if not may broken or error. Boot disk EasUS Partition Master WinPE, format software mobile, you can:
	Works well in Windows, such as extend system partition or settling low disk space and managing disk space, recovery partition deleted , rebuild MBR, restore partition GPT, etc.
	You are allowed to resize the primary drive to...
</description></item><item><title>Download EASEUS Partition Master Unlimited Edition 19.9.0 Build 202508180953</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 20:57:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-partition-master-unlimited-edition-3458.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-partition-master-unlimited-edition-3458.html
</guid><description>
EASEUS Partition Master Unlimited Edition is a partition solution all-in-one and tool kit, disk management PC &amp;amp; Server reliable, especially for large enterprise users. It allows unlimited usage within your company. Just a few clicks to re-partition your hard drive, SSD, USB, flash drive, memory card, SD card, memory card and many other storage devices in Windows 10, 8.1, 8, 7, Vista, XP and Windows Server 2016, 2012, 2008, 2003. EASEUS Partition Master Unlimited Edition extend...
</description></item><item><title>Download Gilisoft DRM Protection 8.7.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 20:57:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-video-drm-protection-5260.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-video-drm-protection-5260.html
</guid><description>
Gilisoft Video DRM Protection is software that helps you can protect your videos and the E-Learning content to another by secure, encrypted the files, your content and distribute them to the target audience authorized of you. Very easy to make video / sound / pictures of you can't see are for anyone except those you allow. Gilisoft Video DRM Protection can encrypt and pack video &amp;amp; codec &amp;amp; player into exe.
Gilisoft Video DRM Protection can easily encode almost any kind of Video...
</description></item><item><title>Download The Foundry Katana 8.0v4</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 20:56:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-the-foundry-katana-2046.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-the-foundry-katana-2046.html
</guid><description>
The Foundry Katana is a 3D application specifically designed for the demand interface development and lighting in a pipe based on the property. First developed at Sony Pictures Imageworks, The Foundry Katana is the core tool of them to grow and glow for all of their products since Spider-Man 3, Beowulf and Surf's Up!. Katana provides a framework very general to develop and efficient lighting, with the goal of scalability, flexibility.
The Foundry Katana - a 3D design application
The...
</description></item><item><title>Download EaseUS Partition Master Technican Edition 19.9.0 Build 202508180953</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 20:56:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-partition-master-350.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-partition-master-350.html
</guid><description>
EaseUS Partition Master is software partition management all-in-one be used to redistribute capacity hard drive with high performance and keep all PC, laptop and server running perfect performance. Engineering software master partition deals with all the task partition in an effective way without loss of data. Just a few clicks to re-partition your hard drive, SSD, USB, flash drive, memory card, SD card, memory card and many other storage devices in Windows 10, 8.1, 8, 7, Vista, XP and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Argente Registry Cleaner 4.0.2.5</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 20:56:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-argente-registry-cleaner-13814.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-argente-registry-cleaner-13814.html
</guid><description>
Argente Registry Cleaner is a free Windows utility designed to scan, clean and repair invalid or obsolete entries in the Windows Registry, helping to improve system stability and performance. This utility quickly analyzes the entire Registry for errors such as invalid entries left by uninstalled programs, missing keys, broken references, and other junk that can cause system crashes.
Key Features:
	Fast and Thorough Scan: Provides multiple scan modes including Safe (fastest), Normal...
</description></item><item><title>Download AVG Clear 25.8.10387</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 20:50:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avg-clear-4945.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avg-clear-4945.html
</guid><description>
AVG Clear is free program help completely erase everything from installing AVG current your including the registry entries, file, settings, files, users, etc. AVG Clear is provided by AVG and is the last measure to use if you encounter a problem when deleting AVG current whether it is error repair, reinstall, or delete altogether.
Please note that all user settings AVG will be removed after the uninstall process is complete. The items should be deleted to include content from Virus...
</description></item><item><title>Download PVS-Studio 7.38.97034.1959</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 20:50:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pvs-studio-1480.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pvs-studio-1480.html
</guid><description>
PVS-Studio is software that performs static code analysis and generate a report to help programmers find and fix bugs. PVS-Studio implements a series of check code, it is also useful to search the prints wrong error and Copy-Paste. Examples of such errors: V501, V517, V522, V523, V3001.
The main value of static analysis is in regular use, hence the error is identified and corrected at the earliest stages. There's no point of wasting 50 hours to search for a fault can be found with static...
</description></item><item><title>Download EASEUS Partition Master Server Edition 19.9.0 Build 202508180953</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 20:49:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-partition-master-server-edition-3457.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-partition-master-server-edition-3457.html
</guid><description>
EASEUS Partition Master Server Edition is a powerful program that allows you to solution delete, create, merge, resize / move, split the partition to use better the full capacity of the hard drive. EasUS Partition Master Server Edition is the partition manager packed full of features and includes three main functions: The recovery guide partition manager partition and wizard restore partition.
These tools will enhance the management of your hard drive and will help you to use disk space...
</description></item><item><title>Download Avast Clear 25.8.10387</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 20:48:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avast-clear-4437.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avast-clear-4437.html
</guid><description>
Avast Clear is a utility to remove accurately and completely line product anti-virus AVAST. Avast to leave a lot of garbage behind the computer and in the register. In particular, the registry hassle can, for example, can be an obstacle to install a program anti-virus Avast other then. In such cases, you can use a special utility Avast!
Avast Clear - Uninstall program Avast
Recommended avoid any inconvenience, should always engage the help of a dedicated tool to know where to search...
</description></item><item><title>Download Argente Malware Cleaner 3.0.2.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 19:01:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-argente-malware-cleaner-13494.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-argente-malware-cleaner-13494.html
</guid><description>
Argente Malware Cleaner is a lightweight utility designed to detect and remove a wide range of malware, including spyware, adware, Trojans and other threats that can compromise your privacy and data. It works as a complementary tool alongside your main antivirus software, helping to detect malware that may slip through the cracks.
Key features of Argente Malware Cleaner include:
	Easy-to-use, clean, and user-friendly interface that suits both casual and advanced users.
	Deep scanning...
</description></item><item><title>Download Argente System Repair 1.0.2.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 19:01:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-argente-system-repair-13813.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-argente-system-repair-13813.html
</guid><description>
Argente System Repair is a lightweight utility designed to diagnose and fix common Windows system problems. It scans your system to identify errors in operating system components, file systems, installation files, and other system components, and then applies targeted fixes to resolve these problems. The tool provides different scan modes, including simple scan, recommended scan, and custom scan, allowing users to customize the repair process according to their needs.
System Repair...
</description></item><item><title>Download CCleaner Browser 139.0.31477.68</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 19:00:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ccleaner-browser-1851.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ccleaner-browser-1851.html
</guid><description>
Piriform, the company produces CCleaner - software cleanup system popular on Windows, has launched Chromium browser new of his own name CCleaner Browser. New browser comes with every feature have been Google's Chrome, and is integrated ad blockers. CCleaner Browser interface is quite similar to Google Chrome, the difference is the appearance of the icon CCleaner familiar on the bar enter the address of the browser, that's all.
CCleaner Browser - web browser ad blocker
In CCleaner...
</description></item><item><title>Download CPU-Z for Android 1.52</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 18:56:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-cpu-z-for-android-9218.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-cpu-z-for-android-9218.html
</guid><description>
CPU-Z for Android is a popular system information and monitoring tool that is available for Android devices. It is developed by CPUID, the same company behind the popular CPU-Z tool for desktops.
CPU-Z for Android provides detailed information about the device's hardware and system, including the CPU, GPU, RAM, storage, and battery. It also provides real-time monitoring of CPU and GPU usage, temperature, and clock speed, which can be useful for troubleshooting and optimizing...
</description></item><item><title>Download SD Maid 2/SE - System Cleaner 1.4.16-beta1</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 18:56:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sd-maid-2se-system-cleaner-10472.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sd-maid-2se-system-cleaner-10472.html
</guid><description>
SD Maid 2/SE - System Cleaner is a reliable helper for your Android, keeping the device clean &amp;amp; orderly. SD Maid SE has optional features that use the AccessibilityService API to automate tedious actions. Using the AccessibilityService API, SD Maid SE can click buttons for you to perform cross-app operations, for example, clear cache. SD Maid SE does not use the AccessibilityService API to collect information.
No one is perfect and neither is Android
	Apps you deleted will leave...
</description></item><item><title>Download All Document Reader and Viewer 2.8.4</title><pubDate> Wed, 20 Aug 2025 18:56:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-all-document-reader-and-viewer-8877.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-all-document-reader-and-viewer-8877.html
</guid><description>
All Document Reader: PDF, excel, word, Documents is a smart office application that helps you read all documents downloaded from the internet, supports reading PDF files, PDF Reader, doc, docx xls, ppt, txt, excel, xlxs files... fast, easy and convenient.. All Document Reader: PDF, excel, word, Documents are providing multiple Document reading features including PDF Reader, Docs Reader &amp;amp; Docx, ppt reader, xls reader, txt, excel &amp;amp; documents different from readers.
All Document...
</description></item></channel></rss>