<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 15:35:24 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 15:35:24 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download UPDF 2.0.11</title><pubDate> Sat, 18 Oct 2025 17:44:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-updf-14160.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-updf-14160.html
</guid><description>
UPDF for Windows is easy-to-use PDF software for Windows! Enjoy powerful editing tools for text, images, links, and more in your PDFs. Customize backgrounds, watermarks, and page sizes as easily as in Word. AI-powered PDF editor and manager that offers a wide range of features including editing, annotating, converting, OCR (Optical Character Recognition), organizing, protecting, sharing, printing, summarizing, translating, and interpreting PDF files.
Features of UPDF
Analyze PDFs with...
</description></item><item><title>Download MassTube 2026 v21.0.3.169 Ultra</title><pubDate> Sat, 18 Oct 2025 17:43:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-masstube-plus-461.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-masstube-plus-461.html
</guid><description>
MassTube Plus is a small utility used to download the favorite videos of you on youtube on your computer. This is a software compact, has a simple design with few options to download videos fastest. The you complete peace of mind because the software is easy to use, built exclusively for a single goal: to retrieve the video file from YouTube, so it doesn't pack the other useful features such as search engine integrated and a download audio file.
MassTube can work with multiple output...
</description></item><item><title>Download Robin YouTube Video Downloader Pro 6.17.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 18 Oct 2025 17:42:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-video-downloader-pro-2828.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-video-downloader-pro-2828.html
</guid><description>
YouTube Video Downloader Pro is a Windows application professional to download and convert videos from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion and thousands of video sharing sites, other. It accelerates your download up to 5 times. YouTube Video Downloader Pro allows you to download multiple videos at the same time. It also allows you to pause, resume and cancel a download at any time.
YouTube Video Downloader Pro - Download online videos on social networks
Features of YouTube Video Downloader...
</description></item><item><title>Download Converseen 0.15.1.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 18 Oct 2025 17:42:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-converseen-7644.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-converseen-7644.html
</guid><description>
Converseen is a free cross-platform batch image processor for Windows and Linux that allows you to convert, resize, rotate, and flip countless images with just one click. Moreover, Converseen can convert an entire PDF file into a series of images with the characteristics you like: you can choose one of more than 100 formats, you can set the size, resolution and name file.
Conversion, thanks to ImageMagick, the powerful image manipulation library on which the program is based, can...
</description></item><item><title>Download HE - Hardware Read and Write Utility 1.25.10.17</title><pubDate> Sat, 18 Oct 2025 17:41:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-he-hardware-read-and-write-utility-4287.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-he-hardware-read-and-write-utility-4287.html
</guid><description>
HE - Hardware Read and Write Utility is a powerful utility intended for hardware engineer, engineer, BIOS developer, driver, engineer, QA engineers, performance test engineers, diagnostic, etc., this utility access almost all the computer hardware, including PCI (PCI Express), index / Data, PCI, memory, index memory / Data space I / O, Index I / O / Data, Super I / O, DIMM SPD, CPU The registers MSR, screen, SMART, physical area of the hard drive identification data, ATA, dump tables ACPI...
</description></item><item><title>Download AI Video Upscaler Pro 1.2.7</title><pubDate> Sat, 18 Oct 2025 17:40:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ai-video-upscaler-pro-14184.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ai-video-upscaler-pro-14184.html
</guid><description>
Break new life into your old or low-resolution videos with AI Video Upscaler Pro. This powerful and private desktop application uses advanced artificial intelligence to enhance and upscale your video files, bringing incredible new levels of detail and clarity. Designed with privacy at its core, AI Video Upscaler Pro works 100% offline after a one-time setup. Your video files will never be uploaded to the cloud or shared with anyone, ensuring your content stays under your control on your...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Acrobat Reader DC 2025.001.20813</title><pubDate> Sat, 18 Oct 2025 17:39:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-acrobat-reader-3707.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-acrobat-reader-3707.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Acrobat Reader DC is a system of application software and Web services developed by Adobe Systems to view, create, manipulate, print and manage PDF files. With Adobe Acrobat Reader DC, you can create, export, edit, and track PDF files from anywhere - and maintain connection with the recent set of files on all your devices.
Adobe Acrobat Reader current DC is connected with Adobe Document Cloud - help working on the computers and mobile devices becomes easier than ever before. This is...
</description></item><item><title>Download SSD Booster .NET 18.33</title><pubDate> Sat, 18 Oct 2025 17:39:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ssd-booster-net-7375.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ssd-booster-net-7375.html
</guid><description>
SSD Booster .NET is our perfect tool to optimize and adjust Windows for the SSD drive to increase performance and maintain the highest performance for your SSD. In addition, the app comes with the system information tab for information about the hardware and operating system of your machine. To check your specifications, move to the Introduction and find the System Information button.
Features of SSD Booster .NET
	The perfect tool to optimize and adjust Windows for the SSD drive to...
</description></item><item><title>Download VCap Downloader Pro 0.1.38.6764</title><pubDate> Sat, 18 Oct 2025 17:38:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vcap-downloader-pro-8474.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vcap-downloader-pro-8474.html
</guid><description>
VCap Downloader Pro (VCapDL) is a popular piece of software that allows you to record video and audio from websites on the internet. The interface of the software is similar to a normal browser, making it easy for users to get used to and work with this software. User just need to copy video url from favorite browser and convert it to VCap Downloader Pro. It will capture the video and make the quality available for download. You can also extract the audio track from any video and convert...
</description></item><item><title>Download BoostPing 1.6.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 18 Oct 2025 17:33:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-boostping-12519.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-boostping-12519.html
</guid><description>
BoostPing helps optimize your online gaming experience by modifying the network throttling index and disabling the Nagle algorithm. By turning this feature off, you can achieve more instantaneous data transfer speeds, potentially reducing latency.
What is Nagle's algorithm?
The Nagle algorithm is designed to improve network efficiency by combining small data packets into larger packets, which can cause lag in online games. Disabling it can result in more responsive gameplay. On the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Certificate Manager 18.33</title><pubDate> Sat, 18 Oct 2025 17:33:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-certificate-manager-13958.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-certificate-manager-13958.html
</guid><description>
Certificate Manager provides an in-depth overview of your current certificates, allowing you to easily access detailed information. It also provides functions for both exporting existing certificates and importing new certificates, enhancing your certificate management capabilities.
Application certificates are often overlooked by most users until problems arise during application installation. For the average end user, there is little reason to focus on application certificates....
</description></item><item><title>Download System Utilities 1.3.8.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 18 Oct 2025 17:32:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-system-utilities-10394.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-system-utilities-10394.html
</guid><description>
System Utilities as its name suggests, contains a collection of tools that can help you maintain your system easily. It can scan your drive for storage, help you quickly uninstall programs, as well as manage startup applications and clean up unnecessary data.
Features of System Utilities
	Scan and organize all the folders on your PC to create more space.
	Uninstall all programs that you do not use. Get rid of data junk on your computer.
	Determine which programs should start...
</description></item><item><title>Download BBE Sound Sonic Sweet 4.7.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 18 Oct 2025 17:31:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bbe-sound-sonic-sweet-5850.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bbe-sound-sonic-sweet-5850.html
</guid><description>
BBE Sound Sonic Sweet is a complete rewrite of the plugins that are included in the original "Sonic Sweet" plug-in package. Designed to make your harmonos clearer and larger like its predecessor, it adds a new fourth addition to the collection, Mach 3 Bass. The centerpiece of the product is still the software version of BBE's famous Sonic Maximiser, which is a simulation of their proprietary processing technologies that set the standard for advanced sound. World-renowned musicians have...
</description></item><item><title>Download BBE Sound Stomp Board 1.7.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 18 Oct 2025 17:31:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bbe-sound-stomp-board-9735.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bbe-sound-stomp-board-9735.html
</guid><description>
BBE Sound Stomp Board is a guitar effects pedal board manufactured by BBE Sound Inc., a company known for manufacturing sound processors, pedals and technology. sound enhancement. Stomp Board is designed to give guitarists a portable and flexible solution for accessing a variety of effects in a single device.
Stomp Board has a sturdy housing that houses multiple effects pedals in a compact design. It incorporates BBE's proprietary sound reinforcement technology, which aims to improve...
</description></item><item><title>Download Spatial Manager Desktop 10.0.1.17275</title><pubDate> Sat, 18 Oct 2025 17:30:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-spatial-manager-desktop-10319.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-spatial-manager-desktop-10319.html
</guid><description>
Spatial Manager Desktop is a software application designed to work with spatial data and geographic information systems (GIS). It is a comprehensive and reliable software solution developed to assist you in successfully managing the spatial data required in planning, infrastructure or construction projects. It is primarily used to manage, import, export, and manipulate spatial data from various sources. Spatial Management Desktop provides tools and features to help work with geographic...
</description></item><item><title>Download Omidsoft System Information 18.33</title><pubDate> Sat, 18 Oct 2025 17:29:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-omidsoft-system-information-12255.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-omidsoft-system-information-12255.html
</guid><description>
System Information is a general Windows utility to display many useful information about Windows, Network and hardware - CPU information, PCI information, PCMCIA information, USB information, SMBus information, SPD information , ACPI method, machine information, hardware sensors, networked computer, operating system information, etc.
System Information is a simple yet highly effective tool designed for individuals who want to gain comprehensive insight into their computer systems. While...
</description></item><item><title>Download Vladovsoft Hotel 16.5.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 18 Oct 2025 17:29:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vladovsoft-hotel-6008.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vladovsoft-hotel-6008.html
</guid><description>
Vladovsoft Hotel is an easy-to-use, affordable hotel management software. It tracks all delivery, sales, booking and dining and helps your hotel management more easily than ever.
Features of Vladovsoft Hotel
	Activities with non-limited product and service numbers
	Activity with no limited number of rooms, reservation and accommodation
	Work with operators with different user rights
	The forms for making delivery and sales
	Activity with bar code scanner and bar code reader
	Can be...
</description></item><item><title>Download FinalMesh Professional 6.2.0.678</title><pubDate> Sat, 18 Oct 2025 17:28:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-finalmesh-professional-1278.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-finalmesh-professional-1278.html
</guid><description>
FinalMesh Professional is a software easy and powerful the incredible to create PDF document with 3D or the website WebGL. FinalMesh Professional will help your 3D model will be converted into application WebGL complete HTML or PDF with 3D content. In addition, FinalMesh is viewer and 3D switch with amazing user interface modern, fast and has many useful features.
FinalMesh Professional
The function of FinalMesh Professional
The 3D viewer
	Lighting in pixels
	Display mode...
</description></item><item><title>Download Daemon Tools Lite 12.3.0.2362</title><pubDate> Sat, 18 Oct 2025 17:28:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-daemon-tools-lite-3391.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-daemon-tools-lite-3391.html
</guid><description>
DAEMON Tools Lite is based on two key features, simulation of virtual disks and building the file disk image as iso. DAEMON Tools Lite can emulate up to 4 virtual drives, DVD, CD or Blu-ray on your computer. The virtual units will be present in your system the same as the unit. After you select the virtual drive you want, you will choose a disc image (nrg, iso, mdf, bin, cue, etc.) that you want to mount. Visit My Computer at the device have The mobile storage and you will find the disk...
</description></item><item><title>Download Steinberg Groove Agent 5.2.30</title><pubDate> Sat, 18 Oct 2025 17:28:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-steinberg-groove-agent-9154.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-steinberg-groove-agent-9154.html
</guid><description>
Steinberg Groove Agent is a virtual drum software tool designed for music production and beat creation. It was developed by Steinberg, a German music software company best known for its digital audio workstation (DAW) software, Cubase.
Steinberg Groove Agent is a versatile drum sampler that allows users to create and control drum sounds and samples for a wide range of genres, from electronic music (EDM) to hip-hop to rock. It includes a large library of drum sounds and samples, as well...
</description></item><item><title>Download Superluminal Performance 1.0.7115.1289</title><pubDate> Sat, 18 Oct 2025 17:27:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-superluminal-performance-12585.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-superluminal-performance-12585.html
</guid><description>
Superluminal is a sophisticated sampling analyzer designed to enhance the performance analysis of applications, especially in environments using C++, C# and Rust. Its unique features enable developers to efficiently visualize performance data without intrusive code modifications.
Features
	The best visualization technology allows you to discover and identify performance issues with minimal effort.
	Commenting your code is meant to be biased towards where you think the problem is,...
</description></item><item><title>Download TheSage 7.70.2822</title><pubDate> Sat, 18 Oct 2025 17:27:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thesage-2794.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thesage-2794.html
</guid><description>
TheSage has full name is TheSage English Dictionary and Thesaurus is a complete dictionary and thesaurus of the English language. It runs locally and does not use your Internet connection. The program provides a screen that has unique structure, as well as searching wildcard, anagram search and much more.
TheSage - English dictionary
During the installation process, you selected install dictionary English TheSage and dictionary in the usual way, or create a mobile version. Create...
</description></item><item><title>Download Internet Video Downloader 7.9.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 18 Oct 2025 17:21:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hdapplications-hd-downloader-6041.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hdapplications-hd-downloader-6041.html
</guid><description>
Internet Video Downloader is a small tool designed to help you download video clips from YouTube, Dailymotion and many other similar sites with high quality that can easily run on smartphones, tablets or the latest Xbox devices. After the quick and simple installation process, you will be welcomed by a user-friendly interface without the ability to cause any problems for you.
Although you can set the app start to download immediately, but you can also create a download list that can be...
</description></item><item><title>Download Edge Remover 18.33</title><pubDate> Sat, 18 Oct 2025 17:21:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-edge-remover-7689.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-edge-remover-7689.html
</guid><description>
Edge Remover is our mini user interfaceless tool to permanently remove Microsoft Edge from your system. Easily remove Microsoft Edge browser from your system, with just one click, with this simple, no UI app.
Features of Edge Remover
	Remove MSEdge and its components
	Prevent reinstalling MSEdge on your system
Requirements:
Operating System: Microsoft Windows 7 or later
Framework: Microsoft .NET Framework 4.0
</description></item><item><title>Download Benthic Golden 8.2.0.822</title><pubDate> Sat, 18 Oct 2025 17:20:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-benthic-software-golden-4113.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-benthic-software-golden-4113.html
</guid><description>
Benthic Software Golden is a query tool for Oracle database. It includes the possibility of advanced queries, edit data and ability to import and export powerful, including support for Excel spreadsheet and Calc. It features compatibility closely with sqlplus estimate scenario consists of the variable binding, variable prompting and parameter scripts to go through. Benthic Software Golden can export directly to Excel files xls and xlsx. Exports can be scripted and run automatically using...
</description></item></channel></rss>