<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 21:36:07 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 21:36:07 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Q-Dir 12.36</title><pubDate> Wed, 08 Oct 2025 00:02:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-q-dir-348.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-q-dir-348.html
</guid><description>
Q-Dir is software to manage the entire file and folder on the computer, allowing to see file in same time 4 different positions (viewport quadro) while still maintaining all the standard features of the Explorer.
It also provides a variety of management features, additional files included the filter file color-coding, layouts and columns can be customized, quick access to file and folder favorites and more.
Other features of Q-Dir , including directory listings (.txt, .doc .html .csv),...
</description></item><item><title>Download CyberLink PowerDirector Ultimate 2026 v24.0.1003.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 08 Oct 2025 00:01:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-powerdirector-ultimate-425.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-powerdirector-ultimate-425.html
</guid><description>
CyberLink PowerDirector Ultimate is software editor, edit video and make movies on the computer from a variety of templates are made available, complete with effects, transitions, animations, and music. CyberLink PowerDirector 17 is a combination of video editing software with advanced video editing features powerful. Cblowing need to add your clips into the time line and click on 'Production'!
The tool design video in CyberLink PowerDirector have the ability to customize helps you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ashampoo Photo Commander 19.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 08 Oct 2025 00:01:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-photo-commander-273.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-photo-commander-273.html
</guid><description>
Ashampoo Photo Commander software brings user photo management tool effectively cover view, sort, edit, convert photos and images to the web. Ashampoo Photo Commander 16 will surprise you immediately! Interface modern user will quickly learn the features of your favorite and adjust accordingly for faster access. The slideshow images appear in the mode 4K stunning and the panoramic feature will steals the show.
Ashampoo Photo Commander - photo editing
Software Ashampoo Photo Commander...
</description></item><item><title>Download Photo Supreme 2025.3.3.8109</title><pubDate> Wed, 08 Oct 2025 00:00:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photo-supreme-430.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photo-supreme-430.html
</guid><description>
Photo Supreme is a software product management professional pictures of idimager. With Photo Supreme you can arrange, manage back stock photo archive of yourself and share them with you here and relatives easily via Email or Facebook. Photo Supreme provides users method to sort images effective, logical, as well as edit and share your photos with friends and relatives in the family. Especially the Photo Supreme allows to work with multiple image formats and support mounting support,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Quick n Easy Web Builder 12.2.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 08 Oct 2025 00:00:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quick-n-easy-web-builder-2924.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quick-n-easy-web-builder-2924.html
</guid><description>
Quick 'n Easy Web Builder is a web development application that lets you easily create websites using drag and drop. This application is the building tool website What What You See Is What You Get (WYSIWYG). This program will create the HTML code for you and allows you to place different objects in any where on your website. These objects include shapes, slideshows, Text, Line, galleries, images, forms and more. Using this software, you will be able to easily create the website without the...
</description></item><item><title>Download AllMapSoft Offline Map Maker 8.355</title><pubDate> Tue, 07 Oct 2025 23:59:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-offline-map-maker-656.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-offline-map-maker-656.html
</guid><description>
AllMapSoft Offline Map Maker is software create, organize, offline map from Google Maps, Yahoo maps, Bing maps and Openstreetmap. You can view offline maps downloaded with map viewer offline. And you can zoom out or zoom in the offline map or export map under the file format .BMP with file world xxx.bpw, and can output files xxx.map for OziExplorer. If you want to make a offline map of your city by yourself, it is very useful for you.
Features AllMapSoft Offline Map Maker
	You can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Imposition Wizard 3.6.7</title><pubDate> Tue, 07 Oct 2025 23:59:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-imposition-wizard-3645.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-imposition-wizard-3645.html
</guid><description>
Imposition Wizard is software apply PDF with integrated Adobe Acrobat, user interface simple, real-time preview and supports command line. Imposition Wizard created with simplicity in mind and features a user interface dead simple allows you to focus on your main task. Imposition Wizard comes with support for all the imposed standards, namely step and repeat,cut stack and diagram booklet, utilities the software will provide a variety of options when rearrange with shuffle feature page of...
</description></item><item><title>Download WhyNotWin11 2.7.0.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 07 Oct 2025 23:57:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-whynotwin11-6630.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-whynotwin11-6630.html
</guid><description>
WhyNotWin11 tells you if your machine is compatible with Windows 11 by running a small script. WhyNotWin11 runs through the currently known system requirements for Windows 11 and then gives you the results.
The results shown tell you:
	Boot Type
	CPU Generation/Core Count/Frequency
	Disk Partitioning
	RAM
	Secure Boot
	Storage&amp;nbsp;and whether or not TPM minimum is activated
	The interface provides clear results and is also color-coded.
</description></item><item><title>Download NoScript 13.1 Chrome + Firefox</title><pubDate> Tue, 07 Oct 2025 23:56:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-noscript-116.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-noscript-116.html
</guid><description>
NoScript is an add-ons extension Firefox , Google Chrome allows you to interactively block Java, JavaScript, Flash a one-click button.
You can choose to temporary block or allow scripts on the current web page and also allows the reliable site by you is excluded from any action to block any.
Whenever you visit a website, all content scripts potential invasive are blocked by default and you can select it on the basis of each script from the status bar of browsers like Google Chrome,...
</description></item><item><title>Download AllMapSoft Universal Maps Downloader 10.225</title><pubDate> Tue, 07 Oct 2025 23:55:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-universal-maps-downloader-736.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-universal-maps-downloader-736.html
</guid><description>
AllMapSoft Universal Maps Downloader is software download map images on the computer for offline viewing support many types such as Google Maps, Yahoo maps, Bing maps, OpenStreet Maps, Yandex Maps, Ovi Maps, MapQuest Maps. All the downloaded photos will be saved on disk. You can view downloaded maps by Maps Viewer Or you can combine them into one big bmp, or jpg file tif by Maps Combiner, and also you can export all the tiles into a database format MBTiles.
AllMapSoft Universal Maps...
</description></item><item><title>Download Symetri Naviate Suite for Autodesk Revit 2026</title><pubDate> Tue, 07 Oct 2025 20:54:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-symetri-naviate-suite-for-autodesk-revit-14213.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-symetri-naviate-suite-for-autodesk-revit-14213.html
</guid><description>
Naviate Accelerate provides advanced functionality for all Revit users. No matter what industry you work in, Accelerate helps you improve your BIM workflow by providing extended features in Revit and reducing manual tasks.
Naviate Analysis (now Daylight) easily automates daylight factor and daylight area ratio calculations in your BIM model to optimize lighting, window placement, and design elements. Easily create brighter, more comfortable working and living spaces.
Naviate...
</description></item><item><title>Download ImageMagick 7.1.2-5</title><pubDate> Tue, 07 Oct 2025 17:26:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-imagemagick-1319.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-imagemagick-1319.html
</guid><description>
ImageMagick is software image processing command line to create, edit, compose, or convert bitmap images. ImageMagick is completely free for users and you easily download it on taiwebs.com. Typical functions most of software is able to read and write images in many formats (over 100) including DPX, EXR, GIF, JPEG, JPEG-2000, PDF, PhotoCD, PNG, Postcript, SVG, and TIFF.
ImageMagick - image Processing
The Windows version of ImageMagick is installed. Just click on the appropriate version...
</description></item><item><title>Download NPS Image Editor 4.4.1.7573</title><pubDate> Tue, 07 Oct 2025 17:25:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nps-image-editor-12735.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nps-image-editor-12735.html
</guid><description>
NPS Image Editor is a unique, free image editor that is perfect for pixel art, drawing, and photo editing. It is lightweight, customizable, and intuitive, yet incredibly powerful. The goal of NPS Image Editor is to provide the world with an easy-to-use image editing application that also allows me (as a developer) to learn new skills and improve my programming knowledge.
In addition, NPS Image Editor also includes an advanced color picker that can run standalone (without opening the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Internet Download Manager (IDM) 6.42 Build 49</title><pubDate> Tue, 07 Oct 2025 17:18:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-inetnet-download-manager-161.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-inetnet-download-manager-161.html
</guid><description>
Internet Download Manager is the download acceleration software, the best download support now, it can help you speed up the download up to five times, continue and schedule downloads. The latest version of IDM adds the compatibility of Windows 10 and Windows 11, it has supported all current popular browsers such as Internet Explorer, Mozilla Firefox, Opera, Google Chrome, ..
Download IDM with the latest version on taiwebs.com making it easy to download and manage your downloaded files...
</description></item><item><title>Download IDM Retail 6.42 Build 49</title><pubDate> Tue, 07 Oct 2025 17:17:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-internet-download-manager-retail-3609.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-internet-download-manager-retail-3609.html
</guid><description>
IDM - Internet Download Manager Retail is a reliable utility and high efficiency will help you to increase your download speed and manage download at better. The program allows you to easily schedule, pause and resume downloads with a single click. Moreover, the application provides error resilience robust and can restart the download at the interrupted or broken. You can restore the download is interrupted due to network problems, lost connections, unexpected power outages, computer...
</description></item><item><title>Download Soft Organizer Pro 10.32</title><pubDate> Tue, 07 Oct 2025 17:17:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-soft-organizer-498.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-soft-organizer-498.html
</guid><description>
Soft Organizer is versatile software just install the software to help uninstall software quickly and safely to release the hard drive or restore when necessary.  That side, Soft Organizer also keep track of the changes made to the system during installation of new utilities or help test the new version of the software on the computer to update timely, classification, and management of programs for users to follow easily.
Soft Organizer has a modern interface with simple manipulation to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Office Timeline Plus 11.28.00.00 Expert / Pro / Pro+ Edition</title><pubDate> Tue, 07 Oct 2025 17:16:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-timeline-2106.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-timeline-2106.html
</guid><description>
Office Timeline is an add-on very useful and powerful software for Microsoft PowerPoint. With add-ons, you can create PowerPoint documents look more beautiful. With add-ons, you can add the time Line on the project by yourself. Application time for the composition and different segments of the document, your PowerPoint will not only increase the beauty for your work, but also for customers and your manager. The people who created this product is also believe that add-ons this is the only...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cockos REAPER 7.48</title><pubDate> Tue, 07 Oct 2025 17:16:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cockos-reaper-889.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cockos-reaper-889.html
</guid><description>
Cockos REAPER is a powerful software for for windows, chp lets you record, arrange, edit, and display the audio waveform multi-track. Cockos REAPER offers an extensive feature set includes many effects and a sample project. REAPER supports ASIO, Kernel Streaming, WaveOut, and DirectSound for playback and recording. It reads the files in WAV, OGG and MP3 files and records WAV files. You can arrange any number of items in any number of tracks and use plug-in sound processing (DirectX and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Files Inspector Pro 4.41</title><pubDate> Tue, 07 Oct 2025 17:15:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-files-inspector-pro-2289.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-files-inspector-pro-2289.html
</guid><description>
Files Inspector is a software that allows you to analyze the data on the hard drive and delete the file obsolete, since it frees up space and improve performance of the system. Despite the fact that the hard drives are becoming cheaper and more voluminous, you have a place to store a large number of files are not really necessary in most cases, due to the repetition and simple data is outdated. If not maintained properly, you can fill the space trash and clean up will eventually become a...
</description></item><item><title>Download PingPlotter Professional 5.25.20.9089</title><pubDate> Tue, 07 Oct 2025 17:15:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pingplotter-professional-4090.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pingplotter-professional-4090.html
</guid><description>
PingPlotter Professional is monitoring software network graphics, drawing graphs latency and data packet loss for maximum hundreds of targets at the same time. It includes everything in PingPlotter Standard, plus tools to monitor multi-targets, communicating with other systems, and collect data remotely. PingPlotter Professional is accessed through interface like web browser. PingPlotter Pro check out hundreds of targets at the same time. Summary chart available to the organization goals...
</description></item><item><title>Download Reg Organizer 9.87</title><pubDate> Tue, 07 Oct 2025 17:14:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reg-organizer-1595.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reg-organizer-1595.html
</guid><description>
Reg Organizer is a software to scan and clean your registry windows register errors and help optimize performance computer system. Reg Organizer is a software subscription, professional, and professional, and any way that the Windows registry are necessary and therefore, the overall performance of Windows improves, there is this software.
Reg Organizer - registry Cleaning and pc optimization
The main features of Reg Organizer
	Cleaning the registry of the lock is not valid and not...
</description></item><item><title>Download ExpanDrive 2025.09.30</title><pubDate> Tue, 07 Oct 2025 17:09:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-expandrive-609.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-expandrive-609.html
</guid><description>
ExpanDrive is software sync cloud storage strong support BackBlaze B2, Google Team Drive, SMB / CIFS and new interface and easy user search file version, share links and much more.  ExpanDrive mapped network drives for macOS and Micosoft Windows connect with all the provide major cloud storage such as Dropbox, Google Drive, Google Team Drive, Amazon Drive, Box, OneDrive, OneDrive for Business, Sharepoint, Openstack Swift , BackBlaze B2, Amazon S3 or SFTP servers, FTP or WebDAV on your own...
</description></item><item><title>Download MusConv 4.10.424 Lifetime</title><pubDate> Tue, 07 Oct 2025 17:08:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html
</guid><description>
MusConv transfers playlists, albums, followed artists and liked songs across a variety of services – Spotify, Apple Music, Amazon Music, YouTube, YouTube Music, iTunes, Deezer, Tidal, SoundCloud, Pandora and more 125 music services!
Features of MusConv Ultimate
	Transfer playlists, albums, followed artists and liked tracks between over 125 music servicesManage playlists (Delete, Merge, Split, Copy...)
	More than 125 music services supported
	Access DAILY updated music charts on...
</description></item><item><title>Download HttpMaster Pro 6.2.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 07 Oct 2025 17:08:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-httpmaster-pro-1925.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-httpmaster-pro-1925.html
</guid><description>
A useful application for web developers who need to automate the test the web application by requesting multiple resources from a specified site web-based application. The professional version httpMaster in order to meet the requirements of many people when related to the test application. When working with HttpMaster Pro, most of the time you will manage the attributes and properties of the project HttpMaster of the items required in project. Project properties provides the global options...
</description></item><item><title>Download Telegram for Desktop 6.1.4</title><pubDate> Tue, 07 Oct 2025 17:08:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-telegram-3376.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-telegram-3376.html
</guid><description>
Telegram is an instant messaging service and voice over IP services on the cloud platform. Client application Telegram is available for Android, iOS, Windows Phone, Windows NT, macOS, and Linux. Users can send messages and exchange photos, videos, stickers, audio and files of any kind.
Telegram - Messaging and free phone calls
Telegram seamless sync across all your devices and can be used on desktop, tablet and phone. You can send unlimited amount of messages, photos, videos and files...
</description></item></channel></rss>