<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 12:32:25 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 12:32:25 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Perfectly Clear WorkBench 5.0.2.3107</title><pubDate> Sun, 22 Feb 2026 00:21:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfectly-clear-workbench-6892.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfectly-clear-workbench-6892.html
</guid><description>
Perfectly Clear Workbench is an application that uses image editing libraries Perfectly Clear by Athentech and is provided to demonstrate the capabilities of the Perfectly Clear processing libraries, which recognize faces and allow quick export of processing settings for use.
One of the key features in Workbench is the ability to "export to API" when saving a Preset. This allows you to make image edits in Workbench and adjust the settings to suit your editing style and needs. You can...
</description></item><item><title>Download StartAllBack 3.9.21.5360</title><pubDate> Sun, 22 Feb 2026 00:20:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-startallback-6857.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-startallback-6857.html
</guid><description>
With the official release of Windows 11, chances are that most of you want to try it out. As the name suggests, StartAllBack is a small, lightweight tool that can help you enjoy the power of the new operating system while keeping the look and feel, especially because main work area, desktop of Windows 7, Windows 10 as taskbars and start menu styles.
StartAllBack is specially designed for Windows 11 and will not work on any older operating systems. If you want to get the start menu back...
</description></item><item><title>Download Soda PDF Desktop Pro 15.0.08.24416</title><pubDate> Sun, 22 Feb 2026 00:20:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-soda-pdf-home-808.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-soda-pdf-home-808.html
</guid><description>
Soda PDF Pro  is intuitive PDF software that helps you to easily process and create PDF files from more than 300 different formats. Soda PDF is built to help you power through any PDF task. Convert to a wide range of file types. Edit the content of your document. Create custom forms. Annotate your files. Send and track contracts for electronic signatures.
Soda PDF Pro: Create PDF file
Features of Soda PDF Pro
	Read your PDFs and digital publications in 3D with unique page-turning...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube Downloader 3.9.18 (2102)</title><pubDate> Sun, 22 Feb 2026 00:18:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube Downloader  is a dedicated software that helps users  downloading youtube videos  Favorites on PC for offline viewing. With MediaHuman YouTube  Downloader  you can download videos from youtube website to your computer with  fast speed , with special software development technology that automatically receives videos from Websites, in addition to the ability to download videos from software websites, can convert downloaded video formats to various formats for the purpose...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft OneDrive 26.017.0126.0002</title><pubDate> Sun, 22 Feb 2026 00:18:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-onedrive-48.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-onedrive-48.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft OneDrive is a client application file transmission to the service cloud storage of Microsoft. If you are familiar with Dropbox, you will find that OneDrive works in a similar way. It creates a OneDrive folder and any files you copy into the folder will automatically be synced and uploaded to the cloud service OneDrive.
Microsoft OneDrive
You can access your files from the client application other on PC. Mac or mobile devices as well as web interface. OneDrive also allows you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tiny11 25H2 Build 26200.7840 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Sun, 22 Feb 2026 00:01:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tiny11-8649.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tiny11-8649.html
</guid><description>
Tiny11 is a compact Windows operating system based on Windows 11 Pro 22H2, Tiny11 has everything you need for a comfortable, hassle-free computing experience. cumbersome and messy like a standard Windows installation. The operating system requires only 8GB of disk space and 2GB of RAM, and requires no TPM (Trusted Platform Module) and Secure Boot support.
The main goal of Tiny11 is to extend the reach of systems that can access Windows 11. The custom edition can run on any system...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter 3.9.18 (2102)</title><pubDate> Sun, 22 Feb 2026 00:00:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-to-mp3-converter-1744.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-to-mp3-converter-1744.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter is the software support download youtube video and convert video to mp3 format fast and most simple. MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter allows you download and convert videos from YouTube and other websites to MP3 format by pasting the YouTube URL into the application. When you paste the URL, the program will display thumbnails for videos and you have the option to customize the title information, artist and album before you begin the process of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Acronis True Image Build 41810 Multilingual Bootable ISO</title><pubDate> Sat, 21 Feb 2026 23:59:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-acronis-true-image-bootable-iso-5344.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-acronis-true-image-bootable-iso-5344.html
</guid><description>
Acronis True Image for Windows PC for reliable backups because you always have reliable data copies so you can restore your entire system or individual files. Acronis True Image quickly restores your entire system or a specific file with confidence, knowing that the backup is just as good as the original.  Acronis True Image  will tell you everything about your backups at a glance. Monitor backup status, view file size and measure backup speed and view rendering.
Acronis True Image...
</description></item><item><title>Download Calibre 9.3.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 21 Feb 2026 23:58:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-calibre-1669.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-calibre-1669.html
</guid><description>
Calibre  is an eBook library management application that allows you to manage your eBook collection, convert eBooks between different formats, Sync with popular e-reading devices and read your e-books with included viewer. You can sort books by author, title, date and other details, download meta information and book covers, add personalized tags and comments, and view your images in the cover display.
Collection of essential tools for adding metadata editing books or managing your...
</description></item><item><title>Download Diffchecker 6.8.5</title><pubDate> Sat, 21 Feb 2026 23:58:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-diffchecker-5025.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-diffchecker-5025.html
</guid><description>
Diffchecker is a application compare text, images and powerful file to desktop of your. Available for Windows, macOS. Compare text files, documents, PDF. Compare photos, graphics. Because Diffchecker Desktop running entirely on your computer, so it does not have to communicate with our servers to create your difference. This means that there is no other way in addition you can view your sensitive data, you.
Diffchecker Desktop run offline, that means you can use it anytime, anywhere and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Professor Teaches QuickBooks 2024 v1.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 21 Feb 2026 23:56:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-professor-teaches-quickbooks-3893.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-professor-teaches-quickbooks-3893.html
</guid><description>
Professor Teaches QuickBooks offers interactive training, practice for QuickBooks 2019 and the version QuickBooks 2018 and 2017. Find out the features of Intuit QuickBooks Pro, plus basic accounting and business plan. Each course provides everything you need to learn the fundamentals of planning and business, and the latest version of QuickBooks.
Professor Teaches QuickBooks - Course sales, and business management
Accounting software small business top, QuickBooks, designed to help...
</description></item><item><title>Download JSoft PDF Reducer 8.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 21 Feb 2026 23:55:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jsoft-pdf-reducer-8994.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jsoft-pdf-reducer-8994.html
</guid><description>
JSoft PDF Reducer is a software application designed to compress and reduce the size of PDF files. The program provides many features and tools to optimize PDF files, such as removing unused objects, compressing images, and removing bookmarks and annotations. You are also allowed to rearrange, delete pages, add or remove text, and secure your PDF files with Watermarks, passwords and digital signatures. It's set up in a wizard format, so you'll be guided through the steps.
Features of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Database Tour Pro 11.6.3.1246</title><pubDate> Sat, 21 Feb 2026 23:55:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-database-tour-pro-5321.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-database-tour-pro-5321.html
</guid><description>
Database Tour Pro application is a comprehensive software that allows you to organize all the database is connected his. It provides support for Borland Database Engine (BDE) and Microsoft ActiveX Data Objects (ADO), SQL scripts, reports, along with conversion and data export, among others.
It contains a browser object for the function, package, triggers, folders, users, roles, profiles, sequences, work, style, Java, exception, link, database, general properties, table, schema, and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ideate Software Apps Bundle 2026.0 For Revit 2023-2026</title><pubDate> Sat, 21 Feb 2026 23:54:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ideate-software-apps-bundle-9460.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ideate-software-apps-bundle-9460.html
</guid><description>
Ideate Software provides a suite of applications specifically designed to enhance the capabilities of Autodesk Revit, a popular Building Information Modeling (BIM) software. The Ideate software application package includes many software applications that provide additional functionality and improve workflow in the Revit environment.
Linking Revit and Excel with Ideate BIMLink allows you to export data from Revit to Excel, streamlining data management tasks and significantly reducing...
</description></item><item><title>Download Imaginando VS 2.1.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 21 Feb 2026 23:53:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-imaginando-vs-11117.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-imaginando-vs-11117.html
</guid><description>
Take your music to another dimension with a captivating visual world. VS - Visual Synthesizer makes it easy to represent your sounds optically in a highly customizable way. At the core of Imaginando VS is a set of graphics shaders called materials, which render procedurally generated geometry in real time, based on each material's unique set of parameters. VS comes equipped with 50 beautifully hypnotic materials for you to customize and combine to create mesmerizing performances.
Visual...
</description></item><item><title>Download WAU Manager 3.8.6.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 21 Feb 2026 23:52:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wau-manager-2911.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wau-manager-2911.html
</guid><description>
WAU Manager (manager automatic updates of Windows) is an alternative full-featured for interface Windows Updates integrated. The program gives you full control over the Windows Updates, you can decide when and how they are installed and it provides support uninstall and full maintenance for the Windows updates.
WAU Manager - controls Windows update
With WAU Manager you can update Windows manually when want just by a click on the keyboard shortcuts for the desktop, you can update...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Lightroom Classic 2026 v15.2.0 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Sat, 21 Feb 2026 21:14:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-photoshop-lightroom-classic-0004-734.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-photoshop-lightroom-classic-0004-734.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Photoshop Lightroom Classic is a desktop-optimized photo editing and organizing software. Lightroom Classic gives you powerful one-click tools and advanced controls to make your photos look great. Easily organize all your photos on your desktop and share them in a variety of ways.
In addition, Lightroom Classic has a powerful import process that allows users to preview images before importing. It supports many camera raw formats and includes a database system for efficient photo...
</description></item><item><title>Download 4K Video Downloader Plus 26.0.5</title><pubDate> Sat, 21 Feb 2026 21:13:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-video-downloader-617.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-video-downloader-617.html
</guid><description>
4K Video Downloader Plus is software support downloads video, audio and subtitles from YouTube with high quality up to 4K. Download process video is very simple: just copy the video link from your browser and click Paste Url. Done! If you want that video on your iPad, iPhone or other device, we have protected you.
The feature on 4K Video Downloader Plus
	Download entire playlists and channels from YouTube and save them in MP4, MKV, M4A, MP3, FLV, 3G, create a file .m3u for...
</description></item><item><title>Download Franzis PANORAMA #1 professional 1.12.04374</title><pubDate> Sat, 21 Feb 2026 21:13:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-franzis-panorama-professional-14575.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-franzis-panorama-professional-14575.html
</guid><description>
Franzis PANORAMA Professional maximizes image potential by processing up to 60 individual images into a high-resolution, high-detail panorama. This ensures the highest image quality and maximum creative adaptability in the output. To meet the demands of various shooting scenarios, the dedicated panorama module offers six defined geometric projections to give each image the desired look.
PANORAMA #1 Professional simplifies and automates the entire process: Multi-row panoramas and special...
</description></item><item><title>Download pdfFactory Pro 9.23</title><pubDate> Sat, 21 Feb 2026 16:12:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdffactory-pro-277.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdffactory-pro-277.html
</guid><description>
pdfFactory Pro is software to create PDF files according to standards in a simple and secure documents secure. pdfFactory Pro on taiwebs.com that support encryption (40 or 128bit) and control access to the PDF file.
pdfFactory Pro has all the features of pdfFactory and adds bookmarks, job order, title a letter and the email function automatically. Only pdfFactory allows printing to paper or PDF without printing twice. Acrobat is not needed for the printing. Increases the convenience of...
</description></item><item><title>Download FinePrint 12.23</title><pubDate> Sat, 21 Feb 2026 16:11:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fineprint-276.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fineprint-276.html
</guid><description>
FinePrint is a software support you work in text saves paper and increases the lifespan of your printer. FinePrint is a software connected printer, you can print 4 or 8 pages file on the computer on a page of paper that still ensure the font is clear, easy to read.
With FinePrint works for you, the incidents of printing annoyances will disappear. Below are just some examples of incidents in which FinePrint can fix. Read more part of our Business for the benefit of the FinePrint in the...
</description></item><item><title>Download 4K YouTube to MP3 26.0.5</title><pubDate> Sat, 21 Feb 2026 16:10:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-youtube-to-mp3-622.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-youtube-to-mp3-622.html
</guid><description>
4K YouTube to MP3 is a software to convert video youtube to mp3 quickly and easily by the manipulation drag-and-drop simple. With 4K YouTube to MP3 you just drag and drop the link to the favorite songs of you and get the MP3 files to your computer, as easy as that. Transfer songs directly to iPod, iPhone and iPad everywhere you go. No install annoying and complex to solve, just a clean interface, user friendly and functional.
When using 4K YouTube to MP3, users will get the playlists,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Windows Server 2025 LTSC 24H2 Build 26100.32370 (x64) MSDN</title><pubDate> Sat, 21 Feb 2026 16:09:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-server-2025-12851.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-server-2025-12851.html
</guid><description>
Windows Server 2025 is a server operating system based on Windows 11, version 24H2 on the Long Term Servicing Channel (LTSC). It improves security, performance, and integration with Azure and cloud technologies. As an LTSC release, Windows Server 2025 includes Desktop Experience and Server Core installation options for the Datacenter and Standard editions. Security features that are part of the current Windows 11 release (24H2) are now available in Windows Server 2025.
Key...
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow WinIcon 3.2.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 21 Feb 2026 16:08:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winicon-maker-9761.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winicon-maker-9761.html
</guid><description>
WinIcon Maker is a simple application to create beautiful Windows icons (ico files) from JPG or PNG images. Just upload your own photo, resize and crop it, convert it to a shape you like, add borders and shadows, and save it as a PNG image or Windows icon.
The .ICO file format is defined and created by Microsoft corporation, .ico files are widely used in Windows operating systems including Windows 7, Windows 10, Windows 11, etc. On the Windows desktop, each application shortcut has an...
</description></item><item><title>Download AdwCleaner 8.7.1.626</title><pubDate> Sat, 21 Feb 2026 16:07:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-malwarebytes-adwcleaner-1132.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-malwarebytes-adwcleaner-1132.html
</guid><description>
Malwarebytes AdwCleaner is ad blocking software on the browser, which helps you completely remove the annoying stuff every time Internet access. The software is completely free for users, also AdwCleaner can remove unwanted software or virus on your computer.
When on the website is not secure, appearance various types of advertising PUP. Very can will appear on the website contain malicious code that when you click on the sensitive area, the virus infected computer very likely to happen....
</description></item></channel></rss>