<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 00:31:16 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 00:31:16 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download OnlyOffice Desktop Editors 9.3.0.140</title><pubDate> Thu, 26 Feb 2026 23:07:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-onlyoffice-7488.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-onlyoffice-7488.html
</guid><description>
OnlyOffice is a free office suite that can open documents, presentations, and spreadsheets in different tabs of the same window, providing interoperability Compatible with the most popular file formats. With an attractive intuitive interface and intuitive controls, OnlyOffice allows users to open documents, spreadsheets and presentations, or create new ones from scratch. It comes with support for the most common file formats, even those native to Microsoft's office suite. Moreover, it can...
</description></item><item><title>Download VMware Workstation Pro 25H2u1 v25.0.1.25219725</title><pubDate> Thu, 26 Feb 2026 23:00:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vmware-workstation-pro-29.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vmware-workstation-pro-29.html
</guid><description>
VMware Workstation Pro can change significantly the way of working with the virtual machine, and extremely useful to the developer.Workstation Pro has won many awards, user support when their operating system is not compatible, bringing experience use, feature-rich and efficient operation smoother.
VMware Workstation Pro help you leverage the tablet the latest Intel sensor tablet virtual Workstation. Used Microsoft Surface tablet with the accelerometer, gyroscope, compass and light...
</description></item><item><title>Download Perfectly Clear WorkBench 5.0.3.3117</title><pubDate> Thu, 26 Feb 2026 22:58:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfectly-clear-workbench-6892.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfectly-clear-workbench-6892.html
</guid><description>
Perfectly Clear Workbench is an application that uses image editing libraries Perfectly Clear by Athentech and is provided to demonstrate the capabilities of the Perfectly Clear processing libraries, which recognize faces and allow quick export of processing settings for use.
One of the key features in Workbench is the ability to "export to API" when saving a Preset. This allows you to make image edits in Workbench and adjust the settings to suit your editing style and needs. You can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Chaos Enscape 4.16.0.1262</title><pubDate> Thu, 26 Feb 2026 22:58:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-enscape-3d-4125.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-enscape-3d-4125.html
</guid><description>
Enscape 3D is the tool support simulation 3D for the software Revit, SketchUp, Rhino, ArchiCAD. With real-time technology of Enscape 3D your project is displayed in the form of walk-3D is fully displayed, can be navigated and explored from every angle, at every moment of the day. With direct link between Enscape 3D and CAD programs, you can track all updates for his plan immediately. More Enscape to your work to give yourself more time to create and innovate. Enscape 3D offers many options...
</description></item><item><title>Download Serato DJ Pro 4.0.3</title><pubDate> Thu, 26 Feb 2026 22:56:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-serato-dj-pro-169.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-serato-dj-pro-169.html
</guid><description>
Serato DJ Pro is software mix DJ music, professional support, sound effects, and combined to create music, Great DJ. Serato DJ Pro supports the sound effects such as Delay, Reverb, Flanger, Echo, PingPong Delay, Phaser, Distortion, High and Low Pass Filter, as well as combinations of them. Supports MIDI in full, be made in the program, providing the ability to adapt to the controller and program for every need. It allows you to use at the same time from two to four floors. Program Serato...
</description></item><item><title>Download Screenpresso Pro 2.2.4</title><pubDate> Thu, 26 Feb 2026 22:55:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-screenpresso-pro-1362.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-screenpresso-pro-1362.html
</guid><description>
Screenpresso Pro is a program easy to take great photos on your screen! Screenpresso blocked Print Screen key and screen capture the best in a few seconds. Allows you to capture windows and screen area, roll the part of the screen, edit the images obtained, add effects, resize a group of images, send screenshots by email and post them to Web resources.
Screenpresso Pro - Shooting the computer screen
Features of Screenpresso Pro
	Take the window and screen area. Take a partial screen...
</description></item><item><title>Download Yamicsoft Windows 11/10 Manager 2.3.3</title><pubDate> Thu, 26 Feb 2026 22:54:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yamicsoft-windows-11-manager-6779.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yamicsoft-windows-11-manager-6779.html
</guid><description>
Windows 11 Manager is an all-in-one utility for Microsoft Windows 11 specially, it includes over forty different utilities to optimize, tweak, clean up, speed up and repair your Windows 11, helps make your system perform faster, eliminate system fault, increase stability and security, personalize your copy of Windows 11, and meet all of your expectations.
Features of Windows 11 Manager:
Information:
	Creates the system restore point manually;
	Gets detailed information about your...
</description></item><item><title>Download DoYourData Uninstaller Pro 5.9</title><pubDate> Thu, 26 Feb 2026 22:53:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-doyourdata-uninstaller-pro-4214.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-doyourdata-uninstaller-pro-4214.html
</guid><description>
DoYourData Uninstaller Pro is an easy solution and smart to completely remove software, Windows applications and plug-ins on your computer. DoYourData Uninstaller not only can remove even the most stubborn of the program, but also completely erase / delete all files, links, and all traces of the program. DoYourData Uninstaller offer solution easy &amp;amp; smart for you to completely uninstall the program, Windows application and plugins on your computer. It does not only help you uninstall...
</description></item><item><title>Download Opera GX (Gaming Browser) 127.0.5778.96</title><pubDate> Thu, 26 Feb 2026 22:52:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-gx-3170.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-gx-3170.html
</guid><description>
Opera GX is a special version of the Opera browser is built to complement gamers avid. Browser this game comes with the unique features to help users make maximum use of both the game and their browser. Opera GX is built specifically to support the game. This browser includes the unique features to help users have the best experience when gaming and surfing the web.
Opera GX - special browser for gamers
GX Control allows you to set a limit on the level of use RAM, CPU and network where...
</description></item><item><title>Download RepairKit 1.3.9</title><pubDate> Thu, 26 Feb 2026 22:51:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-repairkit-11968.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-repairkit-11968.html
</guid><description>
RepairKit is an all-in-one Java-based Windows repair and maintenance toolkit. RepairKit aims to provide a package that provides users with a dedicated system repair tool as well as quick access to some operating system features and some other PC maintenance software that comes with it. it.
If you want to keep your PC running smoothly and want to do it conveniently, RepairKit offers a simple and effective solution for that, with an automatic repair/cleanup module , as well as access to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Iperius Backup Full 8.7.4</title><pubDate> Thu, 26 Feb 2026 22:51:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iperius-backup-621.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iperius-backup-621.html
</guid><description>
Iperius Backup software supports backup and restore of data can be stored on a cloud service, and AES 256-bit. This is the perfect software to get the advantages of the many services that cloud storage is provided by the famous supplier like Google or Microsoft. With a single application, you will can easily save your files externally on Google Drive, Dropbox or Microsoft SkyDrive.
Iperius Backup uses the technology images Windows drive most advanced, allows to copy entire operating...
</description></item><item><title>Download AllMapSoft Universal Maps Downloader 10.239</title><pubDate> Thu, 26 Feb 2026 22:42:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-universal-maps-downloader-736.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-universal-maps-downloader-736.html
</guid><description>
AllMapSoft Universal Maps Downloader is software download map images on the computer for offline viewing support many types such as Google Maps, Yahoo maps, Bing maps, OpenStreet Maps, Yandex Maps, Ovi Maps, MapQuest Maps. All the downloaded photos will be saved on disk. You can view downloaded maps by Maps Viewer Or you can combine them into one big bmp, or jpg file tif by Maps Combiner, and also you can export all the tiles into a database format MBTiles.
AllMapSoft Universal Maps...
</description></item><item><title>Download PC Timer 19.4</title><pubDate> Thu, 26 Feb 2026 22:42:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pc-timer-7519.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pc-timer-7519.html
</guid><description>
PC Timer is a simple tool to automatically shut down, log out, restart or lock your PC based on your scheduled time. A handy feature of the app is its ability to prevent unauthorized cancellation of a scheduled task. To do so, PC Timer .NET allows you to set a password that the user must provide to cancel the operation.
The advantage of the application is its simplicity, small footprint on the system and the fact that it does not require installation. Thanks to the ability to set tasks...
</description></item><item><title>Download Easy Backup 2026 v14.4.0.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 26 Feb 2026 22:41:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easy-backup-9970.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easy-backup-9970.html
</guid><description>
Easy Backup is a free backup solution for your files or the entire system with wizards and video tutorials to assist you through the process. Once configured, the software automatically backs up your data and allows you to store different versions of your files or even your deleted files
Recovering data is very easy. You can restore the integrity of your data or just some files at the desired date and time. For advanced users, restoring can be done manually from the backup media via...
</description></item><item><title>Download QOwnNotes 26.2.12</title><pubDate> Thu, 26 Feb 2026 22:39:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qownnotes-3178.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qownnotes-3178.html
</guid><description>
QOwnNotes is notes bookmark file simple text (GPL) open source application for GNU / Linux , Mac OS X and Windows of Patrizio Bekerle ( pbek on GitHub and IRC) (optional) activity along with the notes application of ownCloud or Nextcloud. QOwnNote store your notes as plain text files and can be synchronized with synchronization function file of ownCloud / Nextcloud. You can also use other apps like Syncthing or Dropbox . Just write out your thoughts as they appear, and edit them if...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinTools.one Professional / Home 26.2.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 26 Feb 2026 22:38:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wintoolsone-10808.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wintoolsone-10808.html
</guid><description>
WinTools.one is a program designed to help both regular and advanced users as well as computer engineers fine-tune the MS Windows operating system. It allows you to increase the performance of the operating system, maintain its performance at a high level, fix operating system errors, free up space on the computer's hard drive and control the operation of installed programs. In addition, the program allows you to store and protect your secret and confidential information, as well as work...
</description></item><item><title>Download Voice Creator Pro 1.1.4</title><pubDate> Thu, 26 Feb 2026 22:37:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-voice-creator-pro-14576.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-voice-creator-pro-14576.html
</guid><description>
A versatile local AI voice creator software that sounds like a real person. Voice copying, voice design, text-to-speech, and speech-to-text conversion, with full REST API access.
Features of Voice Creator Pro
	Voice Copying — Copy any voice with just 3 seconds of audio. Create voices that sound indistinguishable from the original.
	Voice Design — Create custom voices from text descriptions. No audio samples needed — just describe the voice you want.
	Text-to-Speech — Convert...
</description></item><item><title>Download Duplicate File Finder Professional 2026 v411</title><pubDate> Thu, 26 Feb 2026 22:37:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-duplicate-file-finder-professional-4425.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-duplicate-file-finder-professional-4425.html
</guid><description>
Duplicate File Finder Professional is a compact application helps you quickly find and remove files duplicate on the computer. With Duplicate File Finder Professional you can choose any folder on the hard drive or use the folder standard user and our app will analyze the deep content of the selected folder to copy. It will take only a few seconds. The files will be compared by the hash algorithm MD5, which means they will be compared by content, not by name. Then, use our convenient...
</description></item><item><title>Download MAME 0.286</title><pubDate> Thu, 26 Feb 2026 22:36:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mame-3320.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mame-3320.html
</guid><description>
MAME is an emulator of open source and free are designed to recreate the hardware of the game system arcade in software on the personal computer modern and other platforms. The goal is to preserve gaming history by preventing classic games from being lost or being forgotten.
MAME - emulator classic game
MAME (Multiple Arcade Machine Emulator) is a software that has the ability to simulate an arcade machine, allowing you to play the classic arcade game on his computer. This tool can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Do Your Data Recovery Professional / Technician 8.3</title><pubDate> Thu, 26 Feb 2026 22:35:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-do-your-data-recovery-1184.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-do-your-data-recovery-1184.html
</guid><description>
Do Your Data Recovery is recovery tool data easy-to-use help data recovery deleted, formatted or not accessible from PC, laptop, digital or other media. It can also restore lost files from a deleted partition or lost. It can recover deleted images, emails, video, audio, document folder or the file is lost. The current Do Your Data Recovery have provided 3 version Professional / Technician / Enterprise is diverse for people to choose in accordance with user needs.
Do Your Data Recovery -...
</description></item><item><title>Download O&amp;amp;O SafeErase Pro 21.0.26082</title><pubDate> Thu, 26 Feb 2026 22:34:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-safeerase-pro-294.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-safeerase-pro-294.html
</guid><description>
O&amp;amp;O SafeErase Pro is software that helps you to delete sensitive data securely with safeguards against misuse of data. With O&amp;amp;O SafeErase Pro you can be sure that no data is put into the wrong hands. O&amp;amp;O SafeErase provides reliable solution to securely delete files sensitive security and provide you with data protection optimization. With O&amp;amp;O SafeErase even hackers and spyware data can't restore the deleted files of your safety.
&amp;nbsp;O&amp;amp;O SafeErase is the solution...
</description></item><item><title>Download Windows Firewall Control 6.26.0.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 26 Feb 2026 22:33:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-firewall-control-3395.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-firewall-control-3395.html
</guid><description>
Windows Firewall Control is a application which help extend the functionality of the Microsoft Windows Firewall and provides quick access to the most common options of Windows firewall. It works in the system tray and allows users to adjust firewall simple root which does not have to lose time by navigating to the specific part of the firewall.
Windows Firewall Control - firewall App for windows
It runs in the system tray and allows user to control the firewall easily without having to...
</description></item><item><title>Download KILHO ImageConverter 1.5.7</title><pubDate> Thu, 26 Feb 2026 22:30:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kilho-imageconverter-12520.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kilho-imageconverter-12520.html
</guid><description>
ImageConverter is designed for ease of use, making it accessible to everyone, regardless of technical expertise. To get started, drag and drop the image you want onto the user interface. Once uploaded, you can explore different configuration options to suit your needs. These settings allow you to customize the output format, adjust resolution, and apply any necessary filters or enhancements. You can efficiently convert your images to your desired specifications in just a few...
</description></item><item><title>Download Antidote 12 v4.0.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 26 Feb 2026 22:30:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-antidote-8032.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-antidote-8032.html
</guid><description>
Antidote is a multi-resource platform, very useful for anyone writing in English or French. Antidote's debugger flags a wide variety of errors: from capitalization and verb agreement to commas and unwanted redundancies. Once your spelling and grammar are correct, correct typographical and stylistic errors, including repetition of words and boring verbs. Never before has software given you such power to perfect your writing.
The error correction tool analyzes your text and highlights any...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter 3.9.18 (2502)</title><pubDate> Thu, 26 Feb 2026 22:29:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-to-mp3-converter-1744.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-to-mp3-converter-1744.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter is the software support download youtube video and convert video to mp3 format fast and most simple. MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter allows you download and convert videos from YouTube and other websites to MP3 format by pasting the YouTube URL into the application. When you paste the URL, the program will display thumbnails for videos and you have the option to customize the title information, artist and album before you begin the process of...
</description></item></channel></rss>