<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 13:41:28 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 13:41:28 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Tixati 3.39.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 16:41:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tixati-2355.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tixati-2355.html
</guid><description>
A Bittorrent free, good have been updated, are designed for operating systems Microsoft Windows and Linux (for the OS Monday, you can download a version from the official website of the developer). The difference between a client and a large number of others is that users are provided a wide opportunity to control the torrent of them, they also write on your program that it consumes less memory than uTorrent and Halite famous.
Tixati - App download torrent
Tixati is also ready to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft Safety Scanner 1.441.23</title><pubDate> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 16:40:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-safety-scanner-4512.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-safety-scanner-4512.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft Safety Scanner is a scanning tool designed to find and remove malware from a Windows computer. Just download and run the scan to find malware and try to reverse the changes made by the threat identified. Microsoft Safety Scanner has the ability to remove virus, spyware and files other dangers on your computer, Microsoft Safety Scanner completes scanning tasks in just a few minutes, while the computer is moderate stress during handling.
In other words, no real time protection...
</description></item><item><title>Download XRECODE3 1.174 Beta</title><pubDate> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 16:40:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xrecode-iii-2915.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xrecode-iii-2915.html
</guid><description>
"Xrecode II" is the switch and grab the audio allows you to convert from mp2, mp3, ac3, aiff, wma, amr, ogg, ape, flac, cue, mpc, wv, tak, mid, cue, m4b, tta, wav, dts , wav (rf64), m4a, mp4, ra, shn, rm, avi, aac, mpg, vob, mka, mkv, flv, Mov, swf, ofr, divx, wmv, spx, mp3, m4v, 3gp, m2v, 3g2, m4v, m2ts, ts, adts, tak, xm, mod, it, s3m, alac, umx, mtm, mlp to m4a, ape, flac, mp4 (using NeroAAC), raw, ogg, wav, wav (rf64) , wma, mpc, WavPack, mp2, ofr, Speex, ac3, tak, aiff, snd, Shorten...
</description></item><item><title>Download Anthemion Jutoh 3.27</title><pubDate> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 16:39:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anthemion-jutoh-801.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anthemion-jutoh-801.html
</guid><description>
Anthemion Jutoh is a software to create electronic books in popular formats and design your own cover with editor, cover integrated. Create your project in seconds from existing files using The guide to new projects; or create your book from scratch using the text editor as integrated.
Anthemion Jutoh - Create ebooks
The features of Anthemion Jutoh
	Quick to generate Epub, Mobipocket or other format of your.
	Fast to edit content and switch between variations of your ebooks.
	Jutoh...
</description></item><item><title>Download KDEnlive 25.08.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 16:38:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kdenlive-3288.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kdenlive-3288.html
</guid><description>
Kdenlive is a video editor open source. The project was started in about 2003. Kdenlive is built on the Qt libraries and the KDE Frameworks. Most of the video processing is done by the MLT Framework, based on many open-source projects other as FFmpeg , frei0r , Movit, ladspa, sox, etc.
KDEnlive - video editing quickly
Our software is designed to meet most needs, from basic video editing to professional work. Kdenlive allows you to use and arrange a number of music and video, each can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Daemon Tools Lite 12.3.0.2364</title><pubDate> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 16:38:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-daemon-tools-lite-3391.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-daemon-tools-lite-3391.html
</guid><description>
DAEMON Tools Lite is based on two key features, simulation of virtual disks and building the file disk image as iso. DAEMON Tools Lite can emulate up to 4 virtual drives, DVD, CD or Blu-ray on your computer. The virtual units will be present in your system the same as the unit. After you select the virtual drive you want, you will choose a disc image (nrg, iso, mdf, bin, cue, etc.) that you want to mount. Visit My Computer at the device have The mobile storage and you will find the disk...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tomabo MP4 Downloader Pro 5.9.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 16:37:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tomabo-mp4-downloader-pro-3602.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tomabo-mp4-downloader-pro-3602.html
</guid><description>
Tomabo MP4 Downloader Pro is the app designed exclusively for Windows users to help them download videos from the Internet. In addition, it also increase download speeds by up to 500%, or even more. Tomabo MP4 Downloader Pro, interface design, simple, well-organized, beautifully. Here, users can view a list of videos has download with gravatar, URL, quality, duration and size of them. Software allows download video series at the same time, at the same time, support create a list of clips...
</description></item><item><title>Download TubeMate Downloader 5.25.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 16:33:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubemate-downloader-4250.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubemate-downloader-4250.html
</guid><description>
TubeMate Downloader is a smart application that lets you download any clip you want from the website hosting the main video and convert them in when download at or then. If you need a simple and effective tool to download videos, you can give it a try. With TubeMate Downloader, you can directly drag and drop video link from your browser into the drop-down box or application window to start downloading. You don't even need to copy and paste the video URL.
TubeMate Downloader - Support...
</description></item><item><title>Download TeXstudio 4.9.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 16:33:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-texstudio-7399.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-texstudio-7399.html
</guid><description>
TeXstudio is an integrated writing environment for creating LaTeX documents. The goal of TeXstudio is to make writing LaTeX as easy and comfortable as possible. Therefore TeXstudio has many features such as syntax highlighting, built-in viewer, reference checking and various assistants.
Features of TeXstudio
	Advanced Syntax Highlighting
	Checking direct references
	Built-in PDF viewer
	Live Preview
	Complete Latex Command and Check Syntax
	Live grammar check
	Local and global...
</description></item><item><title>Download Silent Camera [High Quality] 8.16.5</title><pubDate> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 16:03:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-silent-camera-10536.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-silent-camera-10536.html
</guid><description>
Introducing the best silent camera! Without the shutter sound, photos can be taken in complete silence! It also ranks number 1 among many silent cameras thanks to its high image quality! Take high-quality photos with the silent camera! You won't disturb anyone around you because the shutter sound can't be heard. You can take high-quality photos of any situation, such as your baby's cute sleeping face, your pet's natural behaviors, and words written on a blackboard!
Silent Camera...
</description></item><item><title>Download WPS Office - PDF, Word, Excel, PPT 18.22</title><pubDate> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 16:03:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wps-office-pdf-word-excel-ppt-8244.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wps-office-pdf-word-excel-ppt-8244.html
</guid><description>
WPS Office is a mobile office suite app that allows users to view, edit and create documents, spreadsheets, and presentations on their Android device. The app is available for download from the Google Play Store and is compatible with a wide range of file formats, including Microsoft Office documents.
WPS Office - Free Office suite for Word, PDF, Excel, is an all-in-one office suite that integrates Word, PDF, Excel, PowerPoint, Forms, Cloud Storage, Online Editing, Template library and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ad Detector &amp;amp; Ad Blocker 1.0.5</title><pubDate> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 16:02:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ad-detector-ad-blocker-14209.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ad-detector-ad-blocker-14209.html
</guid><description>
Are you fed up with mysterious pop-up ads ruining your experience? With Ad Detector &amp;amp; Ad Blocker, you can identify which apps are showing annoying ads and manage them for more efficient, focused use.
Key Features
Popup Ad Detector: This feature helps monitor your device to find out the origin of ads outside the app. When annoying ads appear, Ad Detector will tell you which app is responsible, giving you more control.
Smart Ad Blocker: Limit pop-up and video ads with Ad Blocker....
</description></item><item><title>Download Firewall Security AI - No Root 2.5.7 build 2570</title><pubDate> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 16:02:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-firewall-no-root-8224.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-firewall-no-root-8224.html
</guid><description>
No Root Firewall is an Android application that allows users to block Internet access to specific applications on their device without requiring root access. Blocks internet attacks and protects you from unwanted access to the internet. Determine which applications can and cannot access the internet. With powerful firewall technology, secure filter lists and artificial intelligence, you protect your privacy comprehensively and also stay informed about what is being shared with the...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDF Scanner Plus - Doc Scanner 1.3.15</title><pubDate> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 16:02:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pdf-scanner-plus-doc-scanner-13093.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pdf-scanner-plus-doc-scanner-13093.html
</guid><description>
PDF Scanner Plus - Doc Scanner is your personal scanner for any document, text or image. Turn any paper document, photo or text into a digital document with PDF Scanner Plus in just one click, then convert to PDF format.
THIS IS WHAT IT CAN DO
	Scan any text or image and Scanner Plus will create a digital copy right on your device!
	Our smart app will find the outline of the exact area needed, so you only take what is needed, or manually change the area if you only want a portion of a...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDF Scanner app - TapScanner 3.0.88</title><pubDate> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 16:01:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pdf-scanner-app-tapscanner-12104.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pdf-scanner-app-tapscanner-12104.html
</guid><description>
TapScanner is a mobile application that allows you to scan documents with your smartphone camera and convert them into PDF files or image formats. It essentially turns your device into a portable scanner, making capturing and digitizing physical documents convenient on the go.
TapScanner Features
	Scan documents, receipts, QRs and business cards
	Document Scanner App - Automatic Border Detection
	Tweak your images with multiple filters to achieve perfection
	Easily manage your...
</description></item><item><title>Download Calculator Plus with History 8.1.4</title><pubDate> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 16:01:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-calculator-plus-with-history-10531.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-calculator-plus-with-history-10531.html
</guid><description>
Plus Calculator with History is the perfect calculator for Android. It remembers everything you calculate and allows you to review it at any time, which is perfect for me when shopping, doing homework, balancing my checkbook, or even helping with taxes. And if you need to quit your job and go do something else, I'll have it all ready for you when you get back. You'll never need to re-enter the same calculation twice.
Features of Calculator Plus with History
	Show your calculations in...
</description></item><item><title>Download FotMob - Soccer Live Scores 218.14917.20251028.rc</title><pubDate> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 16:00:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-fotmob-soccer-live-scores-8241.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-fotmob-soccer-live-scores-8241.html
</guid><description>
FotMob gives you all the live scores, stats and storylines to help you keep up with the world of football. Personalized news and notifications make it easy to follow your favorite teams and players. And lightning-fast match updates ensure you never miss a goal, no matter where you are.
Features of FotMob - Live soccer scores
	Live match score
	Results, schedule, standings and lineup
	Detailed statistics, including expected goals (xG) and expected assists (xA)
	Capture map
	Player...
</description></item><item><title>Download 7Fon: Wallpapers &amp;amp; Backgrounds 6.0.81</title><pubDate> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 16:00:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-7fon-wallpapers-4k-pro-11673.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-7fon-wallpapers-4k-pro-11673.html
</guid><description>
7Fon Wallpapers 4K (PRO) Android is a great application for people who love beauty and art. With thousands of high-quality wallpapers, users can find the perfect photos for their phone screen.
This app offers a huge collection of 4K wallpapers from different categories like nature, animals, art, landscapes and more. Users can easily search for wallpapers by topic or keyword, helping them quickly find their favorite photos.
Outstanding features of the application include:
	More than...
</description></item><item><title>Download analiti - Speed Test WiFi Analyzer 2025.10.91199</title><pubDate> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 16:00:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-speed-test-wifi-analyzer-8353.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-speed-test-wifi-analyzer-8353.html
</guid><description>
Speed ​​Test WiFi Analyzer is a tool that can be used to test the performance of a wireless network. It can measure various metrics, such as signal strength, channel interference, and network throughput.
Features of Speed ​​Test WiFi Analyzer
Speed ​​test:
	Internet or iPerf3 speed test (including server and client)
	Simultaneous ping, DNS and HTTP latency results – to multiple servers with configurable load
	Monitor uptime remotely 24/7 for downtime or slowdown
360...
</description></item><item><title>Download Weather &amp;amp; Radar USA - Pro 2025.23</title><pubDate> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 15:59:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-weather-radar-usa-pro-8391.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-weather-radar-usa-pro-8391.html
</guid><description>
Weather &amp;amp; Radar USA is a mobile application that provides users with real-time weather information and forecasts for locations in the United States. The app includes many features such as current weather conditions, hourly and daily forecasts, radar and satellite images, and severe weather alerts. It also includes many customizable settings, such as the ability to set up multiple locations and receive notifications about specific weather conditions.
Features of Weather &amp;amp; Radar...
</description></item><item><title>Download Power VPN: Fast &amp;amp; Secure VPN 2.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 15:59:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-power-vpn-fast-secure-vpn-10109.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-power-vpn-fast-secure-vpn-10109.html
</guid><description>
Power VPN - Free Unlimited VPN Master for Android. Now you can easily access blocked Internet Content with just one click with PowerVPN's Fast and Secure VPN Tunnel. Power VPN Free VPN is the fastest VPN with a secure server network worldwide.
Power VPN Features: Fast and Secure VPN
	This is the best VPN (free VPN) ever created. Create your IPVanish
	Simple interface. Just click to connect
	Over 30 different server locations worldwide to connect to.
	Allows torrenting, P2P, and file...
</description></item><item><title>Download Call Recorder - Cube ACR 2.4.276</title><pubDate> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 15:57:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-call-recorder-cube-acr-11263.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-call-recorder-cube-acr-11263.html
</guid><description>
Call Recorder Cube ACR is an application that records phone and VoIP calls. Supports call recording for most versions of Android devices. If you have tried recording calls using other call recording apps and not getting satisfactory results, try Cube ACR Call Recording, it works best. Cube ACR call recording allows you to easily record incoming and outgoing phone calls as well as VoIP conversations.
Main features:
	Automatically record every call. Record each conversation as it...
</description></item><item><title>Download Calorie Counter by Cronometer 4.47.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 15:57:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-calorie-counter-by-cronometer-13015.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-calorie-counter-by-cronometer-13015.html
</guid><description>
Calorie Counter by Cronometer is a powerful calorie counter, fitness tracker, nutrition and food tracker. It provides personalized nutrition and health insights, whether your goal is weight loss, muscle gain or healthy eating. Cronometer gives you verified data and scientifically proven tools.
Why choose Cronometer?
	Comprehensive nutrition tracking: Count calories, macronutrients, and 84 micronutrients
	1.1 million verified foods: Our lab-tested food database ensures accuracy in...
</description></item><item><title>Download 9GAG: Funny GIF, Meme &amp;amp; Video 8.16.4</title><pubDate> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 15:56:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-9gag-funny-gif-meme-video-11500.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-9gag-funny-gif-meme-video-11500.html
</guid><description>
9GAG has the best funny, cute, weird, wacky, cosplay photos, GIFs, videos, memes, photos on the web. We are your greatest and happiest source. With millions of visitors every day, 9GAG is an application that helps you play LOL, kill time and make new friends around the world.
9GAG features
	The 9GAG app loads quickly and allows for easy scrolling. Don't waste time picking me up or just having a good laugh.
	Carry unlimited fun in your pocket. Enjoy 9GAG anytime, anywhere and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Backdrops - Wallpapers 6.1.1 build 284</title><pubDate> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 15:56:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-backdrops-wallpapers-11912.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-backdrops-wallpapers-11912.html
</guid><description>
Select hundreds of original wallpapers manually created by the Backdrop team. Enjoy exclusive walls designed specifically for your device. You won't find these wallpapers in any other app. Get in on the action and upload the wallpaper yourself. Share your own work or photography. Only high-quality original submissions are approved for the Community tab. This ensures a complete collection of photos worthy of becoming your wallpaper. The Backdrop team will work side by side with you...
</description></item></channel></rss>