<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 21:36:07 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 21:36:07 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download CyberLink PowerDirector Ultimate 2026 v24.0.1230.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 31 Dec 2025 23:36:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-powerdirector-ultimate-425.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-powerdirector-ultimate-425.html
</guid><description>
CyberLink PowerDirector Ultimate is software editor, edit video and make movies on the computer from a variety of templates are made available, complete with effects, transitions, animations, and music. CyberLink PowerDirector 17 is a combination of video editing software with advanced video editing features powerful. Cblowing need to add your clips into the time line and click on 'Production'!
The tool design video in CyberLink PowerDirector have the ability to customize helps you...
</description></item><item><title>Download CyberLink PhotoDirector Ultra 2026 v17.0.1231.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 31 Dec 2025 23:36:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-photodirector-ultra-129.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-photodirector-ultra-129.html
</guid><description>
Cyberlink PhotoDirector Ultra is known to be photo editing tools and videos with the effect is extremely rich, help you to change the style for the individual images or the videos of his favorite. This software integrated the 3D engine helps to speed up Video processing, which allows accessing the repository effect online and extract the Videos into the movies 3D Bru-ray, 3D AVCHD.
Cyberlink PhotoDirector Ultra to offer users a more professional tool to handle their images, remove...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare Recoverit 14.0.13.3</title><pubDate> Wed, 31 Dec 2025 23:35:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-recoverits-374.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-recoverits-374.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare Recoverit is a data recovery software that is easily lost at a rapid rate and is used by many people. You will do what happens if one day your data is suddenly lost due to the virus or deleted it, .. Wondershare Recoverit will provide you with an environment to protect important data.
Wondershare Recoverit has all the scanning processes that are divided into multiple types, from the typical recovery of the deleted files that are deleted to the recovery of missing files due...
</description></item><item><title>Download EmEditor Pro 25.4.4</title><pubDate> Wed, 31 Dec 2025 23:35:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-emeditor-pro-69.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-emeditor-pro-69.html
</guid><description>
EmEditor Pro - the professional version of editor text powerful for programmers, web developers and ordinary users with illumination of syntax and Unicode support. The features of the editor such as search and replace in files using regular expressions, automatic code detect, bookmark link and address email, block selection mode, configure the button bar, menu, font and elements color. With each language you can set separate configuration.
EmEditor Pro - text Editor professional
The...
</description></item><item><title>Download RepairKit 1.3.6</title><pubDate> Wed, 31 Dec 2025 23:34:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-repairkit-11968.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-repairkit-11968.html
</guid><description>
RepairKit is an all-in-one Java-based Windows repair and maintenance toolkit. RepairKit aims to provide a package that provides users with a dedicated system repair tool as well as quick access to some operating system features and some other PC maintenance software that comes with it. it.
If you want to keep your PC running smoothly and want to do it conveniently, RepairKit offers a simple and effective solution for that, with an automatic repair/cleanup module , as well as access to...
</description></item><item><title>Download iTubeGo YouTube Downloader 10.11.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 31 Dec 2025 23:34:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-itubego-youtube-downloader-3681.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-itubego-youtube-downloader-3681.html
</guid><description>
iTubeGo YouTube Downloader  is the best way to download live video from 1000+ streaming sites. iTubeGo YouTube Downloader is a powerful download tool that allows you to save video and audio for free. The output format of high speed converter is high quality MP4, MP3. Fully compatible with iPhone, iPad, iTunes, iMovie, Android Phone and more.
iTubeGo YouTube Downloader - Solution for downloading high quality Youtube video 
Features of iTubeGo YouTube Downloader
	Download videos from...
</description></item><item><title>Download CyberLink AudioDirector Ultra 2026 v16.0.6024.12</title><pubDate> Wed, 31 Dec 2025 23:33:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-audiodirector-ultra-288.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-audiodirector-ultra-288.html
</guid><description>
Sound is half the movie experience and improving the audio in the project video will greatly enhance the final result. AudioDirector contains advanced tools help edit and edit the audio quickly and simply. With the audio feature and seamless integration with PowerDirector.
We provide CyberLink AudioDirector Ultra editor software, mix, and adjust the soundtrack, effects, audio for video, and all the passages spoken in the video. CyberLink AudioDirector Ultra is the upgrade version of...
</description></item><item><title>Download RAM Saver Professional 26.0.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 31 Dec 2025 23:33:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ram-saver-pro-565.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ram-saver-pro-565.html
</guid><description>
RAM Saver Pro is a professional software optimize RAM is for system stable operation with high performance. RAM Saver Pro aims to provide all the tools necessary to increase the amount of free memory, at any time, also monitor and check the RAM.
When using RAM Saver Pro, you will be allowed to access its main menu by right-clicking on the tray icon. Also, if you want to display the main panel of the program you just double-click the icon. In addition, from the main interface of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube Downloader 3.9.18 (3012)</title><pubDate> Wed, 31 Dec 2025 23:31:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube Downloader  is a dedicated software that helps users  downloading youtube videos  Favorites on PC for offline viewing. With MediaHuman YouTube  Downloader  you can download videos from youtube website to your computer with  fast speed , with special software development technology that automatically receives videos from Websites, in addition to the ability to download videos from software websites, can convert downloaded video formats to various formats for the purpose...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Saver Pro 10.11.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 31 Dec 2025 23:31:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-saver-6830.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-saver-6830.html
</guid><description>
YT Saver is a software that supports downloading Video, Audio, Playlist from 10,000+ websites, Convert Video to MP4, MOV, AAC, WAV and more. YT Saver is a powerful downloader that allows you to save video and audio for free. The output format of the high-speed converter is high-quality MP4, MP3. Fully compatible with iPhone, iPad, iTunes, iMovie, Android Phone and more.
Supported Input Formats:
	Video: MP4, M4V, 3GP, MPEG, DAT, AVI, ASF, WMV, VOB, MKV, FLV, 3GS, 3G2, F4V, WEBM, TS,...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinTools.net Professional / Premium / Classic 26.0.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 31 Dec 2025 23:30:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wintoolsnet-304.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wintoolsnet-304.html
</guid><description>
WinTools.net is an optimal tool working performance of the operating system and delete the unnecessary program from the hard drive and control the start-up process of Windows.
WinTools.net integrates many useful tools, to support increased processing speed and ability, stable operation for the computer include: Clean Uninstaller, Scan Files, Scan Registry, Start Up, Tweak UI, Net Tweaker, The Privacy. Scan Files are often used to scan the hard drive periodically, search for junk files or...
</description></item><item><title>Download Agisoft Metashape Professional 2.3.0 Build 21868</title><pubDate> Wed, 31 Dec 2025 23:30:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-agisoft-metashape-professional-1731.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-agisoft-metashape-professional-1731.html
</guid><description>
Agisoft Metashape (formerly PhotoScan) is a software product independently perform image processing and digital data creation, 3D space used in GIS applications, material cultural heritage and the production visual effects as well as the indirect measurement of the different subjects scale. Technical digital photography is deployed wisely is applied with the method of computer vision led to the system processor, smart auto, on the one hand, can be managed by a new person in the field of...
</description></item><item><title>Download QOwnNotes 26.1.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 31 Dec 2025 23:29:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qownnotes-3178.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qownnotes-3178.html
</guid><description>
QOwnNotes is notes bookmark file simple text (GPL) open source application for GNU / Linux , Mac OS X and Windows of Patrizio Bekerle ( pbek on GitHub and IRC) (optional) activity along with the notes application of ownCloud or Nextcloud. QOwnNote store your notes as plain text files and can be synchronized with synchronization function file of ownCloud / Nextcloud. You can also use other apps like Syncthing or Dropbox . Just write out your thoughts as they appear, and edit them if...
</description></item><item><title>Download Gilisoft Watermark Remover 8.9.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 31 Dec 2025 23:29:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-watermark-remover-12261.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-watermark-remover-12261.html
</guid><description>
Gilisoft Watermark Remover provides comprehensive solutions to remove watermarks from different types of media. It offers both options to remove watermarks from images and videos. This can be really helpful for people who need to edit or clean up their visual content.
Do you have any specific needs for removing watermarks from images or videos? Maybe you're working on a project or have some personal photos you want to improve. Either way, it's good to have these tools available. Inpaint...
</description></item><item><title>Download PPTube 10.11.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 31 Dec 2025 23:28:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pptube-12556.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pptube-12556.html
</guid><description>
PPTube Video Downloader allows you to download HD videos easily, from 720p, 1080p, 2K, 4K and 8K. You can save multiple videos at the same time. Just copy multiple video URLs from various websites and paste them into PPTube Downloader, then you can download multiple videos in seconds.
In addition, you can download HD videos from Instagram, TikTok, Facebook, Apple Music, Vimeo, adult websites, etc. and convert them to MP4, MP3, MOV, AAC and more than 20 other output formats. PPTube...
</description></item><item><title>Download CapCut PC 7.7.0.3143 / 7.8.0.3261 Beta 7</title><pubDate> Wed, 31 Dec 2025 23:28:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capcut-pc-9995.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capcut-pc-9995.html
</guid><description>
CapCut PC is a simple video editing tool that you can freely use anywhere. You can create videos on your browser, desktop and laptop, or on your phone. Versatile editing, magical AI tools, team collaboration, and built-in assets. Create videos in a whole new way.
You can edit videos based on editing the timeline, in the process you can add different elements and effects to the video to give the best effect to your work. It is a simple and intuitive set of editing tools and effects that...
</description></item><item><title>Download NetSpeedTray 1.1.9 + Portable</title><pubDate> Wed, 31 Dec 2025 23:27:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-netspeedtray-14068.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-netspeedtray-14068.html
</guid><description>
NetSpeedTray is a lightweight, open source network monitor for Windows that displays upload/download speeds directly on the Taskbar with a native look and feel.
Designed to blend seamlessly with Windows 10/11 user interface. Includes intelligent detection of light and dark themes on the taskbar to ensure text is always visible. Sits quietly in the system tray without hogging resources. Features "Dynamic Update Rate" that automatically reduces update frequency when the network is idle to...
</description></item><item><title>Download ExtraMAME 26.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 31 Dec 2025 23:26:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-extramame-2608.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-extramame-2608.html
</guid><description>
ExtraMAME is a simple tool that allows simulation of the arcade game from the most popular platform but is long forgotten, thanks to which the game industry has reached the current level. After launch, you will get 11 games pre-installed, among which are: Super Mario Bros, Pac-Man Plus, Space Invaders II and other games.
The simulation of multiple machine arcade is authored by Nicola Salmoria and team MAME. MAME lets you play thousands of arcade game old school on your computer. ExtraMAME...
</description></item><item><title>Download iDownerGo 10.11.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 31 Dec 2025 23:26:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idownergo-12439.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idownergo-12439.html
</guid><description>
iDownerGo is the best tool that allows users to download videos, music and playlists from more than 10,000 streaming sites. It can easily convert videos to MP4, MOV, MKV, 3GP, AAC, WAV, FLAC and other formats on PC and Mac. With this amazing program, users can enjoy their favorite media content without restrictions.
iDownerGo Features
	Download any video up to 8K resolution
	Download 1080p videos online from over 10,000 popular streaming sites easily.
	Save any video in various...
</description></item><item><title>Download Shotcut 25.12.30</title><pubDate> Wed, 31 Dec 2025 23:24:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-shotcut-2756.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-shotcut-2756.html
</guid><description>
Shotcut is a video editing application multi-platform free and open source for FreeBSD, Linux, macOS and Windows. Was started in 2011 by Dan Dennedy, Shotcut is developed on the multimedia MLT, which was developed from 2004. With age grow quite long years, Shotcut offers users many tools to perform the manipulation, Video editing based on adjusting each frame to enhance image quality. You can add an introduction, edit rate, bitrate, resolution or file encryption, and optionally use the...
</description></item><item><title>Download 3DEqualizer4 Release 8.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 31 Dec 2025 23:24:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-3dequalizer4-12367.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-3dequalizer4-12367.html
</guid><description>
3DEqualizer4 is the industry-leading 3D tracking solution for VFX, seamlessly combining live action footage with digital visual effects at the highest quality. It is the foundation of modern post-production, trusted by virtually every major company globally. With 3DEqualizer4, visual effects artists can precisely track camera and object movements in live-action or 3D footage. This tracking information is crucial in seamlessly integrating computer-generated imagery (CGI) with real footage,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Monkfish XML Software XML Blueprint 22.2025.1229</title><pubDate> Wed, 31 Dec 2025 23:23:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-monkfish-xml-software-xml-blueprint-12529.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-monkfish-xml-software-xml-blueprint-12529.html
</guid><description>
The intelligent XML editor in XMLBlueprint fully supports DTD, Relax NG, Schematron, XSD, XSLT (1.0, 2.0, 3.0) and XPath (1.0, 2.0, 3.1). The unique combination of relevant features and an affordable price for both professional and home users makes this a smart choice for all your XML-related work. With XMLBlueprint you can edit and validate very large XML files (1GByte or more). With an intuitive user interface, XMLBlueprint makes XML editing quick and easy. XMLBlueprint is the best...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinScan2PDF 9.51 + Portable</title><pubDate> Wed, 31 Dec 2025 17:20:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winscan2pdf-2117.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winscan2pdf-2117.html
</guid><description>
WinScan2PDF is a simple tool that allows you to scan documents from scanner and save them as PDF files. The program also supports multi-page scanning, then will be combined into one PDF document. Useful if your scanning software does not provide PDF conversion.
WinScan2PDF - Scan document to computer
WinScan2PDF allows users to perform scans the entire text or document at the same time to serve for the saved PDF format. Not only that, you also can choose the page any of a text to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Realtek Ethernet Controller All-In-One Drivers 11.27.1229.2025</title><pubDate> Wed, 31 Dec 2025 17:19:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-realtek-ethernet-controller-all-in-one-drivers-6485.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-realtek-ethernet-controller-all-in-one-drivers-6485.html
</guid><description>
Realtek Ethernet All-In-One Controller Driver is the software driver for the Realtek Ethernet cards. It is a program used to communicate from the Windows PC OS to the device. This software is required in most cases for the hardware device to function properly. In most cases, drivers come with Windows or can be found by going to Windows Update in Control Panel and checking for updates as well as downloaded from the Realtek support website.
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare Filmora 15.1.2.17051</title><pubDate> Wed, 31 Dec 2025 17:17:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-filmora-2025-31.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-filmora-2025-31.html
</guid><description>
In early November 2020 Wondershare came up with a new version called Wondershare Filmora 13 with two new ways to edit: Action Cam Tool (Lens distortion correction, Clean up your audio, Control speed new) and Instant Cutter (Cut or merge clips quickly, Export instantly).
Wondershare Filmora 13  allows you to add your favorite tracks to your videos, creating a more stylish, romantic film reel, with a rich music library besides Users can manually add their favorite songs to the editing...
</description></item></channel></rss>