<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 21:45:34 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 21:45:34 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Mozilla Firefox 141.0.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 05 Aug 2025 19:13:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-firefox-quantum-501.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-firefox-quantum-501.html
</guid><description>
Firefox Quantum is a web browser independently provide the tabbed browsing combined with numerous handy features like pop-up blocker, Bookmarks, direct (integrated RSS), password manager, and more. Functionality can be extended with dozens of plugins available for free (extensions).
Firefox Quantum are interface completely new, beautiful, neat, minimalistic and delicate, eats less RAM to 30% compared with the old version and solve the condition consuming capacity
Firefox can import all...
</description></item><item><title>Download Revo Registry Cleaner Pro 1.5.6</title><pubDate> Tue, 05 Aug 2025 19:11:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-revo-registry-cleaner-pro-12750.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-revo-registry-cleaner-pro-12750.html
</guid><description>
Revo Registry Cleaner Pro provides complete solutions to advanced Registry cleaning. It uses more than 15 separate scanning categories to identify and completely delete invaluable and redundant registry items that can slow down your system performance. You can customize the cleaning process by specifying the items including and the main exclusion, allowing a more appropriate approach to maintain the integrity of the registration book. In addition, Revo Registry Cleaner has four flexible...
</description></item><item><title>Download GiliSoft Audio Toolbox Suite 13.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 05 Aug 2025 19:11:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-audio-toolbox-suite-856.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-audio-toolbox-suite-856.html
</guid><description>
GiliSoft Audio Toolbox Suite is software that contains 9 program powerful audio like Audio Recorder , Audio Cutter, Audio Joiner, Audio Converter, Video to Mp3,ID3 Tag Editor,Transfer to iTunes,CD Ripper,CD Burner. With GiliSoft Audio Toolbox Suite, you can easily convert and edit any audio file, how to extract, create and copy CD, convert audio files, burn music to CD, rip CD / DVD to the audio file to another, etc.
GiliSoft Audio Toolbox Suite - software sound synthesis
The main...
</description></item><item><title>Download AutoClose Pro 3.4.6</title><pubDate> Tue, 05 Aug 2025 19:11:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-autoclose-7044.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-autoclose-7044.html
</guid><description>
AutoClose allows you to automatically close the programs as well as scheduling shortcuts, hibering or restarting the system. It will also allow you to perform multiple tasks at once and allow you to end the background tasks effectively. AutoClose is designed to automatically close all programs and turn off or log out after a user specified and simple enough to establish it useful for all types of users.
This utility application has been designed to automatically close all programs and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wise Memory Optimizer 4.2.3.129</title><pubDate> Tue, 05 Aug 2025 19:10:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wise-memory-optimizer-2380.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wise-memory-optimizer-2380.html
</guid><description>
Wise Memory Optimizer is a free software to help you clean up, speed up system. Wise Memory Optimizer will free up memory of the computer, freeing up hard drive space occupied by unnecessary applications. Wise Memory Optimizer will show the disk space used, and capacity to you have the tuning more suitable, avoid overloaded hard drive as well as RAM memory. You can set the application to automatically perform the optimal function of memory.
Wise Memory Optimizer - Clean up, speed up...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Illustrator 2025 v29.7.1.8 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Tue, 05 Aug 2025 19:10:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-illustrator-0015-749.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-illustrator-0015-749.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Illustrator is a powerful vector graphics editor developed by Adobe Inc., first released in 1987. It is primarily used by graphic designers, illustrators, and artists to create high-quality illustrations, logos, icons, and digital artwork. Unlike raster graphics editors like Adobe Photoshop, which manipulate images pixel by pixel, Illustrator uses mathematical formulas to create vector graphics. This allows designs to be scaled infinitely without losing quality, making it ideal for...
</description></item><item><title>Download Advanced Renamer Commercial 4.14</title><pubDate> Tue, 05 Aug 2025 19:09:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-renamer-2647.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-renamer-2647.html
</guid><description>
Advanced Renamer is a program to rename multiple files and folders at the same time. By configuring the method name change, the name can be manipulated in many different ways. It's easy to set up a batch job using multiple methods on a large number of files. 14 different modes allow you to change the name, attributes and timestamp of the file in once. The file can also be copied or moved to new location based on information in the file.
The program can rename files in many different ways,...
</description></item><item><title>Download ExpanDrive 2025.06.20</title><pubDate> Tue, 05 Aug 2025 19:08:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-expandrive-609.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-expandrive-609.html
</guid><description>
ExpanDrive is software sync cloud storage strong support BackBlaze B2, Google Team Drive, SMB / CIFS and new interface and easy user search file version, share links and much more.  ExpanDrive mapped network drives for macOS and Micosoft Windows connect with all the provide major cloud storage such as Dropbox, Google Drive, Google Team Drive, Amazon Drive, Box, OneDrive, OneDrive for Business, Sharepoint, Openstack Swift , BackBlaze B2, Amazon S3 or SFTP servers, FTP or WebDAV on your own...
</description></item><item><title>Download GiliSoft Audio Recorder Pro 13.6</title><pubDate> Tue, 05 Aug 2025 19:08:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-audio-recorder-pro-855.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-audio-recorder-pro-855.html
</guid><description>
GiliSoft Audio Recorder Pro is software perfect recorder to record audio and microphone of your computer to AAC, AC3, AIFF, AMR, AU, FLAC, M4A, M4B, M4R, MKA, MP2, MP3, OGG, RA, VOC , WAV Files or WMA files on Windows 7/8. Recording the sound that goes through your sound card is not at all a difficult task, but GiliSoft Audio Recorder Pro promises to make everything a lot easier, even for those who do not have computer knowledge advanced.
GiliSoft Audio Recorder Pro - audio recording...
</description></item><item><title>Download ArmorTools Professional / Home 25.8.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 05 Aug 2025 19:07:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-armortools-7726.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-armortools-7726.html
</guid><description>
ArmorTools is a set of tools that extend the capabilities of the MS Windows operating system in the field of security and protection of user confidential information. ArmorTools allows you to create secure virtual disks encrypted with AES128/AES256 algorithms, encrypting files and folder contents using any file as a password.
ArmorTools erases the user's work traces on the computer, deletes the history of accessing websites, deletes confidential information without the possibility of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Directory Opus Pro 13.17.5 Beta</title><pubDate> Tue, 05 Aug 2025 19:07:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-opus-pro-779.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-opus-pro-779.html
</guid><description>
Directory Opus Pro is a software replacement for Explorer with traditional strength and function more than any manager other files. Directory Opus Pro full support for high DPI screen (for example 4K and 5K) with the rename dialog is redesigned, with new features. Besides being a recording macro only allows you to perform mass renaming complex that don't need regular expressions. In addition, Directory Opus Pro also enhances the ability to script.Better handling of renaming recursive and...
</description></item><item><title>Download XtraTools Pro 25.8.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 05 Aug 2025 19:06:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xtratools-pro-7168.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xtratools-pro-7168.html
</guid><description>
XtraTools Pro is a universal tool for MS Windows system optimization that takes care of all aspects of your computer like optimizing the registry and removing unnecessary program to establish network connection and increase RAM speed. It is a compact tool with an intuitive interface that gives you complete control over the boot process, memory monitoring and a huge set of system settings that control your computer. The current version of the software provides the following tools: Folder...
</description></item><item><title>Download Gilisoft MarkEase 10.5.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 05 Aug 2025 19:06:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-markease-12705.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-markease-12705.html
</guid><description>
MarkEase to quickly delete unnecessary objects such as logos, text, data stamps, watermarks, blemishes, people and automatically repair them instantly, images, as if they never existed . Complete magical images in seconds to minutes, not minutes to hours. People around the world use MarkEase every day to beautify their photos. It aims to provide a simple and effective photo editing application for all users. Try it today and become more creative.
Features of Gilisoft MarkEase
	Remove...
</description></item><item><title>Download Youtube Downloader HD 5.9.8.6</title><pubDate> Tue, 05 Aug 2025 19:00:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-downloader-hd-3122.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-downloader-hd-3122.html
</guid><description>
Youtube Downloader HD is the best application to download and save Youtube videos. And it's completely free :) You can also convert the downloaded video into various formats easily. Youtube Downloader HD is the download at video free. Download at your videos easily and convert to AVI video format or into MP4 video format (compatible with iPad, iPhone). You can download high quality videos, high definition videos and Full HD from YouTube.
Youtube Downloader HD - Download Youtube videos...
</description></item><item><title>Download StartAllBack 3.9.13.5293</title><pubDate> Tue, 05 Aug 2025 18:12:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-startallback-6857.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-startallback-6857.html
</guid><description>
With the official release of Windows 11, chances are that most of you want to try it out. As the name suggests, StartAllBack is a small, lightweight tool that can help you enjoy the power of the new operating system while keeping the look and feel, especially because main work area, desktop of Windows 7, Windows 10 as taskbars and start menu styles.
StartAllBack is specially designed for Windows 11 and will not work on any older operating systems. If you want to get the start menu back...
</description></item><item><title>Download MAGIX Photostory Deluxe 2025 v24.0.1.233</title><pubDate> Tue, 05 Aug 2025 18:11:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-magix-photostory-deluxe-717.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-magix-photostory-deluxe-717.html
</guid><description>
MAGIX Photostory Deluxe version 2019 provides the movement of camera, zoom and music in a slideshow of photos incredible. Our templates help you to create the slideshow entertainment absolutely does take time. Includes: new photos and 1,500 effects and music. Add to that, get more effects, more in Store Photostory!
MAGIX Photostory Deluxe - professional photo editing and add effects on the photos
Unlimited slideshows. Explore the design possibilities endless: With the stunning effects...
</description></item><item><title>Download UniFab 3.0.2.4</title><pubDate> Tue, 05 Aug 2025 18:10:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-unifab-10377.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-unifab-10377.html
</guid><description>
UniFab is software to efficiently convert, compress and edit more than 1000 video formats for playback on any device without losing quality. Enlarge video/audio to 1080p/DTS 7.1 and upgrade video to HDR10 or Dolby Vision with AI Enhancer. UniFab Pro provides the best AI-powered zoom tool that allows you to enlarge videos from low resolutions, such as 360p, 480p and 720p, to 1080p without losing any quality. Clearer and sharper image details will bring you an exceptional viewing...
</description></item><item><title>Download Prepros 7.27</title><pubDate> Tue, 05 Aug 2025 18:10:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-prepros-4471.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-prepros-4471.html
</guid><description>
Prepros is a tool simple to use display interface is minimalistic and allows users to load, view and preprocess images, CSS and JS. Prepros available in a bright and dark themes, the user interface has a sleek style and is optimized to show all the highlights the potential that you encountered in the process of compiling highlights. You can start by adding the project you are implementing, an action you can complete in a convenient way by dragging and dropping.
Prepros - Learn to write...
</description></item><item><title>Download ChrisPC Win Experience Index 7.25.0804</title><pubDate> Tue, 05 Aug 2025 18:09:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-win-experience-index-2338.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-win-experience-index-2338.html
</guid><description>
ChrisPC Win Experience Index helps to check performance of RAM, processor CPU to know that his machine still works fine with the program ChrisPC Win Experience Index brings back the Windows Experience Index are installed on windows 8.1 of you to take out only the number of hardware, after checking the software, return the original interface of your operating system.
ChrisPC Win Experience Index - performance test computer
ChrisPC Win Experience Index installed quickly, after launch,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Zortam Mp3 Media Studio Pro 33.10</title><pubDate> Tue, 05 Aug 2025 18:09:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zortam-mp3-media-studio-pro-135.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zortam-mp3-media-studio-pro-135.html
</guid><description>
Zortam Mp3 Media Studio Pro brings you rich processing tools music includes extract and convert music from CD to Mp3 format, edit, music cards, music download....You can also create discs CD high-quality music, with Zortam Mp3 Media Studio search music files duplicated to remove them from the system, rename music files, switch back and forth between formats.
Zortam Mp3 Media Studio Pro is rated as perfect software in the processing of the MP3 files on the computer. First of all, you can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Gilisoft DRM Protection 8.5</title><pubDate> Tue, 05 Aug 2025 18:08:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-video-drm-protection-5260.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-video-drm-protection-5260.html
</guid><description>
Gilisoft Video DRM Protection is software that helps you can protect your videos and the E-Learning content to another by secure, encrypted the files, your content and distribute them to the target audience authorized of you. Very easy to make video / sound / pictures of you can't see are for anyone except those you allow. Gilisoft Video DRM Protection can encrypt and pack video &amp;amp; codec &amp;amp; player into exe.
Gilisoft Video DRM Protection can easily encode almost any kind of Video...
</description></item><item><title>Download Trellix Stinger (McAfee Stinger) 13.0.0.426</title><pubDate> Tue, 05 Aug 2025 18:07:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mcafee-stinger-202.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mcafee-stinger-202.html
</guid><description>
McAfee Stinger is a free utility that functions to scan, check and remove the hazards and obstacles as virus or malware for Windows, whether they are hiding deep into the system.
In addition, due to the ability to search for the correct folder, or the data at risk contains viruses to scan instead you have to remove a long time waiting for antivirus software to scan all system on your computer. Thus speed of work of the McAfee Stinger faster and somewhat more accurate.
Themselves McAfee...
</description></item><item><title>Download ExtraDisks Home 25.8.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 05 Aug 2025 18:07:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-extradisks-home-7758.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-extradisks-home-7758.html
</guid><description>
ExtraDisks is a set of tools for creating virtual disks on your computer physical drives that do not change and are not divided into additional partitions. The program contains tools for creating encrypted disks, file-based virtual disks and directory-based virtual disks. The current version includes the following tools: Encrypted Disks, Virtual Disks, Folder Disks, Startup Manager, System Tweaker.
Features of ExtraDisks
ExtraDisks: Encrypted Disk
This tool is used to create encrypted...
</description></item><item><title>Download Extra Subst Home 10.8</title><pubDate> Tue, 05 Aug 2025 18:07:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-extra-subst-2605.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-extra-subst-2605.html
</guid><description>
Extra Subst is program designed to help access to the folder is regular use of your computer easier. It is also used to create, edit and remove virtual drives of your computer. Extra Subst creates virtual drives on the basis of the selected folder. Physical drives remain unchanged and are not divided into additional partitions.
Create a new virtual disk is very simple, because you only need to specify the folder which will be connected to, then select the letters and go to it. New virtual...
</description></item><item><title>Download Fast File Encryptor 13.8</title><pubDate> Tue, 05 Aug 2025 18:06:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fast-file-encryptor-2606.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fast-file-encryptor-2606.html
</guid><description>
Fast File Encryptor is the encoder files fast designed for fast processing of the file very big. It can encrypt or decrypt files, contents of folders and contains a lot of additional tools. In addition, there is a tool responsible to completely remove files from the hard drive, you need it if you don't want to leave traces 100 percent in the system. You need to specify the password or key, then select the encryption method, remember remember everything, otherwise it will not work, then...
</description></item></channel></rss>