<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 15:47:21 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 15:47:21 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Windows and Office Genuine ISO Verifier 12.29.50.25</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 17:47:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-and-office-genuine-iso-verifier-542.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-and-office-genuine-iso-verifier-542.html
</guid><description>
Windows and Office Genuine ISO Verifier is a small utility used to check for Microsoft Office and Windows ISO genuine or not by carrying out verification fast SHA-1 and MD5. The software has a friendly interface with the user and not cause you any real trouble whatsoever while navigating.
Users use tool requires to specify the file input and the application will automatically perform the rest of the work. Windows and Office Genuine ISO Verifier can compare the file SHA-1 with the...
</description></item><item><title>Download AllDup 4.5.72</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 17:42:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-alldup-2023.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-alldup-2023.html
</guid><description>
AllDup is a file manager app intuitive comes with a powerful search engine to help you find and delete the duplicate files. You can copy the AllDup on any USB flash drive or any other device and carry it with you whenever you want to scan the computer to copy files. Added to that, it does not leave any traces in the Windows Registry.
AllDup - Manager and search file
The search process can be done on name, extension, size, contents, date last modified, attributes, and creation date....
</description></item><item><title>Download CyberLink PhotoDirector Ultra 2026 v17.0.1205.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 17:41:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-photodirector-ultra-129.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-photodirector-ultra-129.html
</guid><description>
Cyberlink PhotoDirector Ultra is known to be photo editing tools and videos with the effect is extremely rich, help you to change the style for the individual images or the videos of his favorite. This software integrated the 3D engine helps to speed up Video processing, which allows accessing the repository effect online and extract the Videos into the movies 3D Bru-ray, 3D AVCHD.
Cyberlink PhotoDirector Ultra to offer users a more professional tool to handle their images, remove...
</description></item><item><title>Download Free YouTube Download 4.4.47.1210 Premium</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 17:40:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-download-1177.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-download-1177.html
</guid><description>
Free YouTube Download Premium is the most popular application to download videos from YouTube. The program was released in 2006 and regularly updated since then. Use the program to download and convert YouTube videos to view offline anytime.
Free YouTube Download - added Support to download youtube
Download more videos! Save whole playlists and YouTube channels, videos from a playlist individually (history, video be favorite, favourites, Watch later), videos from many different...
</description></item><item><title>Download reaConverter Pro 8.0.171</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 17:40:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html
</guid><description>
reaConverter Pro is software image processing feature with batch conversion and image editing periodically becomes simple. eaConverter also provide command line utilities allow you to process images automatically, thus helping you shorten the time for other work.
reaConverter Pro integrated powerful tool of Uber with many great features. It provides advanced solutions to process and adjust images. Management of the conversion process the base image with the latest version of...
</description></item><item><title>Download AllMapSoft Universal Maps Downloader 10.233</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 17:39:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-universal-maps-downloader-736.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-universal-maps-downloader-736.html
</guid><description>
AllMapSoft Universal Maps Downloader is software download map images on the computer for offline viewing support many types such as Google Maps, Yahoo maps, Bing maps, OpenStreet Maps, Yandex Maps, Ovi Maps, MapQuest Maps. All the downloaded photos will be saved on disk. You can view downloaded maps by Maps Viewer Or you can combine them into one big bmp, or jpg file tif by Maps Combiner, and also you can export all the tiles into a database format MBTiles.
AllMapSoft Universal Maps...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaMonkey Gold 2024.2.0.3184</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 17:39:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediamonkey-gold-231.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediamonkey-gold-231.html
</guid><description>
MediaMonkey Gold is music manager and music player multimedia for the music collection and iPod users. MediaMonkey lists the audio file of you as CD, OGG, WMA, MPC, FLAC, APE, WAV and MP3 and includes the edit smart card and an automatic file and folder to arrange your music library.
MediaMonkey Gold also has CD ripper, CD / DVD Burner, and audio converter for saving music, and manual or editor list automatically to create mixed music.
Features MediaMonkey Gold
	Automatically find...
</description></item><item><title>Download Summitsoft FontPack Pro Master Collection 2025</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 17:39:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-summitsoft-fontpack-pro-master-collection-10951.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-summitsoft-fontpack-pro-master-collection-10951.html
</guid><description>
Summitsoft FontPack Pro Master Collection is a comprehensive font collection provided by Summitsoft Corporation. It includes a wide range of fonts suitable for various design projects, from graphic design to web design, presentations, branding, and more. Collections typically include a variety of typeface options, from classic and elegant fonts to modern and unique fonts, meeting different design preferences and needs.
All of our Creative Fonts are OpenType, the same industry standard...
</description></item><item><title>Download DBF Viewer 2000 8.94</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 17:38:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbf-viewer-2000-7869.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbf-viewer-2000-7869.html
</guid><description>
DBF Viewer 2000 is a fast, efficient solution for viewing and editing all types of DBF files. It can handle files from dBase, Visual dBase, Foxpro, Visual FoxPro and Clipper, just to name a few, with performance that easily rivals expensive professional database utilities. DBF Viewer 2000 is extremely fast, does any task, just one simple query and cleanup copy to export data at lightning speed.
With DBF Editor's simple, dynamically generated visual dialogs, you can easily view the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Geometric Glovius Prime 6.7.0.120</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 17:37:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-geometric-glovius-pro-754.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-geometric-glovius-pro-754.html
</guid><description>
Geometric Glovius Pro is viewer CAD 3D modern for files CATIA, NX, STEP, IGES, Pro/ENGINEER and Creo, SolidWorks, Inventor and Solid Edge. The work of Geometric Glovius Pro is made exact measurements, cut dynamic sections, compare differences between models and export to 3D PDF, STL and Glovius Mobile.
Geometric Glovius Pro - manager, and view CAD 3D
The features of Geometric Glovius Pro
	Modern interface, simple, easy to use
	Mobile app for free for iOS &amp;amp; Android powerful...
</description></item><item><title>Download Zoom Player Max 22.0.0.2200</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 17:37:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zoom-player-max-104.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zoom-player-max-104.html
</guid><description>
Zoom Player MAX help you to see the film on DVD, Blu-ray, Flash movies and HD format with high quality and the ability to display subtitles in English very well. The advantage of software is that takes up very little system resources to play the movie with quick speed, change the wallpaper options while viewing movies.
Zoom Player MAX is the movies, browse high-quality photos on the computer with the advantages such as compact size, quick start, built-in codec. The application supports...
</description></item><item><title>Download MyLanViewer Enterprise 6.7.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 17:36:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mylanviewer-enterprise-1274.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mylanviewer-enterprise-1274.html
</guid><description>
MyLanViewer is a program for scanning IP address, Netbios and LAN / Network powerful for Windows tool whois and traceroute, remote shutdown and process management Wake On LAN (WOL), scan and monitor wireless networks. This app will help you find all IP addresses, MAC addresses and shared folders of computers on the network wired or wireless (Wi-Fi).
MyLanViewer Enterprise - Scan IP address LAN/Network
The program scans network and displays the computer network in your window, friends...
</description></item><item><title>Download AllMapSoft Offline Map Maker 8.364</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 17:36:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-offline-map-maker-656.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-offline-map-maker-656.html
</guid><description>
AllMapSoft Offline Map Maker is software create, organize, offline map from Google Maps, Yahoo maps, Bing maps and Openstreetmap. You can view offline maps downloaded with map viewer offline. And you can zoom out or zoom in the offline map or export map under the file format .BMP with file world xxx.bpw, and can output files xxx.map for OziExplorer. If you want to make a offline map of your city by yourself, it is very useful for you.
Features AllMapSoft Offline Map Maker
	You can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Keyshot Network Rendering 2025.3 v14.2.1.3</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 17:30:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-keyshot-network-rendering-8910.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-keyshot-network-rendering-8910.html
</guid><description>
Keyshot Network Rendering is software that allows you to connect multiple computer systems in your office network and use available hardware to significantly reduce rendering times. In addition, rendering over the network is very convenient. You can continue working in KeyShot or any other application without slowing down your system while designated render stations handle your rendering “work”.
It is a software solution developed by KeyShot that allows users to distribute rendering...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tecplot Fieldview 2025</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 17:29:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intelligent-light-fieldview-6314.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intelligent-light-fieldview-6314.html
</guid><description>
FieldView is the technical and technical software name of the company, the familiar name of Intelligent Light in the field of engineering analysis on the models you designed. Using this software, you will be able to increase your ability to make decisions in your projects. The software in front of you is designed for engineers who want to get better results in their built model in the shorter time. This software with powerful tools can help you a lot in increasing the speed of action and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium 4.4.47.1210</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 17:29:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-to-mp3-converter-premium-844.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-to-mp3-converter-premium-844.html
</guid><description>
Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium version is a software used to convert YouTube to MP3, extract audio from playlists YouTube, show listings, charts, video responses, channels, favorites of the user. With Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium, you can download and convert playlists, channels, stream original tv series and get them into iTunes at the same time.
Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium - convert YouTube to MP3
Features Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium from the...
</description></item><item><title>Download AllMapSoft Google Maps Downloader 8.885</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 17:28:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-google-maps-downloader-2796.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-google-maps-downloader-2796.html
</guid><description>
AllMapSoft Google Maps Downloader is a reliable application aimed at downloading maps from Google at high speed. The result is a set of small images can be combined in a larger map. This can serve in a large variety of projects, from creating a tile map to presentations and tutorials.
Google Maps Downloader successfully fulfills both of those conditions, providing simple means to quickly grab maps at the resolution satisfactory. In addition, it is extremely easy to use and integrated a...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adlice Protect (formerly RogueKiller) 16.5.4.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 17:28:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rogueKiller-171.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rogueKiller-171.html
</guid><description>
RogueKiller is a tool anti-malware independent can assist advanced users with the removal of a number of difficulties in the removal of malware, in security software rogue special.
The program can terminate processes, malware has to know to you can delete them manually or use the tool clear of the Tuesday to complete the work. RogueKiller can also restore HOSTS file as well as your DNS settings and Proxy, which is often modified by rogue applications.
RogueKiller
When you run...
</description></item><item><title>Download TeamViewer QuickSupport 15.73.3</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 17:27:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-teamviewer-quicksupport-1933.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-teamviewer-quicksupport-1933.html
</guid><description>
A different version of TeamViewer is TeamViewer QuickSupport is a solution easy to use allows you to share your desktop with a users TeamViewer other to receive technical support or other support. All what you need to do is run the TeamViewer QuickSupport and provides for the remote user ID and your password to grant access to the computer to your desk. Only people you trust can connect to your computer and access password will automatically change after each session.
The software also...
</description></item><item><title>Download PLC-Lab Pro 3.3.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 17:27:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-plc-lab-pro-6025.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-plc-lab-pro-6025.html
</guid><description>
With  PLC-Lab , you can create your own simple digital duo to train your PLC or find all logic errors in your PLC program. Objects in PLC-Lab provide rich design and installation options, so the variety of project types that can be done with PLC-Lab is very high
Objects can be assigned physical properties, which in turn affect the behavior of the objects during the simulation. For example, objects may depend on gravity and be magnetic. In addition, you can set parameters such as...
</description></item><item><title>Download AllmapSoft Google Satellite Maps Downloader 8.414</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 17:26:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-google-satellite-maps-downloader-687.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-google-satellite-maps-downloader-687.html
</guid><description>
AllmapSoft Google Satellite Maps Downloader is software help download map images from google maps on computer for you to get the satellite images from google map. All the downloaded photos will be saved on disk. You can see the map is downloaded by viewer Or you can combine them into the map BMP, big. It supports proxy server. And you can easily get the longitude and latitude of each image tile small download.
You can use offline maps in GIS software such as Global Mapper, QGIS,...
</description></item><item><title>Download AnyTrans for iOS 8.9.14.20251216</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 17:26:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anytrans-for-ios-755.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anytrans-for-ios-755.html
</guid><description>
AnyTrans for iOS is content manager essential fully managed iPhone, Android and content of your cloud. Including all mobile devices, all cloud drives from your iPhone, iPad, iPod touch to phones and tablets. From local disk to cloud storage. AnyTrans has protected them all, providing you convenient management for all data and your files, regardless of whether they are stored where.
AnyTrans is the one stop solution to meet all the management needs of your data. For the first time, you can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Software Ideas Modeler Ultimate 15.20</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 17:25:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-software-ideas-modeler-ultimate-10388.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-software-ideas-modeler-ultimate-10388.html
</guid><description>
Software Ideas Modeler Ultimate is a feature-rich CASE tool that can help you design software using various modeling tools and schematic notations. It will help you create a UML model, ERD designer, diagram generator, wireframing tool or BPMN editor.
Features of Software Ideas Modeler Ultimate
	Tools for UML diagrams, class diagrams, block diagrams, data flow diagrams, and other tools help you design your software or its key parts accurately.
	Handle user requests...
</description></item><item><title>Download GOM Player Free 2.3.115 Build 5385</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 17:25:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gom-player-994.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gom-player-994.html
</guid><description>
GOM Player is a program to listen to music for free with the ability to play all format music and video now without the need to install additional codec. GOM Media Player brings all video codecs needed to play multiple video formats and various audio. Simple interface, light volume but powerful function is the factor which makes GOM Player famous in the music software.
GOM Media Player according to the reviews is considered the listen to music, watch video best. The user can control GOM...
</description></item><item><title>Download Danil Pristupov Fork 2.15.3</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Dec 2025 17:24:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fork-6879.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fork-6879.html
</guid><description>
Fork is a great Git client app that allows you to keep tabs on every file line so you can know who is the last person to make changes. The simple and intuitive design of this app helps the management of all of your warehouses much easier. The Fork interface is extremely friendly to users. There is a long list of repositories, branches, origins, tags and archives on the left side of the screen.
With Fork, you can also search and open any of the repositories quickly, from the top of the...
</description></item></channel></rss>