<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 13:40:18 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 13:40:18 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Pulsar Music Player Pro 1.13.8 build 285</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 16:40:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pulsar-music-player-pro-9602.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pulsar-music-player-pro-9602.html
</guid><description>
Pulsar Music Player has long been one of the best music players on Android. It is an ad-free offline audio player. Its beautiful user interface matches every detail of material design principles. Pulsar contains almost every feature needed to satisfy all your musical needs, including: seamless playback, lyrics display, interlacing, playback speed adjustment, tag editing, Last recording .fm, Chromecast, voice command, Android Auto, equalizer, music visualizer, equalizer, ReplayGain, sleep...
</description></item><item><title>Download IgeBlock - Tube ad blocker 2.0.5</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 16:39:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-igeblock-tube-ad-blocker-11113.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-igeblock-tube-ad-blocker-11113.html
</guid><description>
IgeBlock is an app that allows you to watch videos without ads, watch videos with sound, and watch videos in pop-up player while using other apps.
IgeBlock Features
Block ads
	Automatically skip annoying video ads.
	Automatically skip ads even in sound and pop-up player mode.
Pop-up player (PIP)
	You can play videos in floating mode without additional permissions.
Can be added
	Full screen touch lock function
	looped video
	Bookmark function without logging in
	Timer to turn...
</description></item><item><title>Download Yoga &amp;amp; Meditation | Gotta Yoga 2.1.24</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 16:39:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-yoga-meditation-gotta-yoga-13510.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-yoga-meditation-gotta-yoga-13510.html
</guid><description>
Gotta Yoga is a versatile yoga and meditation app designed for users of all levels, from beginners to advanced practitioners. The app offers over 350 classes, including styles like Vinyasa, Yin, Hatha, Ashtanga, Iyengar, meditation and pranayama, with session lengths ranging from 5 to 90 minutes, many of which can be taken offline.
Key features include:
	Live classes via Zoom with certified yoga teachers, providing real-time interaction and feedback.
	Integrated with Apple Health and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Librera PRO - Book reader 9.0.19</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 16:38:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-librera-pro-all-my-books-9008.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-librera-pro-all-my-books-9008.html
</guid><description>
PRO Librera Reader is an easy-to-use and highly configurable reading application that supports most popular document formats, including: PDF, EPUB, EPUB3, MOBI, DjVu, FB2, FB2.zip, TXT, RTF, AZW, AZW3, CBR, CBZ, HTML, XPS, MHT and more. With a simple yet powerful interface, Librera Reader makes reading documents a real pleasure. Librera even has a unique hands-free, auto-scrolling music mode.
Some key features of Librera reader include:
Easily explore documents with optional and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Turbo Alarm: Alarm clock 9.9.5</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 16:37:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-turbo-alarm-alarm-clock-10935.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-turbo-alarm-alarm-clock-10935.html
</guid><description>
Turbo Alarm is the most complete and advanced alarm clock available. It has everything you need to get out of bed easier. Perfect for both heavy sleepers and early risers. Elegant, simple, reliable material design, allowing you to play your own music.
Main features of Turbo Alarm
	Music playlist - set a folder of your songs or music playlist as ringtone to have a different music alarm clock every day!
	Skip any day of the week – long press a day to skip and you'll never forget to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wakey: Keep Screen On 11.2.1 build 805922877</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 16:37:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wakey-keep-your-screen-on-8414.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wakey-keep-your-screen-on-8414.html
</guid><description>
Wakey: Keep your screen on is a mobile application that provides users with a variety of tools to help them wake up and start their day on their Android devices. It typically includes features such as alarm clock, weather forecast, and news. The app also includes a variety of customizable settings, such as the ability to choose between different alarm sounds, to set snooze time, and to choose the news sources.
Features of Wakey for Android
	Alarm clock: Users can set alarms to wake up...
</description></item><item><title>Download Code Editor - Compiler &amp;amp; IDE 0.11.2 build 103</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 16:37:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-code-editor-compiler-ide-8735.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-code-editor-compiler-ide-8735.html
</guid><description>
Code editor is an optimized text editor focused on coding. It is a useful tool for developing on Android. It contains essential features for coding, including syntax highlighting, auto-indenting, code support, auto-completion, etc.
Features of Code Editor for Android
	Syntax highlighting for over 110 languages ​​(c++, java, javascript, html, markdown, php, Perl, python, lua, Dart, etc.).
	Supports code folding and auto-completion.
	Easy navigation between multiple tabs.
	Unlimited...
</description></item><item><title>Download Multi Timer: Timer + Stopwatch 2.2.14</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 16:36:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-timer-plus-with-stopwatch-10105.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-timer-plus-with-stopwatch-10105.html
</guid><description>
Multi Timer is a comprehensive mobile app designed to revolutionize how you track and manage time. The stopwatch and digital timer are simple, easy -to -use and accurate applications for Android to help you measure the time of all situations, such as sports, cooking, etc. With the time application, you will enjoy the freedom of the time counter and the timer and the full -featured and complete stopwatch with the ring and the clear display function.
Features of Multi Timer
	Easy to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Dumbbell Workout at Home &amp;amp; Gym 5.15</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 16:35:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-dumbbell-home-workout-8634.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-dumbbell-home-workout-8634.html
</guid><description>
Dumbbell Workout at Home is a fitness app for Android devices that offers users a variety of workout routines that can be done at home using only weights. This app is designed for people who want to stay fit and healthy but don't have access to a gym or workout equipment.
Features of Weightlifting at Home for Android
	Customizable workout routines: The app offers users a variety of workout routines that can be customized based on their fitness level, goals, and the amount of time they...
</description></item><item><title>Download Glucose tracker - Diabetic diary 3.5.3</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 16:34:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-glucose-tracker-diabetic-diary-13642.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-glucose-tracker-diabetic-diary-13642.html
</guid><description>
Diabetes Diary - will become an indispensable companion for anyone with gestational, type 1 or type 2 diabetes. The blood glucose diary will allow you to regularly track your hemoglobin, sugar, blood pressure, insulin reminders and also add tags, medications, conditions and weight to each record. With the help of regular sugar diary, observe the trends in the blood sugar diary and decide with that information how you can treat it and also provide your doctor with all the necessary...
</description></item><item><title>Download SmartSystemMenu 2.32.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 02:54:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-smartsystemmenu-6018.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-smartsystemmenu-6018.html
</guid><description>
SmartSystemMenu will help to work with more windows becoming a more efficient process with many useful functions to arrange your work. It can be attached to the title bar menu for easy access. The fact that it can be portable is just another bonus because you can quickly upload it to the flash drive to use on any machine you might be using.
SmartSystemMenu will be a significant upgrade to the default Windows installation with the ability to be added to help with window management...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare PDFelement Pro 12.0.6.3738</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Sep 2025 17:24:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-pdfelement-pro-105.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-pdfelement-pro-105.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare PDFelement Pro support users to convert PDF to office documents for easier use, modify in every situation. Is one of the software conversion material is rated best today, integrated with many features. We recommend that you should use experience software many useful features this.
Wondershare PDFelement Pro - conversion Fie PDF more features, multi-language
Wondershare PDFelement Pro what?
Convert PDF into Word, Excel, PowerPoint...
• Convert PDF and protected PDF into...
</description></item><item><title>Download Master PDF Editor 5.9.95</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Sep 2025 17:24:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-master-pdf-editor-612.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-master-pdf-editor-612.html
</guid><description>
Master PDF Editor is a powerful software that helps users to view, create and modify PDF documents or combine multiple files into one, split a source document into several documents, and also review, sign, and encrypt PDF files. With Master PDF Editor you can add text with any format to documents in PDF or edit existing text. You can also insert images into your document, select and move the object, change the size of the object save image to a file and copy them to the...
</description></item><item><title>Download JRiver Media Center 34.0.70</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Sep 2025 17:22:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jriver-media-center-110.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jriver-media-center-110.html
</guid><description>
JRiver Media Center can help you strictly manage all your files media and enjoy them in a completely new way. Launching the application for the first time, users will be immediately impressed with the intuitive and eye-catching interface with many interesting features to explore. Most people who have used JRiver Media Center evaluate that the software interface design is youthful and modern.
The software for arranging cover art of music files is also extremely neat, especially Insert...
</description></item><item><title>Download SkinFiner 5.7.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Sep 2025 17:22:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-skinfiner-6346.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-skinfiner-6346.html
</guid><description>
SkinFiner  is photo editing software designed to free you from tedious manual work in skin retouching. It helps to smooth and strengthen the skin easily and quickly.
Features of SkinFiner
	Smartly smooths skin and removes blemishes while preserving skin texture to give portraits a natural and professional look
	Skin tone adjustment helps you to improve skin tone, change skin color, refine skin light with shadows and highlights, adjust skin brightness and contrast, make skin look...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mozilla Firefox 143.0.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Sep 2025 17:21:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-firefox-quantum-501.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-firefox-quantum-501.html
</guid><description>
Firefox Quantum is a web browser independently provide the tabbed browsing combined with numerous handy features like pop-up blocker, Bookmarks, direct (integrated RSS), password manager, and more. Functionality can be extended with dozens of plugins available for free (extensions).
Firefox Quantum are interface completely new, beautiful, neat, minimalistic and delicate, eats less RAM to 30% compared with the old version and solve the condition consuming capacity
Firefox can import all...
</description></item><item><title>Download MEmu Android Emulator 9.2.8</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Sep 2025 17:20:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-memu-2975.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-memu-2975.html
</guid><description>
MEmu or also known as Android Emulator is the Android emulator light and free, allowing Windows users to enjoy Android experience the original on the computer and device Microsoft their. This app provides outstanding performance, allowing you to play on PC a series of games designed to run on Android devices. This app allows you to play the game favorite Android on larger screens, to bring you a better gaming experience.
MEmu - Android emulator, lightweight and free
Software MEmu also...
</description></item><item><title>Download Any Video Downloader Pro 9.6.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Sep 2025 17:20:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-video-downloader-pro-3731.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-video-downloader-pro-3731.html
</guid><description>
Any Video Downloader Pro is software support you can download video HD 720p, 1080p, 2K, 4K and 8K from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion, Vimeo, Metacafe and thousands of video sharing sites, other. It is a tool to speed up multi-threading can speed up your download faster up to 5 times. This helpful program support download at the same time. Any Video Downloader Pro lets you download multiple videos at the same time. Moreover, it allows you to pause and resume downloads if you need more...
</description></item><item><title>Download R-Drive Image 7.3 Build 7310</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Sep 2025 17:19:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-drive-image-1971.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-drive-image-1971.html
</guid><description>
R-Drive Image is a powerful utility provides create a file disk image for backup purposes, or copy. File disk image contains the exact copy each and every byte of hard drive, partition or logical disk and can be created with various levels compression without stopping Windows os and therefore without interrupting your work. The image file this drive can then be stored in many places, including various removable media as different as a CD-R (W) / DVD, Iomega Zip or Jazz, etc.
R-Drive...
</description></item><item><title>Download WYSIWYG Web Builder 20.3.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Sep 2025 17:18:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wysiwyg-web-builder-177.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wysiwyg-web-builder-177.html
</guid><description>
WYSIWYG Web Builder : The construction of the website from scratch using HTML code isn't a pleasant process, even when you know what you are doing. The website can be built using WYSIWYG Web Builder with using the element similar to the package published on the desktop: text and images placed in frames and tables on the page, so very little surprised when most of the efforts to make the web become a experience user-friendly than. the controls do you use to build your pages.
WYSIWYG Web...
</description></item><item><title>Download R-Drive Image BootCD 7.3 Build 7310</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Sep 2025 17:18:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-drive-image-bootcd-4878.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-drive-image-bootcd-4878.html
</guid><description>
R-Drive Image BootCD is a powerful utility provides create a file disk image for backup purposes, or copy. File disk image contains the exact copy each and every byte of hard drive, partition or logical disk and can be created with various levels compression without stopping Windows os and therefore without interrupting your work. The image file this drive can then be stored in many places, including various removable media as different as a CD-R (W) / DVD, Iomega Zip or Jazz,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Automatic Email Processor 3.8.14</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Sep 2025 17:17:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-automatic-email-processor-702.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-automatic-email-processor-702.html
</guid><description>
Automatic Email Processor is a software for managing Email in Outlook efficiency by automatically working with predefined settings. The user interface is divided into two main parts, which is the area allows you to view a list of profiles that you have created and their status and the filters located in the lower part of the interface.
Automatic Email Processor is a comprehensive solution in the archive and print emails and attachments on Outlook fully-automatic. Therefore, you can create...
</description></item><item><title>Download Stardock Start11 2.5.5.3 Beta</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Sep 2025 17:16:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stardock-start11-7029.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stardock-start11-7029.html
</guid><description>
Start11 is an application capable of customizing the Start Menu and Taskbar on Windows 11 and Windows 10. This is an application that allows users to customize Windows 11 to suit their preferences. his personal. Start11 will help you bring the new Start Menu of Windows 11 to Windows 10. And vice versa, Start11 also helps you to bring the Start Menu of Windows 10 to Windows 11.
Start11 also helps users bring some functions of Windows 10 to Windows 11 through customizing the Taskbar such...
</description></item><item><title>Download DumboFab Blu-ray Ripper 7.3.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Sep 2025 17:16:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dumbofab-blu-ray-ripper-12024.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dumbofab-blu-ray-ripper-12024.html
</guid><description>
DumboFab Blu-ray Ripper is a widely used Blu-ray/DVD to MP4 conversion software in just a few minutes, to highly compressed HEVC, MKV (multi-track) and many other formats for playback again on iPhone, iPad, Android, HDTV, Mac, PSP, Xbox, VLC, etc.; Copy Blu-ray/DVD in 1:1 ratio with original quality.
Equipped with leading Blu-ray/DVD decoding algorithms, DumboFab Blu-ray Ripper supports copying almost all Blu-ray and DVD movies regardless of region restrictions. It also allows you to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cascadeur 2025.2.4</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Sep 2025 17:15:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cascadeur-9720.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cascadeur-9720.html
</guid><description>
Cascadeur is a standalone software for 3D keyframe animation of human figures or other characters. Never before has it been so easy and fun to create an animation from scratch or re-edit. Thanks to AI-powered tools, you can perform key poses very quickly, see the physical results immediately, and adjust the secondary movement. All while retaining full control at any point.
Cascadeur uses advanced simulation techniques and algorithms to accurately simulate the movements and interactions...
</description></item></channel></rss>