<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 19:58:25 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 19:58:25 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download MobiPDF: PDF Editor &amp;amp; Scanner 11.8.267269</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 19:55:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pdf-extra-scan-edit-sign-8390.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pdf-extra-scan-edit-sign-8390.html
</guid><description>
PDF Extra PDF Editor &amp;amp; Scanner is a mobile application that allows users to create, edit and sign PDF documents on their Android or iOS devices. It includes many tools and features that make it easy to work with PDF files, including scanning, editing, and signing. This application also allows users to combine multiple PDF files into a single document and export PDF files in various file formats, such as JPEG, PNG, and Microsoft Word.
Features of PDF Extra PDF Editor &amp;amp;...
</description></item><item><title>Download MobiOffice: Word, Sheets, PDF 15.8.57529</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 19:55:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-officesuite-word-sheets-pdf-8508.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-officesuite-word-sheets-pdf-8508.html
</guid><description>
OfficeSuite allows you to easily view, edit, and create Word, Excel, and PowerPoint documents and perform advanced PDF operations. Our integrated file manager, Chat app with document exchange capabilities, and tons of other handy tools make this the most feature-rich mobile office solution available on Android. Pre-installed by leading manufacturers including Sony, ZTE, Amazon, Sharp, Acer, CAT, Alcatel, Kyocera, Toshiba, etc.
Features of OfficeSuite for Android
	View, create, and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Photo Studio PRO 2.8.5.4438</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 19:55:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-photo-studio-pro-8247.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-photo-studio-pro-8247.html
</guid><description>
Photo Studio APK is a powerful multifunctional photo editing application for photographers of all levels. It contains a huge set of editing tools for basic and advanced editing of your photos. Turn each of your photos into a finished work of art using a variety of effects, filters, text editing and color enhancement tools, and many other available features.
Features of Photo Studio Pro APK
	More than 200 unique filters, amazing special effects, large collection of picture-in-picture...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Photoshop Express Photo Editor 17.7.12 build 1986</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 19:54:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-photoshop-express-photo-editor-02en-8249.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-photoshop-express-photo-editor-02en-8249.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Photoshop Express is a mobile photo editing app that allows users to edit photos quickly and easily on their Android devices. Join millions of creators who trust and use Adobe Photoshop Express, one of the best photo editors and collage makers on Android for fast, easy, and powerful editing on mobile devices.
Premium version / No Adobe ID account required
Features of Adobe Photoshop Express APK
	Basic photo editing: Users can crop, rotate, adjust brightness, contrast and...
</description></item><item><title>Download AnExplorer Pro File Transfer 5.8.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 19:54:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-file-manager-pro-tv-usb-otg-8358.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-file-manager-pro-tv-usb-otg-8358.html
</guid><description>
AnExplorer File Explorer is a unique file manager for TV and Watch file management tool. It is simple, small, fast and efficient File Explorer. Only file managers support RTL and display the size of folders on storage. It is designed for all devices including Phones, Phablets, Tablets, Watches and TVs. It is completely designed using Material Design.
Pro TV USBOTG File Manager Features
	Full-featured It provides all file management features including cut, copy, delete, rename,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Lightroom Photo &amp;amp; Video Editor 10.5.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 19:53:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-adobe-lightroom-photo-video-editor-8401.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-adobe-lightroom-photo-video-editor-8401.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Photoshop Lightroom is a powerful, free camera app and photo editor that empowers your photography, helping you capture and edit stunning images. Easy image editing tools like sliders and filters simplify photo editing. Edit full-resolution photos, apply photo filters, or start editing photos anytime, anywhere.
It offers a variety of editing tools, including basic adjustments like cropping, rotation, and brightness control as well as advanced features like color grading, selective...
</description></item><item><title>Download Pulsar Music Player Pro 1.13.5 build 280</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 19:53:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pulsar-music-player-pro-9602.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pulsar-music-player-pro-9602.html
</guid><description>
Pulsar Music Player has long been one of the best music players on Android. It is an ad-free offline audio player. Its beautiful user interface matches every detail of material design principles. Pulsar contains almost every feature needed to satisfy all your musical needs, including: seamless playback, lyrics display, interlacing, playback speed adjustment, tag editing, Last recording .fm, Chromecast, voice command, Android Auto, equalizer, music visualizer, equalizer, ReplayGain, sleep...
</description></item><item><title>Download Easy Notes - Note Taking Apps 1.3.21.0811</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 19:52:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-easy-notes-notebook-notepad-8388.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-easy-notes-notebook-notepad-8388.html
</guid><description>
Easy Notes - Great note taking app, Notepad, Notebook, Free Notes is a free easy to use note taking app for notes app. With this easy notebook and notepad app, take quick notes with colorful backgrounds and checklists to organize notes and tasks easily. Use this aesthetic note taker and note taker to add photos or audio to your notes. Easy Notes is a useful notebook and note-taking app for taking notes and organizing work.
Features of Easy Notes - Notebook, Notepad
	Free Notepad and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Elevate - Brain Training Games 5.202.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 19:52:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-elevate-brain-training-games-8564.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-elevate-brain-training-games-8564.html
</guid><description>
Elevate is a brain training program designed to improve speech, processing speed, memory skills, mental math, and more. Each person is provided with their own personalized learning program, which is adjusted over time to maximize results.
The more you practice with Elevate, the more you'll improve key cognitive skills proven to increase productivity, earning potential, and confidence. More than 90% said their vocabulary, memory, math skills and overall acuity improved when they...
</description></item><item><title>Download AccuWeather: Weather Radar 21.1.1-6-rc</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 19:52:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-accuweather-weather-radar-8893.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-accuweather-weather-radar-8893.html
</guid><description>
Weather warnings from AccuWeather are exceptionally accurate. Whether it's windy, sunny or rainy, you can stay one step ahead with AccuWeather weather radar. Be prepared for daily forecasts or sudden changes in weather with live alerts and accurate weather forecasts. Daily weather snapshots provide storm warnings, weather updates and RealFeel Temperature®, helping to predict today's weather.
With AccuWeather's superior accuracy™ for local forecasts, you'll never miss a memorable...
</description></item><item><title>Download Listen Audiobook Player 5.3.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 19:51:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-listen-audiobook-player-8511.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-listen-audiobook-player-8511.html
</guid><description>
Listen Audiobook Player is a mobile app for playing audiobooks on your phone or tablet. It lets you play, pause, rewind, and fast-forward audiobooks with ease, while also providing a convenient way to track your listening progress.
Some key features of Listen Audiobook Player include:
	Library Management: Allows you to store and organize your audiobooks in a virtual library for easy access.
	Bookmark: Automatically saves your listening position so you can pick up where you left...
</description></item><item><title>Download TuneIn Radio Pro - Live Radio 39.8.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 19:51:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-tunein-radio-pro-live-radio-8217.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-tunein-radio-pro-live-radio-8217.html
</guid><description>
TuneIn Radio Pro allows users to listen to many radio stations and podcasts from around the world. The Pro version offers additional features like the ability to record live stations, remove ads, and access more premium content. It is available for download on Google Play Store as an apk file.
All your sounds in one app:
	News: Listen and update live news 24/7 from local, national and global news sources, including CNBC, CNN, MSNBC and FOX News Radio.
	Sports: Listen live to NFL, NHL...
</description></item><item><title>Download ClevCalc - Calculator 2.23.16</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 19:51:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-clevcalc-calculator-8333.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-clevcalc-calculator-8333.html
</guid><description>
ClevCalc - Calculator is a mobile application that provides calculator functionality for Android devices. This is a simple, easy-to-use calculator application that can perform basic mathematical operations such as addition, subtraction, multiplication and division as well as more advanced functions such as square roots, logarithms and trigonometric functions.&amp;lt; /p&amp;gt;
Features of ClevCalc - Calculator
	Basic math operations such as addition, subtraction, multiplication and...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDF-XChange Pro 10.7.0.398.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 18:27:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-xchange-editor-pro-3422.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-xchange-editor-pro-3422.html
</guid><description>
PDF-XChange Editor Pro is an application to manipulate and create PDF versatile, offering a wide range of useful features and powerful will help you to easily work with PDF files. This application is very flexible and allows you to easily create and modify PDF files. PDF-XChange Editor Pro provides a powerful set of tools and flexibility to work with PDF files, such as editor PDF-XChange new, utilities series, OFFice2PDF and the Addin tool Bar allows you to easily convert multiple file...
</description></item><item><title>Download Balabolka 2.15.0.902</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 18:26:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-balaboka-142.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-balaboka-142.html
</guid><description>
Balabolka is a text-to-speech (TTS) program. It can read text on your screen in a human-like voice. You can use Balabolka to listen to text from a variety of file formats, convert text to spoken audio files, and adjust speech parameters such as speed and pitch. It is often used for accessibility purposes, helping people who have difficulty reading or multi-tasking by listening to text while doing other activities. Balabolka supports multiple languages and uses different TTS engines,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Digiarty Aiarty Video Enhancer 2.5</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 18:26:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-digiarty-aiarty-video-enhancer-13862.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-digiarty-aiarty-video-enhancer-13862.html
</guid><description>
Digiarty Aiarty Video Enhancer is an AI-powered desktop software designed to upscale, denoise, deblur, and enhance videos up to 4K resolution with professional quality and speed. It uses advanced AI models optimized for GPU acceleration and Turbo mode, enabling real-time or near-real-time video processing, including frame interpolation for smooth motion up to 90fps, 120fps, or higher. This tool is effective in restoring low-resolution, old, blurry, jerky or underexposed footage,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Acrobat Pro DC 2025.001.20630 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 18:26:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-001en-adobe-acrobat-pro-458.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-001en-adobe-acrobat-pro-458.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Acrobat Pro DC is a comprehensive software that helps you create and edit the PDF&amp;nbsp;document, or create form, sign, protect PDF, connect, split PDF, export PDF to various formats. The Acrobat Pro DC is the latest version of Adobe with improvements in the interface with the polished ribbon bar and the ability to create and handle pdf files as well as its male versions.
The highlight of the Acrobat Pro DC is probably the ability to connect, store documents on the cloud, you can...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDF-XChange Editor Plus 10.7.0.398.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 18:24:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-xchange-editor-plus-645.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-xchange-editor-plus-645.html
</guid><description>
PDF-XChange Editor Plus is the editor, PDF viewer, compact, fast with many features, add-ons, professional. When using the PDF-XChange Editor Plus, easy for users to create, view, edit, annotate, OCR and digital signing PDF files, plus much more.
PDF-XChange Editor is a PDF editing full-featured. With the help of it, you can edit, fix, add, or delete text easily. Graphics can also be moved, resized or removed.
Features PDF-XChange Editor Plus
Edit documents
	Use a variety of editing...
</description></item><item><title>Download GOM Player Free 2.3.111 Build 5381</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 18:24:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gom-player-994.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gom-player-994.html
</guid><description>
GOM Player is a program to listen to music for free with the ability to play all format music and video now without the need to install additional codec. GOM Media Player brings all video codecs needed to play multiple video formats and various audio. Simple interface, light volume but powerful function is the factor which makes GOM Player famous in the music software.
GOM Media Player according to the reviews is considered the listen to music, watch video best. The user can control GOM...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Downloader 9.16</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 18:23:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html
</guid><description>
YTD Youtube Downloader is an application that reliable and intuitive, allowing you to quickly download YouTube videos and save them to your computer. You can also convert the media files to the format desired video or extract audio streams and save separately. YTD Youtube Downloader lets you save your favorite clips of yourself from Youtube, Facebook, Vimeo and Dailymotion to your desktop. The software supports URLS from many web site hosting, multimedia and allows you to download desired...
</description></item><item><title>Download Muziza YouTube Downloader Converter 8.12</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 18:22:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-muziza-youtube-downloader-converter-3972.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-muziza-youtube-downloader-converter-3972.html
</guid><description>
Muziza YouTube Downloader Converter is a tool to create conditions for an attractive interface and many features to help you to download video clips from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion, Instagram and other sites. Muziza YouTube Downloader Converter can also download the video UHD 8K, 5K, 4K, QHD 2K, HD 1080p and 720p from YouTube. The app allows you download only audio stream from YouTube and save as MP3. You don't need to download the entire video file.
Muziza YouTube Downloader...
</description></item><item><title>Download Clementine Music Player 1.4.1-50</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 18:22:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-clementine-4762.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-clementine-4762.html
</guid><description>
Clementine is a tools multi-platform software which allows you to listen to music from hard drive, library, audio CDS or the Internet, as well as manage it, edit the card and see the lyrics. Clementine is inspired by Amarok 1.4, focusing on a easy to use interface for searching and playing your music.
Clementine also allows you can view track information such as length, bit rate, sample rate, size, file type, number of times played and your ranking, as well as complete the card...
</description></item><item><title>Download TubeMate Downloader 5.22</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 18:22:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubemate-downloader-4250.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubemate-downloader-4250.html
</guid><description>
TubeMate Downloader is a smart application that lets you download any clip you want from the website hosting the main video and convert them in when download at or then. If you need a simple and effective tool to download videos, you can give it a try. With TubeMate Downloader, you can directly drag and drop video link from your browser into the drop-down box or application window to start downloading. You don't even need to copy and paste the video URL.
TubeMate Downloader - Support...
</description></item><item><title>Download Disk Sorter Ultimate 17.2.14 + Server + Pro</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 18:21:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-disk-sorter-ultimate-1464.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-disk-sorter-ultimate-1464.html
</guid><description>
Disk Sorter Ultimate is the utility classification file lightweight and simple helps people detect files on most types of drives, as well as manage them according to many different criteria to create more capacity on the disc. This app allows you to search through the 500,000 files, have storage capacity of 2TB. To start sorting, all what you have to do is select a directory, drive or server and click the button "Classification". You should know that you can search for the type specific...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tomabo MP4 Downloader Pro 5.7</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 18:21:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tomabo-mp4-downloader-pro-3602.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tomabo-mp4-downloader-pro-3602.html
</guid><description>
Tomabo MP4 Downloader Pro is the app designed exclusively for Windows users to help them download videos from the Internet. In addition, it also increase download speeds by up to 500%, or even more. Tomabo MP4 Downloader Pro, interface design, simple, well-organized, beautifully. Here, users can view a list of videos has download with gravatar, URL, quality, duration and size of them. Software allows download video series at the same time, at the same time, support create a list of clips...
</description></item></channel></rss>