<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 20:01:36 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 20:01:36 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download SwapVoice 1.0.14</title><pubDate> Wed, 05 Nov 2025 18:22:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-swapvoice-14126.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-swapvoice-14126.html
</guid><description>
Convert your voice into instant, actionable text with SwapVoice's intelligent trigger recognition system, for just a one-time subscription fee instead of the monthly licensing fees of other similar tools. Perfect for professionals, content creators, and anyone who wants to work faster and smarter.
SwapVoice Features
	Offline Speech Recognition - Cloud-Independent, Absolutely Secure
	Multilingual Support - 15 languages ​​including English, Dutch, German, French, Spanish, Italian,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Duplicate Cleaner Pro 5.26.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 05 Nov 2025 18:21:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-duplicate-cleaner-pro-1591.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-duplicate-cleaner-pro-1591.html
</guid><description>
Duplicate Cleaner Pro is software scan and sort content in hard drive to find and remove files duplicate do not use. The special of Duplicate Cleaner Pro is that it will deep scan all file types photos, music, movies, videos, documents Word, presentation PowerPoint, text files-you name it, if it appears twice on your computer then Duplicate Cleaner will find it. When these files are found, you are provided with helpful tools to allow you to select copies to delete or move. These files can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Gilisoft Copy Protect 8.3.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 05 Nov 2025 18:21:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-copy-protect-8047.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-copy-protect-8047.html
</guid><description>
Gilisoft Copy Protect is software that helps you protect audio, video, PDF, DOC, PPT, XLS and image files so that they cannot be copied or distributed by illegal means. Users can play from, video encoded on macOS, android using Gilisoft's GCP reader.
Features of Gilisoft Copy Protect
	A document security tool that creates shareless GCP files to protect your Video, Photo, DOC, PDF, XLS, PPT files from unauthorized sharing, editing, copying or viewing .
	Protect document files from...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tenorshare 4DDiG File Repair 4.3.0.7</title><pubDate> Wed, 05 Nov 2025 18:20:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tenorshare-4ddig-file-repair-5630.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tenorshare-4ddig-file-repair-5630.html
</guid><description>
Tenorshare 4DDiG File Repair is AI-powered software to repair damaged or damaged videos, photos, files and audios, improve their quality and add color to black media white. 4DDiG photo editing solves all photo problems like blurry photos, overexposed photos, etc. Powered by AI, it can dramatically improve image resolution and colorize black and white photos in seconds, not hours.
Features of Tenorshare 4DDiG File Repair
	Easily repair any blurry, overexposed and damaged videos, photos...
</description></item><item><title>Download Fotosizer Professional 3.20.1.592</title><pubDate> Wed, 05 Nov 2025 18:20:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fotosizer-professional-2279.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fotosizer-professional-2279.html
</guid><description>
Fotosizer is a photo editing tool / photo series. It lets you resize hundreds of photos in few minutes quickly and easily. Increasingly, sharing photos on the internet is becoming increasingly popular. Image, is represented as JPEG files from digital cameras, taken at high resolution too big to send over the Internet, with some photos ending at 5 mega bytes. Upload photos to a website share photos is good, but 10, 20, or even more, this can last forever, especially on a dial-up...
</description></item><item><title>Download Zortam Mp3 Media Studio Pro 33.45</title><pubDate> Wed, 05 Nov 2025 18:08:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zortam-mp3-media-studio-pro-135.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zortam-mp3-media-studio-pro-135.html
</guid><description>
Zortam Mp3 Media Studio Pro brings you rich processing tools music includes extract and convert music from CD to Mp3 format, edit, music cards, music download....You can also create discs CD high-quality music, with Zortam Mp3 Media Studio search music files duplicated to remove them from the system, rename music files, switch back and forth between formats.
Zortam Mp3 Media Studio Pro is rated as perfect software in the processing of the MP3 files on the computer. First of all, you can...
</description></item><item><title>Download PerfectXL Compare 1.7.7</title><pubDate> Wed, 05 Nov 2025 18:08:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfectxl-compare-12435.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfectxl-compare-12435.html
</guid><description>
PerfectXL Compare is a software tool designed to streamline and simplify the Excel variance analysis and process. It helps identify differences between two or more Excel files, highlighting cells, formulas, and structural changes. With PerfectXL Compare, you can easily compare Excel files to identify differences and errors, track changes made to formulas and cells, and easily identify inconsistencies in formatting. form or structure. The tool provides a user-friendly interface, allowing...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sandboxie 5.71.5</title><pubDate> Wed, 05 Nov 2025 18:07:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sandboxie-818.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sandboxie-818.html
</guid><description>
Sandboxie software to browse the Web securely while still keeping all the functionality your browser for content works against harmful agents such as sanbox up your computer. You may not know, when you browse the Web, the change will occur with the system of your computer. When you use Sandboxie, the software will protect the web browser of their own.
Sandboxie - web protection, safe browsing
The main features of Sandboxie
Stay safe on the Internet with Sandboxie
	Run the program in...
</description></item><item><title>Download Lightmap HDR Light Studio 9.2.0.2025.1016</title><pubDate> Wed, 05 Nov 2025 18:07:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lightmap-hdr-light-studio-xenon-5459.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lightmap-hdr-light-studio-xenon-5459.html
</guid><description>
HDR Light Studio software gives 3D artists a new way to illuminate 3D images. Adorn your photos with lights. Lighting process is now easy, fast, accurate, creative and fun. HDR Light Studio builds the lighting used by your existing 3D rendering software and renderers. By adding HDR Light Studio, 3D artists become more productive and image quality improves.
When combining photography and CG images, combining light between the image content and CG elements is the key to a successful and...
</description></item><item><title>Download reaConverter Pro 8.0.151</title><pubDate> Wed, 05 Nov 2025 18:06:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html
</guid><description>
reaConverter Pro is software image processing feature with batch conversion and image editing periodically becomes simple. eaConverter also provide command line utilities allow you to process images automatically, thus helping you shorten the time for other work.
reaConverter Pro integrated powerful tool of Uber with many great features. It provides advanced solutions to process and adjust images. Management of the conversion process the base image with the latest version of...
</description></item><item><title>Download MusConv 4.10.430 Lifetime</title><pubDate> Wed, 05 Nov 2025 17:59:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html
</guid><description>
MusConv transfers playlists, albums, followed artists and liked songs across a variety of services – Spotify, Apple Music, Amazon Music, YouTube, YouTube Music, iTunes, Deezer, Tidal, SoundCloud, Pandora and more 125 music services!
Features of MusConv Ultimate
	Transfer playlists, albums, followed artists and liked tracks between over 125 music servicesManage playlists (Delete, Merge, Split, Copy...)
	More than 125 music services supported
	Access DAILY updated music charts on...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sandboxie Plus 1.16.5</title><pubDate> Wed, 05 Nov 2025 17:59:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sandboxie-plus-4962.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sandboxie-plus-4962.html
</guid><description>
Sandboxie Plus is an application version of the open source project on Github, equipped with software to protect your information while browsing the web or running valuable software. doubt. Web browsing, downloading or running software can affect system security. To prevent this from happening, a high user experience and strong layers of protection are needed to prevent malware from spreading to the system. For example, by opening an unknown application, malware in flash memory can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ocenaudio 3.16.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 05 Nov 2025 17:58:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ocenaudio-837.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ocenaudio-837.html
</guid><description>
Ocenaudio: software for windows, this is the sound editing easy, fast and powerful. ocenaudio is a program for audio editing multi-platform, easy to use, fast and functional. This is the ideal software for those who need to edit and analyze audio files.
Ocenaudio - editor powerful audio for windows
This software is based on Ocen Framework , a powerful library developed to simplify and standardize the development of application analysis and sound processing on many platforms.
Features...
</description></item><item><title>Download Diffchecker 6.6.3</title><pubDate> Wed, 05 Nov 2025 17:57:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-diffchecker-5025.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-diffchecker-5025.html
</guid><description>
Diffchecker is a application compare text, images and powerful file to desktop of your. Available for Windows, macOS. Compare text files, documents, PDF. Compare photos, graphics. Because Diffchecker Desktop running entirely on your computer, so it does not have to communicate with our servers to create your difference. This means that there is no other way in addition you can view your sensitive data, you.
Diffchecker Desktop run offline, that means you can use it anytime, anywhere and...
</description></item><item><title>Download PerfectXL Risk Finder 1.2.9</title><pubDate> Wed, 05 Nov 2025 17:57:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfectxl-risk-finder-12429.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfectxl-risk-finder-12429.html
</guid><description>
The world runs on Excel and the need to trust spreadsheets is greater than ever. Detect errors and identify risks with PerfectXL Risk Finder.
Features
Recognize errors and risks
	Quick scan for risks and errors
	Check for circular references
	Search for hidden information
	Check and resolve Excel error messages
	Check the use of external sources
	Provide provable Excel models to customers
	Detect hard-coded numbers in formulas
	Ensure models comply with official...
</description></item><item><title>Download PerfectXL Explore 1.6.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 05 Nov 2025 17:56:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfectxl-explore-12430.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfectxl-explore-12430.html
</guid><description>
Spreadsheets can be scary monsters. Capture even the most complex models using PerfectXL Explore's powerful lists and visualizations.
Features
Grasp complex Excel models
	Check circular references
	Check the specified name
	Clean up the model
	Check the use of external sources
	Separate input, computation and output
	Simplify models
	Check all unique formulas
	Create a macro model without VBA
The fastest way to understand and record spreadsheets
	Visualize information flow
	Gain...
</description></item><item><title>Download Playfair Audio Dynamic Grading 2.0.4</title><pubDate> Wed, 05 Nov 2025 17:21:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-playfair-audio-dynamic-grading-10062.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-playfair-audio-dynamic-grading-10062.html
</guid><description>
With Playfair Audio Dynamic Grading, you can precisely shape and control different parts of the sound's dynamic range. Thanks to dynamic charts and intuitive graphical controls, advanced dynamic processing is easier than ever.
Main Features:
	New paradigm for dynamic processing
	Create powerful mixes with depth and boldness.
	Create depth by placing tracks in front or at a distance.
	Keep Usher Body in Shape tracks in their proper place in the mix. Make the instrument as solid as a...
</description></item><item><title>Download 3DCoat 2025.12</title><pubDate> Wed, 05 Nov 2025 17:20:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-3d-coat-1269.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-3d-coat-1269.html
</guid><description>
3D Coat is a computer program that trade for modeling objects of different organic and 3D models low-poly. The app provides a variety of tools allow users to create sculptures, adding topology, create UV maps, texture surface interactions of the model, showing the static and animated round of the pattern.
3D Coat - 3D modeling
The content in the software 3D Coat:
Texture simple and PBR:
	Support drawing drawings top en model, draw the pixel and Ptex
	Rendered physics-based (PBR)...
</description></item><item><title>Download Native Instruments Traktor Pro 4.4.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 05 Nov 2025 17:17:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-traktor-pro-220.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-traktor-pro-220.html
</guid><description>
Traktor PRO is the professional DJ software is the world's top DJS trust, and is designed to handle even the biggest clubs. Traktor PRO is integrated with filter, EQ and studio quality effects, with flexible operation , functions intuitive controls and mark automatically matching with the DJ of all styles and levels of experience.
Now, with TRAKTOR PRO 3 new tools for sculpting sound, quality sound our best, and clear interface of our best to date - so you can play whatever you want,...
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 7.4.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 05 Nov 2025 17:16:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-11-7760.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-11-7760.html
</guid><description>
TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 is a program that allows users to discover hidden settings in Windows 11. This application is specially designed for Windows 11, groups many registry settings and distribute them from the easy and secure user interface. With TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 you can move the Windows taskbar to the top and resize the taskbar by editing the registry value. With any application that modifies the registry, we recommend that you have a backup copy...
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 7.4.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 05 Nov 2025 17:16:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-10-7759.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-10-7759.html
</guid><description>
TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 is a utility that allows users to discover hidden settings in Windows 10. This application is specially designed for Windows 10, groups many registry settings and provide them from an easy and secure user interface. With TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 you can move the Windows taskbar to the top and resize the taskbar by editing the registry value. With any application that modifies the registry, we recommend that you have a backup copy to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Kush Audio Hammer Mk2 1.0.5</title><pubDate> Wed, 05 Nov 2025 17:16:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kush-audio-hammer-mk2-13895.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kush-audio-hammer-mk2-13895.html
</guid><description>
Kush Audio Hammer Mk2 is a tube-based equalizer plugin built on the original Hammer DSP with significant sonic and technical improvements. It faithfully reproduces the harmonic character and "default" sound signature of the original hardware unit, delivering the distinctive high gloss and thick, tube-like bass that made it popular on mixing buses worldwide.
Key Features of Hammer Mk2
	Improved DSP with tube-simulated EQ that doubles the number of frequency points per band compared to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mario Nieto Chord Generator 1.1.6</title><pubDate> Wed, 05 Nov 2025 17:16:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mario-nieto-chord-generator-14023.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mario-nieto-chord-generator-14023.html
</guid><description>
Mario Nieto Chord Generator is a MIDI plugin designed to create chords with unexpected, magical variations, breathing new life into music production. The plugin offers a rich chord library with options to create more complex chords than basic triads, useful for musicians, producers, and composers looking for fresh harmony ideas and dynamic rhythms.
Key features include:
	Customize scales and key signatures: Choose from 57 scales and modes, with key randomization options to explore...
</description></item><item><title>Download Dawesome Myth 1.59</title><pubDate> Wed, 05 Nov 2025 17:15:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dawesome-myth-11855.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dawesome-myth-11855.html
</guid><description>
MYTH is built to create the joy and inspiration we feel when playing with hardware. Instead of “programming” sounds, you create sounds by exploring and adjusting. MYTH offers a paradigm shift: drag and drop audio and it will be aggregated as IRIS. The inherent variations and richness of patterns can now be exploited with the TRANSFORMER dial. Of course - you can also add as many LFOs, envelopes or vintage filters as you like.
Main features of Dawesome Myth
	Advanced organic...
</description></item><item><title>Download COAA PlanePlotter 6.7.2.7</title><pubDate> Wed, 05 Nov 2025 17:15:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coaa-planeplotter-7840.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coaa-planeplotter-7840.html
</guid><description>
PlanePlotter receives and decodes digital position reports directly from the aircraft and plots them on a chart. Using PlanePlotter, you can see the radar-like display of all aircraft around you transmitting the appropriate digital messages including ACARS, ADS-B and HFDL.
PlanePlotter Features
	PlanePlotter displays a table showing messages received and decoded from direct plane transmissions.
	PlanePlotter stores all digital data it receives and decodes into a log...
</description></item></channel></rss>