<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 15:45:21 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 15:45:21 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Total Commander Ultima Prime 9.3</title><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jan 2026 17:39:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-total-commander-ultima-prime-462.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-total-commander-ultima-prime-462.html
</guid><description>
Total Commander Ultima Prime is file management software, professional data for windows can be replaced by default Windows Explorer. With this software the management of files on the computer is easy and quick. Total Commander Ultima Prime is a very good improvement of Total Commander, where you are available for additional features, which will help you arrange your files and folders more efficiently. The installation process comes with a number of steps in which you can configure some...
</description></item><item><title>Download Parted Magic 2025.12.31</title><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jan 2026 17:39:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-parted-magic-2298.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-parted-magic-2298.html
</guid><description>
Powerful tools for home or Office! - Parted Magic is a solution to manage hard disk complete. PartedMagic has the tools to complete the job. With The edit partitions, you can resize, copy, and move partitions. You can grow or shrink your C: drive. Create space for the new operating system. Attempt data rescue from lost partitions.
A pack of very powerful utility has been updated is very useful to work with partitions of your hard disk based on the disk boot Linux. Please note that you can...
</description></item><item><title>Download n-Track Studio Suite 10.2.3.10395</title><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jan 2026 17:38:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-n-track-studio-2991.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-n-track-studio-2991.html
</guid><description>
n-Track Studio is a recording software allows you record and create MIDI music and sounds top quality. The software allows you to add effects, VST3, DirectX, AU (Mac), VST and ReWire different on each track or channel. This program also allows you to automatically fade out, fade in and fade out or increase the volume of the music to indicate the voice of the singer.
n-Track Studio can record and playback the number of audio, MIDI and sound unlimited. In addition, you can handle the...
</description></item><item><title>Download WizFlow Flowcharter Professional 7.49.2219</title><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jan 2026 17:36:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wizflow-flowcharter-professional-3604.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wizflow-flowcharter-professional-3604.html
</guid><description>
WizFlow Flowcharter Professional is a tool for drawing diagrams and diagram easy-to-use, feature-rich, abundant for Windows. WizFlow lets you define "styles" shape using more than a hundred shapes and arrow heads to be determined first. Save your styles in the template to set the method of mapping your own. WizFlow comes with the template complete diagram to help you get started. WizFlow can create flowcharts and diagrams similar with minimal effort. When you draw a diagram of WizFlow...
</description></item><item><title>Download EDGE Diagrammer 7.49.2219</title><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jan 2026 17:35:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-edge-diagrammer-9462.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-edge-diagrammer-9462.html
</guid><description>
EDGE Diagrammer is a software application used to create graphical diagrams, especially in the field of systems engineering. The term "EDGE" stands for "Enhanced Diagram Graphics Environment". It provides a user-friendly interface and a set of tools for designing and documenting complex systems, processes, and workflows.
EDGE Diagrammer is all you need for block diagrams, flowcharts, organization charts, family trees, data flow diagrams and more. Free extension packs are available to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Chaos Corona 14.1 for 3ds Max 2018 - 2026</title><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jan 2026 17:35:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chaos-corona-2986.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chaos-corona-2986.html
</guid><description>
Corona Renderer is the name of the plug-in technique and dedicated powerful, but have high functionality for Autodesk software 3ds Max. Plug before you is a standalone application known to the CLI. In addition, users can use this tool to promote their business on software Maxon Cinema 4D is also used. The manufacturers of this product believe that working with this tool is very simple and in fact you only need to press the activities rendered. With this tool easier than ever can do the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Chaos Corona 14.1 for Cinema 4D R17 - 2026</title><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jan 2026 17:35:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-corona-renderer-for-cinema-4d-6499.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-corona-renderer-for-cinema-4d-6499.html
</guid><description>
Corona Renderer  is the name of a powerful, but highly functional engineering and dedicated plug-in for Autodesk 3ds Max software. Plug in before you are a known CLI standalone application. In addition, users can use this tool to advertise their business on Maxon Cinema 4D software which is also used. The manufacturers of this product firmly believe that working with this tool is very simple, and in fact you just need to hit render the rendering operations. With this tool it's easier...
</description></item><item><title>Download Shotcut 25.12.31</title><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jan 2026 15:55:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-shotcut-2756.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-shotcut-2756.html
</guid><description>
Shotcut is a video editing application multi-platform free and open source for FreeBSD, Linux, macOS and Windows. Was started in 2011 by Dan Dennedy, Shotcut is developed on the multimedia MLT, which was developed from 2004. With age grow quite long years, Shotcut offers users many tools to perform the manipulation, Video editing based on adjusting each frame to enhance image quality. You can add an introduction, edit rate, bitrate, resolution or file encryption, and optionally use the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Dropbox 238.4.6305</title><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jan 2026 15:55:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dropbox-1313.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dropbox-1313.html
</guid><description>
Dropbox on taiwebs.com is free tool, the data synchronization across multiple PC become easier than never before: after installation, all what you have to do is enter your name, email address and password before opening the folder My Dropbox. If you install the software on a different computer, Dropbox will reflect the content of the online storage. So you exchange any data between the different computer is connected to Dropbox account. In addition the client is installed on the computer,...
</description></item><item><title>Download R-Studio 9.5 Build 191671 Network / Technician</title><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jan 2026 15:52:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-studio-1415.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-studio-1415.html
</guid><description>
R-Studio is a group of software data recovery and data recovery powerful and effective. -STUDIO is the solution to recover most comprehensive data for the file restored from the variants NTFS, NTFS5, ReFS, FAT12 / 16/32, exFAT, HFS / HFS + (Macintosh), Little and Big Endian of UFS1 / UFS2 (FreeBSD / OpenBSD / NetBSD / Solaris) and Ext2 / Ext3 / Ext4 partition FS (Linux).
R-Studio is also used to recover file raw (scan known file types) for the file system is damaged or not determined. It...
</description></item><item><title>Download Print Artist Premier 25.0.3.4</title><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jan 2026 15:52:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-print-artist-premier-12692.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-print-artist-premier-12692.html
</guid><description>
Print Artist Premier 25 is unlike any printing software you have ever used. Its amazing quality combined with unmatched ease of use allows you to create amazing print projects for home, school or your business. Impress friends, family and customers with the creativity that only Print Artist Premier can offer with over 28,000 professionally designed templates, over 377,000 sensational graphics, over 1,000 premium fonts and more!
With powerful yet easy-to-use design, text, and drawing...
</description></item><item><title>Download GPU-Z Portable 2.68.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jan 2026 15:51:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gpu-z-portable-11862.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gpu-z-portable-11862.html
</guid><description>
GPU-Z is a lightweight and portable software utility that provides users with detailed information about their graphics processing unit (GPU) and video card. This app is useful for monitoring your GPU's performance, verifying its specifications, and troubleshooting any problems that may arise.
GPU-Z Portable Features
	One of the main advantages of GPU-Z Portable is its portability. You can run the application directly from a USB flash drive or any other portable device without...
</description></item><item><title>Download VectorStyler 1.3.006</title><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jan 2026 15:51:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vectorstyler-7917.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vectorstyler-7917.html
</guid><description>
VectorStyler provides a complete set of drawing, design and illustration tools needed for modern design. Create illustrations, logos, icons, drawings, typography, vector art for screen, print and web. With many new features, VectorStyler redefines and extends the tools available to illustrators and designers, improving the creation of complex illustrations and designs.
Shape effects can be used to adjust the shape of objects, create different distortions, or add detail to shapes. Shape...
</description></item><item><title>Download HTML Compiler 2026.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jan 2026 15:51:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-html-compiler-2548.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-html-compiler-2548.html
</guid><description>
HTML Compiler is a program for Microsoft Windows (tm) allows you to put an entire HTML application (including HTML, CSS, JavaScript, images, etc.) into a Windows application independent can be executed like any other application window the application. HTML Compiler allows you to customize file real exam results by changing the icon of them and set some other options. For example, you can allow or not allow the ability to print the HTML pages, allow or disallow the text selection and many,...
</description></item><item><title>Download VLC Media Player 3.0.23</title><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jan 2026 15:50:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vlc-media-player-63.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vlc-media-player-63.html
</guid><description>
VLC Media Player is a multimedia player supporting many audio formats and video (MPEG-1, MPEG-2, MPEG-4, DivX, mp3, ogg, etc.) without the need for additional codecs , as well as DVDS, VCDS, and various streaming protocols different online.It also comes with a server, streaming allows you to stream media in unicast or multicast from your network.
VLC Media Player 
VLC Media Player provides a simple interface, with simple buttons control the playback standard and make the most of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Kaizen Home Manager 2026 v4.10.1000</title><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jan 2026 15:50:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kaizen-home-manager-5150.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kaizen-home-manager-5150.html
</guid><description>
Kaizen Home Manager is tool that helps you can sort and track his inventory. Easily enter the details about your belongings and use the features integrated search to find quickly. If you already have lots of digital pictures, simply drag and drop them into the program to automatically create inventory items for each category.
Sort your inventory by category and location, at the same time drag and drop the items from this category to other categories. Keep a history of maintenance and...
</description></item><item><title>Download RealVoice Text to Speech 2.0.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jan 2026 15:49:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-realvoice-text-to-speech-14227.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-realvoice-text-to-speech-14227.html
</guid><description>
RealVoice TTS turns your text into natural speech using Microsoft's voice AI. Preview instantly, tweak speed and pitch, then export high-quality audio. Add background music, adjust volume, and optionally fade in the music at the end for a clean finish. The app is designed to be simple, fast, and reliable—great for creators, educators, podcasters, and anyone who needs quick voiceover audio.
No sign-in required. Voice preview and voice-only export work instantly. If bundled, the app...
</description></item><item><title>Download MyLanViewer Enterprise 6.7.3</title><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jan 2026 15:48:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mylanviewer-enterprise-1274.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mylanviewer-enterprise-1274.html
</guid><description>
MyLanViewer is a program for scanning IP address, Netbios and LAN / Network powerful for Windows tool whois and traceroute, remote shutdown and process management Wake On LAN (WOL), scan and monitor wireless networks. This app will help you find all IP addresses, MAC addresses and shared folders of computers on the network wired or wireless (Wi-Fi).
MyLanViewer Enterprise - Scan IP address LAN/Network
The program scans network and displays the computer network in your window, friends...
</description></item><item><title>Download App Builder 2026.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jan 2026 15:48:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-app-builder-241.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-app-builder-241.html
</guid><description>
App Builder is a software application developer to help create and design apps, HTML5, web app, web app PWA on both platforms mobile and desktop. App Builder is professional software supports users to create the program HTML5 without writing code. It is very easy to use, suitable with all users who lack of professional knowledge in the field of programming and application design.
App Builder brings to 22 different themes that users can use to design for your app. You can choose 1 or a...
</description></item><item><title>Download High-Logic FontCreator Professional 15.0.0.3040</title><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jan 2026 15:47:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-high-logic-fontcreator-professional-1533.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-high-logic-fontcreator-professional-1533.html
</guid><description>
High-Logic FontCreator Professional allows you to create and edit TrueType fonts and OpenType. It has the powerful drawing tools that typographers and graphic designers require, and an intuitive interface that allows beginners to become productive immediately.
When you create or open a font, FontCreator displays an overview of all available characters. You can only add the characters missing, or select an existing character, and modify its appearance. You can import (scanned) signature...
</description></item><item><title>Download The Bat! Professional 12.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jan 2026 15:46:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-the-bat-professional-3072.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-the-bat-professional-3072.html
</guid><description>
The Bat! Professional is an email program guest safety, developed to protect your correspondence against the side Tuesday. The Bat! Professional protection of your data through multi-threaded encoding with a choice encoding of your emails on disk and during communication through SSL / TLS connections. Free email providers global hosting your mail on the cloud and free for the Web clients, The Bat! ensure your data is kept private.
The Bat! Professional - mail application security
The...
</description></item><item><title>Download SonarQube Data Center Edition 2025.6.1.117629</title><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jan 2026 15:46:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sonarqube-data-center-edition-8059.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sonarqube-data-center-edition-8059.html
</guid><description>
SonarQube empowers all developers to write cleaner and safer code. Join the Open Community of over 200,000 developer groups. SonarQube provides reports on duplicate code, coding standards, unit testing, code coverage, code complexity, comments, bugs, and security recommendations.
Features of SonarQube
	Detect complex bugs to prevent undefined behavior from affecting end users.
	Fix your apps' vulnerabilities and learn about AppSec along the way with Secure Hotspot.
	Make sure your...
</description></item><item><title>Download TaskbarPlus 0.59</title><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jan 2026 15:41:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-taskbarplus-13876.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-taskbarplus-13876.html
</guid><description>
TaskbarPlus is a smart and intuitive desktop enhancement utility that complements the Windows Taskbar by providing quick access to folders, files, shortcuts, etc., keeping your desktop clean and your workflow seamless and efficient.
Move all your desktop shortcuts to one of the customizable taskbars
TaskbarPlus is actually a shortcut organizer and app/folder launcher that can neatly organize all your shortcuts. You should pin TaskbarPlus to the Windows taskbar for quicker access to all...
</description></item><item><title>Download Unicodia 3.0.7</title><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jan 2026 15:40:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-unicodia-8521.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-unicodia-8521.html
</guid><description>
Unicodia is free, open source software that can be used as an alternative character map for your Windows machine. The interface contains everything you need, allowing you to easily cycle through all the available ASCII symbols and copy them to the clipboard. Uncicodia is a great alternative to your standard Unicode characters and is filled with symbols/characters that make it useful for a number of different uses.
Features of Unicodia
	In Windows 10/11 — all characters of Unicode 15...
</description></item><item><title>Download fb2kPortable (foobar2000 Portable) 2.25.4</title><pubDate> Thu, 01 Jan 2026 15:36:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fb2kportable-11860.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fb2kportable-11860.html
</guid><description>
fb2kPortable (foobar2000) is an advanced freeware audio player for the Windows platform. Supported audio formats: MP3, MP4, AAC, CD Audio, WMA, Vorbis, Opus, FLAC, WavPack, WAV, AIFF, Musepack, Speex, AU, SND... and many others with components supplement. Playback has no gap. Easily customize the user interface layout. Advanced tagging capabilities. Supports ripping audio CDs as well as transcoding all supported audio formats using the Converter component. Full ReplayGain support....
</description></item></channel></rss>