<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 13:46:17 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 13:46:17 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download File Manager 3.6.5</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 16:14:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-file-manager-8886.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-file-manager-8886.html
</guid><description>
File Manager+ is an easy and powerful file browser for Android devices. It's free, fast, and full-featured. Because of its simple user interface, it is extremely easy to use. With File Manager+, you can easily manage files and folders on your devices, NAS (Network Attached Storage), and cloud storage. What's more, you can quickly see how many files and apps you have on your device right after opening File Manager+.
It supports all file management actions (opening, searching, navigating...
</description></item><item><title>Download Volume Control 6.5.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 16:14:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-volume-control-9600.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-volume-control-9600.html
</guid><description>
Volume Control is a great app that lets you control your device's volume – instead of being controlled by it! Simply adjust existing volume profiles or create new predefined volume profiles and switch between them with a single tap. Individual profiles include: Alarm, Media, Ringer, Notifications, Voice (in-call), Bluetooth, and overall system volume.
Volume Control Features
	Volume control also detects when you plug in headphones or activate Bluetooth and automatically switches to...
</description></item><item><title>Download MobiOffice: Word, Sheets, PDF 16.0.58429</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 16:14:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-officesuite-word-sheets-pdf-8508.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-officesuite-word-sheets-pdf-8508.html
</guid><description>
OfficeSuite allows you to easily view, edit, and create Word, Excel, and PowerPoint documents and perform advanced PDF operations. Our integrated file manager, Chat app with document exchange capabilities, and tons of other handy tools make this the most feature-rich mobile office solution available on Android. Pre-installed by leading manufacturers including Sony, ZTE, Amazon, Sharp, Acer, CAT, Alcatel, Kyocera, Toshiba, etc.
Features of OfficeSuite for Android
	View, create, and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Solid Explorer File Manager 3.2.8</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 16:13:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-solid-explorer-file-manager-8924.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-solid-explorer-file-manager-8924.html
</guid><description>
Solid Explorer is a file management application inspired by old file management applications. Solid Explorer is a popular file management app for Android devices that allows users to manage and organize their files and folders in an intuitive and user-friendly interface. It offers many features that make it stand out from other file management apps.
Solid Explorer allows you to navigate to files stored on your device and automatically organize them into collections. You can view,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Photo Editor 12.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 16:13:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-iudesk-photo-editor-8321.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-iudesk-photo-editor-8321.html
</guid><description>
Photo Editor is a small but powerful photo editing application. If you have some knowledge about photography, you can do a lot with Photo Editor. Now use Photo Editor to edit photos on your mobile phone just like on your PC.
Photo Editor Features
	Color: exposure, brightness, contrast, saturation, temperature, tone, and hue
	Curves &amp;amp; levels: color fine-tuning
	Effects: gamma correction, auto contrast, auto tone, vibrance, blur, sharpen, oil painting, sketch, high contrast black...
</description></item><item><title>Download Firewall Security AI - No Root 2.5.8 build 2581</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 16:13:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-firewall-no-root-8224.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-firewall-no-root-8224.html
</guid><description>
No Root Firewall is an Android application that allows users to block Internet access to specific applications on their device without requiring root access. Blocks internet attacks and protects you from unwanted access to the internet. Determine which applications can and cannot access the internet. With powerful firewall technology, secure filter lists and artificial intelligence, you protect your privacy comprehensively and also stay informed about what is being shared with the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Code Editor - Compiler &amp;amp; IDE 0.11.3 build 104</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 16:13:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-code-editor-compiler-ide-8735.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-code-editor-compiler-ide-8735.html
</guid><description>
Code editor is an optimized text editor focused on coding. It is a useful tool for developing on Android. It contains essential features for coding, including syntax highlighting, auto-indenting, code support, auto-completion, etc.
Features of Code Editor for Android
	Syntax highlighting for over 110 languages ​​(c++, java, javascript, html, markdown, php, Perl, python, lua, Dart, etc.).
	Supports code folding and auto-completion.
	Easy navigation between multiple tabs.
	Unlimited...
</description></item><item><title>Download AdGuard Ad Blocker 4.12.80 Final</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 16:12:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-adguard-block-ads-without-root-8215.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-adguard-block-ads-without-root-8215.html
</guid><description>
AdGuard for Android is the only root-free ad blocker for Android that removes ads in apps and browsers, protects your privacy, and helps you manage your apps. Adguard is designed to block unwanted ads, pop-ups and banners while you browse the web on your device. It uses a combination of local VPN technology and a custom DNS server to block ads, meaning it can block ads in apps as well as in web browsers.
In addition, Adguard also blocks tracking scripts from collecting information about...
</description></item><item><title>Download BetterSleep: Sleep tracker 25.22.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 16:12:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-bettersleep-sleep-tracker-8274.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-bettersleep-sleep-tracker-8274.html
</guid><description>
BetterSleep is a sleep tracking app that helps users track and improve their sleeping habits. The app uses the phone's sensors to track movement and sounds during sleep, then provides users with detailed sleep reports and analysis. It also includes features such as a sleep log, smart alarm, and white noise generation to help users fall asleep and wake up more refreshed. Additionally, BetterSleep allows users to set sleep goals, track their progress, and receive personalized...
</description></item><item><title>Download SnapTube for Android 7.51.1.75172501</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 16:12:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-snaptube-youtube-downloader-hd-video-8351.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-snaptube-youtube-downloader-hd-video-8351.html
</guid><description>
SnapTube is a mobile application that allows users to download videos from various platforms, such as YouTube, Vimeo, and Dailymotion. It provides video resolution in multiple formats 144p, 720p, 1080p HD, 2K HD, 4K HD and audio formats MP3 and M4A. With Snaptube, users can search for content across all their platforms without using multiple apps.
Features of SnapTube for Android
Download in multiple resolutions
	MP4 videos are available in resolutions: choose small 360 pixels or...
</description></item><item><title>Download Calculator Plus 8.1.7</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 16:11:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-calculator-plus-8135.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-calculator-plus-8135.html
</guid><description>
Calculator Plus is a perfect calculator program for Android that is easy to read and saves you time and effort. It can remember everything you calculate and let you review it at any time, making it perfect for shopping, doing homework, balancing a checkbook, or even helping with taxes. .
Plus Calculator Features
	Calculator Plus displays your calculations in clear, elegant, easy-to-read typeface, with commas in the right places
	You'll never forget where you are in the calculation - I...
</description></item><item><title>Download Duolingo: language lessons 6.59.4</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 16:11:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-duolingo-language-lessons-8265.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-duolingo-language-lessons-8265.html
</guid><description>
Duolingo is a popular language learning app that offers interactive lessons to help users learn new languages. This application offers many languages for you to choose from, including Spanish, French, German, Italian, Portuguese, Chinese, Japanese and many more.
This app offers an gamified learning experience with interactive lessons, exercises, and quizzes designed to help users learn new words, phrases, and grammar rules. This app is designed to be easy to use and suitable for people...
</description></item><item><title>Download Smart Launcher 6 ‧ Home Screen 6.5 build 055</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 16:11:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-smart-launcher-8412.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-smart-launcher-8412.html
</guid><description>
Smart Launcher is a mobile app that provides users with a customized home screen and app launcher on their Android devices. It includes features like minimalist interface, automatic app sorting, and gesture controls. The app also includes many customizable settings, such as the ability to change the theme, icon size, and screen layout, as well as the ability to create custom categories for the app.
Smart Launcher Features
	Ambient theme: Smart launcher automatically changes theme...
</description></item><item><title>Download AdGuard for Android TV 4.12.80</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 16:10:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-adguard-for-android-tv-12118.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-adguard-for-android-tv-12118.html
</guid><description>
To provide full compatibility with Android TV, we've created a streamlined version of AdGuard for Android. This version incorporates key features designed to enhance your TV browsing experience. AdGuard for Android TV is the only app that blocks ads, protects your privacy and acts as a firewall for your Smart TV. Relax and watch your favorite shows with top security and no ads!
Main features:
Block ads on TV
	AdGuard blocks banners, pop-ups, and ads on the home screen. Watch your...
</description></item><item><title>Download YoWindow Weather - Unlimited 2.54.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 16:10:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-yowindow-weather-unlimited-8421.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-yowindow-weather-unlimited-8421.html
</guid><description>
YoWindow is a unique new weather app. The magic of YoWindow is a living landscape that reflects your real-life weather. For example, if it rains - it will rain in YoWindow. Sunset and sunrise in YoWindow take place at the same time as in real life. But the cool thing is you can roll time forward. Just swipe the screen and you'll see how the weather changes throughout the day.
YoWindow Weather Features - Unlimited
	All the weather at your fingertips. You see the current weather,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Speed test 4G 5G WiFi &amp;amp; maps 2.15.21 build 21521001</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 16:09:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-speed-test-4g-5g-wifi-maps-9642.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-speed-test-4g-5g-wifi-maps-9642.html
</guid><description>
More than just a simple speed test, nPerf offers you the best and most complete mobile connection quality measurement tool with speeds up to 1 Gbps! All your results are saved in history with all test locations on the map. Easily share your results on social networks with the nPerf share image that presents a useful summary of your test. Customize your app by switching the background theme using Settings.
Features of Speed ​​test 4G 5G WiFi &amp;amp; maps
	Full QoS test: In seconds,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Squid: Take Notes, Markup PDFs 4.5.0-GP</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 16:08:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-squid-take-notes-markup-pdfs-8747.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-squid-take-notes-markup-pdfs-8747.html
</guid><description>
Squid is a note-taking and PDF markup app for Android devices. It allows users to create handwritten notes, sketch drawings, and markup PDF documents with a variety of tools and options. With Squid you can write just like you would on paper using an active pen, passive stylus, or your finger. Easily markup PDFs to fill out forms, edit/grade papers, or sign documents. Import images, draw shapes, and add typed text to your notes. Quickly select, copy/paste, and move content between pages...
</description></item><item><title>Download Math Tricks Workout 2.7.4</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 16:08:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-math-tricks-workout-8232.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-math-tricks-workout-8232.html
</guid><description>
Math Tricks Exercises can be an Android app designed to help users improve their math skills and speed through the use of various tricks and techniques. Math Tricks Exercises is one of the best math tricks app that brings you the most interesting exercises and practice to test and improve your math skills. Inspired by Vedic Maths, This is the most fun and free math learning app ever!
Features of Math Tricks Workout
	Various math problems, including addition, subtraction,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Moon+ Reader Pro 10.3 build 1003001</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 16:08:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-moon-reader-pro-8577.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-moon-reader-pro-8577.html
</guid><description>
Moon+ Reader Pro is an all-in-one ebook document manager and better designed book reader with powerful and fully functional controls, supporting EPUB, PDF, DJVU, AZW3, MOBI, FB2, PRC, CHM, CBZ, CBR, UMD, DOCX, ODT, RTF, TXT, HTML, MD(MarkDown), WEBP, RAR, ZIP or OPDS formats.
This is a versatile e-book reading application that gives users a rich reading experience, while helping them easily access and manage their e-book library. Whether you're looking to read your favorite novels,...
</description></item><item><title>Download WiFi Analyzer Pro 6.6</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 16:07:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wifi-analyzer-pro-8672.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wifi-analyzer-pro-8672.html
</guid><description>
WiFi Analyzer Pro is a mobile application that provides users with advanced tools to analyze and optimize their Wi-Fi network. It allows users to monitor Wi-Fi signal strength and quality, view graphical charts of their network's channel usage, and select the optimal channel for their network to minimize interference from other neighboring networks.
In addition, WiFi Analyze Pro can help users diagnose connection issues, such as slow speeds or lost connections, by displaying signal...
</description></item><item><title>Download Genius Scan Enterprise 7.33.6 build 7103</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 16:07:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-genius-scan-enterprise-8561.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-genius-scan-enterprise-8561.html
</guid><description>
Genius Scan Enterprise: Quickly scan your paper documents on the go and export them as multi-page PDF files. Place any document in front of your device's camera: our scanner app automatically recognizes the paper on the background, crops it and cleans the result. You get sharp, easy-to-read scans. Batch scanning allows you to scan dozens of pages in just a few seconds. Powerful tools help you organize, share or archive your documents.
Features of Genius Scan Enterprise for...
</description></item><item><title>Download Fing - Network Tools 12.11.5 build 121105002</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 16:07:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-fing-network-tools-8540.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-fing-network-tools-8540.html
</guid><description>
Fing is a popular network scanning application that allows users to discover devices connected to the local network, view their IP and MAC addresses, and perform various network tests. Fing is the #1 Network Scanner: detects all devices connected to your WiFi and identifies them with our patented technology that is also used by router manufacturers and companies antivirus used worldwide.
Features of Fing for Android
	Network Scan: Quickly find all devices connected to your Wi-Fi...
</description></item><item><title>Download 9GAG: Funny GIF, Meme &amp;amp; Video 8.17.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 16:06:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-9gag-funny-gif-meme-video-11500.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-9gag-funny-gif-meme-video-11500.html
</guid><description>
9GAG has the best funny, cute, weird, wacky, cosplay photos, GIFs, videos, memes, photos on the web. We are your greatest and happiest source. With millions of visitors every day, 9GAG is an application that helps you play LOL, kill time and make new friends around the world.
9GAG features
	The 9GAG app loads quickly and allows for easy scrolling. Don't waste time picking me up or just having a good laugh.
	Carry unlimited fun in your pocket. Enjoy 9GAG anytime, anywhere and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Habitify: Habit Tracker 30.0.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 16:06:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-habitify-habit-tracker-8612.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-habitify-habit-tracker-8612.html
</guid><description>
Habitify is an easy-to-use and award-winning habit tracker that helps remind and motivate you to stick to your daily habits, track your progress, and reward you for achievements nice. With our minimalist and intuitive design, the Habitify habit tracker is here to make building and monitoring your habits more effective and completely effortless.
Features of Habitify: Habit Tracker
	Habit management: create, organize, perfect and unlearn habits
	Customizable routine and routine area...
</description></item><item><title>Download SayIt: Read with Ears 3.8</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Dec 2025 16:06:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sayit-read-with-ears-13730.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sayit-read-with-ears-13730.html
</guid><description>
SayIt: Read with Ears is an app designed to enhance the reading experience by converting text to natural speech. It's especially useful for people who want to listen to written content on the go, such as articles, books, documents, or web pages.
Want to say it? Share with SayIt!
	Turn any text selection, article or web page into a Podcast
	Any PDF, EPUB or MOBI (Kindle) eBook into an Audiobook
	Translate instantly into your language
	Learn another language with bilingual...
</description></item></channel></rss>