<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 13:49:28 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 13:49:28 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download SnapTube for Android 7.52.0.75250110</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 16:49:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-snaptube-youtube-downloader-hd-video-8351.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-snaptube-youtube-downloader-hd-video-8351.html
</guid><description>
SnapTube is a mobile application that allows users to download videos from various platforms, such as YouTube, Vimeo, and Dailymotion. It provides video resolution in multiple formats 144p, 720p, 1080p HD, 2K HD, 4K HD and audio formats MP3 and M4A. With Snaptube, users can search for content across all their platforms without using multiple apps.
Features of SnapTube for Android
Download in multiple resolutions
	MP4 videos are available in resolutions: choose small 360 pixels or...
</description></item><item><title>Download Dumbbell Workout at Home &amp;amp; Gym 5.20</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 16:49:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-dumbbell-home-workout-8634.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-dumbbell-home-workout-8634.html
</guid><description>
Dumbbell Workout at Home is a fitness app for Android devices that offers users a variety of workout routines that can be done at home using only weights. This app is designed for people who want to stay fit and healthy but don't have access to a gym or workout equipment.
Features of Weightlifting at Home for Android
	Customizable workout routines: The app offers users a variety of workout routines that can be customized based on their fitness level, goals, and the amount of time they...
</description></item><item><title>Download Rotation | Orientation Manager 29.2.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 16:48:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-rotation-orientation-manager-8332.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-rotation-orientation-manager-8332.html
</guid><description>
Rotate | Orientation Manager is a mobile application for Android devices that allows users to control screen rotation settings on their devices. This app allows users to set custom rotation settings for different apps, and also provides a quick toggle to enable or disable rotation globally.
Rotation feature | Orientation Manager
	Control screen rotation on a per-app basis
	Option to set custom rotation settings for different applications
	Quick toggle switch to enable or disable...
</description></item><item><title>Download KillApps: Close Running Apps 1.56.7 build 969</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 16:48:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-killapps-close-running-apps-10803.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-killapps-close-running-apps-10803.html
</guid><description>
KillApps allows you to automatically close background apps with a simple tap. You can choose to close all apps at once, or you can select specific apps to close. This app requires access to accessibility services to be able to close other apps. This application will be able to observe interface-related actions to guide the process of automating the task of closing the application, by monitoring the transitions between windows during simulation of interaction with interface.
Features of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Reminder Pro 4.1.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 16:47:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-reminder-pro-8695.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-reminder-pro-8695.html
</guid><description>
Are you looking for a simple pop-up reminder app? Do you want to create reminders for one-time and recurring tasks? Get reminders and increase your productivity. Never forget an important task again! Finally, a simple and easy way to set reminders or deadline notifications. This hourly reminder app gets straight to the point. Set notifications to remind you of all your tasks, chores, and to-do list items, then sit back and clear your head.
No unnecessary or complicated features....
</description></item><item><title>Download Bluetooth Volume Manager 3.1.0-rc0</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 16:47:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-bluetooth-volume-manager-14080.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-bluetooth-volume-manager-14080.html
</guid><description>
Bluetooth Volume Manager can respond when Bluetooth devices are connected or disconnected. This app allows Android to remember the volume levels of different Bluetooth devices.
Available features:
	Adjust the volume of music, calls, ringtones, and notifications.
	Send the media command 'Play' or 'Next'.
	Open a specific app.
	Keep the screen on.
	Prevent volume changes.
	Restore previous volume level after disconnection.
This app cannot "increase" the volume or change the volume if...
</description></item><item><title>Download Twilight: Blue light filter 14.20 build 600</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 16:47:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-twilight-blue-light-filter-12193.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-twilight-blue-light-filter-12193.html
</guid><description>
Are you having trouble falling asleep? Is your child hyperactive when playing with the tablet before going to bed? The Twilight app helps your device's screen adapt to the time of day. It filters the blue light emitted from your phone or tablet after sunset and protects your eyes with a soft and pleasant red filter. Filter intensity is smoothly adjusted to the solar cycle based on your local sunset and sunrise times.
Get more from Twilight
	- Reading in bed: Twilight is more...
</description></item><item><title>Download Password Safe and Manager 9.0.1 build 900003</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 16:47:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-password-safe-and-manager-8210.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-password-safe-and-manager-8210.html
</guid><description>
Password Safe and Manager is a password management application for Android devices. The app also includes features like login autofill, a password generator, and a built-in browser to access your account directly from the app. It's a great way to securely store and manage your login information and other sensitive information.
Summary of essential functions
	securely store passwords, access data, etc.
	classify your entries in Password Security
	access via a single master...
</description></item><item><title>Download Who's on my wifi 29.1.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 16:46:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-whos-on-my-wifi-10497.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-whos-on-my-wifi-10497.html
</guid><description>
Who\'s on my wifi will help you know who is using your wifi network without your consent, then automatically disconnect them to ensure your wifi has faster speed. When a new IP invades and uses your wifi, the software will send a sound warning so you can promptly take measures.
Features of Who\'s on my wifi
	Customize the name and icon of your devices.
	Access to the router configuration web page.
	History of devices and networks analyzed.
	Shows the devices connected and disconnected...
</description></item><item><title>Download Browser For Tv 2.9.6</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 16:44:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-browser-for-tv-9209.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-browser-for-tv-9209.html
</guid><description>
Browser for TV is an Android application that allows users to browse the web on TV using an Android TV device or TV box. Our ad blocking browser is an ad blocker web browser for Android TV. You can open websites and browse the internet. Our browser is optimized for TV control. You can easily use all web browser functions using the TV's remote control.
Tv Browser Features
	Ad blocker: no annoying ads
	Pop-up blocker: no annoying pop-ups
	Cookie message blocker: no annoying...
</description></item><item><title>Download Hibernator: Force Stop Apps 2.55.6</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 16:44:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-hibernator-close-all-apps-11091.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-hibernator-close-all-apps-11091.html
</guid><description>
Hibernator provides an easy way to close running apps with just a tap and can also automatically close apps every time the screen turns off.
Features
	Force stop application
	Automatically close the application when the screen turns off
	Supports user applications and system applications
	Utilities
	Shortcuts
What is the difference between KillApps and Hibernator?
Hibernator is more advanced than Killapps because it allows you to automatically close the application every time the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Seven - 7 Minute Workout 9.24.4</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 16:42:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-seven-7-minute-workout-8424.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-seven-7-minute-workout-8424.html
</guid><description>
Working out has never been easier – or more fun. Seven's workouts are scientifically researched to deliver maximum benefits in the shortest possible time. With personalized training plans, Seven also ensures you get the most out of your workouts. Want to get fit, lose weight, or be healthier? Just set your goals and fitness level, and let Seven take care of the rest.
Seven - 7 Minute Workout Features
	Work out anytime, anywhere, no equipment needed
	Create a workout routine with our...
</description></item><item><title>Download VRadio - Online Radio App 2.8.10</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 16:42:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-vradio-online-radio-app-8279.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-vradio-online-radio-app-8279.html
</guid><description>
VRadio is a mobile application that allows users to listen to online radio stations from around the world. This app offers a wide variety of radio stations, including popular music genres, news, talk shows, and sports. VRadio gives you quick access to many terrestrial radio stations transmitted over the Internet and of course to many web-only radio stations. All stations are transmitted via the internet.
Features of VRadio - Online Radio App
	There are many radio stations of different...
</description></item><item><title>Download Everyday | Calendar Widget 19.2.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 16:42:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-everyday-calendar-widget-8422.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-everyday-calendar-widget-8422.html
</guid><description>
Daily is a widget to check calendar information from the home screen. It is highly customizable with a dynamic theme engine to match your style. Try exploring its other features.
Everyday Features | Calendar Widget
	A utility to check events.
	A utility for the things that matter most.
	A utility to navigate through different dates.
	Calendar First Date Number of Days # Empty Days
	Event number Event indicator Shows events and more.
	Dynamic theme engine is background aware to avoid...
</description></item><item><title>Download Barometer &amp;amp; Altimeter 2.9.00</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 16:41:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-barometer-altimeter-8934.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-barometer-altimeter-8934.html
</guid><description>
Barometer and altimeter is a simple app to measure atmospheric pressure and altitude.
Application used
	Integrated GPS
	Integrated pressure sensor / barometer (if the device does not have a barometric sensor, the application will get barometric pressure data via the Internet from the nearest meteorological station)
	Automatic altitude and barometric pressure correction algorithm, based on data from local meteorological stations
Barometric and altimeter features
	Accurate...
</description></item><item><title>Download Our Groceries Shopping List 7.0.7</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 16:41:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-our-groceries-shopping-list-10474.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-our-groceries-shopping-list-10474.html
</guid><description>
OurGroceries automatically keeps your family's grocery list in sync with the latest changes—on everyone in the family's phone or web browser. Any changes to your shared shopping list will appear in a few seconds. See items being checked out while your partner shops!
Features of our Grocery Shopping List
	Share your shopping list with family members, even if they have an iPhone.
	Share your recipes; Add them to your shopping list with just one tap.
	Add items using your Amazon Alexa...
</description></item><item><title>Download iTop Easy Desktop 4.0.0.231</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 02:30:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-itop-easy-desktop-7879.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-itop-easy-desktop-7879.html
</guid><description>
iTop Easy Desktop is a lightweight and easy-to-use desktop manager that organizes desktop icons, files and folders according to your rules, helping you Freed from the tedious arrangement of icons on the screen. It provides various practical features including but not limited to grouping desktop items, awakening live search, and quickly accessing icons and files even across multiple desktop sites. desktop.
Untidy desktop If you're not one to diligently organize your Windows desktop icons...
</description></item><item><title>Download CalendarTask (formerly DesktopCal) 3.26.261.8274</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 02:29:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopcal-1831.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopcal-1831.html
</guid><description>
CalendarTask (formerly DesktopCal) is a simple desktop calendar that blends into your desktop without blocking access to your desktop icons. You can double-click on a date to quickly add notes and also jump to specific dates in the past or future.
CalendarTask - Computer calendar
CalendarTask can use your current wallpaper or loop through images from your folder and update your desktop every few minutes. The program helps you make appointments, make plans... Not only that, the Screen...
</description></item><item><title>Download MuseScore 4.6.5 + Portable</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 02:29:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musescore-2857.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musescore-2857.html
</guid><description>
MuseScore is the tool score for Windows, macOS and Linux, can compare with Finale and Sibelius, support multiple file formats and input methods. It is released as free software and open source under The GNU general public License.
MuseScore - The application composer
Features of MuseScore
	Design WYSIWYG, notes are entered on a "virtual notice"
	TrueType fonts for printing and display allows split ratio high quality for all sizes
	Enter notes easily and quickly
	Many editing...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare PDFelement Pro 12.1.2.3904</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 02:27:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-pdfelement-pro-105.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-pdfelement-pro-105.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare PDFelement Pro support users to convert PDF to office documents for easier use, modify in every situation. Is one of the software conversion material is rated best today, integrated with many features. We recommend that you should use experience software many useful features this.
Wondershare PDFelement Pro - conversion Fie PDF more features, multi-language
Wondershare PDFelement Pro what?
Convert PDF into Word, Excel, PowerPoint...
• Convert PDF and protected PDF into...
</description></item><item><title>Download XYplorer 28.10.0200</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 02:27:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-533.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-533.html
</guid><description>
XYplorer - File Manager for Windows is software that supports users to manage files on the Window quickly and to arrange the folder tidy. XYplorer features tabbed browsing, search, files, powerful, preview, flexible, highly customizable interface, dual frame options and a variety of unique ways to automate effective tasks often repeat. It's fast, lightweight, and portable.
Features XYplorer
	XYplorer is a file manager mobile. It does not require any settings, store all configuration...
</description></item><item><title>Download Edraw Max Ultimate 15.0.6.1445</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 02:27:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-edraw-max-1121.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-edraw-max-1121.html
</guid><description>
Edraw Max is software draw professional looking diagrams help simplify creating diagrams, organization charts, network diagrams, business presentations, building plans, mind mapping, illustration, science, fashion designs, UML diagrams , workflows, program structure diagrams, web design diagrams, electrical engineering, directional maps, diagrams, databases, and more.
Edraw Max - Draw professional looking diagrams
EdrawSoft Edraw Max use software mapping best suits what you know and...
</description></item><item><title>Download HashTools 4.8.3</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 02:26:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hashtools-3056.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hashtools-3056.html
</guid><description>
HashTools is a program to encode files, hash files with user interface intuitive, which can operate with different algorithms: CRC32, MD5, SHA1, SHA256, SHA384 and SHA512. Archive with HashTools has the mobile version of the program, very convenient and suitable in these days, it's enough to unzip an archive file and you can use right this utility. The interface looks clean and easy to navigate in it, you will not be distracted by any graphic element, which means you can immediately...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ashampoo Backup Pro 27.5.36</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 02:25:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-backup-pro-716.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-backup-pro-716.html
</guid><description>
Ashampoo Backup Pro is software to backup and restore data professional to save the file, the important data for your computer. Ashampoo Backup Pro will remove the fear of viruses, ransomware, or hardware errors. Ashampoo® Backup Pro offers you various options to backup individual files or entire disk partitions on any storage media or on the cloud. User friendly, intuitive, fast. Even in case an error occurs the entire system, application integrated emergency can bring your...
</description></item><item><title>Download GiliSoft Audio Recorder Pro 15.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 02:25:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-audio-recorder-pro-855.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-audio-recorder-pro-855.html
</guid><description>
GiliSoft Audio Recorder Pro is software perfect recorder to record audio and microphone of your computer to AAC, AC3, AIFF, AMR, AU, FLAC, M4A, M4B, M4R, MKA, MP2, MP3, OGG, RA, VOC , WAV Files or WMA files on Windows 7/8. Recording the sound that goes through your sound card is not at all a difficult task, but GiliSoft Audio Recorder Pro promises to make everything a lot easier, even for those who do not have computer knowledge advanced.
GiliSoft Audio Recorder Pro - audio recording...
</description></item></channel></rss>