<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 13:48:56 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 13:48:56 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download W10Privacy 5.4.0.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 17 Jan 2026 16:48:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-w10privacy-2956.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-w10privacy-2956.html
</guid><description>
W10Privacy is a program lightweight and simple application that allows you to easily and quickly configure the privacy settings in system Windows its 10. Typically these options can be configured directly from the operating system, but they are hidden in some menu that the user can not normally access easily.
W10Privacy - Configure the options the right to privacy in Windows
The application will display the settings available clear, allowing you to configure the desired options...
</description></item><item><title>Download Diamond Cut Forensics Audio Laboratory 11.09</title><pubDate> Sat, 17 Jan 2026 16:48:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-diamond-cut-forensics-audio-laboratory-4390.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-diamond-cut-forensics-audio-laboratory-4390.html
</guid><description>
Diamond Cut Forensics Audio Laboratory is the sound engine also allows you to change the sample rate, resolution, quality switch mode and color scheme of the file, start recording based on time of day, create a wave test signal, convert the audio file into two single file or vice versa. as import and export presets to share with other users (e.g., average bandwidth, blender, compressor, constant noise, speed reducers, dynamics, echo, the enhanced).
Diamond Cut Forensics Audio Laboratory...
</description></item><item><title>Download SAPIEN PrimalSQL 2026 v4.5.90</title><pubDate> Sat, 17 Jan 2026 16:47:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sapien-primalsql-6922.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sapien-primalsql-6922.html
</guid><description>
Using PrimalSQL, you can connect to any database: from Microsoft SQL Server, Oracle, Microsoft Access, PostgreSQL or even MySQL. PrimalSQL can be used to build rich and complex queries. From the inside of the app, you can check and refine your queries, publish the results or create the code in a variety of languages. Modern interface, streamlined, makes PrimalSQL easy to understand and easy to use.
PrimalSQL has all the tools you need daily to create effective SQL statements quickly and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Newfangled Audio Articulate 1.1.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 17 Jan 2026 16:47:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-newfangled-audio-articulate-13682.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-newfangled-audio-articulate-13682.html
</guid><description>
Articulate by Newfangled Audio is a next-generation envelope shaping plugin designed to provide precise control over the dynamics of any audio source. Unlike traditional transient shapers, Articulate divides the envelope into four independent segments—Attack, Decay, Sustain, and Release—allowing users to shape each phase separately to add “Smack,” “Punch,” “Body,” and “Air” to their sound. This allows for detailed enhancement of transient, presence, sustain and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Newfangled Audio Generate 1.7.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 17 Jan 2026 16:47:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-newfangled-audio-generate-6627.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-newfangled-audio-generate-6627.html
</guid><description>
Generate is based on a set of chaotic generators. What looks like randomness contains underlying patterns, interconnectedness, constant feedback loops, repetition, self-similarity, fractals, and self-organization. Each of Generate’s 8 chaotic generators bring out these underlying patterns and create an oscillator that can smoothly fade from a sine wave to total chaos, with an expanse of territory to explore in between. The musical textures created include distortion, harmonics, grunge,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Easy Backup 2026 v14.2.0.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 17 Jan 2026 16:46:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easy-backup-9970.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easy-backup-9970.html
</guid><description>
Easy Backup is a free backup solution for your files or the entire system with wizards and video tutorials to assist you through the process. Once configured, the software automatically backs up your data and allows you to store different versions of your files or even your deleted files
Recovering data is very easy. You can restore the integrity of your data or just some files at the desired date and time. For advanced users, restoring can be done manually from the backup media via...
</description></item><item><title>Download Alternate TextBrowser 4.470</title><pubDate> Sat, 17 Jan 2026 16:45:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-alternate-textbrowser-2743.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-alternate-textbrowser-2743.html
</guid><description>
Alternate TextBrowser is a text editor, markup syntax, reliable and useful, useful for users that need to browse through a number of documents TXT and HTML in few minutes. Alternate TextBrowser will syntax highlighting for some programming languages / file types are available and can be configured for the file extensions different. The program includes the memorandum replaced and the Computer replaced as the additional tool. It is free software and requires Net-Framework 2.0 or higher...
</description></item><item><title>Download SAPIEN CIM Explorer 2026 v2.4.116</title><pubDate> Sat, 17 Jan 2026 16:42:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sapien-cim-explorer-6920.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sapien-cim-explorer-6920.html
</guid><description>
CIM Explorer is the next generation tool for exploring the vast universe of Windows Management Instrumentation databases. The CIM database represents an extensive repository of information about your servers and clients that you, as a network or system administrator, need to use every day.
Use CIM Explorer's Windows PowerShell code generation capabilities to generate code for queries or even a GUI application with just a few clicks. The built-in PowerShell console for Windows PowerShell...
</description></item><item><title>Download SAPIEN PrimalScript 2026 v8.1.223</title><pubDate> Sat, 17 Jan 2026 16:42:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sapien-primalscript-6923.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sapien-primalscript-6923.html
</guid><description>
PrimalScript is the next generation of our industry-leading Universal Script Environment. As a system, database or network administrator, web developer, or end-user developer, you need to work with multiple technologies, languages, and file formats at the same time. The ribbon interface of PrimalScript has been carefully designed to provide almost all the functions you use every day on the Home tab. Create scenario templates based on your requirements and business needs to drive faster...
</description></item><item><title>Download SAPIEN PrimalXML 2026 v4.7.86</title><pubDate> Sat, 17 Jan 2026 16:41:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sapien-primalxml-6921.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sapien-primalxml-6921.html
</guid><description>
Working with XML as text can be complicated, tedious, and difficult. Why not use a tool specifically designed to edit, manipulate and create XML files? With PrimalXML you can open any XML file and view it as text, apply syntax highlighting to elements and attributes making everything clear. Apply styleSheets to XML data and view the results in HTML. XML validation against a schema.
Features of PrimalXML:
	Provides PrimalSense XML code completion .
	Automatically colorize your XML...
</description></item><item><title>Download TidyWindow 3.8.9</title><pubDate> Sat, 17 Jan 2026 00:48:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tidywindow-14454.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tidywindow-14454.html
</guid><description>
TidyWindow is a Windows desktop assistant that automates developer PC setup, cleanup, diagnostics, software package installation, registry tweaking, and driver updates—powered by a WPF interface and robust PowerShell 7 automation capabilities in the background.
Key Features
	Essentials Repair Center (docs/essentials.md): Queues selected automation tasks Filter for network, Defender, printing, and Windows Update issues. Each task supports preview run, sequential execution, restore...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mirillis Action! 4.47.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 23:24:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mirillis-action-213.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mirillis-action-213.html
</guid><description>
Mirillis Action! is a game video recording software,  screen recording, take screenshot with impressive sharpness and 4K quality. It's a simple, reliable and effective software solution that's worth it when you need to access features like streaming and recording and work on desktop with unique HD video quality.
Mirillis Action makes exporting and uploading your recordings to popular services and social networks like YouTube and Facebook very easy. Work! provides predefined export...
</description></item><item><title>Download VectorStyler 1.3.007</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 23:24:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vectorstyler-7917.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vectorstyler-7917.html
</guid><description>
VectorStyler provides a complete set of drawing, design and illustration tools needed for modern design. Create illustrations, logos, icons, drawings, typography, vector art for screen, print and web. With many new features, VectorStyler redefines and extends the tools available to illustrators and designers, improving the creation of complex illustrations and designs.
Shape effects can be used to adjust the shape of objects, create different distortions, or add detail to shapes. Shape...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare UniConverter 17.1.5.476</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 23:23:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-uniconverter-4808.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-uniconverter-4808.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare UniConverter ( old name is Wondershare Video Converter Ultimate) which allows you to convert the video format. You can cut, splice, move, or add effects, subtitles a easy way. When using software you easily cut, splice, move, as well as add the effects, the subtitles to the video.... Or can switch the clods SD, HD video to any format popular for use with iPod (Classic, Nano and Touch), iPhone, Apple TV, Zune, PSP, Pocket PC...
Wondershare UniConverter helps convert formats...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ashampoo Backup Pro 27.5.41</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 23:23:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-backup-pro-716.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-backup-pro-716.html
</guid><description>
Ashampoo Backup Pro is software to backup and restore data professional to save the file, the important data for your computer. Ashampoo Backup Pro will remove the fear of viruses, ransomware, or hardware errors. Ashampoo® Backup Pro offers you various options to backup individual files or entire disk partitions on any storage media or on the cloud. User friendly, intuitive, fast. Even in case an error occurs the entire system, application integrated emergency can bring your...
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 7.8.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 23:21:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-11-7760.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-11-7760.html
</guid><description>
TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 is a program that allows users to discover hidden settings in Windows 11. This application is specially designed for Windows 11, groups many registry settings and distribute them from the easy and secure user interface. With TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 you can move the Windows taskbar to the top and resize the taskbar by editing the registry value. With any application that modifies the registry, we recommend that you have a backup copy...
</description></item><item><title>Download Aiseesoft HEIC Converter 1.0.50</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 23:21:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aiseesoft-heic-converter-7111.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aiseesoft-heic-converter-7111.html
</guid><description>
Aiseesoft HEIC Converter is a professional tool that allows you to convert iPhone, iPad, iPod photos from HEIC to JPG or PNG on Windows. With this powerful HEIC converter, you can convert all your HEIF (.heic) photos to JPG/JPEG or to PNG on your Windows or Mac computer without any hassle.
This highly efficient image format allows you to create and store images at a much smaller size without sacrificing image quality. With Aiseesoft HEIC Converter, you can simply convert HEIF (.heic)...
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 7.8.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 23:20:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-10-7759.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-10-7759.html
</guid><description>
TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 is a utility that allows users to discover hidden settings in Windows 10. This application is specially designed for Windows 10, groups many registry settings and provide them from an easy and secure user interface. With TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 you can move the Windows taskbar to the top and resize the taskbar by editing the registry value. With any application that modifies the registry, we recommend that you have a backup copy to...
</description></item><item><title>Download PC Internals Pro 2.100</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 23:20:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pc-internals-pro-13002.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pc-internals-pro-13002.html
</guid><description>
PC Internals Pro is a new solution that allows Windows users to comprehensively analyze the system components and reliable monitoring of the hard drive. This software is aimed at individual users as well as IT experts and retail agents attach importance to transparency, early detection and data security. PC Internals provides detailed information about the processor, RAM, graphics card, drive and other system components. The chart directly displays the current load, while the specific...
</description></item><item><title>Download PerfectTUNES 2026-01-16</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 23:19:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfecttunes-7115.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfecttunes-7115.html
</guid><description>
PerfectTUNES is a versatile music file manager that lets you find album art, check music folders for duplicates, and scan your songs for rip errors. export. PerfectTUNES comes as a software package, containing three applications that handle each function individually. PerfectTUNES is an intuitive, yet easy-to-use tool that allows you to organize your albums and music files, remove damaged songs, or remove duplicates. You can use its functions to clean up your music folder as well as find...
</description></item><item><title>Download Snappy Driver Installer 1.26.0 (R2600)</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 23:14:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-snappy-driver-installer-9472.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-snappy-driver-installer-9472.html
</guid><description>
Snappy Driver Installer is a free and open source software tool designed to help users install and update device drivers on Windows operating systems. Device drivers are software programs that allow the operating system to communicate with and control hardware devices such as graphics cards, sound cards, network adapters, etc.
It's important to note that while Snappy Driver Installer can be a useful tool for managing drivers on Windows systems, we always recommend caution when...
</description></item><item><title>Download KDEnlive 25.12.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 23:12:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kdenlive-3288.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kdenlive-3288.html
</guid><description>
Kdenlive is a video editor open source. The project was started in about 2003. Kdenlive is built on the Qt libraries and the KDE Frameworks. Most of the video processing is done by the MLT Framework, based on many open-source projects other as FFmpeg , frei0r , Movit, ladspa, sox, etc.
KDEnlive - video editing quickly
Our software is designed to meet most needs, from basic video editing to professional work. Kdenlive allows you to use and arrange a number of music and video, each can...
</description></item><item><title>Download TechSmith Snagit 2026 v26.0.0.9483</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 23:11:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-techsmith-snagit-01en-280.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-techsmith-snagit-01en-280.html
</guid><description>
TechSmith Snagit software screen capture anything on your screen, then easily add text arrows or effects and save the snapshot to a file or share it immediately by e-mail or IM. With TechSmith Snagit you can capture and share the article, photo or Web page directly from your screen.
TechSmith Snagit
TechSmith Snagit help you can take a photo screen in the form of roll, panoramic shooting, shooting photos of and easy photo editing after shooting. Besides it is feature - video recording...
</description></item><item><title>Download Accentize dxRevive Pro 1.2.8</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 23:11:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-accentize-dxrevive-pro-11436.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-accentize-dxrevive-pro-11436.html
</guid><description>
dxRevive Pro is a flexible voice recovery plugin, designed to enhance the quality of various dialogue recordings. Unlike many other recovery plugins, dxRevive does more than just filter signals. It goes even further, identifying and reintegrating missing frequency components, creating studio-like recordings from multi-source material.
Accentize dxRevive Pro Features
	Noise removal
	Resonance reduction
	Restore absent frequency
	Remove Codec components (for example, from Skype or Zoom...
</description></item><item><title>Download COAA PlanePlotter 6.7.3.6</title><pubDate> Fri, 16 Jan 2026 23:11:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coaa-planeplotter-7840.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coaa-planeplotter-7840.html
</guid><description>
PlanePlotter receives and decodes digital position reports directly from the aircraft and plots them on a chart. Using PlanePlotter, you can see the radar-like display of all aircraft around you transmitting the appropriate digital messages including ACARS, ADS-B and HFDL.
PlanePlotter Features
	PlanePlotter displays a table showing messages received and decoded from direct plane transmissions.
	PlanePlotter stores all digital data it receives and decodes into a log...
</description></item></channel></rss>