<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 19:56:59 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 19:56:59 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download AudioRealism ADM1x 1.6.2.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Sep 2025 22:56:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-audiorealism-adm1x-11483.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-audiorealism-adm1x-11483.html
</guid><description>
AudioRealism ADM1x is a combination of three classic drum machines (808, 909 and 606) using virtual analog emulation and sample player in one plug-in. The ADM emulates three classic drum machines from that era rolled into one, combined with a 32-step internal sequencer and sample control (PCF) effects.
ADM contains 25 drum generators, each carefully modeled after classic analog circuitry, and 4 PCM players, for a total of 34 sounds (some generators have two sounds). Certain sounds have...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDF-XChange Editor Plus 10.7.2.400.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Sep 2025 17:42:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-xchange-editor-plus-645.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-xchange-editor-plus-645.html
</guid><description>
PDF-XChange Editor Plus is the editor, PDF viewer, compact, fast with many features, add-ons, professional. When using the PDF-XChange Editor Plus, easy for users to create, view, edit, annotate, OCR and digital signing PDF files, plus much more.
PDF-XChange Editor is a PDF editing full-featured. With the help of it, you can edit, fix, add, or delete text easily. Graphics can also be moved, resized or removed.
Features PDF-XChange Editor Plus
Edit documents
	Use a variety of editing...
</description></item><item><title>Download ET Optimizer 6.07.35</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Sep 2025 17:42:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-et-optimizer-9574.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-et-optimizer-9574.html
</guid><description>
ET-Optimizer is a free, open source script to improve your computer's overall performance and optimize it for your workflow through optimized scripting. With this optimization, setup takes little effort. The script is developed from many sources found on the Internet, tested and updated for different versions of the system. The whole script is contained in 1 file, it uses: command prompt, powershell, power plan configuration, startup configuration, registry changes, network interface...
</description></item><item><title>Download MemoryCleaner 1.8.8</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Sep 2025 17:41:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-memorycleaner-12469.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-memorycleaner-12469.html
</guid><description>
MemoryCleaner is a tool to free up memory on your computer. This is a free app with a simple user interface that makes it easy for users of all skill levels to use. MemoryCleaner uses many functions built into Windows to free up memory without affecting your system. You can also access Memory Cleaner's functions right from the system tray without having to open the program. The cleaning processes are silent and the only time you see a warning is to briefly display the amount of RAM...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDF-XChange Pro 10.7.2.400.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Sep 2025 17:40:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-xchange-editor-pro-3422.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-xchange-editor-pro-3422.html
</guid><description>
PDF-XChange Editor Pro is an application to manipulate and create PDF versatile, offering a wide range of useful features and powerful will help you to easily work with PDF files. This application is very flexible and allows you to easily create and modify PDF files. PDF-XChange Editor Pro provides a powerful set of tools and flexibility to work with PDF files, such as editor PDF-XChange new, utilities series, OFFice2PDF and the Addin tool Bar allows you to easily convert multiple file...
</description></item><item><title>Download Bitvise SSH Client 9.47</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Sep 2025 17:39:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bitvise-ssh-client-2845.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bitvise-ssh-client-2845.html
</guid><description>
Bitvise SSH Client is a SSH terminal, tunneling and file transfer application SFTP for free with the command line interface and graphics. It supports all versions desktop and server of Windows! Bitvise SSH Client for free use! Bitvise SSH Client is an application multipurpose, fast and powerful in the transmission of the advanced file helps users control and manage the terminal remotely in a flexible manner. Bitvise SSH Client intensive support for establishing the secure connection...
</description></item><item><title>Download USB Device Tree Viewer 4.6.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Sep 2025 17:39:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-usb-device-tree-viewer-3286.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-usb-device-tree-viewer-3286.html
</guid><description>
USB Device Tree Viewer provides detailed information for all the ports and USB hub on the computer in the format tree. If a device is connected to a port, it also provides detailed information for the properties of the device and connection. USB Device Tree Viewer analyze your system configuration and display details about the controller server is connected, such as the manufacturer, drivers, bus types, list, location, devices, drive letters, COM ports, and debugging and statistics bus...
</description></item><item><title>Download Bitwig Studio 5.3.13</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Sep 2025 17:39:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bitwig-studio-3626.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bitwig-studio-3626.html
</guid><description>
Find new standard in the process of individual work. Bitwig Studio excite you good control over his music, give you access to all features of your production. Streamline course creation of you and quickly develop your ideas into the songs, compositions and music full.
Bitwig Studio - Create your own music
Arrange and record, perform and improvise, or do all at the same time. Choose among the many records displayed. Design your sound with the equipment container commitment. Mixing the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Google Chrome 140.0.7339.81</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Sep 2025 17:38:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-chrome-1012.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-chrome-1012.html
</guid><description>
Google Chrome web browser is the most used today. Support surf the web, listen to music, watch movies, play web game effective no jerky lag with the internet connection stable. When you are surfing the web or performing an important task, whether it is operation big or small, work or entertainment, then Chrome has the smart features and the speed you need to make, create and explore on the net.
The latest version of Google Chrome is the third 114. But we are providing for users Google...
</description></item><item><title>Download Android Studio 2025.1.3.7</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Sep 2025 17:37:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-android-studio-3890.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-android-studio-3890.html
</guid><description>
Android Studio is an Android development environment, completely new, provides many improvements and new features compared to Eclipse ADT. This software solution will is IDE the official Android when is finishing. This tool provides many tools and features such as editing, layout, rich set of tools to capture usability, compatibility version, performance and other issues, create a lot APK, build system based on Gradle flexibility, extended support for Google Services, integrated support...
</description></item><item><title>Download SRWare Iron 138.7000.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Sep 2025 17:36:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-srware-iron-6304.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-srware-iron-6304.html
</guid><description>
SRWare Iron  is a Chromium-based web browser developed by the German company SRWare. It is mainly intended to remove usage tracking and other privacy-infringing functionality that Google Chrome browser includes. SRWare Iron Browser is an exact copy of Google Chrome, but it does not have features for collecting personal information. This ensures you can still take advantage of the power of Google Chrome, while being completely assured of your personal information.
A useful feature...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft PowerToys for Windows 10/11 0.94</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Sep 2025 17:36:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-powertoys-for-windows-6014.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-powertoys-for-windows-6014.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft PowerToys is a user-proficiency set to adjust and streamline their Windows experience for higher productivity. Inspired by Windows 95's PowerToys project, this reboot provides users with proficiency in ways to exploit the more efficient Windows 10 and customisable processes it provides for each work process.
Utility of Microsoft PowerToys
	FancyZones is a window manager that allows you to easily create complex windows layout and quickly locate windows in those layout.
	Image...
</description></item><item><title>Download Photo Supreme 2025.3.3.8084</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Sep 2025 17:35:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photo-supreme-430.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photo-supreme-430.html
</guid><description>
Photo Supreme is a software product management professional pictures of idimager. With Photo Supreme you can arrange, manage back stock photo archive of yourself and share them with you here and relatives easily via Email or Facebook. Photo Supreme provides users method to sort images effective, logical, as well as edit and share your photos with friends and relatives in the family. Especially the Photo Supreme allows to work with multiple image formats and support mounting support,...
</description></item><item><title>Download JWIZARD Cleaner 1.8.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Sep 2025 17:33:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jwizard-cleaner-12853.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jwizard-cleaner-12853.html
</guid><description>
Effective Windows cleaning software to remove unnecessary files from your PC. JWIZARD Cleaner for Windows quickly frees up disk space and keeps your system in an optimal state, ensuring your PC runs stably and efficiently. This application is designed to provide you with a comprehensive tool to analyze and optimize your PC by performing a comprehensive cleanup or a more detailed cleanup, targeting specific areas such as system, browser, mail, etc.
Features of JWIZARD Cleaner
	Clean...
</description></item><item><title>Download Benthic Golden 8.2.0.820</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Sep 2025 17:32:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-benthic-software-golden-4113.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-benthic-software-golden-4113.html
</guid><description>
Benthic Software Golden is a query tool for Oracle database. It includes the possibility of advanced queries, edit data and ability to import and export powerful, including support for Excel spreadsheet and Calc. It features compatibility closely with sqlplus estimate scenario consists of the variable binding, variable prompting and parameter scripts to go through. Benthic Software Golden can export directly to Excel files xls and xlsx. Exports can be scripted and run automatically using...
</description></item><item><title>Download VovSoft Website File Collector 1.6</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Sep 2025 17:31:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-website-file-collector-12765.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-website-file-collector-12765.html
</guid><description>
Vovsoft Website File Collector is a powerful Windows application designed to simplify downloading files from websites. Whether you need documents, images, scripts or media files, the software allows you to collect the resources you need quickly and efficiently.
With an easy-to-use interface, you can enter a website URL or multiple URLs, specify the file type you are interested in (such as PDF, DOC, JPG, CSS, JS or any custom file extension) and let the software do the rest. The program...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sophia Script Wrapper 6.9.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Sep 2025 17:31:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sophia-script-wrapper-7074.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sophia-script-wrapper-7074.html
</guid><description>
Sophia Script Wrapper is another Windows 10 "debugger" that uses Powershell to fine-tune and automate the flow of tasks in Windows 10 and Windows 11. The script is designed Designed and best used on clean installs of Windows 10 and Windows 11. Over 150 tweaks available at this time.
The script divides all available tweaks into 11 categories, including telemetry and privacy, games, context menus, Windows Security, and more. Best of all, once you make all your selections, you can export...
</description></item><item><title>Download Pulsar Modular Complete Effects Bundle 2025.9.3</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Sep 2025 17:29:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pulsar-modular-complete-effects-bundle-11871.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pulsar-modular-complete-effects-bundle-11871.html
</guid><description>
Pulsar module complete effects package for high quality audio mixing and mastering, is a powerful and thorough passive EQ plugin. The program combines the power of the leading passive equalizers from 70 years ago with several unique design elements to create a completely original sound. With extremely rich sources such as synth pads or synth bass, it can also be used as a sculpting tool. It has a simple and user-friendly graphical interface with a quick and adaptable process to produce...
</description></item><item><title>Download DesktopOK 11.98</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Sep 2025 17:29:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopok-1635.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopok-1635.html
</guid><description>
DesktopOK is software save and restore the positions of icons. DesktopOK also offers a solution small but effective for the user to change the screen resolution often. DesktopOK is not installed and can be executed easily from the desktop, and can be carried on a small USB or memory device to another. Start of the program. The first time you use the program, the program will show you screen license. Free program and license info is only displayed the first time (on each PC).
DesktopOK -...
</description></item><item><title>Download Footej Camera - PRO HD Camera 1.2.13</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Sep 2025 16:39:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-footej-camera-pro-hd-camera-10592.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-footej-camera-pro-hd-camera-10592.html
</guid><description>
Footej Camera - Pro HD Camera is a new, attractive, user-friendly and powerful professional camera app that is here, ready to capture, organize and give a new life to your best moments! Improve the quality of your photos with the best camera app! Footej is a unique photo and video camera app that uses Android's Camera 2 API! Professional-grade Camera app that's easy to use, take photos and create a masterpiece.
Experience a whole new level of mobile photography! FUL DSLR Camera, Manual...
</description></item><item><title>Download FV File Pro 1.26.8</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Sep 2025 16:39:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-fv-file-pro-10802.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-fv-file-pro-10802.html
</guid><description>
File Explorer folder. Fast and powerful file manager for Android. Go to /Android/data and on /Android/obb Android 13 without root. Manage your files via HTTP, FTP or SFTP within your LAN without using data cables. It's convenient to transfer documents, images, text files, etc. between computer and mobile phone. Don't have to waste mobile card traffic to share files with colleagues or family members.
Features of FV File Pro
	Supports viewing jpg, png, bmp, tiff, webp, heif, avif, ico,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Shazam: Find Music &amp;amp; Concerts 16.7.0-250826</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Sep 2025 16:38:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-shazam-music-discovery-10763.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-shazam-music-discovery-10763.html
</guid><description>
Shazam will identify any song in seconds. Discover, artists, lyrics, videos &amp;amp; playlists, all for free. Over 1 billion installs and counting. Use Pop-up Shazam to identify music in any app - Instagram, YouTube, TikTok... No connection? No problem! Shazam while offline.
Features of Shazam: Music Discovery
	Find the name of any song in seconds.
	Listen and add to Apple Music playlists.
	Follow along with time-synced lyrics.
	Watch music videos from Apple Music or YouTube.
	Enable...
</description></item><item><title>Download jetAudio+ Hi-Res Music Player 12.3.4</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Sep 2025 16:38:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-jetaudio-hd-music-player-plus-8339.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-jetaudio-hd-music-player-plus-8339.html
</guid><description>
jetAudio is an mp3 player with a 10/20 band graphic equalizer and various sound effects. jetAudio HD Music Player Plus is a mobile music player app for Android devices that offers advanced audio features and customization options. This application is famous for its high-quality sound reproduction and support for many audio formats, including lossless formats such as FLAC and WAV.
Features of jetAudio HD Music Player Plus
	High quality sound reproduction
	Supports many audio formats,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Auto Text: Schedule Messages 5.7.9</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Sep 2025 16:33:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-auto-text-auto-send-message-8447.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-auto-text-auto-send-message-8447.html
</guid><description>
Auto Text: Auto send WA &amp;amp; SMS is a feature or application that allows users to automatically send pre-written text messages at a specific time or in response to a request. specific activation. This feature can be useful in many situations, such as sending reminders, sending messages to loved ones at a specific time, or sending messages in response to certain events, such as calls to or location-based triggers.
Auto Text features: Auto send WA &amp;amp; SMS
	Automatically send happy...
</description></item><item><title>Download Anti Spy Detector: Anti Hack 44.28.8.25</title><pubDate> Wed, 03 Sep 2025 16:33:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-anti-spy-detector-firewall-10779.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-anti-spy-detector-firewall-10779.html
</guid><description>
With the powerful built-in firewall in this app, you can monitor every outgoing connection each app makes. If you don't trust the app, you can block it from accessing the internet with a firewall to prevent tracking and analysis. Every outgoing IP or domain will be saved and you can see them, the Firewall will show you the address, organization and information about that IP and if you feel suspicious you can block that domain so that application is no longer accessible. Additionally, you...
</description></item></channel></rss>