<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 10:24:58 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 10:24:58 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Intel Graphics Driver for Windows 10 / 11 32.0.101.8509</title><pubDate> Sun, 15 Feb 2026 01:02:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intel-graphics-driver-for-windows-10-5954.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intel-graphics-driver-for-windows-10-5954.html
</guid><description>
Intel Graphics Driver for Windows 10 supports Intel ' s latest 8th-generation Core processor, introducing the Intel ® UHD graphics, with the ability to immerve in the top 4K UHD entertainment from your laptop for a maximum of 10 hours. Along with some security fixes, this driver also optimised the system's inactivity to reduce power consumption.
Look at the complete new interface of gameplay.intel.com, where you will find the proposed game settings for many of your favorite PC games....
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare PDFelement Pro 12.1.12.4034</title><pubDate> Sun, 15 Feb 2026 01:01:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-pdfelement-pro-105.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-pdfelement-pro-105.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare PDFelement Pro support users to convert PDF to office documents for easier use, modify in every situation. Is one of the software conversion material is rated best today, integrated with many features. We recommend that you should use experience software many useful features this.
Wondershare PDFelement Pro - conversion Fie PDF more features, multi-language
Wondershare PDFelement Pro what?
Convert PDF into Word, Excel, PowerPoint...
• Convert PDF and protected PDF into...
</description></item><item><title>Download ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro 15.26.0214</title><pubDate> Sun, 15 Feb 2026 01:00:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-videotube-downloader-pro-1276.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-videotube-downloader-pro-1276.html
</guid><description>
ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro is the professional version support download videos and playlists from YouTube, videos from Dailymotion, BBC iPlayer, ITV Player, ABC,  FOX,CBS.com Vimeo, Prosieben, Metacafe, Blip.tv CBC.ca many more video sites. After the video is downloaded, you can convert them to the formats compatible with iPad, iPhone, iPod, MPEG-4, H. 264, MP3, AC3.
ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro - Download videos on Youtube
This is one of the software download the most...
</description></item><item><title>Download Photo Mechanic All-in-One 2026.2 build 9034</title><pubDate> Sun, 15 Feb 2026 00:59:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photo-mechanic-all-in-one-12282.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photo-mechanic-all-in-one-12282.html
</guid><description>
Photo Mechanic All-in-One is an image management software, photo collection and categorization of all photos on your computer, it allows you to Import, Edit and Export quickly, helping you reduce your work. work in the workflow. Powerful batch processing, full support for image variables, IPTC and Exif metadata, make it the perfect tool for any digital photographer.
Photo Mechanic All-in-One Features
	Photo Mechanic takes this step further by automating other tasks at the same time,...
</description></item><item><title>Download OkMap Desktop 19.4.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 15 Feb 2026 00:59:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-okmap-desktop-581.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-okmap-desktop-581.html
</guid><description>
OkMap Desktop is interactive software working on the computer with web maps or digital maps bought or scanned. OkMap can also import a data vector from the most common formats and data DEM related to information height.
Through the map you can organize your path by creating waypoints , routesand tracks on the screen your computer, and upload this data to your GPS . OkMap set data high speedautomatic and estimated moving time . Furthermore OkMap provides you also have autorouting and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Libre Hardware Monitor 0.9.6</title><pubDate> Sun, 15 Feb 2026 00:58:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-libre-hardware-monitor-7447.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-libre-hardware-monitor-7447.html
</guid><description>
Libre Hardware Monitor, a fork of Open Hardware Monitor, is free software that can monitor your temperature, fan speed, voltage, load, and clock speed sensors. your computer. With the help of LibreHardwareMonitor you can read information from devices like:
	Motherboard
	Intel and AMD processors
	NVIDIA and AMD Graphics Card
	HDD, SSD, and NVMe
	Network cards.
</description></item><item><title>Download Symantec Ghost Boot CD 12.0.0.13027</title><pubDate> Sun, 15 Feb 2026 00:56:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-symantec-ghost-boot-cd-4093.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-symantec-ghost-boot-cd-4093.html
</guid><description>
Symantec Ghost Boot CD is a program to create and restore backup images of entire disks, partitions, or individual directories, and allows you to restore the system even when everything seems to hurt. Symantec Ghost Boot CD will help you create a backup of the entire system that you can use to restore your computer in case an error occurs, the hard drive or system malfunction, big. Ghost allows you to backup to any media type, including CD and DVD, external hard drive or disk, Iomega Zip...
</description></item><item><title>Download Macrorit Partition Expert Pro 8.9.0 All Editions</title><pubDate> Sun, 15 Feb 2026 00:55:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-macrorit-partition-expert-pro-4116.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-macrorit-partition-expert-pro-4116.html
</guid><description>
Macrorit Partition Expert Pro is software partition powerful drive, allowing users to expand, create and format the partition, bug fixes, disk space low, manage disk space on MBR disk and GPT. The disk management utility is completely free this is designed for home users, supports operating systems Windows 32/64 bit including Windows XP, Vista, Windows 7/8 and Windows 10 latest. Besides, Macrorit Partition Expert Pro also owns protection technology, unique data and algorithms, data...
</description></item><item><title>Download Opera One 127.0.5778.64</title><pubDate> Sun, 15 Feb 2026 00:54:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-972.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-972.html
</guid><description>
Opera is a fast, safe, configurable and compliant intranet web browser, which includes both the reader and the application. The Opera browser supports web browsing, listening to music, watching high speed movies, you can open many tabs on the Opera without affecting your browsing speed. Opera now supports almost all devices and operating systems such as windows, IOS, Android, linux, MacOS ...
Opera is a beautiful interface and many interesting features, operating on both PCs and mobile,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Quicken WillMaker &amp;amp; Trust 26.3.3133</title><pubDate> Sun, 15 Feb 2026 00:53:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quicken-willmaker-trust-4277.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quicken-willmaker-trust-4277.html
</guid><description>
Quicken WillMaker &amp;amp; Trust is the easiest way to create a package of your estate, whether you beginner or you want to update the sort earlier. This powerful software guides you throughout the process from beginning to end, provide you with practical information and legal that you need to take the best decision for you and your family. Quicken WillMaker &amp;amp; Trust is software write wills original, created and regularly updated by the experts of Nolo. Updates free legal will continue the...
</description></item><item><title>Download nTopology 5.40.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 15 Feb 2026 00:52:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ntopology-7887.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ntopology-7887.html
</guid><description>
nTopology is software that enables engineers and designers to create any geometry no matter how complex and meet the requirements of high performance products . Our software is used from research through production to create breakthrough products and processes for the aerospace, automotive, medical and consumer industries. Our customers depend on the general design capabilities of the nTopology to get the most out of new hardware, optimize components where performance is important,...
</description></item><item><title>Download tinyMediaManager 5.2.7</title><pubDate> Sun, 15 Feb 2026 00:51:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tinymediamanager-1819.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tinymediamanager-1819.html
</guid><description>
tinyMediaManager is a media manager full-featured to arrange and cleanup your media library your. Just choose (s) the folder containing your movies and the program can automatically get all meta data required for movies and program your TV from TheMovieDB.org, Imdb.com, OFDb.de and other online sources. tinyMediaManager download at artwork, film, cast, plot and details of other communication. Each film or program is presented with a unique art background, category, and appropriate...
</description></item><item><title>Download Rocrail Build 6654</title><pubDate> Sun, 15 Feb 2026 00:51:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rocrail-3193.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rocrail-3193.html
</guid><description>
Rocrail is a free software to control the training model for the operating system Linux , Apple macOS , Windows and Raspbian / Armbian . Rocrail bear all responsibility in the control of a railway model, and accessories of them. Trains can be controlled manually or fully controlled by software in automatic mode. A mixed operation, i.e. control a number of ships and other vessels at high speed fully automatic is possible.
Rocrail - control layout for the operating system
With Rocrail,...
</description></item><item><title>Download XL-Connector 3.6.49.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 15 Feb 2026 00:50:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xl-connector-12415.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xl-connector-12415.html
</guid><description>
XL-Connector is a popular plugin that securely integrates Excel and Salesforce to export, import, refresh and transform data seamlessly with ultra-fast api connection. It provides Salesforce administrators with a comprehensive toolbox that easily performs data and metadata management activities in a familiar Excel environment.
Features
Export from Salesforce to Excel
	Get data from existing Salesforce reports or build your own SOQL queries directly into Excel.
Import data into...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft Edge 145.0.3800.58</title><pubDate> Sun, 15 Feb 2026 00:49:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-edge-3940.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-edge-3940.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft Edge is web browser developed specifically for Windows operating system 10 alternatives to Internet Explorer is the default browser on Windows. Browser Microsoft Edge built-in assistant Cortana brings content and website based on the user's preferences, there are also system utilities quite extensive help you to customize according to individual. Microsoft Edge has the similarity with Google Chrome quite large, except the target is marked more of the interface and the rounded...
</description></item><item><title>Download Topaz Gigapixel Pro 1.1.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 14 Feb 2026 16:42:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-ai-gigapixel-1318.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-ai-gigapixel-1318.html
</guid><description>
Topaz ONE Gigapixel is the first app and only use the power of artificial intelligence to enhance your photos, add natural details, for great results. Use technology to learn deep, AIGigapixel ™ can zoom in and fill in the details that the products change in size other are not included. The traditional method this created blurred image, a non-realistic and do not have the detail present in the image have high resolution.
Topaz A.I. Gigapixel - enhance image quality
The content of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Fan Control v259</title><pubDate> Sat, 14 Feb 2026 16:41:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fancontrol-5749.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fancontrol-5749.html
</guid><description>
FanControl is a highly customizable fan control software for Windows. Stay in control of every aspect of your PC's GPU and CPU fan with the help of this highly customizable fan control app.
Features of FanControl
	Save, edit and load multiple configurations
	Multiple temperature sources (CPU, GPU, motherboard, hard drive, ".sensor" files)
	Custom fan curve
	Fine tune fan control response with steps,% start,% stop, response time and delay
	Mix different curves and sensors...
</description></item><item><title>Download .NET Checker 1.5</title><pubDate> Sat, 14 Feb 2026 16:41:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-net-checker-10355.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-net-checker-10355.html
</guid><description>
.NET Checker is a free utility that gives you an easy way to determine which version of Microsoft .NET and Visual C++ is currently installed on your device. You can also find out what version of .NET a particular application needs. .NET Checker makes the process of checking which versions you have and which ones you don't easy, and the fact that it's small and portable is a bonus. Results are compiled and displayed quickly, and usage is simple, making it great for users of all levels who...
</description></item><item><title>Download reaConverter Pro 8.0.197</title><pubDate> Sat, 14 Feb 2026 16:40:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html
</guid><description>
reaConverter Pro is software image processing feature with batch conversion and image editing periodically becomes simple. eaConverter also provide command line utilities allow you to process images automatically, thus helping you shorten the time for other work.
reaConverter Pro integrated powerful tool of Uber with many great features. It provides advanced solutions to process and adjust images. Management of the conversion process the base image with the latest version of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Urban VPN 5.0.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 14 Feb 2026 16:39:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-urban-vpn-7155.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-urban-vpn-7155.html
</guid><description>
Urban VPN is a subsidiary of Urban Cyber ​​Security and the creators of one of the world's most trusted and free virtual private networks. VPN Browser Extension Gives You Quick and Easy Activation &amp;amp; Unlimited bandwidth! Urban VPN helps you keep your device activities safe and private. Protect your device from harmful ads and protect your device from malware and other security holes when using public Wi-Fi connections. With Urban VPN, you can safely surf the web without fear of...
</description></item><item><title>Download PhraseExpress 17.0.135</title><pubDate> Sat, 14 Feb 2026 16:38:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-phraseexpress-41.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-phraseexpress-41.html
</guid><description>
PhraseExpress is a useful application that helps users save time when typing frequently used text or commands. This application allows users to create shortcuts to automatically insert text quickly and conveniently.
With PhraseExpress, users can create "templates" for common commands, regular emails, chat messages, or any text they have to retype frequently. Users only need to set up shortcuts for each template and when needed, just type that shortcut and the text will automatically...
</description></item><item><title>Download ExamDiff Pro Master Edition 16.0.1.23</title><pubDate> Sat, 14 Feb 2026 16:37:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-examdiff-pro-master-312.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-examdiff-pro-master-312.html
</guid><description>
ExamDiff Pro Master is a tool to compare files and folders intuitive and easy to use, intuitive and easy to use for Windows. ExamDiff Pro Master has unique features distinguishes ExamDiff Pro with the program compare other. ExamDiff Pro Master to help perform reviews of code and share other reports with your colleagues and compare local website with FTP server by plug-ins more integrated.
ExamDiff Pro Master can create a snapshot folder for comparison and storage in the future, compare...
</description></item><item><title>Download AllMapSoft Offline Map Maker 8.367</title><pubDate> Sat, 14 Feb 2026 16:36:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-offline-map-maker-656.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-offline-map-maker-656.html
</guid><description>
AllMapSoft Offline Map Maker is software create, organize, offline map from Google Maps, Yahoo maps, Bing maps and Openstreetmap. You can view offline maps downloaded with map viewer offline. And you can zoom out or zoom in the offline map or export map under the file format .BMP with file world xxx.bpw, and can output files xxx.map for OziExplorer. If you want to make a offline map of your city by yourself, it is very useful for you.
Features AllMapSoft Offline Map Maker
	You can...
</description></item><item><title>Download MeinPlatz 8.56</title><pubDate> Sat, 14 Feb 2026 16:36:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-meinplatz-1860.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-meinplatz-1860.html
</guid><description>
MeinPlatz is a free software provides an easy and fast way to scan the hard disk to find the disk space lost. After the search is complete, results can be exported to XLS, HTM, CSV and TXT. MeinPlatz "My-Place" also has a print function with preview feature integrated print and frame rate change, and is also a magnifying glass the small screen.
MeinPlatz - Scan disk
The new features of MeinPlatz
	General optimization and general improvements as well as update the file language in...
</description></item><item><title>Download DirPrintOK 7.52</title><pubDate> Sat, 14 Feb 2026 16:35:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dirprintok-2073.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dirprintok-2073.html
</guid><description>
DirPrintOK allows you to print and save the contents of the folder and / or entire folder structures. You can browse the directory with Explorer-like interface and arbitrary filter folder contents by file extensions or matching the wildcard. You can also right-click to exclude files or folders selected from the printed version.
&amp;nbsp;
Folder contents can be grouped by path, date, size or file extension and you can customize the data columns to be included in the printed book. Very easy...
</description></item></channel></rss>