<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 10:28:12 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 10:28:12 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download 3uTools 9.02.025</title><pubDate> Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:44:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-3utools-4336.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-3utools-4336.html
</guid><description>
3uTools is tool data management and file iOS the most effective. 3uTools help easily manage the apps, photos, music, ringtones, video files and other multimedia. Watch full the different status of iOS devices, including activating, unlocking, status, pin lock and iCloud, as well as detailed information about iOS &amp;amp; iDevice. 3uTools can automate the hardware available for iOS devices. iOS flashing in normal mode, DFU mode and recovery mode are supported. Unlocking with a click of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download ChrisPC Screen Recorder Pro 2.26.0210.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:27:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-screen-recorder-pro-3020.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-screen-recorder-pro-3020.html
</guid><description>
ChrisPC Screen Recorder Pro is an application screen shot features and high efficiency allows you to easily record, enhance and share video online. The program can record any application running on your system. You can use a microphone to add words of your own narration to the video of your presentation. You can use this program to present how to use an application or website, to introduce the cursor to your game, to create guide, and more.
ChrisPC Screen Recorder Pro - Rotating, and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare DVD Creator 6.6.1.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:26:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-dvd-creator-131.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-dvd-creator-131.html
</guid><description>
The software allows you to edit, create a DVD or simply combine videos with photos in your DVD. Anything you want to see, Wondershare DVD Creator to do all. Just pull fiction favorite into DVD Creator for Win (Windows 10 support), adjust the quality and click burn. Or use the integrated editor's powerful DVD Creator to combine photos, videos and your own music into home movies, slideshow, really anything that your imagination can handle.
Wondershare DVD Creator - Create DVD for your...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft PowerToys for Windows 10/11 0.97.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:25:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-powertoys-for-windows-6014.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-powertoys-for-windows-6014.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft PowerToys is a user-proficiency set to adjust and streamline their Windows experience for higher productivity. Inspired by Windows 95's PowerToys project, this reboot provides users with proficiency in ways to exploit the more efficient Windows 10 and customisable processes it provides for each work process.
Utility of Microsoft PowerToys
	FancyZones is a window manager that allows you to easily create complex windows layout and quickly locate windows in those layout.
	Image...
</description></item><item><title>Download Agisoft Metashape Professional 2.3.1 Build 22070</title><pubDate> Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:25:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-agisoft-metashape-professional-1731.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-agisoft-metashape-professional-1731.html
</guid><description>
Agisoft Metashape (formerly PhotoScan) is a software product independently perform image processing and digital data creation, 3D space used in GIS applications, material cultural heritage and the production visual effects as well as the indirect measurement of the different subjects scale. Technical digital photography is deployed wisely is applied with the method of computer vision led to the system processor, smart auto, on the one hand, can be managed by a new person in the field of...
</description></item><item><title>Download ArmorTools Professional / Home 26.2.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:24:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-armortools-7726.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-armortools-7726.html
</guid><description>
ArmorTools is a set of tools that extend the capabilities of the MS Windows operating system in the field of security and protection of user confidential information. ArmorTools allows you to create secure virtual disks encrypted with AES128/AES256 algorithms, encrypting files and folder contents using any file as a password.
ArmorTools erases the user's work traces on the computer, deletes the history of accessing websites, deletes confidential information without the possibility of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Garden Planner 3.8.83</title><pubDate> Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:24:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-garden-planner-186.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-garden-planner-186.html
</guid><description>
Garden Planner : If you want to create a garden plan, create a landscape by activity or simply be curious, then you can download Garden Planner .   Garden Planner is a program that helps the user to design a dream garden through the layout and arrangement of plants, plants, buildings and objects, creating living spaces. style is consistent with the user's criteria and standards.
Garden Planner application is very simple, just select bushes, other plants, trees, pond and drag them into...
</description></item><item><title>Download Coolmuster Android Assistant 6.0.112</title><pubDate> Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:23:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-android-assistant-226.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-android-assistant-226.html
</guid><description>
Coolmuster Android Assistant is a lightweight application that allows you to export the data important from your mobile device to your computer for safekeeping just in few clicks.
Coolmuster Android Assistant allows you to browse a number of types of data on your mobile device, you, namely the apps, contacts, SMS, music, photos, videos , and books. In case you can't preview the contents of the desired part, then you can fix this minor inconvenience by access to the child folder of...
</description></item><item><title>Download XtraTools Pro 26.2.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:23:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xtratools-pro-7168.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xtratools-pro-7168.html
</guid><description>
XtraTools Pro is a universal tool for MS Windows system optimization that takes care of all aspects of your computer like optimizing the registry and removing unnecessary program to establish network connection and increase RAM speed. It is a compact tool with an intuitive interface that gives you complete control over the boot process, memory monitoring and a huge set of system settings that control your computer. The current version of the software provides the following tools: Folder...
</description></item><item><title>Download VX Search Ultimate 17.8.12 + Enterprise + Pro</title><pubDate> Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:22:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vx-search-ultimate-enterprise-1476.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vx-search-ultimate-enterprise-1476.html
</guid><description>
VX Search Ultimate is an automated file search solution, based on a rule that allows a person to search for file types, categories, file names, sizes, locations, extensions, formal expressions, text patterns and binary, create, modify, and date access, the EXIF card, etc. Users are offered the ability to classify and filter results, copy, move or delete files, save reports and export results to SQL databases.
VX Search allows a person to perform file search operations, review the search...
</description></item><item><title>Download AnyDesk 9.6.10</title><pubDate> Tue, 10 Feb 2026 21:02:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anydesk-1321.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anydesk-1321.html
</guid><description>
AnyDesk is software computer control remote, easy connection with remote computer management and manipulation on the computer. After installing the AnyDesk up 2 the computer then you can easily use the software to provide technical support for a friend or family member or you have access to your computer while you away from home or office.
AnyDesk - control your computer remotely
The process of using very simple software, want to allow access to his computer, only need to provide for...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare PDFelement Pro 12.1.11.4032</title><pubDate> Tue, 10 Feb 2026 21:02:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-pdfelement-pro-105.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-pdfelement-pro-105.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare PDFelement Pro support users to convert PDF to office documents for easier use, modify in every situation. Is one of the software conversion material is rated best today, integrated with many features. We recommend that you should use experience software many useful features this.
Wondershare PDFelement Pro - conversion Fie PDF more features, multi-language
Wondershare PDFelement Pro what?
Convert PDF into Word, Excel, PowerPoint...
• Convert PDF and protected PDF into...
</description></item><item><title>Download Abelssoft YouTube Song Downloader Plus 2026 v26.06</title><pubDate> Tue, 10 Feb 2026 21:02:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-abelssoft-youtube-song-downloader-plus-111.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-abelssoft-youtube-song-downloader-plus-111.html
</guid><description>
Abelssoft YouTube Song Downloader Plus 2018.18.17 Program YouTube Song Downloader Plus will help you search the music and video files from YouTube, after you can download them at. To search for music you just need to enter song name in the required field and you will get results, then you can download all videos and audio files. The program can search the entire album, this function will help to find individual songs from separate albums, because of this we specify the name of the artist...
</description></item><item><title>Download HiBit Uninstaller 4.0.10 + Portable</title><pubDate> Tue, 10 Feb 2026 21:01:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hibit-uninstaller-3897.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hibit-uninstaller-3897.html
</guid><description>
HiBit Uninstaller offer alternative solution for applet "Programs and features" standard of Windows allows you to uninstall software.
Software HiBit Uninstaller offer you a list of all the programs currently installed and allows you to uninstall any item that does not leave any rest whatsoever. HiBit Uninstaller will first launch the application uninstall comes standard with software and after removal is complete, it will provide you scan every file, directory and registry entries left by...
</description></item><item><title>Download SeekFast 6.3 Build 2</title><pubDate> Tue, 10 Feb 2026 21:00:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-seekfast-7524.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-seekfast-7524.html
</guid><description>
SeekFast has the ability to quickly search for specific text in all documents on your computer. SeekFast then sorts the results in a way that makes it easy to find the text you're looking for, see its context, and open the file that contains it. All you have to do is select a folder to search for and enter search words or phrases - you'll get all the sentences they appear in within seconds. This is especially useful if you need to find something quickly.
SeekFast uses state-of-the-art...
</description></item><item><title>Download Syncios WhatsApp Transfer 2.5</title><pubDate> Tue, 10 Feb 2026 21:00:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncios-whatsapp-transfer-5944.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncios-whatsapp-transfer-5944.html
</guid><description>
Syncios WhatsApp Transfer helps to backup your WhatsApp history more easily than ever before. It allows you to backup and restore your WhatsApp iPhone/iPad/Android data in just one click. Syncios WhatsApp Transfer can meet all your needs for publishing WhatsApp conversations.
You can export and print the WhatsaS conversations; publish WhatsApp messages, photos, videos and audio files selectively or by a click.
The features of Syncios WhatsApp Transfer
	Why saves all WhatsApp content...
</description></item><item><title>Download PVS-Studio 7.41.103095.2136</title><pubDate> Tue, 10 Feb 2026 20:59:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pvs-studio-1480.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pvs-studio-1480.html
</guid><description>
PVS-Studio is software that performs static code analysis and generate a report to help programmers find and fix bugs. PVS-Studio implements a series of check code, it is also useful to search the prints wrong error and Copy-Paste. Examples of such errors: V501, V517, V522, V523, V3001.
The main value of static analysis is in regular use, hence the error is identified and corrected at the earliest stages. There's no point of wasting 50 hours to search for a fault can be found with static...
</description></item><item><title>Download Zoom Player Max 22.2 Beta 3</title><pubDate> Tue, 10 Feb 2026 20:59:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zoom-player-max-104.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zoom-player-max-104.html
</guid><description>
Zoom Player MAX help you to see the film on DVD, Blu-ray, Flash movies and HD format with high quality and the ability to display subtitles in English very well. The advantage of software is that takes up very little system resources to play the movie with quick speed, change the wallpaper options while viewing movies.
Zoom Player MAX is the movies, browse high-quality photos on the computer with the advantages such as compact size, quick start, built-in codec. The application supports...
</description></item><item><title>Download PanFone WhatsApp Transfer 2.5.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 10 Feb 2026 20:58:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-panfone-whatsapp-transfer-5580.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-panfone-whatsapp-transfer-5580.html
</guid><description>
PanFone WhatsApp Transfer is the best solution to backup, restore and transfer WhatsApp iOS / Android messages as well as export WhatsApp messages to HTML and CSV files. This PanFone WhatsApp Transfer easily and securely transferred iOS to Android WhatsApp can be a useful tool to help you backup and restore WhatsApp data. It will not overwrite or delete previous backups. You can restore WhatsApp backups to your phone any time you want.
Seamlessly transfer all WhatsApp chat history,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Disk Sorter Ultimate 17.8.12 + Server + Pro</title><pubDate> Tue, 10 Feb 2026 20:58:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-disk-sorter-ultimate-1464.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-disk-sorter-ultimate-1464.html
</guid><description>
Disk Sorter Ultimate is the utility classification file lightweight and simple helps people detect files on most types of drives, as well as manage them according to many different criteria to create more capacity on the disc. This app allows you to search through the 500,000 files, have storage capacity of 2TB. To start sorting, all what you have to do is select a directory, drive or server and click the button "Classification". You should know that you can search for the type specific...
</description></item><item><title>Download MobiPDF: PDF Editor &amp;amp; Scanner 11.12.270246</title><pubDate> Tue, 10 Feb 2026 20:57:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pdf-extra-scan-edit-sign-8390.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pdf-extra-scan-edit-sign-8390.html
</guid><description>
PDF Extra PDF Editor &amp;amp; Scanner is a mobile application that allows users to create, edit and sign PDF documents on their Android or iOS devices. It includes many tools and features that make it easy to work with PDF files, including scanning, editing, and signing. This application also allows users to combine multiple PDF files into a single document and export PDF files in various file formats, such as JPEG, PNG, and Microsoft Word.
Features of PDF Extra PDF Editor &amp;amp;...
</description></item><item><title>Download All in One Unit Converter Pro 4.5.9</title><pubDate> Tue, 10 Feb 2026 20:56:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-all-in-one-unit-converter-tool-9570.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-all-in-one-unit-converter-tool-9570.html
</guid><description>
Most of us need to convert different units and do some scientific calculations like to convert Length units we may need to convert inches to mm, convert inches to cm, convert inches to feet, convert cm to inches and convert Weight units like convert kg to lbs, convert lbs to kg or convert Farenheit to Celcius etc.
So, for scientific calculations and to help you easily convert units, the All-in-One Multi-Unit Conversion Calculator is an engineering Unit conversion calculator that...
</description></item><item><title>Download Compass and GPS tools 30.0.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 10 Feb 2026 20:56:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-compass-and-gps-tools-8300.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-compass-and-gps-tools-8300.html
</guid><description>
Compass and GPS tool is a compass and GPS tool. There are many apps available on the Google Play Store or other app stores that provide compass and GPS functionality for Android devices.
Compass and GPS tool features
	GPS Essentials: This app provides many GPS-related tools such as compass, speedometer, and waypoint navigation.
	GPS Navigation &amp;amp; Maps: This app offers turn-by-turn voice navigation, offline maps, and real-time traffic updates.
	Compass: This app provides a simple...
</description></item><item><title>Download Twilight: Blue light filter 14.24 build 605</title><pubDate> Tue, 10 Feb 2026 20:56:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-twilight-blue-light-filter-12193.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-twilight-blue-light-filter-12193.html
</guid><description>
Are you having trouble falling asleep? Is your child hyperactive when playing with the tablet before going to bed? The Twilight app helps your device's screen adapt to the time of day. It filters the blue light emitted from your phone or tablet after sunset and protects your eyes with a soft and pleasant red filter. Filter intensity is smoothly adjusted to the solar cycle based on your local sunset and sunrise times.
Get more from Twilight
	- Reading in bed: Twilight is more...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Photoshop Express Photo Editor 17.9.22 build 1996</title><pubDate> Tue, 10 Feb 2026 20:56:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-photoshop-express-photo-editor-02en-8249.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-photoshop-express-photo-editor-02en-8249.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Photoshop Express is a mobile photo editing app that allows users to edit photos quickly and easily on their Android devices. Join millions of creators who trust and use Adobe Photoshop Express, one of the best photo editors and collage makers on Android for fast, easy, and powerful editing on mobile devices.
Premium version / No Adobe ID account required
Features of Adobe Photoshop Express APK
	Basic photo editing: Users can crop, rotate, adjust brightness, contrast and...
</description></item></channel></rss>