<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 03:32:02 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 03:32:02 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download 3DP Chip 25.10</title><pubDate> Sun, 19 Oct 2025 17:34:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-3dp-chip-2282.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-3dp-chip-2282.html
</guid><description>
3DP Chip is software commonly used in the update of the version latest driver for your computer. The advantage of this software is completely free, compact and easy to use. 3DP Chip will help the hardware always works in the best state, with the 3DP Chip, you can know the driver has been outdated, then let the software automatically searches for the latest version and installed for your system.
3DP Chip - Download and update driver
With the 3DP Chip you can learn everything about the...
</description></item><item><title>Download PMAS - PowerShell Multi Activation System 6.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 19 Oct 2025 17:34:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-powershell-tsf-activation-13584.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-powershell-tsf-activation-13584.html
</guid><description>
This advanced PowerShell script is a flexible and modular solution designed for licensing Windows and Office products. It runs a custom .NET library called LibTSforge.dll directly from memory to license Office. It can work in GUI mode or silent mode.
Features
	License management for both Windows and Office products
	Generate product keys with the help of LibTSforge.dll
	User-friendly graphical options with Out-GridView
	Compatible with KMS, MAK, RETAIL, OEM, AVMA license types
	In...
</description></item><item><title>Download R-Wipe &amp;amp; Clean 20.0 Build 2531</title><pubDate> Sun, 19 Oct 2025 17:27:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-wipe-clean-891.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-wipe-clean-891.html
</guid><description>
R-Wipe &amp;amp; Clean is software to delete junk files, unnecessary files from your computer to release the storage space and speed up your computer. In addition, R-Wipe &amp;amp; Clean also unleash the capacity of your drive and delete information invasion of privacy on different operations online and offline including your internet history and cookies, the list of downloaded files and documents were open, buffer different data, temporary files and many other items, created by the operating...
</description></item><item><title>Download PrivaZer Pro Donors 4.0.113</title><pubDate> Sun, 19 Oct 2025 17:27:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-privazer-donors-198.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-privazer-donors-198.html
</guid><description>
PrivaZer Donors  cleans and removes filth traces from the system. Intensive cleaning of unwanted traces of what you've done, viewed, downloaded, deleted, etc. Take ownership of your security and freedom - Free up disk space. Keep your PC snug and secure !!!
With one click, PrivaZer can safely clean: Internet browsers, Index.dat, Cookies, Tor Cookies, Flash Cookies, Silverlight Cookies, DOM Storing, IndexedDB, AppCache Registry, RAM, Pagefile.sys and Hiberfil.sys files.  PrivaZer  can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Fotosizer Professional 3.20.0.590</title><pubDate> Sun, 19 Oct 2025 17:26:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fotosizer-professional-2279.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fotosizer-professional-2279.html
</guid><description>
Fotosizer is a photo editing tool / photo series. It lets you resize hundreds of photos in few minutes quickly and easily. Increasingly, sharing photos on the internet is becoming increasingly popular. Image, is represented as JPEG files from digital cameras, taken at high resolution too big to send over the Internet, with some photos ending at 5 mega bytes. Upload photos to a website share photos is good, but 10, 20, or even more, this can last forever, especially on a dial-up...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare Recoverit 14.0.2.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 19 Oct 2025 17:26:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-recoverits-374.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-recoverits-374.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare Recoverit is a data recovery software that is easily lost at a rapid rate and is used by many people. You will do what happens if one day your data is suddenly lost due to the virus or deleted it, .. Wondershare Recoverit will provide you with an environment to protect important data.
Wondershare Recoverit has all the scanning processes that are divided into multiple types, from the typical recovery of the deleted files that are deleted to the recovery of missing files due...
</description></item><item><title>Download RustDesk 1.4.3</title><pubDate> Sun, 19 Oct 2025 17:25:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rustdesk-12244.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rustdesk-12244.html
</guid><description>
RustDesk is a full-featured open source remote alternative for self-hosting and security with minimal configuration. It allows users to access and control their computers remotely from anywhere in the world, providing a convenient solution for remote work, technical support, or accessing files and applications on the go. transfer.
RustDesk is continuously updated and improved, providing a reliable and effective remote desktop solution. Whether you work remotely, need remote technical...
</description></item><item><title>Download Plagius Professional 2.9.10</title><pubDate> Sun, 19 Oct 2025 17:25:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-plagius-professional-5717.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-plagius-professional-5717.html
</guid><description>
Plagius Professional is a tool capable of analyzing documents and notifying the user in case of plagiarism detection. The program automatically generates reports after checking documents or web pages and supports rendering reports into HTML files for later analysis. Plagius Professional supports several file formats, such as PDF, TXT, RTF, HTML, HTM, ODT, SXW, DOCX or DOC, but for the last two formats you need to have Microsoft Word installed on your PC (otherwise, they can't be...
</description></item><item><title>Download Internet Download Manager Portable 6.42 Build 51</title><pubDate> Sun, 19 Oct 2025 17:24:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-internet-download-manager-portable-11965.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-internet-download-manager-portable-11965.html
</guid><description>
Internet Download Manager (IDM) is a popular software tool that helps users download files from the internet at faster speeds. It is designed to increase download speeds up to five times, resume and schedule downloads, and support multiple download queues. IDM also has many features that make it easy to use and customize to fit your needs.
IDM has a simple and friendly interface that makes it easy to use. The software integrates seamlessly with popular web browsers such as Google Chrome,...
</description></item><item><title>Download AllMapSoft Universal Maps Downloader 10.229</title><pubDate> Sun, 19 Oct 2025 17:24:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-universal-maps-downloader-736.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-universal-maps-downloader-736.html
</guid><description>
AllMapSoft Universal Maps Downloader is software download map images on the computer for offline viewing support many types such as Google Maps, Yahoo maps, Bing maps, OpenStreet Maps, Yandex Maps, Ovi Maps, MapQuest Maps. All the downloaded photos will be saved on disk. You can view downloaded maps by Maps Viewer Or you can combine them into one big bmp, or jpg file tif by Maps Combiner, and also you can export all the tiles into a database format MBTiles.
AllMapSoft Universal Maps...
</description></item><item><title>Download Core Temp 1.19.5.69</title><pubDate> Sun, 19 Oct 2025 17:23:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-core-temp-2229.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-core-temp-2229.html
</guid><description>
Core Temp is a simple utility capable of displaying the temperature of your processor online after the start, when the load on it changes, the temperature also will change. You can see the temperature for each core processor, if you have core multi-core. Core Temp will work perfectly on every motherboard. This program is mobile.
Core Temp - Displays the temperature of CPU computer
This feature will help you take the measures timely processing when the temperature up too high,...
</description></item><item><title>Download RiDoc 5.0.14.27</title><pubDate> Sun, 19 Oct 2025 17:21:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ridoc-3999.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ridoc-3999.html
</guid><description>
RiDoc is a program to grab images from a scanner and reduce the size of the image file. This program reduces the file size of documents or electronic images without reducing image quality. With the help of the assembly function, the frame images in accordance with page format A4 size and an image file is reduced without reducing image quality. The convergence of documents into graphical format to help protect these documents from unauthorized copying. To increase the level of protective...
</description></item><item><title>Download 4K Video Downloader Plus Portable 25.3.3.0232</title><pubDate> Sun, 19 Oct 2025 17:21:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-video-downloader-plus-portable-12527.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-video-downloader-plus-portable-12527.html
</guid><description>
4K Video Downloader Plus Portable is a cross-platform application that allows you to save high-quality videos from YouTube and other websites in seconds. This app works faster than any free online video downloader — just one click and you can enjoy content anytime, anywhere.
Save private clips and playlists that you have access to. Download private videos not only from YouTube but also from Facebook, Vimeo, Bilibili and many other sites. Access and download login-protected media...
</description></item><item><title>Download Executor 2.1.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 19 Oct 2025 17:16:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-executor-271.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-executor-271.html
</guid><description>
Executor for windows is a software alternative premium customization features for the Windows "Run" and "Search Programs". When you press WIN + Z and provides the search results instant, as-you-type for any keywords you enter. By default, Executor will index all the Desktop and Start Menu and you can easily expand the search range by adding the folder location additional.
Executor for windows
The program comes with a list of commands built in which you can use to quickly access many...
</description></item><item><title>Download FanControl v245</title><pubDate> Sun, 19 Oct 2025 17:16:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fancontrol-5749.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fancontrol-5749.html
</guid><description>
FanControl is a highly customizable fan control software for Windows. Stay in control of every aspect of your PC's GPU and CPU fan with the help of this highly customizable fan control app.
Features of FanControl
	Save, edit and load multiple configurations
	Multiple temperature sources (CPU, GPU, motherboard, hard drive, ".sensor" files)
	Custom fan curve
	Fine tune fan control response with steps,% start,% stop, response time and delay
	Mix different curves and sensors...
</description></item><item><title>Download RadioLogger 4.1.1.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 19 Oct 2025 17:15:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-radiologger-11441.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-radiologger-11441.html
</guid><description>
RadioLogger is a program used to record (store) radio stations on a computer hard drive. Archiving can be useful, for example, in disputes with advertisers over the fact that an ad is being broadcast, or useful for various vetting activities. Recording can be done 24 hours a day or during certain periods of time. The program uses leading audio compression technologies so the files created are very small in size.
RadioLogger Features
	Scheduler: automatically start/stop recording...
</description></item><item><title>Download F-Secure Uninstallation Tool 19.2.85</title><pubDate> Sun, 19 Oct 2025 17:15:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-f-secure-uninstallation-tool-2250.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-f-secure-uninstallation-tool-2250.html
</guid><description>
F-Secure Uninstallation Tool is a simple program that allows you to completely delete the product from F-Secure from your computer. You can delete products from the system without leaving traces such as service platform, F-Secure 5.x, 6.x, 7.x, 8.x, security service F-Secure for consumers 6.x, 7.x, 8.x , 9.x, security service F-Secure for business 3.x, 4.x, F-Secure Anti-Virus / Internet Security 2005, 2006, 2007, 2008, 2009, 2010, 2011, 2012, 2013,..
F-Secure Uninstallation Tool to...
</description></item><item><title>Download FlashBoot 3.4</title><pubDate> Sun, 19 Oct 2025 17:14:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-flashboot-2625.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-flashboot-2625.html
</guid><description>
FlashBoot supports USB flash drive and USB hard drive. FlashBoot partitions, formats USB storage device and then automatically install the files to the operating system for it. Operating systems supported: Windows 8/7 / Vista / XP, disc-based SysLinux disk, GRUB4DOS, Linux kernel, etc., You can create flash USB can boot with the file system minimum and then adjust for your needs or switch CD-ROM can launch full-featured or floppy disk to USB Flash can boot and keep all functionality.
The...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaMonkey Gold 2024.2.0.3171 Beta</title><pubDate> Sun, 19 Oct 2025 17:14:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediamonkey-gold-231.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediamonkey-gold-231.html
</guid><description>
MediaMonkey Gold is music manager and music player multimedia for the music collection and iPod users. MediaMonkey lists the audio file of you as CD, OGG, WMA, MPC, FLAC, APE, WAV and MP3 and includes the edit smart card and an automatic file and folder to arrange your music library.
MediaMonkey Gold also has CD ripper, CD / DVD Burner, and audio converter for saving music, and manual or editor list automatically to create mixed music.
Features MediaMonkey Gold
	Automatically find...
</description></item><item><title>Download XRECODE3 1.173 Beta</title><pubDate> Sun, 19 Oct 2025 17:13:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xrecode-iii-2915.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xrecode-iii-2915.html
</guid><description>
"Xrecode II" is the switch and grab the audio allows you to convert from mp2, mp3, ac3, aiff, wma, amr, ogg, ape, flac, cue, mpc, wv, tak, mid, cue, m4b, tta, wav, dts , wav (rf64), m4a, mp4, ra, shn, rm, avi, aac, mpg, vob, mka, mkv, flv, Mov, swf, ofr, divx, wmv, spx, mp3, m4v, 3gp, m2v, 3g2, m4v, m2ts, ts, adts, tak, xm, mod, it, s3m, alac, umx, mtm, mlp to m4a, ape, flac, mp4 (using NeroAAC), raw, ogg, wav, wav (rf64) , wma, mpc, WavPack, mp2, ofr, Speex, ac3, tak, aiff, snd, Shorten...
</description></item><item><title>Download Xilisoft YouTube Video Converter 5.7.14 Build 20251018</title><pubDate> Sun, 19 Oct 2025 17:13:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xilisoft-youtube-video-converter-3367.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xilisoft-youtube-video-converter-3367.html
</guid><description>
Xilisoft YouTube Video Converter is a smart software helps for users to easily download Youtube videos, convert into Video files of different to be able to easily playback on mobile devices. Through Xilisoft YouTube Video Converter, you can batch download the application quickly browse and sort the video allows you to search information quickly and conveniently.
Xilisoft YouTube Video Converter - convert and download Youtube videos
Xilisoft YouTube Video Converter allows to convert...
</description></item><item><title>Download Hallo Northern SKY 4.3.2e</title><pubDate> Sun, 19 Oct 2025 17:12:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hallo-northern-sky-8489.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hallo-northern-sky-8489.html
</guid><description>
Hallo Northern SKY is a free semi-professional planetarium program HNSKY for Windows. This program can control your telescope through the ASCOM or INDI interface, has a comprehensively updated deep sky database of 30,000 objects and detailed descriptions. Star database with millions of stars and hundreds of Deep Sky Survey images matching each other precisely.
Additionally, the program can access an online version of the Deep Sky Survey which allows an online update of the asteroid and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Psiphon 186.20251017</title><pubDate> Sun, 19 Oct 2025 17:12:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-psiphon-7347.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-psiphon-7347.html
</guid><description>
Psiphon is a firewall bypass tool by Psiphon Inc. Uses VPN, SSH and HTTP Proxy technology to give you uncensored access to Internet content. Your Psiphon app automatically learns about new hotspots to maximize your chances of bypassing censorship.
The way the software works is that Psiphon constantly changes the proxy, so the user's IP address is also constantly changing, the server will not detect the user's real address, so you can feel free. roof. access to websites and software...
</description></item><item><title>Download 4K YouTube to MP3 Portable 25.3.3.0232</title><pubDate> Sun, 19 Oct 2025 17:12:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-youtube-to-mp3-portable-12526.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-youtube-to-mp3-portable-12526.html
</guid><description>
4K YouTube to MP3 Portable is a portable, installation-free version specifically created to extract audio from YouTube, Vimeo or Facebook and save it as MP3, M4A, OGG. No need to deal with annoying and complicated settings, just a clean, friendly and functional interface. Downloading is simple and straightforward: just copy the link from your browser and click 'Paste Url'. Done!
No toolbars, no adware, no malware. And best of all it's a FREE YouTube to MP3 converter! Enjoy your audio...
</description></item><item><title>Download PrivaZer 4.0.113</title><pubDate> Sun, 19 Oct 2025 17:11:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-privazer-66.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-privazer-66.html
</guid><description>
PrivaZer : the program performs the scan is very thorough not only includes the trace downloads like registration, Internet history, cookies, etc but also find the traces of potential in the field of free disk space of you. PrivaZer can permanently delete all traces by using the method of secure erase and also re-establish the sector disk free to 0 to remove all traces from the delete operation earlier. The process of scanning and cleaning the original can spend less time (20-30 minutes),...
</description></item></channel></rss>