<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 05:55:19 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 05:55:19 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Adobe Premiere Pro 2026 v26.0.1 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Sat, 14 Feb 2026 03:04:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-premiere-pro-0022-1361.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-premiere-pro-0022-1361.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Premiere Pro is the leading video editing software for film, TV, and the web. Creative tools, integration with other Adobe apps and services, and the power of Adobe Sensei help you turn footage into finished movies and videos in a seamless workflow. It offers high-quality video editing at 4K x 4K resolution and beyond, with 32-bit color, in both RGB and YUV color spaces. Edit audio samples, support for VST audio plug-ins (plug-ins), and 5.1 surround sound tracks. The Premiere Pro...
</description></item><item><title>Download CyberLink PowerDirector Ultimate 2026 v24.2.1410.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 14 Feb 2026 03:03:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-powerdirector-ultimate-425.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-powerdirector-ultimate-425.html
</guid><description>
CyberLink PowerDirector Ultimate is software editor, edit video and make movies on the computer from a variety of templates are made available, complete with effects, transitions, animations, and music. CyberLink PowerDirector 17 is a combination of video editing software with advanced video editing features powerful. Cblowing need to add your clips into the time line and click on 'Production'!
The tool design video in CyberLink PowerDirector have the ability to customize helps you...
</description></item><item><title>Download WonderFox DVD Video Converter 31.4</title><pubDate> Sat, 14 Feb 2026 03:02:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wonderfox-dvd-video-converter-189.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wonderfox-dvd-video-converter-189.html
</guid><description>
WonderFox DVD Video Converter is a software to convert Video DVD to the Video format the other with fast speed. Convenient program to convert the popular video formats and movie DVD, download WonderFox DVD Video Converter below. You can create videos that will be optimized for viewing on mobile devices. There is a simple video editor, it will allow you to add effects, crop photos, and etc.
WonderFox DVD Video Converter
WonderFox DVD Video Converter support rip DVD and videos to various...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Substance 3D Painter 11.1.3.5196 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Sat, 14 Feb 2026 03:01:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-substance-painter-1279.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-substance-painter-1279.html
</guid><description>
Substance Painter is a drawing application 3D completely new with the possibility of unprecedented and workflow is optimized, help in creating graphics easier than ever. To create sprites or 3D characters, no need to have knowledge about a painters professional animation, now it has become easy and accessible for the average user . The program is recognized in the world is creative tool and the most convenient to draw 3D create character models.
Substance Painter - App 3D drawing
The...
</description></item><item><title>Download Proteus Professional 9.1 SP2</title><pubDate> Sat, 14 Feb 2026 03:00:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-proteus-professional-2164.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-proteus-professional-2164.html
</guid><description>
Proteus is a software package for design computer-aided of electronic circuits. This package is a system of circuit simulation, based on models of electronic components to be applied in PSpice. A special feature of the package Proteus Professional is the ability to simulate the operation of the programmable devices: microcontrollers, microprocessors, DSP, v. v. in Addition, the package Proteus system includes a PCB design. Proteus Professional can simulate the microcontroller following:...
</description></item><item><title>Download GPU-Z 2.69</title><pubDate> Sat, 14 Feb 2026 02:59:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gpu-z-1144.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gpu-z-1144.html
</guid><description>
GPU-Z is a compact utility, simple help display parameters GPU and video Card the computer. GPU-Z to display information adapter details, Bios version, memory details, overclock, default clock, 3D clock, and much more. Besides, the program also includes check download GPU to verify configuration lane PCI-Express, as well as monitoring sensors in real time.
GPU-Z - information Display, GPU and display Card
Features of GPU-Z
	Small utility that displays the parameters of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download WonderFox HD Video Converter Factory Pro 28.6</title><pubDate> Sat, 14 Feb 2026 02:59:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hd-video-converter-factory-pro-1458.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hd-video-converter-factory-pro-1458.html
</guid><description>
WonderFox HD Video Converter Factory Pro is a software powerful video conversion . This program can convert the video files the quality standard of the file SD card, the files HD as HD MP4, HD MKV, HD AVI, HD MTS, HD TRP. This can also in the opposite direction. This software includes more than 100 video formats, while maintaining quality output, faster than 50 times compared to some software. This software also supports VBR or VBR, using this option will keep the original quality of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Valentina Studio Pro 17.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 14 Feb 2026 02:58:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-valentina-studio-pro-2122.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-valentina-studio-pro-2122.html
</guid><description>
Valentina Studio Pro is the best way to transform your data into meaningful information; create, manage, query and explore MySQL, Postgre MariaDB, MS SQL Server and SQLite database.
Valentina Studio Pro
Features of Valentina Studio Pro
SCHEMA EDITING &amp;amp; MAPPING
	Manage multiple databases in tabs and views that can be attached is
	Create / Drop / alter / Browse Tables, fields, index, trigger, constraints, links, views, stored procedures, properties, Sequences, Types, ...
	Edit the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Filezo 6.0.15</title><pubDate> Sat, 14 Feb 2026 02:58:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-filezo-14317.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-filezo-14317.html
</guid><description>
Filezo instantly finds any file, folder or application on your Windows PC at lightning speed. Just type a few keys and launch! That's it! Filezo's smart search feature ensures meaningful and clean results. It makes your computing life more enjoyable by eliminating boring clicks. Saves a lot of time and effort!
	Quickly access any document, folder or program on Windows in less than 5 seconds! Whether it's on your local hard drive, cloud drive or network drive.
	Tag files and folders to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Valentina Server 17.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 14 Feb 2026 02:57:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-valentina-server-10771.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-valentina-server-10771.html
</guid><description>
Valentina Server is software that provides reports from all major databases or with its own advanced object-relational database system. It will combine an enterprise reporting server and two database servers into a single solution. You get all the technical features of Valentina Server in terms of usage, more connections and live technical support.
Features of Valentina Server
	Enterprise report server turns data into highly formatted reports in the form of multimedia web pages, text,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Perfectly Clear WorkBench 5.0.2.3097</title><pubDate> Fri, 13 Feb 2026 22:40:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfectly-clear-workbench-6892.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfectly-clear-workbench-6892.html
</guid><description>
Perfectly Clear Workbench is an application that uses image editing libraries Perfectly Clear by Athentech and is provided to demonstrate the capabilities of the Perfectly Clear processing libraries, which recognize faces and allow quick export of processing settings for use.
One of the key features in Workbench is the ability to "export to API" when saving a Preset. This allows you to make image edits in Workbench and adjust the settings to suit your editing style and needs. You can...
</description></item><item><title>Download EverNote 11.3.5</title><pubDate> Fri, 13 Feb 2026 22:40:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-evernote-3261.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-evernote-3261.html
</guid><description>
EverNote is the all in one tool allows you to track notes, todo items, memos, outlines, excerpts, websites, ideas and other things and automatically synchronize them between multiple computers and mobile devices (iPhone, Android, etc.). You can choose to sort their notes into categories, password protect them, export them to XML and more. EverNote supports a number of pattern notes allow you to add to-do list, spreadsheet like Excel to calculate costs (automatic sum), notes, phone, contact...
</description></item><item><title>Download PerfectTUNES R2026-02-06</title><pubDate> Fri, 13 Feb 2026 22:39:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfecttunes-7115.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfecttunes-7115.html
</guid><description>
PerfectTUNES is a versatile music file manager that lets you find album art, check music folders for duplicates, and scan your songs for rip errors. export. PerfectTUNES comes as a software package, containing three applications that handle each function individually. PerfectTUNES is an intuitive, yet easy-to-use tool that allows you to organize your albums and music files, remove damaged songs, or remove duplicates. You can use its functions to clean up your music folder as well as find...
</description></item><item><title>Download SeekFast 6.4 Build 1</title><pubDate> Fri, 13 Feb 2026 22:39:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-seekfast-7524.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-seekfast-7524.html
</guid><description>
SeekFast has the ability to quickly search for specific text in all documents on your computer. SeekFast then sorts the results in a way that makes it easy to find the text you're looking for, see its context, and open the file that contains it. All you have to do is select a folder to search for and enter search words or phrases - you'll get all the sentences they appear in within seconds. This is especially useful if you need to find something quickly.
SeekFast uses state-of-the-art...
</description></item><item><title>Download dbForge Studio for Oracle Enterprise 2025.3.93</title><pubDate> Fri, 13 Feb 2026 22:38:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbforge-studio-for-oracle-enterprise-14049.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbforge-studio-for-oracle-enterprise-14049.html
</guid><description>
dbForge Studio for Oracle is a trusted integrated development environment (IDE) for Oracle SQL developers. This database solution speeds up PL/SQL coding, synchronizes data between different Oracle servers, and automates the process of managing schema changes during development. The solution is equipped with a graphical user interface (GUI) and versatile data editing tools, making it easy to manage both internal and external data.
Key features of the studio include a PL/SQL coding...
</description></item><item><title>Download RealCADD 5.71</title><pubDate> Fri, 13 Feb 2026 22:38:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-realcadd-14309.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-realcadd-14309.html
</guid><description>
RealCADD is a vector-based 2D computer-aided drawing (CAD) program used for drawing technical drawings, plans, and diagrams on desktop operating systems. The software is positioned as a lighter and more intuitive alternative to large CAD suites like AutoCAD, for users who primarily need 2D drawing.
Features of RealCADD
	Supports precise 2D drawing with straight lines, arcs, splines, dimensions, crosshatching, and text, suitable for architectural, mechanical, and general engineering...
</description></item><item><title>Download Photo &amp;amp; Picture Resizer 1.0.372</title><pubDate> Fri, 13 Feb 2026 21:09:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-photo-picture-resizer-14385.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-photo-picture-resizer-14385.html
</guid><description>
Image resizing apps for Android devices are utilities that allow you to reduce image size by selecting the appropriate resolution. This app is designed to help you resize images quickly and easily. It performs a simple task like resizing images quickly and easily. This app maintains the image's aspect ratio by providing a list of resolutions based on the camera's resolution. Image resizing apps help you resize images before posting them to Instagram, Facebook, Twitter, Pinterest, Reddit,...
</description></item><item><title>Download CCleaner – Phone Cleaner 26.02.0 build 800011361</title><pubDate> Fri, 13 Feb 2026 21:09:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ccleaner-pro-for-android-3428.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ccleaner-pro-for-android-3428.html
</guid><description>
CCleaner is a system cleaning and optimization tool for Android devices. CCleaner for Android allows users to delete unnecessary files, such as temporary files and caches, as well as identify and uninstall applications that are taking up too much space on the device. It also includes a task kill to close running applications and free up memory. This can help free up storage space and improve device performance. In addition, CCleaner for Android also has a security feature that allows you...
</description></item><item><title>Download ClevNote - Notepad, Checklist 2.24.14</title><pubDate> Fri, 13 Feb 2026 21:08:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-clevnote-notepad-checklist-8746.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-clevnote-notepad-checklist-8746.html
</guid><description>
ClevNote is a note-taking and checklist app for Android devices. It allows users to create and manage various types of notes, such as to-do lists, grocery lists, reminders, and more. ClevNote is a memo application that helps users write necessary daily memos
Features of ClevNote for Android
	Simple and easy-to-use interface
	Supports creating and managing multiple notes and checklists
	Ability to set reminders for specific notes or tasks
	Built-in templates for common note types, such...
</description></item><item><title>Download All PDF Editor &amp;amp; Reader | Xodo 10.12.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 13 Feb 2026 21:08:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-xodo-pdf-reader-editor-8451.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-xodo-pdf-reader-editor-8451.html
</guid><description>
Xodo PDF Reader &amp;amp; Editor is a mobile application for reading and editing PDF documents on Android and iOS devices. The app allows users to view, annotate, and edit PDF files using a variety of tools, including highlighting, underlining, and adding notes. With Xodo, you can read, annotate, sign, and share PDFs and fill out PDF forms, all while syncing with Google Drive, Dropbox, and OneDrive.
Xodo PDF Reader &amp;amp; Editor Features
	PDF Viewer: Application that allows users to view...
</description></item><item><title>Download Smart Launcher 6 ‧ Home Screen 6.6 build 003</title><pubDate> Fri, 13 Feb 2026 21:07:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-smart-launcher-8412.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-smart-launcher-8412.html
</guid><description>
Smart Launcher is a mobile app that provides users with a customized home screen and app launcher on their Android devices. It includes features like minimalist interface, automatic app sorting, and gesture controls. The app also includes many customizable settings, such as the ability to change the theme, icon size, and screen layout, as well as the ability to create custom categories for the app.
Smart Launcher Features
	Ambient theme: Smart launcher automatically changes theme...
</description></item><item><title>Download Rosetta Stone: Learn Languages 8.35.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 13 Feb 2026 21:07:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-rosetta-stone-learn-practice-11241.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-rosetta-stone-learn-practice-11241.html
</guid><description>
Interactive and contextual lessons combined with Extended Learning features are truly at your fingertips–anytime, anywhere, on any device; online or offline and completely ad-free. Learn to speak Spanish, French, German, Italian, English, Japanese, Korean, Chinese, Arabic, Portuguese, Russian, Dutch, Filipino, Greek , Hebrew, Hindi, Irish, Persian, Polish, Swedish, Turkish, Vietnamese and more!
Rosetta Stone helps you speak confidently: With many lessons and features focused on...
</description></item><item><title>Download Shazam: Find Music &amp;amp; Concerts 16.28.0-260205</title><pubDate> Fri, 13 Feb 2026 21:07:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-shazam-music-discovery-10763.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-shazam-music-discovery-10763.html
</guid><description>
Shazam will identify any song in seconds. Discover, artists, lyrics, videos &amp;amp; playlists, all for free. Over 1 billion installs and counting. Use Pop-up Shazam to identify music in any app - Instagram, YouTube, TikTok... No connection? No problem! Shazam while offline.
Features of Shazam: Music Discovery
	Find the name of any song in seconds.
	Listen and add to Apple Music playlists.
	Follow along with time-synced lyrics.
	Watch music videos from Apple Music or YouTube.
	Enable...
</description></item><item><title>Download Speedtest by Ookla 6.6.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 13 Feb 2026 21:06:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-speedtest-by-ookla-for-android-8605.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-speedtest-by-ookla-for-android-8605.html
</guid><description>
Speedtest by Ookla is a popular online service that allows users to measure the speed of their internet connection. The service works by sending small amounts of data to a user's device and measuring the time it takes for that data to return to the server. Based on this measurement, the service provides reports on the user's download and upload speeds as well as connection latency.
Features of Ookla Speedtest
	Explore your downloads, uploads, and pings
	The only Internet connection...
</description></item><item><title>Download Smart Tools 2 1.2.4</title><pubDate> Fri, 13 Feb 2026 21:06:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-smart-tools-8136.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-smart-tools-8136.html
</guid><description>
Smart Tools is a complete package of 6 individual applications. It has 6 sets below with a total of 15 tools.
	Offline support (Wi-Fi tablets only): Open this section multiple times using internet, you can open it without internet.
	Magnetic sensor required. So this app cannot support some Android devices (e.g. HTC One V).
	This is one of the essential applications of Google Play for Education.
6 application sets include:
	Set 1. Smart Ruler Pro: length, angle, slope, level,...
</description></item></channel></rss>