<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 21:40:03 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 21:40:03 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Mozilla Firefox 142.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 18 Aug 2025 23:52:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-firefox-quantum-501.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-firefox-quantum-501.html
</guid><description>
Firefox Quantum is a web browser independently provide the tabbed browsing combined with numerous handy features like pop-up blocker, Bookmarks, direct (integrated RSS), password manager, and more. Functionality can be extended with dozens of plugins available for free (extensions).
Firefox Quantum are interface completely new, beautiful, neat, minimalistic and delicate, eats less RAM to 30% compared with the old version and solve the condition consuming capacity
Firefox can import all...
</description></item><item><title>Download CapCut PC 6.9.0.2786</title><pubDate> Mon, 18 Aug 2025 23:52:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capcut-pc-9995.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capcut-pc-9995.html
</guid><description>
CapCut PC is a simple video editing tool that you can freely use anywhere. You can create videos on your browser, desktop and laptop, or on your phone. Versatile editing, magical AI tools, team collaboration, and built-in assets. Create videos in a whole new way.
You can edit videos based on editing the timeline, in the process you can add different elements and effects to the video to give the best effect to your work. It is a simple and intuitive set of editing tools and effects that...
</description></item><item><title>Download Glary Utilities Pro 6.30.0.34</title><pubDate> Mon, 18 Aug 2025 23:50:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-utilities-pro-76.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-utilities-pro-76.html
</guid><description>
Glary Utilities Pro is a collection of tools and system utilities to fix, speed up, maintain and protect your computer. Glary Utilities Pro allows you to clean junk files, system downloads, as well as the subscriptions are not valid and Internet traces (that support the plug-in more for the 45+ program outside). You can also manage and delete add-ons of the browser, analyze the use of disk and find the file duplicate.
Glary Utilities Pro - optimized system
Key features Glary Utilities...
</description></item><item><title>Download Trellix Stinger (McAfee Stinger) 13.0.0.436</title><pubDate> Mon, 18 Aug 2025 23:49:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mcafee-stinger-202.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mcafee-stinger-202.html
</guid><description>
McAfee Stinger is a free utility that functions to scan, check and remove the hazards and obstacles as virus or malware for Windows, whether they are hiding deep into the system.
In addition, due to the ability to search for the correct folder, or the data at risk contains viruses to scan instead you have to remove a long time waiting for antivirus software to scan all system on your computer. Thus speed of work of the McAfee Stinger faster and somewhat more accurate.
Themselves McAfee...
</description></item><item><title>Download Uninstall Tool 3.8.0 Build 5730</title><pubDate> Mon, 18 Aug 2025 23:49:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-uninstall-tool-333.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-uninstall-tool-333.html
</guid><description>
Uninstall Tool is a removal unique and powerful help for your computer work faster. Uninstall Tool is a quick, safe, and convenient to delete the application and system components is not necessary. Uninstall Tool would be great software to replace the Windows program Add / Remove.
Uninstall Tool - uninstaller powerful
The program has lots of features and options mising in the applet of Microsoft. Uninstaller tool installation works with MAXIMUM SPEED and COMPLETELY removes any program...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Acrobat Reader DC 2025.001.20630</title><pubDate> Mon, 18 Aug 2025 23:48:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-acrobat-reader-3707.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-acrobat-reader-3707.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Acrobat Reader DC is a system of application software and Web services developed by Adobe Systems to view, create, manipulate, print and manage PDF files. With Adobe Acrobat Reader DC, you can create, export, edit, and track PDF files from anywhere - and maintain connection with the recent set of files on all your devices.
Adobe Acrobat Reader current DC is connected with Adobe Document Cloud - help working on the computers and mobile devices becomes easier than ever before. This is...
</description></item><item><title>Download Aiseesoft Screen Recorder 3.1.30</title><pubDate> Mon, 18 Aug 2025 23:47:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aiseesoft-screen-recorder-631.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aiseesoft-screen-recorder-631.html
</guid><description>
Aiseesoft Screen Recorder is the software supports recording, take a screenshot with any videos and save them back with high quality. Apps screen recording video strong this can help you get online movies and radio, game capture, make video tutorials, record videos, capture screenshot, etc. on Windows 10/8/7.
Screen capture software helps you record almost any video screen you want. You can use it to record online video, game, podcast, webinars, lectures, presentations, Skype calls,...
</description></item><item><title>Download GSoft4U Music Collection 3.9.3.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 18 Aug 2025 23:47:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gsoft4u-music-collection-2437.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gsoft4u-music-collection-2437.html
</guid><description>
GSoft4U Music Collection is a free software to help you fully organized music collection of an archive can search quality. Archiving process is very simple; put on details related to format, genre, release date, record label, as well as rating the 'why' of it. The artists will be divided up alphabetically for easy access.
GSoft4U Music Collection - Manage music collection
The app will allow you to add additional information into its music, as this of course you must have an Internet...
</description></item><item><title>Download Draftable Desktop 25.8.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 18 Aug 2025 23:46:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-draftable-desktop-3749.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-draftable-desktop-3749.html
</guid><description>
Draftable Desktop is comparison tool documents the fastest. Compare over 300 pages in a few seconds. Draftable Desktop 2.0 is now available - faster and stronger than ever! See all the changes in your documents, locally and online. Take your work to the next level. Compare secret and private do not use the internet and your documents never leave your computer. Specifically, Draftable Desktop compatible with .xls, .xlsx, .xlsxm. With Office 2013, 2016 or 365, you can compare text in...
</description></item><item><title>Download BriskBard 4.6.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 18 Aug 2025 23:46:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-briskbard-2913.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-briskbard-2913.html
</guid><description>
BriskBard software is powerful and efficient designed for MS Windows, letting you easily surf the web, chat with friends, manage personal information and contacts, watch videos online account management, e-mail, read latest news, listen to music, perform file transfers, and more. Packed program this feature will help you save precious time and improve your productivity.
BriskBard is web browser two engine integrated 10 different Internet applications into one, including email, news group,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Red Gate SmartAssembly Professional 8.3.7.6539</title><pubDate> Mon, 18 Aug 2025 23:46:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-red-gate-smartassembly-1593.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-red-gate-smartassembly-1593.html
</guid><description>
Red Gate SmartAssembly is a tool that helps protect your application against reverse engineering or modifications prevent side Tuesday access to source code. This comprehensive solution protects the data card of you and more likely to report errors. This program makes files difficult can disassemble and injection code does not use, to help engineer can reverse and understand the core structure of the code. With your smartphone, you will have many features to tamper with the code as the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Print Conductor 11.0.2508.11190</title><pubDate> Mon, 18 Aug 2025 23:45:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-print-conductor-1559.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-print-conductor-1559.html
</guid><description>
Print Conductor is the software supports automatic printing of documents, text in different formats at the same time, all without opening each one. Print Conductor supports more than 75 kinds of different material and works with all types of printers. With Print Conductor, the printing of large volume of files as easy as 1-2-3. You no longer need to manually open each file, select printer, make settings to print, click "Print" and repeat. Instead, just drag and drop your documents into the...
</description></item><item><title>Download PhraseExpander Professional 5.9.8.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 18 Aug 2025 23:44:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-phraseexpander-professional-10882.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-phraseexpander-professional-10882.html
</guid><description>
PhraseExpander Professional is a versatile software designed to streamline and automate typing tasks, allowing professionals to work more efficiently. Store all common medical terms, formulas, and forms in a single place and pull them up instantly by entering an acronym. It supports creating and managing custom text paragraphs, templates and phrases, which can be activated with keyboard shortcuts or abbreviations, saving time and reducing repetitive typing. This tool is commonly used in...
</description></item><item><title>Download Minimal Firewall 2.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 18 Aug 2025 23:44:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minimal-firewall-13877.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minimal-firewall-13877.html
</guid><description>
Minimal Firewall works in conjunction with Windows Firewall to block all unknown connections by default, prompting you to create application-based rules to mitigate malware, telemetry, and data leaks. Completely eliminate applications that call home without your knowledge. Minimal Firewall provides a more secure and integrated approach by interacting directly with the native Windows Firewall, eliminating the need for risky system modifications.
Core Features
	Lockdown Mode: The core...
</description></item><item><title>Download Zortam Mp3 Media Studio Pro 33.15</title><pubDate> Mon, 18 Aug 2025 23:44:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zortam-mp3-media-studio-pro-135.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zortam-mp3-media-studio-pro-135.html
</guid><description>
Zortam Mp3 Media Studio Pro brings you rich processing tools music includes extract and convert music from CD to Mp3 format, edit, music cards, music download....You can also create discs CD high-quality music, with Zortam Mp3 Media Studio search music files duplicated to remove them from the system, rename music files, switch back and forth between formats.
Zortam Mp3 Media Studio Pro is rated as perfect software in the processing of the MP3 files on the computer. First of all, you can...
</description></item><item><title>Download LastPass Password Manager 5.0.7</title><pubDate> Mon, 18 Aug 2025 23:43:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lastpass-269.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lastpass-269.html
</guid><description>
LastPass is a free software to help manage passwords allows you to store all the login information of your site in a warehouse password cross-platform compatibility only. Instead of remember the user name and personal password, you only need to remember the main password to open the lock the password of his safe.
LastPass
LastPass can automatically fill in the login box for all the account website is your hosting. Whenever you log into a website has stored your vault, the program will...
</description></item><item><title>Download Glarysoft Malware Hunter Pro 1.204.0.835</title><pubDate> Mon, 18 Aug 2025 23:42:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glarysoft-malware-hunter-pro-235.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glarysoft-malware-hunter-pro-235.html
</guid><description>
Glarysoft Malware Hunter capabilities, comprehensive protection against threats, data protection and privacy, ensure the computer is no longer virus. It allows you against many types of viruses, trojans with the ability to super fast scanning to detect and remove the malware quickly. Glarysoft Malware Hunter has a simple design of the interface, but the pace of new work is the most important problem of this software.
Features Glarysoft Malware Hunter Pro
	Automatically search, detect,...
</description></item><item><title>Download MP3Studio YouTube Downloader 2.0.28.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 18 Aug 2025 23:42:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mp3studio-youtube-downloader-6778.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mp3studio-youtube-downloader-6778.html
</guid><description>
MP3Studio YouTube Downloader is an efficient and user-friendly software developed to provide you with an easy means of getting all your favorite videos from the web and store them on your PC, in one of the available formats. With MP3Studio YouTube Downloader, you can download up to 99 songs at once in the background as you start your business.
Use this media editor to preload various songs via YouTube and other services. It will provide you with good quality music that you can listen to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Glary Disk Cleaner 6.0.1.31</title><pubDate> Mon, 18 Aug 2025 23:42:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-disk-cleaner-1341.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-disk-cleaner-1341.html
</guid><description>
Glary Disk Cleaner is the software helps to erase the file system temporarily, cleanup your browser cache, or release the folder. Glary Disk Cleaner show scan results in detail, help you pick exactly each file to delete. The list file is much more wide open, with temporary files, user-generated, or the file system, cache, bug report, log files, data in recycle bin, the shortcut expires.
Glary Disk Cleaner - garbage system
Glary Disk Cleaner is designed to be simple as possible in use....
</description></item><item><title>Download Glary Tracks Eraser 6.0.1.24</title><pubDate> Mon, 18 Aug 2025 23:34:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-tracks-eraser-1342.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-tracks-eraser-1342.html
</guid><description>
Glary Tracks Eraser is security software privacy when browsing the web, allows you to delete all traces of network access and trace number, including browser cache, cookies, the website is already open, the URL has been entered, the document new mines, temporary files,... Glary Tracks Eraser that helps you free up space in hard disk drives, scan entire junk files in the drive with the speed of processing is extremely fast. Data deleted by Glary Tracks Eraser will not be able to restore,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Glary Malware Hunter PRO 1.204.0.835</title><pubDate> Mon, 18 Aug 2025 23:33:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-malware-hunter-pro-77.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-malware-hunter-pro-77.html
</guid><description>
Glary Malware Hunter PRO - detection of file malware on your computer and delete dangerous content, allowing you to run on-demand scan of the area, important system or specific files. As suggested by its name, Malware Hunter is designed to find and remove the files and components potential danger on your computer, keep it out of the virus and the type of threat other.
Glary Malware Hunter PRO - perfect protection of your equipment
Features Glary Malware Hunter PRO
- Scan ultrasound...
</description></item><item><title>Download hashcat 7.1.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 18 Aug 2025 23:32:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hashcat-6759.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hashcat-6759.html
</guid><description>
hashcat is the world's fastest and most advanced password recovery utility, supporting five unique attack modes for over 300 highly-optimized hashing algorithms. hashcat currently supports CPUs, GPUs, and other hardware accelerators on Linux, Windows, and macOS and has facilities to help enable distributed password cracking.
Features of hashcat
	Open-Source (MIT License)
	Multi-OS (Linux, Windows, and macOS)
	Multi-Platform (CPU, GPU, APU, etc., everything that comes with an OpenCL...
</description></item><item><title>Download Fast Video Cutter Joiner 6.8.8</title><pubDate> Mon, 18 Aug 2025 23:31:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fast-video-cutter-joiner-7542.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fast-video-cutter-joiner-7542.html
</guid><description>
Fast Video Cutter Joiner is a fast video cutter and joiner with an easy to use interface. It allows users to trim parts of a video quickly while maintaining the quality of the original video. It supports various formats like AVI, MPEG, MP4, WMV, 3GP, FLV...
This tool helps you to cut video files into small parts, to keep only the parts you need and remove unwanted parts like trailers and advertisements in a movie. The clips you cut can then be used for other video productions or for a...
</description></item><item><title>Download EstlCAM 12.145</title><pubDate> Mon, 18 Aug 2025 23:31:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-estlcam-13476.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-estlcam-13476.html
</guid><description>
EstlCAM is a user-friendly CNC and CAM (Computer-Aided Manufacturing) control software, designed to generate toolpaths and G-code for CNC machines, especially suitable for 2D, 2.5D and 3D milling operations. The software supports importing a variety of design file formats, including 2D drawings (.dxf, .svg, .png, .jpg) and 3D models (.stl), allowing users to position, scale, and rotate designs before generating toolpaths.
The software is especially popular among enthusiasts and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Betterbird 140.2.0esr-bb9</title><pubDate> Mon, 18 Aug 2025 23:31:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-betterbird-8318.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-betterbird-8318.html
</guid><description>
Betterbird is a tweaked version of Mozilla Thunderbird, Thunderbird on steroids, if you will. It closely follows Thunderbird's Extended Support Releases (ESRs), thus avoiding the mistakes of other forks that cause it to quickly lose track of upstream Thunderbird, thus opening users to vulnerabilities. security.
Betterbird makes emailing safer, faster and easier than ever with the implementation of industry best features like smart spam filter, built-in spell checker , extension support,...
</description></item></channel></rss>