<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 23:44:21 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 23:44:21 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Vovsoft Window Resizer 4.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 02:29:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-window-resizer-7339.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-window-resizer-7339.html
</guid><description>
Vovsoft Window Resizer is a utility that allows you to resize any window to an exact, predefined size. This is extremely useful when designing websites, as it allows you to see how the page will look when viewed at a smaller size. This utility is also handy when compiling screenshots for documents, using Window Resizer allows you to easily maintain the same window size across monitors.
Alternatively, you can save the current positions (width, height, left, top) as a CSV file and "Load...
</description></item><item><title>Download Irix HDR Pro 2.3.49</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 02:07:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-irix-hdr-pro-10653.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-irix-hdr-pro-10653.html
</guid><description>
Irix HDR Pro is an AI-powered photo editing application for Windows, it is available on Microsoft Store. This program has tons of professional HDR photo editing features including Sky Replacement, Face Sculpting &amp;amp; body, over 200 presets &amp;amp; AI powered tool' and is a Photo Editor in the category of photo &amp;amp; Graphics. It delivers true-to-life HDR photo editing, providing one-click edits for a full-scale professional editing toolkit.
Features of Irix HDR Pro
	Sky Replacement...
</description></item><item><title>Download StartAllBack 3.9.13.5296</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 02:07:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-startallback-6857.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-startallback-6857.html
</guid><description>
With the official release of Windows 11, chances are that most of you want to try it out. As the name suggests, StartAllBack is a small, lightweight tool that can help you enjoy the power of the new operating system while keeping the look and feel, especially because main work area, desktop of Windows 7, Windows 10 as taskbars and start menu styles.
StartAllBack is specially designed for Windows 11 and will not work on any older operating systems. If you want to get the start menu back...
</description></item><item><title>Download FxSound (FxSound Enhancer Premium) 1.1.34 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 02:06:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fxsound-enhancer-premium-2013.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fxsound-enhancer-premium-2013.html
</guid><description>
FxSound Enhancer Premium formerly DFX Audio Enhance, is accessories multimedia software most popular in the world with over 46 million downloads worldwide. FxSound enhances the sound of most of the music content and online video is live streaming on the Web, including the streaming service, YouTube, Pandora, Spotify and Apple Music. FxSound Enhancer Premium also implemented enhanced real-time audio on the player PC multimedia most popular include iTunes, Windows Media Player, Winamp and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Irix HDR Classic Pro 2.3.49</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 02:06:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-irix-hdr-classic-pro-10652.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-irix-hdr-classic-pro-10652.html
</guid><description>
Irix HDR Classic Pro is an AI-powered photo editor that delivers true-to-life HDR photo editing, providing one-click edits to the editing toolkit professional at full scale with a highly cognitive user interface (UI).
Main features:
	Sky replacement (SkyXpress): replaces the sky and imports weather. Import custom skies and merge, blend, and integrate with your images for a natural look with AI Edge Detect.
	Presets &amp;amp; Filters: 200+ social media optimized presets with just one tap...
</description></item><item><title>Download Advanced CSV Converter 7.79</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 02:05:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-csv-converter-4508.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-csv-converter-4508.html
</guid><description>
Advanced CSV Converter is a conversion tool CSV to DBF, Excel (XLS, XLSX), TXT, HTML, PRG, XML, SQL, RTF. To convert a file, the program provides an interface controlled by the wizard, guides you step by step conversion. Use the wizard, you select file input, select the format and destination folder. If necessary, you can set the filter switch according to the example and select columns you want to exclude from the process. When the conversion process is started, the program will extract...
</description></item><item><title>Download eDocPrinter PDF Pro 10.36 Build 10365</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 02:05:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-edocprinter-pdf-pro-3915.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-edocprinter-pdf-pro-3915.html
</guid><description>
eDocPrinter PDF Pro is an application to create PDF files from applications in Windows 2000, Windows XP and above. eDocPrinter PDF Pro works as a printer under windows environment, hence users can print from any application window using the device printing GDI. Extremely easy to work with this tool, because it installs on your system as a virtual printer and lets you convert documents to PDF in an easy way. eDocPrinter PDF Pro comes with advanced functions that can meet the requirements of...
</description></item><item><title>Download FileLocator Pro 2022 Build 3527</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 02:04:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-filelocator-pro-1056.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-filelocator-pro-1056.html
</guid><description>
FileLocator Pro is software manage files and search function the file quickly the software and data. FileLocator Pro helps you find things quickly. The unique feature of it allows the extraction of information in all file formats the most obscure.
FileLocator Pro - file Manager
The features of FileLocator Pro
	Search algorithm based on the C ++ multi-threading for ultra-fast
	Search for network drive by mapped drive or UNC paths
	Support regular expressions for file name and...
</description></item><item><title>Download RevisionFX Effections Plus for OFX 25.08</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 02:03:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-revisionfx-effections-plus-for-ofx-12466.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-revisionfx-effections-plus-for-ofx-12466.html
</guid><description>
RevisionFX Effections Plus is a comprehensive suite of video editing plugins designed for multiple OpenFX (OFX) servers. It enhances video editing with a series of tools focused on motion effects, noise reduction, and color matching.
Main features of Effects Plus
	DEFlicker: Removes flicker from high frame rate and time-lapse footage.
	DE:Noise: Reduces noise using advanced spatial filtering and optical flow techniques.
	FieldsKit: Provides smarter deinterlacing and better workflow...
</description></item><item><title>Download FxSound Pro 1.1.34 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 02:03:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fxsound-5966.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fxsound-5966.html
</guid><description>
FxSound Pro is a professional software that helps to enhance the quality of sound, volume, depth, and sound on your PC. FxSound brings you a great sound just with a downloadable download. After using FxSound, you will know if it is for you or not. Most people do n' t know what they ' re missing in their sound until they try their software/sound hardware better. It ' s hard to convey if you do n' t really experience yourself.
Reason to use FxSound Pro:
	The perfect sound on every...
</description></item><item><title>Download Chris-PC RAM Booster 7.25.0818</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 02:02:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chris-pc-ram-booster-1181.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chris-pc-ram-booster-1181.html
</guid><description>
ChrisPC RAM Booster is software speed up your system by managing and acceleration of the RAM in the operating system. RAM Booster will monitor the RAM usage (memory random access) and upon reaching the threshold memory certain low, it will trigger the process of freeing up memory for the new program open while moving at the same time the old programs from the RAM memory into virtual memory on disk.
Chris-PC RAM Booster - speed up processing RAM
Certainly this is a slower process...
</description></item><item><title>Download 7thShare DVD Burner Creator Pro 1.4.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 02:02:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-7thshare-dvd-burner-creator-pro-5018.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-7thshare-dvd-burner-creator-pro-5018.html
</guid><description>
7thShare DVD Burner Creator Pro is DVD burner software best for Windows users. It meets all the requirements of you to record, create, create DVD / CD and converting / ripping DVD to other video formats each other. 7thShare DVD Burner Creator Pro is DVD burning software, reliable to burn DVD disc / folder / file ISO from videos in formats of up to more than 500, such as AVI, MP4 , FLV, MKV, MPEG, TS, MTS, M2TS, MOV, WMV, VOB, MOD, AVCHD, H. 264, H. 265, TRP, MP3 and M4V, HD video, etc. in...
</description></item><item><title>Download CleverPrint Pro 9.2.64361</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 02:01:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cleverprint-pro-1372.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cleverprint-pro-1372.html
</guid><description>
CleverPrint Pro is software that supports printing can export print jobs of you as JPG, PNG or even PDF files. CleverPrint allows you to print multiple document pages on a single sheet of paper. This means that you not only use less paper but also print the document in smaller sizes which also use less toner.
CleverPrint Pro - Support printing multiple pages on one sheet of paper
CleverPrint includes a PDF printer that can be used to convert any documents into PDF documents. This...
</description></item><item><title>Download SAPIEN PowerShell Studio 2025 v5.9.259</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 02:00:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sapien-powershell-studio-7201.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sapien-powershell-studio-7201.html
</guid><description>
PowerShell Studio is the premier editing and tooling environment for PowerShell. Create graphical tools using PowerShell with an easy-to-use GUI designer. Eliminates the need to manually write hundreds of lines of code. Use PowerShell Studio's built-in templates and wired controls to create advanced GUIs quickly. Create a PowerShell script module in minutes with PowerShell Studio. Easily convert your existing functions into a deliverable module. PowerShell Studio has a powerful editor...
</description></item><item><title>Download SonarQube Data Center Edition 2025.4.2.112048</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 02:00:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sonarqube-data-center-edition-8059.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sonarqube-data-center-edition-8059.html
</guid><description>
SonarQube empowers all developers to write cleaner and safer code. Join the Open Community of over 200,000 developer groups. SonarQube provides reports on duplicate code, coding standards, unit testing, code coverage, code complexity, comments, bugs, and security recommendations.
Features of SonarQube
	Detect complex bugs to prevent undefined behavior from affecting end users.
	Fix your apps' vulnerabilities and learn about AppSec along the way with Secure Hotspot.
	Make sure your...
</description></item><item><title>Download Personal Backup 6.3.33.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 01:57:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-personal-backup-1117.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-personal-backup-1117.html
</guid><description>
Personal Backup is software to backup data on computer hard drive professional with the ability to copy data on the hard drive and save any folder. Personal Backup is the most optimal solutions to ensure safety for data on avoid computer viruses, malicious code, intrusion and data loss because you can restore lost data at any time if it has to be backed up and stored on the folder of the computer.
Personal Backup - backup computer data
Features of Personal Backup
	Backup cross data...
</description></item><item><title>Download Inno Setup Compiler 6.5.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 01:29:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-inno-setup-compiler-2655.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-inno-setup-compiler-2655.html
</guid><description>
Inno Setup Compiler is a system installed based on free software created by Delphi by Jordan Russell. The first version was released in 1997. QuickStart of Inno Setup include main Inno Setup and also includes an option to install the script editor Inno Script Studio. The script editor is not official and is not mandatory for general use, but help Inno Setup easier to use.
Inno Setup Compiler - software create file setup.exe
The features of Inno Setup Compiler
	Support for every...
</description></item><item><title>Download EverNote 10.151.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 01:29:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-evernote-3261.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-evernote-3261.html
</guid><description>
EverNote is the all in one tool allows you to track notes, todo items, memos, outlines, excerpts, websites, ideas and other things and automatically synchronize them between multiple computers and mobile devices (iPhone, Android, etc.). You can choose to sort their notes into categories, password protect them, export them to XML and more. EverNote supports a number of pattern notes allow you to add to-do list, spreadsheet like Excel to calculate costs (automatic sum), notes, phone, contact...
</description></item><item><title>Download Net Blocker - Firewall per app 1.8.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 01:24:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-net-blocker-firewall-per-app-11073.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-net-blocker-firewall-per-app-11073.html
</guid><description>
Net Blocker allows you to block specific applications from accessing the Internet without root. As you know, there are apps and games that can:
	Only access the Internet to display ads or steal your personal data
	Continue Internet access in background services even after you exit
Therefore, you should consider blocking applications from accessing the Internet to help
	Reduce your data usage
	Increase your privacy
	Save your battery
Net Blocker Features - Per-App Firewall
	Safe...
</description></item><item><title>Download Magnifier Plus with Flashlight 4.8.11</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 01:23:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-magnifier-plus-with-flashlight-8494.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-magnifier-plus-with-flashlight-8494.html
</guid><description>
Are you tired of trying to read labels with small fonts? Now you can use your Android device as the perfect digital magnifier! No need to use a magnifying glass to read small labels - this app lets you see text large and clearly. The magnifier has on-screen zoom and illumination controls for easy operation. You can also use the flash as a light to get a brighter image, and the negative mode inverts the colors so you can see this differently when they're hard to see.
Features of...
</description></item><item><title>Download TeraBox: 1TB Cloud &amp;amp; AI Space 4.3.9</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 01:23:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-terabox-cloud-storage-space-13078.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-terabox-cloud-storage-space-13078.html
</guid><description>
Sign up to get 1024GB of free cloud storage for life! Automatically back up your photos and videos. Support online photo preview and video playback. Using TeraBox, you can store about 300,000 photos, more than 2500 movies or 6.5 million documents. We provide a secure storage space for all your files, while protecting them from the risk of theft. You can securely back up, sync, access, and share your important content.
Get free cloud storage now and back up your data to avoid loss!...
</description></item><item><title>Download CapCut Pro - Video Editor 14.8.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 01:23:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-capcut-video-editor-11703.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-capcut-video-editor-11703.html
</guid><description>
CapCut is a versatile video editing application developed by Bytedance, the company behind TikTok. It provides users with a range of powerful editing tools and features to create professional-looking videos right from their mobile devices. One of the key features of CapCut is its intuitive interface, which makes it easy and convenient for users to navigate and access various editing options. The app supports importing media from your device's library, allowing you to work with photo,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Screenshot Pro - Auto trimming 7.1.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 01:18:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-screenshot-pro-auto-trimming-10495.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-screenshot-pro-auto-trimming-10495.html
</guid><description>
High-speed screenshot capture, optimized for continuous shooting. Status bar area and navigation bar area can be automatically cropped.
Features of Screenshot Pro for Android
	Cut status bar area: Automatically cut status bar area.
	Cut navigation bar area: Automatically crop navigation bar area.
	Moving photo capture: Turn ON/OFF moving photo capture.
	Overlay capture button: Convenient and portable overlay capture button.
	Notification icon: Function to display notification bar...
</description></item><item><title>Download Camera Editor- Sweet Selfie 5.7.1749</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 01:10:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-camera-editor-sweet-selfie-13570.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-camera-editor-sweet-selfie-13570.html
</guid><description>
The best FREE selfie photo editor and beauty camera with all the features, face editor, body editor, background blur, art filters, live stickers and makeup effects! Sweet Selfie is the top selfie photo editor and beauty camera with real-time beauty effects, help you take selfies easily, edit photos, images and videos even boomerang for Instagram, Facebook, Messenger, Whatsapp, Snapchat, Twitter, Wechat, etc.
Features:
	Selfie camera can help you take perfect selfies and easily share...
</description></item><item><title>Download Dumbbell Workout at Home &amp;amp; Gym 5.14</title><pubDate> Tue, 19 Aug 2025 01:10:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-dumbbell-home-workout-8634.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-dumbbell-home-workout-8634.html
</guid><description>
Dumbbell Workout at Home is a fitness app for Android devices that offers users a variety of workout routines that can be done at home using only weights. This app is designed for people who want to stay fit and healthy but don't have access to a gym or workout equipment.
Features of Weightlifting at Home for Android
	Customizable workout routines: The app offers users a variety of workout routines that can be customized based on their fitness level, goals, and the amount of time they...
</description></item></channel></rss>