<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 00:01:56 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 00:01:56 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download CyberLink AudioDirector Ultra 2026 v16.1.6122.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jan 2026 21:25:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-audiodirector-ultra-288.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-audiodirector-ultra-288.html
</guid><description>
Sound is half the movie experience and improving the audio in the project video will greatly enhance the final result. AudioDirector contains advanced tools help edit and edit the audio quickly and simply. With the audio feature and seamless integration with PowerDirector.
We provide CyberLink AudioDirector Ultra editor software, mix, and adjust the soundtrack, effects, audio for video, and all the passages spoken in the video. CyberLink AudioDirector Ultra is the upgrade version of...
</description></item><item><title>Download RocketCake Professional 7.0.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jan 2026 21:24:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rocketcake-professional-2632.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rocketcake-professional-2632.html
</guid><description>
RocketCake Professional is a WYSIWYG HTML editor that allows you to create a website based on the responsive template without coding. Simply choose your template and customize it or create a new design from scratch.In addition to text content you can add images, galleries, slideshows, YouTube videos, Flash, buttons, audio / video HTML5, table and many page elements enhance the other.
RocketCake Professional - design application Website
Allows you to create a website as quickly as...
</description></item><item><title>Download Freemake Video Converter Gold 5.0.0.32</title><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jan 2026 21:24:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-freemake-video-converter-gold-167.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-freemake-video-converter-gold-167.html
</guid><description>
Freemake Video Converter Gold is a software to help convert tail high quality videos with many different formats on many devices. Freemake Video Converter - convert video to AVI, MP4, WMV, MKV, 3GP, DVD, MP3, iPad, iPhone, PSP, Android phone. Video to MP3 just with one click! Rip and burn DVD. Convert YouTube to MP4, AVI, etc. with Freemake! Results guaranteed. Freemake Video Converter has fast conversion speed, guarantee the output quality,support create HTML5 videos have the embed code...
</description></item><item><title>Download RocketCake 7.0.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jan 2026 21:23:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rocketcake-1697.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rocketcake-1697.html
</guid><description>
RocketCake is WYSIWYG HTML editor allows you to create a website based on the responsive template without coding. Simply choose your template and customize it or create a new design from scratch.In addition to text content you can add images, galleries, slideshows, YouTube videos, Flash, buttons, audio / video HTML5, table and many page elements enhance the other.
RocketCake - WYSIWYG HTML editor
RocketCake does not require any knowledge of HTML or CSS, you only need to drag the page...
</description></item><item><title>Download 4K YouTube to MP3 26.0.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jan 2026 21:22:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-youtube-to-mp3-622.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-youtube-to-mp3-622.html
</guid><description>
4K YouTube to MP3 is a software to convert video youtube to mp3 quickly and easily by the manipulation drag-and-drop simple. With 4K YouTube to MP3 you just drag and drop the link to the favorite songs of you and get the MP3 files to your computer, as easy as that. Transfer songs directly to iPod, iPhone and iPad everywhere you go. No install annoying and complex to solve, just a clean interface, user friendly and functional.
When using 4K YouTube to MP3, users will get the playlists,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Intuitibits WiFi Explorer Pro 1.1.12.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jan 2026 21:21:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intuitibits-wifi-explorer-pro-14331.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intuitibits-wifi-explorer-pro-14331.html
</guid><description>
Use WiFi Explorer Pro to help design and validate wireless networks, identify channel conflicts and overlapping channels, low signal quality, and other issues that may affect the connectivity or performance of your home, office, or business wireless network.
Includes visual visibility of the Wi-Fi environment, support for Wi-Fi 4 through 7 across 2.4, 5, and 6 GHz bands, custom columns from over 850 data fields, advanced filtering features, and compatibility with remote sensors. It allows...
</description></item><item><title>Download TickTick Premium 8.0.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jan 2026 21:21:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ticktick-premium-7770.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ticktick-premium-7770.html
</guid><description>
TickTick Premium is a task management application that helps users stay organized, it is very suitable for educators and students with many incentives. TickTick turns your Windows PC device into a flexible, easy-to-use and highly efficient office platform. Join millions of people to capture ideas, organize their lives, and do something creative every day.
Whether there are work related tasks or personal goals, TickTick is here to help you manage all your to-dos. With five different...
</description></item><item><title>Download WonderFox DVD Video Converter 31.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jan 2026 21:21:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wonderfox-dvd-video-converter-189.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wonderfox-dvd-video-converter-189.html
</guid><description>
WonderFox DVD Video Converter is a software to convert Video DVD to the Video format the other with fast speed. Convenient program to convert the popular video formats and movie DVD, download WonderFox DVD Video Converter below. You can create videos that will be optimized for viewing on mobile devices. There is a simple video editor, it will allow you to add effects, crop photos, and etc.
WonderFox DVD Video Converter
WonderFox DVD Video Converter support rip DVD and videos to various...
</description></item><item><title>Download MobiKin Eraser for iOS 2.1.21</title><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jan 2026 21:20:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mobikin-eraser-for-ios-5373.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mobikin-eraser-for-ios-5373.html
</guid><description>
MobiKin Eraser for iOS is one of the top deletion programs that gives you the functionality to delete all deleted files, private data, system settings and other files on your iOS device without have a chance to recover. When you decide to give up your old iDevice, you need to delete all the data on it. Otherwise, your personal data such as bank accounts and passwords, contact information, chat records or other information will be at high risk of disclosure. Luckily, you have MobiKin Eraser...
</description></item><item><title>Download WonderFox DVD Ripper Pro 24.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jan 2026 21:20:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wonderfox-dvd-ripper-pro-2066.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wonderfox-dvd-ripper-pro-2066.html
</guid><description>
WonderFox DVD Ripper is a tool to extract DVD fast number 1 really, only takes about 20 minutes to extract DVD 150 minutes to MP4, AVI, MKV, MOV, WMV with 0-quality loss and takes less time to MPG (only 5 ~ 10 minutes). Moreover, it complements the presets are optimized for all mobile devices pop as DVD to iPhone 5S, iPad Air, iPad mini 3, DVD to Samsung Galaxy S5, Sony, Nokia, BlackBerry, HTC, Xbox, Android devices, etc. WonderFox DVD Ripper Pro provides the best solution to convert DVD...
</description></item><item><title>Download Axialis IconVectors Pro 1.20</title><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jan 2026 21:19:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-axialis-iconvectors-pro-14187.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-axialis-iconvectors-pro-14187.html
</guid><description>
Axialis IconVectors is a lightweight and fast SVG icon editor built specifically for developers, providing precise control and quick editing of vector icons. It easily integrates into existing development workflows with real-time code preview (SVG, ReactTS, VueTS, XAML, C++), compatible with Visual Studio, VS Code and Adobe Illustrator. Its developer-focused features remove unnecessary complexity, making vector icon creation efficient and simple.
Features of Axialis IconVectors...
</description></item><item><title>Download Eagle Mode 0.96.4</title><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jan 2026 21:19:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-eagle-mode-11944.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-eagle-mode-11944.html
</guid><description>
Eagle Mode is a powerful and innovative file management application for Windows that provides users with a unique and rich way to navigate and organize files and folders. One of Eagle Mode's key features is its 3D interface, which allows users to navigate their files and folders in an impressively intuitive and interactive way. The app displays all your files and folders in three-dimensional space, with each file represented as a clickable icon. Users can easily zoom in and out of the 3D...
</description></item><item><title>Download NoiseWorks DynAssist 2.2.3</title><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jan 2026 21:18:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-noiseworks-dynassist-13844.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-noiseworks-dynassist-13844.html
</guid><description>
NoiseWorks DynAssist is an AI-powered vocal editing plugin designed to automate and simplify vocal processing tasks like gain balancing, noise gate, breath detection, and hiss control. It integrates directly into your DAW workflow via ARA (Audio Random Access) support, allowing real-time, non-destructive processing and live waveform editing without the need to render or reverb tracks.
Key Features:
	Automatic Loudness Adjustment: DynAssist adjusts vocal loudness to a target level in...
</description></item><item><title>Download Coolmuster iOS Eraser 3.1.22</title><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jan 2026 21:17:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-ios-eraser-4948.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-ios-eraser-4948.html
</guid><description>
Coolmuster iOS Eraser security tool for IOS that helps you protect against theft of data on iPad, iPhone and iPod your old when you sell, donate or exchange your device, Coolmuster released a meticulously erase tool iOS delete all personal information, system settings, delete files, and more from devices recover. Fully compatible with iOS 13. Deletion software is done by this software is permanent so that no any software can recover them back.
Coolmuster iOS Eraser works with almost all...
</description></item><item><title>Download 4K Video Downloader Plus 26.0.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jan 2026 18:25:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-video-downloader-617.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-video-downloader-617.html
</guid><description>
4K Video Downloader Plus is software support downloads video, audio and subtitles from YouTube with high quality up to 4K. Download process video is very simple: just copy the video link from your browser and click Paste Url. Done! If you want that video on your iPad, iPhone or other device, we have protected you.
The feature on 4K Video Downloader Plus
	Download entire playlists and channels from YouTube and save them in MP4, MKV, M4A, MP3, FLV, 3G, create a file .m3u for...
</description></item><item><title>Download VirtualBox 7.2.6.172322</title><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jan 2026 16:09:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-virtualbox-285.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-virtualbox-285.html
</guid><description>
VirtualBox is a virtualization software open source allows you to run one or more operating system in a virtual machine while running Windows. It is used for purposes such as experience app or try to play the game new in a safe environment, do not affect the main operating system of you. With this software, users will better control multiple virtual machines at the same time.
VirtualBox - Create virtual drive allows running multiple operating systems at the same time
The program comes...
</description></item><item><title>Download Office Timeline Plus 13.22.00.00 Expert / Pro / Pro+ Edition</title><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jan 2026 16:08:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-timeline-2106.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-timeline-2106.html
</guid><description>
Office Timeline is an add-on very useful and powerful software for Microsoft PowerPoint. With add-ons, you can create PowerPoint documents look more beautiful. With add-ons, you can add the time Line on the project by yourself. Application time for the composition and different segments of the document, your PowerPoint will not only increase the beauty for your work, but also for customers and your manager. The people who created this product is also believe that add-ons this is the only...
</description></item><item><title>Download Active UNERASER Ultimate 26.0.6</title><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jan 2026 16:07:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-active-uneraser-ultimate-2635.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-active-uneraser-ultimate-2635.html
</guid><description>
Active UNERASER Ultimate is a powerful program and effectively allow you to recover files, folder and partition accidentally deleted. You can install it and work from the boot disk. Active UNERASER Ultimate works with the file system such as NTFS, FAT, HFS +, Unix UFS, etc. the interface is quite convenience, minimal installation, it easily works in general, I hope the program will be useful.
Active UNERASER Ultimate - Restore permissions for specific and partition the drive
The basic...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mozilla Thunderbird 147.0.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jan 2026 16:01:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thunderbird-1788.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thunderbird-1788.html
</guid><description>
Thunderbird is an email program full featured with controls spam integration, mail filter, address book, news groups and more. It provides a clean interface and easy to use (customizable). Thunderbird also provides the security features such as S / MIME, digital signing, message encryption, support for certificates and security devices.
Before using this feature, you should review the settings IMAP, SMTP, and SSL/TLS his. Now, what all you need to do is provide your name, email address,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Perfectly Clear WorkBench 5.0.1.3063</title><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jan 2026 16:00:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfectly-clear-workbench-6892.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfectly-clear-workbench-6892.html
</guid><description>
Perfectly Clear Workbench is an application that uses image editing libraries Perfectly Clear by Athentech and is provided to demonstrate the capabilities of the Perfectly Clear processing libraries, which recognize faces and allow quick export of processing settings for use.
One of the key features in Workbench is the ability to "export to API" when saving a Preset. This allows you to make image edits in Workbench and adjust the settings to suit your editing style and needs. You can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Directory List and Print Pro 4.40</title><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jan 2026 16:00:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-list-and-print-pro-481.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-list-and-print-pro-481.html
</guid><description>
Directory List and Print Pro is software that provides function lists and support printing content, quick, simple. In addition, the file list can be formatted, filtered, saved to several file formats and also further processed (delete / copy / move files). By copying to the clipboard the list can be exported into other programs or opened directly in Word and Excel.
The features Directory List and Print basic
	Choose the folders listed in a tree structure.
	Select the folder by...
</description></item><item><title>Download reaConverter Pro 8.0.188</title><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jan 2026 15:59:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html
</guid><description>
reaConverter Pro is software image processing feature with batch conversion and image editing periodically becomes simple. eaConverter also provide command line utilities allow you to process images automatically, thus helping you shorten the time for other work.
reaConverter Pro integrated powerful tool of Uber with many great features. It provides advanced solutions to process and adjust images. Management of the conversion process the base image with the latest version of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Free YouTube Download 4.5.2.117 Premium</title><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jan 2026 15:54:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-download-1177.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-download-1177.html
</guid><description>
Free YouTube Download Premium is the most popular application to download videos from YouTube. The program was released in 2006 and regularly updated since then. Use the program to download and convert YouTube videos to view offline anytime.
Free YouTube Download - added Support to download youtube
Download more videos! Save whole playlists and YouTube channels, videos from a playlist individually (history, video be favorite, favourites, Watch later), videos from many different...
</description></item><item><title>Download Atlantis Word Processor 5.0.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jan 2026 15:54:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-atlantis-word-processor-585.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-atlantis-word-processor-585.html
</guid><description>
Atlantis Word Processor is a word processor app with features format, standard text, autocorrect, and spell check.  Atlantis is a word processor in accordance with most of the tasks handled daily text. The interface is very easy to use and offers the toolbars, hotkeys and sound effects thanh can customize (can turn off). It includes a clip library for quick access to the text or images used regular preview, font format and many other features aimed at improving the process of your...
</description></item><item><title>Download Stardock Start11 2.6.0.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 29 Jan 2026 15:48:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stardock-start11-7029.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stardock-start11-7029.html
</guid><description>
Start11 is an application capable of customizing the Start Menu and Taskbar on Windows 11 and Windows 10. This is an application that allows users to customize Windows 11 to suit their preferences. his personal. Start11 will help you bring the new Start Menu of Windows 11 to Windows 10. And vice versa, Start11 also helps you to bring the Start Menu of Windows 10 to Windows 11.
Start11 also helps users bring some functions of Windows 10 to Windows 11 through customizing the Taskbar such...
</description></item></channel></rss>