<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 03:36:36 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 03:36:36 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download DesktopOK 11.94</title><pubDate> Sat, 09 Aug 2025 01:33:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopok-1635.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopok-1635.html
</guid><description>
DesktopOK is software save and restore the positions of icons. DesktopOK also offers a solution small but effective for the user to change the screen resolution often. DesktopOK is not installed and can be executed easily from the desktop, and can be carried on a small USB or memory device to another. Start of the program. The first time you use the program, the program will show you screen license. Free program and license info is only displayed the first time (on each PC).
DesktopOK -...
</description></item><item><title>Download WebMinds Hard Drive Optimizer 1.8.1.11</title><pubDate> Sat, 09 Aug 2025 01:30:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hard-drive-optimizer-7835.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hard-drive-optimizer-7835.html
</guid><description>
Hard Drive Optimizer is a software that optimizes your hard drive, with it you will quickly recover free disk space! The job of this program is to find the biggest files on your hard drive and delete the ones you don't need easily.
Features of Hard Drive Optimizer
	Hard Drive Optimizer provides the fastest and easiest way to free up your hard drive and free up precious space.
	Scan your hard drive or any folder on your computer for large files that are eating up disk space.
	Review...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare Recoverit 13.5.25.4</title><pubDate> Sat, 09 Aug 2025 01:30:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-recoverits-374.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-recoverits-374.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare Recoverit is a data recovery software that is easily lost at a rapid rate and is used by many people. You will do what happens if one day your data is suddenly lost due to the virus or deleted it, .. Wondershare Recoverit will provide you with an environment to protect important data.
Wondershare Recoverit has all the scanning processes that are divided into multiple types, from the typical recovery of the deleted files that are deleted to the recovery of missing files due...
</description></item><item><title>Download Aiseesoft Blu-ray Player 6.7.82</title><pubDate> Sat, 09 Aug 2025 01:30:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aiseesoft-blu-ray-player-118.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aiseesoft-blu-ray-player-118.html
</guid><description>
Aiseesoft Blu-ray Player Program is a multimedia good. After launch, you can produce absolutely any Blu-ray how you can work with documents, menus, and other elements, you can download at The Blu-ray Aiseesoft below. Please note, players can also play almost every video format, audio is also supported, the list is waiting for you on the official website. In addition, Aiseesoft Blu-ray Player will be able to view ISO images. It has a pleasant interface, style.
Aiseesoft Blu-ray Player -...
</description></item><item><title>Download EaseUS ScreenShot 1.4.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 09 Aug 2025 01:29:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-screenshot-7937.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-screenshot-7937.html
</guid><description>
Capture everything on your screen easily through this tool, EaseUS ScreenShot provides users with a powerful set of screen capture tools to meet all their needs. The app is easy to start and use, and it does exactly what you'd expect: it helps you take screenshots without much effort.
You can capture the entire screen or just an area of ​​it. To help improve usability, double-pressing the Alt key automatically captures the full screen, while pressing Ctrl twice will let you select...
</description></item><item><title>Download GoodSync Enterprise 12.9.4.4</title><pubDate> Sat, 09 Aug 2025 01:29:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-goodsync-enterprise-163.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-goodsync-enterprise-163.html
</guid><description>
GoodSync Enterprise is a software that saves files and files easily and is reliable. It automatically analyts, synchronize and backup your email, family photos, contacts, MP3, financial documentation and other important files-between desktop computers, laptops, servers, external drives and Windows Mobile devices as well as remotely via FTP , SFTP, WebDAV and more. The GoodSync synchronized software combines bulletproof reliability with an extremely easy interface to compare, synchronize...
</description></item><item><title>Download Free YouTube Download 4.4.34.808 Premium</title><pubDate> Sat, 09 Aug 2025 01:28:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-download-1177.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-download-1177.html
</guid><description>
Free YouTube Download Premium is the most popular application to download videos from YouTube. The program was released in 2006 and regularly updated since then. Use the program to download and convert YouTube videos to view offline anytime.
Free YouTube Download - added Support to download youtube
Download more videos! Save whole playlists and YouTube channels, videos from a playlist individually (history, video be favorite, favourites, Watch later), videos from many different...
</description></item><item><title>Download Causality 4.0.10</title><pubDate> Sat, 09 Aug 2025 01:28:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-causality-6895.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-causality-6895.html
</guid><description>
Causality is a new kind of writing app where you develop your stories visually, giving you an amazing overview of your stories. Friend. Causality works with your story the way it looks in your mind, but with the ability to visualize a much larger structure.
Causality supports writing in over 100 languages, checks spells in multiple languages ​​simultaneously, and comes with a gigabyte of fonts for identical rendering on all platforms. With Causality, it's easy to write screenplays...
</description></item><item><title>Download Syncios WhatsApp Transfer 2.4.7</title><pubDate> Sat, 09 Aug 2025 01:27:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncios-whatsapp-transfer-5944.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncios-whatsapp-transfer-5944.html
</guid><description>
Syncios WhatsApp Transfer helps to backup your WhatsApp history more easily than ever before. It allows you to backup and restore your WhatsApp iPhone/iPad/Android data in just one click. Syncios WhatsApp Transfer can meet all your needs for publishing WhatsApp conversations.
You can export and print the WhatsaS conversations; publish WhatsApp messages, photos, videos and audio files selectively or by a click.
The features of Syncios WhatsApp Transfer
	Why saves all WhatsApp content...
</description></item><item><title>Download Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium 4.4.34.808</title><pubDate> Sat, 09 Aug 2025 01:27:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-to-mp3-converter-premium-844.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-to-mp3-converter-premium-844.html
</guid><description>
Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium version is a software used to convert YouTube to MP3, extract audio from playlists YouTube, show listings, charts, video responses, channels, favorites of the user. With Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium, you can download and convert playlists, channels, stream original tv series and get them into iTunes at the same time.
Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium - convert YouTube to MP3
Features Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium from the...
</description></item><item><title>Download simplewall 3.8.7</title><pubDate> Sat, 09 Aug 2025 01:26:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-simplewall-1173.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-simplewall-1173.html
</guid><description>
simplewall as an alternative for filters firewalls default of Windows, allows you to control and restrict the applications and processes access the Internet. simplewall allows you to override the default settings of the Windows Filtering Platform (offers APIS and services required for the application security network to filter network data) and install the new filter block the processes be selected, thereby protecting the computer from malicious software.
simplewall - firewall blocked...
</description></item><item><title>Download Photo Supreme 2025.3.1.7997</title><pubDate> Sat, 09 Aug 2025 01:21:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photo-supreme-430.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photo-supreme-430.html
</guid><description>
Photo Supreme is a software product management professional pictures of idimager. With Photo Supreme you can arrange, manage back stock photo archive of yourself and share them with you here and relatives easily via Email or Facebook. Photo Supreme provides users method to sort images effective, logical, as well as edit and share your photos with friends and relatives in the family. Especially the Photo Supreme allows to work with multiple image formats and support mounting support,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Coder Technologies Coder 2.24.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 09 Aug 2025 01:20:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coder-oss-enterprise-8726.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coder-oss-enterprise-8726.html
</guid><description>
Coder OSS Enterprise is a development platform that provides a complete cloud-based solution for software development, testing and deployment. It is designed to simplify the software development process by providing developers with a collaborative and streamlined environment.
Coder offloads development from local workstations to your on-premises infrastructure and public cloud. Boost developer productivity with powerful server resources and instant integration. Keep the code and data...
</description></item><item><title>Download Pazu StreamGet All-In-One Video Downloader 2.7.7</title><pubDate> Sat, 09 Aug 2025 01:20:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pazu-streamget-all-in-one-video-downloader-12037.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pazu-streamget-all-in-one-video-downloader-12037.html
</guid><description>
StreamGet All-In-One Video Downloader is the ultimate downloading solution for you. It supports downloading any movies and shows from the most popular streaming sites including Netflix, Prime Video, Disney Plus, Max, Hulu, and Apple TV Plus. The downloader is continuously updated to support more platforms in the future.
Download movies and shows from various streaming platforms to MP4/MKV on your Windows device and enjoy them anywhere you want.
Features of Pazu StreamGet All-In-One...
</description></item><item><title>Download Eusing Free Registry Cleaner 4.8.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 09 Aug 2025 01:16:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-eusing-free-registry-cleaner-1002.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-eusing-free-registry-cleaner-1002.html
</guid><description>
Eusing Free Registry Cleaner is a software cleans and remove the registry files Registry error on the system, uninstall the root programs left of the software was clear. Eusing Free Registry Cleaner will make your computer board works fine and smooth. The Files and invalid will be removed completely and permanently.
Eusing Free Registry Cleaner - Clean Registry errors
Eusing Free Registry Cleaner has ability to quick scan the system to find the outdated registry entries, and invalid....
</description></item><item><title>Download Argente Registry Cleaner 4.0.2.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 09 Aug 2025 01:16:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-argente-registry-cleaner-13814.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-argente-registry-cleaner-13814.html
</guid><description>
Argente Registry Cleaner is a free Windows utility designed to scan, clean and repair invalid or obsolete entries in the Windows Registry, helping to improve system stability and performance. This utility quickly analyzes the entire Registry for errors such as invalid entries left by uninstalled programs, missing keys, broken references, and other junk that can cause system crashes.
Key Features:
	Fast and Thorough Scan: Provides multiple scan modes including Safe (fastest), Normal...
</description></item><item><title>Download priPrinter Professional 7.0.0.2594 Beta</title><pubDate> Sat, 09 Aug 2025 01:15:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-priprinter-professional-633.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-priprinter-professional-633.html
</guid><description>
priPrinter Professional is the printer driver allows you to manipulate the output of the printer before being printed. PriPrinter is installed and select the same as the printer driver other. After printing it automatically displays the preview in where you can preview his print, change the layout, page position back, cut them, and much more. Then, you print it to printer or save your document for later use. With PriPrinter you will always be sure his prints will look like. You can measure...
</description></item><item><title>Download Pazu Apple Music Converter 1.8.7</title><pubDate> Sat, 09 Aug 2025 01:15:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pazu-apple-music-converter-11027.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pazu-apple-music-converter-11027.html
</guid><description>
Pazusoft Apple Music Converter for Windows allows you to easily download Apple Music songs, albums and playlists to M4A, MP3, AAC, FLAC, WAV, AIFF. So you can play Apple Music songs offline wherever you want, without the Music app or iTunes.
Pazu Apple Music Converter helps you download songs, albums, and Apple Music playlists to M4A/MP3/AAC/FLAC/WAV/AIFF while preserving the original sound quality (up to 256kbps). Additionally, custom output settings such as audio quality, file name...
</description></item><item><title>Download Apeaksoft Blu-ray Player 1.1.66</title><pubDate> Sat, 09 Aug 2025 01:15:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-apeaksoft-blu-ray-player-2458.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-apeaksoft-blu-ray-player-2458.html
</guid><description>
Apeaksoft Blu-ray Player is the software movie playback Blu-ray professional can help you play Blu-ray folder, Blu-ray disc / DVD folder, files ISO with photo effects high quality. It can also work as a media player powerful to play 4K UHD / HD 1080p / SD videos in MP4, MOV, AVI, MKV and other formats.
Apeaksoft Blu-ray Player is specially designed to play Blu-ray folder and file ISO. It supports very high for the Blu-ray movie new releases and guarantee you playback Blu-ray 1080p full...
</description></item><item><title>Download PanFone WhatsApp Transfer 2.4.7</title><pubDate> Sat, 09 Aug 2025 01:14:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-panfone-whatsapp-transfer-5580.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-panfone-whatsapp-transfer-5580.html
</guid><description>
PanFone WhatsApp Transfer is the best solution to backup, restore and transfer WhatsApp iOS / Android messages as well as export WhatsApp messages to HTML and CSV files. This PanFone WhatsApp Transfer easily and securely transferred iOS to Android WhatsApp can be a useful tool to help you backup and restore WhatsApp data. It will not overwrite or delete previous backups. You can restore WhatsApp backups to your phone any time you want.
Seamlessly transfer all WhatsApp chat history,...
</description></item><item><title>Download PVS-Studio 7.38.96703.1953</title><pubDate> Sat, 09 Aug 2025 01:13:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pvs-studio-1480.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pvs-studio-1480.html
</guid><description>
PVS-Studio is software that performs static code analysis and generate a report to help programmers find and fix bugs. PVS-Studio implements a series of check code, it is also useful to search the prints wrong error and Copy-Paste. Examples of such errors: V501, V517, V522, V523, V3001.
The main value of static analysis is in regular use, hence the error is identified and corrected at the earliest stages. There's no point of wasting 50 hours to search for a fault can be found with static...
</description></item><item><title>Download Syncovery Premium 11.6.5.80</title><pubDate> Sat, 09 Aug 2025 01:13:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncovery-pro-enterprise-232.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncovery-pro-enterprise-232.html
</guid><description>
Syncovery Pro Enterprise is a great application used to back up data and to synchronize personal computers, servers, laptops, notepads and storage online. The software comes with support for FTP and secure FTP servers, SSH, WebDAV, Amazon S3, http, update the part file, ZIP compression, data encryption, and schedule automatic backups.
Syncovery Pro Enterprise have the ability to freely select files and folders across the whole folder hierarchy in tree view and supports email...
</description></item><item><title>Download Argente Malware Cleaner 3.0.2.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 09 Aug 2025 01:08:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-argente-malware-cleaner-13494.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-argente-malware-cleaner-13494.html
</guid><description>
Argente Malware Cleaner is a lightweight utility designed to detect and remove a wide range of malware, including spyware, adware, Trojans and other threats that can compromise your privacy and data. It works as a complementary tool alongside your main antivirus software, helping to detect malware that may slip through the cracks.
Key features of Argente Malware Cleaner include:
	Easy-to-use, clean, and user-friendly interface that suits both casual and advanced users.
	Deep scanning...
</description></item><item><title>Download Argente System Repair 1.0.1.9</title><pubDate> Sat, 09 Aug 2025 01:08:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-argente-system-repair-13813.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-argente-system-repair-13813.html
</guid><description>
Argente System Repair is a lightweight utility designed to diagnose and fix common Windows system problems. It scans your system to identify errors in operating system components, file systems, installation files, and other system components, and then applies targeted fixes to resolve these problems. The tool provides different scan modes, including simple scan, recommended scan, and custom scan, allowing users to customize the repair process according to their needs.
System Repair...
</description></item><item><title>Download StaxRip 2.48.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 09 Aug 2025 01:07:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-staxrip-2930.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-staxrip-2930.html
</guid><description>
StaxRip app is a comprehensive and powerful, allowing you to convert all video files DVB, DVD, or DV video into a variety of file formats. The program is open Source, meaning completely free to download and use. StaxRip can support many video formats such as x264, MPEG-4, DivX, XviD, MPEG-2 and many other formats. The format sounds different also be supported, including MP2 / MPA, AAC, WAV, Ogg Vorbis, MP3, AC3, DTS and other formats. Moreover, the program also supports a variety of...
</description></item></channel></rss>