<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 14:34:04 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 14:34:04 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download SmartSystemMenu 2.33.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 23 Feb 2026 17:22:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-smartsystemmenu-6018.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-smartsystemmenu-6018.html
</guid><description>
SmartSystemMenu will help to work with more windows becoming a more efficient process with many useful functions to arrange your work. It can be attached to the title bar menu for easy access. The fact that it can be portable is just another bonus because you can quickly upload it to the flash drive to use on any machine you might be using.
SmartSystemMenu will be a significant upgrade to the default Windows installation with the ability to be added to help with window management...
</description></item><item><title>Download 3D Youtube Downloader 1.26.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 23 Feb 2026 17:21:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-3d-youtube-downloader-1631.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-3d-youtube-downloader-1631.html
</guid><description>
3D Youtube Downloader is application support users to download the videos from Youtube website with great quality. The advantage of this software is the ability to download the videos in 3D, make the download process is fully automated and the download speed is extremely fast. In addition to Youtube, this tool also allows to download videos from many other sites, so users can own any favorite videos yet. 3D Youtube Downloader is a downloads simple but powerful from Youtube, Vimeo,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Artweaver Plus 8.1.3.3746</title><pubDate> Mon, 23 Feb 2026 17:20:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-artweaver-plus-1324.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-artweaver-plus-1324.html
</guid><description>
Artweaver Plus is a software graphics editor with many functions fundamental to advanced and supports many different formats. Artweaver Plus works with image files in formats BMP, GIF, JPEG, JPG, JPE, PCX, PNG, TGA, VDA, ICB, VST, TIF, TIFF and AWD. Out of the possibilities of it, you can do outstanding work with layers, import and export graphic in different formats.
Artweaver Plus - editing software graphics
Artweaver Plus owner interface very similar to Photoshop , so users very...
</description></item><item><title>Download GoodSync Enterprise 12.9.25.5</title><pubDate> Mon, 23 Feb 2026 17:19:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-goodsync-enterprise-163.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-goodsync-enterprise-163.html
</guid><description>
GoodSync Enterprise is a software that saves files and files easily and is reliable. It automatically analyts, synchronize and backup your email, family photos, contacts, MP3, financial documentation and other important files-between desktop computers, laptops, servers, external drives and Windows Mobile devices as well as remotely via FTP , SFTP, WebDAV and more. The GoodSync synchronized software combines bulletproof reliability with an extremely easy interface to compare, synchronize...
</description></item><item><title>Download FreeFileSync Donation Edition 14.8</title><pubDate> Mon, 23 Feb 2026 17:18:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-freefilesync-donation-edition-13970.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-freefilesync-donation-edition-13970.html
</guid><description>
FreeFileSync Donation Edition is a special version of the FreeFileSync file synchronization software for donors who financially support projects. It is used to compare and synchronize folders, create and manage backups of all your important files. Instead of copying every file each time, FreeFileSync determines the difference between the source and destination folders and transfers only the minimum amount of data necessary.
FreeFileSync version with additional functionality and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Helium Music Manager Premium 18.0.692</title><pubDate> Mon, 23 Feb 2026 17:17:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-helium-music-manager-premium-164.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-helium-music-manager-premium-164.html
</guid><description>
Helium Music Manager is a music manager that can rip, tag, play, browse, search, rename, burn and synchronize your music with the mobile. You can control your music collection with Helium Music Manager. Stop using time looking for the file on your computer or looking through CDS, vinyl records and tapes - instead, simply enjoy and explore your music! Helium Music Manager can replace the ripper, the player, tag editor and related software to audio your other.
Helium Music Manager...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter 3.9.18 (2202)</title><pubDate> Mon, 23 Feb 2026 17:17:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-to-mp3-converter-1744.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-to-mp3-converter-1744.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter is the software support download youtube video and convert video to mp3 format fast and most simple. MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter allows you download and convert videos from YouTube and other websites to MP3 format by pasting the YouTube URL into the application. When you paste the URL, the program will display thumbnails for videos and you have the option to customize the title information, artist and album before you begin the process of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Simple Sticky Notes 6.9.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 23 Feb 2026 17:15:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-simple-sticky-notes-2180.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-simple-sticky-notes-2180.html
</guid><description>
Simple Sticky Notes is software that creates sticky notes on screen Desktop computer help you easily remember the schedule of his. Simple Sticky Notes allow users to fashion digital sticky / post it notes and almost "sticky" notes on a desktop operation Windows. It is completely ideal for the kind of users who need to write everything down with pen and paper to avoid the discomfort of forget everything. This program of articles simple digital notes, it certainly will prove to be of great...
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow Snap2PDF 1.3.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 23 Feb 2026 17:15:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-snap2pdf-13944.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-snap2pdf-13944.html
</guid><description>
Convert documents easily. Snap2PDF combines image to PDF conversion, high-quality PDF to image extraction, and fast, accurate PDF splitting — all in one smart, lightweight app.
Snap2PDF is your smart companion for managing your documents anytime, anywhere. Convert images to PDF smoothly, extract pages into high-quality images, or split large PDFs with pinpoint accuracy — all in one fast, intuitive app.
Why Snap2PDF?
	Convert images to clean, shareable PDFs
	Extract any PDF page...
</description></item><item><title>Download Diffchecker 6.8.6</title><pubDate> Mon, 23 Feb 2026 17:14:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-diffchecker-5025.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-diffchecker-5025.html
</guid><description>
Diffchecker is a application compare text, images and powerful file to desktop of your. Available for Windows, macOS. Compare text files, documents, PDF. Compare photos, graphics. Because Diffchecker Desktop running entirely on your computer, so it does not have to communicate with our servers to create your difference. This means that there is no other way in addition you can view your sensitive data, you.
Diffchecker Desktop run offline, that means you can use it anytime, anywhere and...
</description></item><item><title>Download QOwnNotes 26.2.9</title><pubDate> Mon, 23 Feb 2026 17:13:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qownnotes-3178.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qownnotes-3178.html
</guid><description>
QOwnNotes is notes bookmark file simple text (GPL) open source application for GNU / Linux , Mac OS X and Windows of Patrizio Bekerle ( pbek on GitHub and IRC) (optional) activity along with the notes application of ownCloud or Nextcloud. QOwnNote store your notes as plain text files and can be synchronized with synchronization function file of ownCloud / Nextcloud. You can also use other apps like Syncthing or Dropbox . Just write out your thoughts as they appear, and edit them if...
</description></item><item><title>Download MassTube 2026 v21.5.1.191 Ultra</title><pubDate> Mon, 23 Feb 2026 17:12:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-masstube-plus-461.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-masstube-plus-461.html
</guid><description>
MassTube Plus is a small utility used to download the favorite videos of you on youtube on your computer. This is a software compact, has a simple design with few options to download videos fastest. The you complete peace of mind because the software is easy to use, built exclusively for a single goal: to retrieve the video file from YouTube, so it doesn't pack the other useful features such as search engine integrated and a download audio file.
MassTube can work with multiple output...
</description></item><item><title>Download SQLite Expert Professional 5.5.40.651</title><pubDate> Mon, 23 Feb 2026 17:11:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sqlite-expert-professional-109.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sqlite-expert-professional-109.html
</guid><description>
SQLite Expert Professional  is a powerful program that allows you to manage and  organize  SQLite databases, visually display you tables and working classes. The user interface is convenient, but due to the lack of Russian support and a lot of customization, not everyone can figure it out, although if you work with the database I think you can understand where and click. In the main window, you can see all your databases, and if you want you can execute the   SQL   using the  SQL ...
</description></item><item><title>Download Handicap Manager for Excel 8.0.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 23 Feb 2026 17:10:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-handicap-manager-for-excel-5837.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-handicap-manager-for-excel-5837.html
</guid><description>
Handicap Manager is a customisable application written in Visual Basic as an application for Microsoft Excel. Fully compatible with Excel and meet all requirements of the USGA handicap system to calculate the USGA handicap index. It can be used to calculate the average score, statistics, the approval rate of the tournament and custom approval based on the user's settings.
The user-friendly interface and "point and click" are easy to help you easily work with the program, which is even...
</description></item><item><title>Download Executor 2.2.5.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 23 Feb 2026 17:10:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-executor-271.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-executor-271.html
</guid><description>
Executor for windows is a software alternative premium customization features for the Windows "Run" and "Search Programs". When you press WIN + Z and provides the search results instant, as-you-type for any keywords you enter. By default, Executor will index all the Desktop and Start Menu and you can easily expand the search range by adding the folder location additional.
Executor for windows
The program comes with a list of commands built in which you can use to quickly access many...
</description></item><item><title>Download Schoolhouse Test Professional Enterprise 6.1.161.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 23 Feb 2026 17:09:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-schoolhouse-test-professional-1708.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-schoolhouse-test-professional-1708.html
</guid><description>
Schoolhouse Test Professional is a software to create and print a test paper and pencil test or quiz has never been easier. Schoolhouse Test makes a time consuming job a lot easier and more professional results significantly. A number of our customers have even hinted that creating tests with Schoolhouse Test can actually be an enjoyable process. If you are looking for a generator testing professional that makes quick work of creating the test paper and pen, quizzes, and exams then...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tax Assistant for Excel Professional 7.11</title><pubDate> Mon, 23 Feb 2026 17:08:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tax-assistant-for-excel-professional-10690.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tax-assistant-for-excel-professional-10690.html
</guid><description>
Tax Assistant for Excel Professional is a custom application written for Microsoft Excel and requires Microsoft Excel 2010/2013/2016/2019/365. It simplifies your Federal Income Tax preparation by providing an Excel workbook with IRS-approved alternative forms to Form 1040 and Form 1040A with Forms A, B, C, C-EZ, D, E, SE, Forms 6251 (AMT), 4952, 6781, 8829, 8949 and 8995. There are also several worksheets related to deductions and Schedule D covering Benefits Social Security, Qualified...
</description></item><item><title>Download dbForge SQL Complete Enterprise 2025.3.107</title><pubDate> Mon, 23 Feb 2026 17:07:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbforge-sql-complete-pro-7827.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbforge-sql-complete-pro-7827.html
</guid><description>
dbForge SQL Complete Pro is an advanced solution for SQL database development, management and administration. Available as an add-in for Visual Studio and SSMS, this tool provides great autocompletion.Write, beautify, refactor your SQL code and give your productivity a huge boost with features included in SQL Complete.
dbForge SQL Complete Pro provides a wide range of code completion features that save users from having to memorize long and complex object names, column names, SQL...
</description></item><item><title>Download NETworkManager 2026.2.22.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 23 Feb 2026 17:06:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-networkmanager-3328.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-networkmanager-3328.html
</guid><description>
NETworkManager is an open-Source tool that allows you to manage the network and troubleshoot the network. NETworkManager focus a number of tools can support managing network connections. You are granted access to a large assortment of tools available from the main window of NETworkManuber to effective use. You can use this tool to view network interface along with many bit other essential information such as IP address, DNS server, etc.). The network Card is connected can be configured...
</description></item><item><title>Download Unit Converter Pro 2.6.6</title><pubDate> Mon, 23 Feb 2026 17:00:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-unit-converter-pro-9060.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-unit-converter-pro-9060.html
</guid><description>
Pro Unit Converter is the 6th set of the Smart Tools® collection. This app includes currency exchange rates (money, bitcoin). It has no ads and ads are replaced with useful texts. There are many unit conversion applications on the market. However, most are inconvenient and difficult to use because of poor and complicated user interfaces.
Features of Unit Converter Pro
	Basic: length (distance), area, weight (mass), volume (capacity)
	Life: exchange rates, temperature, time, speed,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Nova Launcher 81033 (8.4.0)</title><pubDate> Mon, 23 Feb 2026 16:59:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-nova-launcher-10503.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-nova-launcher-10503.html
</guid><description>
Nova Launcher is a powerful, customizable, and flexible home screen replacement. Nova brings advanced features to enhance your home screen but remains a great, user-friendly choice for everyone. Whether you want to completely overhaul your home screen or are looking for a cleaner, faster home screen launcher, Nova is the answer.
Nova Launcher Features
	Latest features: Nova brings the latest Android launcher features to all other phones.
	Custom icon themes: Nova supports thousands of...
</description></item><item><title>Download 3C All-in-One Toolbox 3.1.6d</title><pubDate> Mon, 23 Feb 2026 16:59:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-3c-all-in-one-toolbox-8399.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-3c-all-in-one-toolbox-8399.html
</guid><description>
3C All-in-One Toolbox combines many features into one giant toolbox with a modern and easy-to-use interface. All the tools you need to monitor, control and fine-tune all your Android devices. This app uses the Accessibility service to help you stop the app on non-rooted devices but will never collect any information.
Features of 3C All-in-One Toolbox
	Device Manager offers very powerful configurations, task scheduling, and device watchdogs that you can find to optimize performance and...
</description></item><item><title>Download CodeMatics Universal TV Remote Control 3.0.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 23 Feb 2026 16:59:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-codematics-universal-tv-remote-control-11491.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-codematics-universal-tv-remote-control-11491.html
</guid><description>
For Smart TV/Devices, the only setting required is to connect your phone as well as your Smart TV/Device to the same Wifi network. For IR TVs, your phone must have a built-in Infrared (IR) feature for the app to work as a remote control. The IR feature is required to send signals from the phone to the TV like a regular TV remote.
You can now Cast media files stored on your mobile phone to your Smart TV screen.
Smart TV function
	Voice search
	Power control.
	Mute / Volume...
</description></item><item><title>Download Solid Explorer File Manager 3.4.1 build 304012</title><pubDate> Mon, 23 Feb 2026 16:58:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-solid-explorer-file-manager-8924.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-solid-explorer-file-manager-8924.html
</guid><description>
Solid Explorer is a file management application inspired by old file management applications. Solid Explorer is a popular file management app for Android devices that allows users to manage and organize their files and folders in an intuitive and user-friendly interface. It offers many features that make it stand out from other file management apps.
Solid Explorer allows you to navigate to files stored on your device and automatically organize them into collections. You can view,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Weather &amp;amp; Radar USA - Pro 2026.4.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 23 Feb 2026 16:58:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-weather-radar-usa-pro-8391.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-weather-radar-usa-pro-8391.html
</guid><description>
Weather &amp;amp; Radar USA is a mobile application that provides users with real-time weather information and forecasts for locations in the United States. The app includes many features such as current weather conditions, hourly and daily forecasts, radar and satellite images, and severe weather alerts. It also includes many customizable settings, such as the ability to set up multiple locations and receive notifications about specific weather conditions.
Features of Weather &amp;amp; Radar...
</description></item></channel></rss>