<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 03:32:19 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 03:32:19 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Visual Studio Code 1.105.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 10 Oct 2025 17:05:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-visual-studio-code-3182.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-visual-studio-code-3182.html
</guid><description>
Visual Studio Code is the encryption tool of Microsoft has met most of the needs of the developer. Environment this encoding was introduced to compete with other products such as Sublime and Nodepad ++ . Microsoft, in its new product, has not been released in many years, has provided many features in a simple environment. In addition to the familiar with a dozen programming languages, the syntax and get to know coding language as soon as be encrypted and allows for syntax highlighting, it...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ant Download Manager Pro 2.16.0 Build 91579</title><pubDate> Fri, 10 Oct 2025 17:05:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ant-download-manager-pro-137.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ant-download-manager-pro-137.html
</guid><description>
Ant Download Manager Pro is software support download has the same features as IDM, even it has many prominent features, more user friendly more and have speed download data incredible. Ant Download Manager is a Internet content downloader quickly with support download at video! Function: fully Integrated with the web browsers most popular: Internet Explorer 8+, Mozilla Firefox 32 +, Google Chrome 31+ and the copies of them (Pale Moon, Opera, Vivaldi, Slimjet, ComodoDragon, etc.). you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Google Chrome 141.0.7390.77</title><pubDate> Fri, 10 Oct 2025 17:04:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-chrome-1012.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-chrome-1012.html
</guid><description>
Google Chrome web browser is the most used today. Support surf the web, listen to music, watch movies, play web game effective no jerky lag with the internet connection stable. When you are surfing the web or performing an important task, whether it is operation big or small, work or entertainment, then Chrome has the smart features and the speed you need to make, create and explore on the net.
The latest version of Google Chrome is the third 114. But we are providing for users Google...
</description></item><item><title>Download ON1 Photo RAW MAX 2026 v20.0.4.17586</title><pubDate> Fri, 10 Oct 2025 17:03:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-on1-photo-raw-max-10717.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-on1-photo-raw-max-10717.html
</guid><description>
ON1 Photo RAW MAX 2024 is powerful photo editing software that provides photographers with many tools and features to enhance and edit their images. With a user-friendly interface, it offers advanced editing capabilities, including non-destructive editing, AI-powered adjustments, and precise control over color and tone. It also supports raw files from over 800 cameras and works with JPEG, TIF, PSD, PSB, PNG and DNG files. Additionally, it also includes photo organization tools to manage...
</description></item><item><title>Download ON1 Photo RAW 2026 v20.0.4.17586</title><pubDate> Fri, 10 Oct 2025 17:02:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-on1-photo-raw-1791.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-on1-photo-raw-1791.html
</guid><description>
ON1 Photo RAW 2023  includes the essential tools and features every photographer needs in their workflow. Our state-of-the-art, super-fast, non-destructive processing engine gives you an extremely smooth and efficient editing experience.
ON1 Photo RAW focuses on letting you get the most out of every photo. Photographers now have a quick photo management engine, hundreds of customizable photo effects, fast and beautiful HDR, masking and selection tools, layers and more in one app. Quickly...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Downloader 9.17.8</title><pubDate> Fri, 10 Oct 2025 17:01:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html
</guid><description>
YTD Youtube Downloader is an application that reliable and intuitive, allowing you to quickly download YouTube videos and save them to your computer. You can also convert the media files to the format desired video or extract audio streams and save separately. YTD Youtube Downloader lets you save your favorite clips of yourself from Youtube, Facebook, Vimeo and Dailymotion to your desktop. The software supports URLS from many web site hosting, multimedia and allows you to download desired...
</description></item><item><title>Download Chaos Corona 13.2 for 3ds Max 2016 - 2026</title><pubDate> Fri, 10 Oct 2025 17:01:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chaos-corona-2986.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chaos-corona-2986.html
</guid><description>
Corona Renderer is the name of the plug-in technique and dedicated powerful, but have high functionality for Autodesk software 3ds Max. Plug before you is a standalone application known to the CLI. In addition, users can use this tool to promote their business on software Maxon Cinema 4D is also used. The manufacturers of this product believe that working with this tool is very simple and in fact you only need to press the activities rendered. With this tool easier than ever can do the...
</description></item><item><title>Download All About PDF Advanced Edition 3.2035</title><pubDate> Fri, 10 Oct 2025 17:00:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-all-about-pdf-advanced-edition-14110.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-all-about-pdf-advanced-edition-14110.html
</guid><description>
All About PDF is a fast, beautifully designed, intuitive and portable PDF utility that you can use to merge, split, protect, compress, convert PDF files and more. We always strive to simplify pricing and deliver great value. Merge PDF, split PDF, convert PDF, protect PDF and more.
Features of All About PDF Advanced
Focus on privacy: As a desktop application, you don't need to upload your private PDF files to an unknown third-party remote server for processing. We also do not collect or...
</description></item><item><title>Download Chaos Corona 13.2 for Cinema 4D R17 - 2025</title><pubDate> Fri, 10 Oct 2025 17:00:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-corona-renderer-for-cinema-4d-6499.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-corona-renderer-for-cinema-4d-6499.html
</guid><description>
Corona Renderer  is the name of a powerful, but highly functional engineering and dedicated plug-in for Autodesk 3ds Max software. Plug in before you are a known CLI standalone application. In addition, users can use this tool to advertise their business on Maxon Cinema 4D software which is also used. The manufacturers of this product firmly believe that working with this tool is very simple, and in fact you just need to hit render the rendering operations. With this tool it's easier...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft Edge 141.0.3537.71</title><pubDate> Fri, 10 Oct 2025 16:59:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-edge-3940.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-edge-3940.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft Edge is web browser developed specifically for Windows operating system 10 alternatives to Internet Explorer is the default browser on Windows. Browser Microsoft Edge built-in assistant Cortana brings content and website based on the user's preferences, there are also system utilities quite extensive help you to customize according to individual. Microsoft Edge has the similarity with Google Chrome quite large, except the target is marked more of the interface and the rounded...
</description></item><item><title>Download My Music Collection 2.3.15.159</title><pubDate> Fri, 10 Oct 2025 16:58:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nuclear-coffee-my-music-collection-1242.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nuclear-coffee-my-music-collection-1242.html
</guid><description>
Nuclear Coffee My Music Collection is a software directory the most comprehensive music designed to organize and manage the music collection of any kind, including CD discs, MP3 files or vinyl records. Organizer music this allows you to create a database CD is to order and view its contents, even when the disk is located on the shelf or being a friend of you borrow. You can now forget about creating the music database on a paper, in Excel or text file. Just insert a disc, scan barcode or...
</description></item><item><title>Download Muziza YouTube Downloader Converter 8.15.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 10 Oct 2025 16:57:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-muziza-youtube-downloader-converter-3972.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-muziza-youtube-downloader-converter-3972.html
</guid><description>
Muziza YouTube Downloader Converter is a tool to create conditions for an attractive interface and many features to help you to download video clips from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion, Instagram and other sites. Muziza YouTube Downloader Converter can also download the video UHD 8K, 5K, 4K, QHD 2K, HD 1080p and 720p from YouTube. The app allows you download only audio stream from YouTube and save as MP3. You don't need to download the entire video file.
Muziza YouTube Downloader...
</description></item><item><title>Download Radiant Photo 2.1.1.790 + Addon Pack</title><pubDate> Fri, 10 Oct 2025 15:01:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-radiant-photo-8319.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-radiant-photo-8319.html
</guid><description>
Radiant Photo is a photo editing software that allows users to edit, enhance and organize their digital photos. It provides many tools to adjust color, brightness, contrast, saturation, and other image properties, as well as features to crop, rotate, and resize images.
Radiant Photo also includes many filters and effects that can be applied to photos to change their appearance. Additionally, it also allows users to organize their photos by creating albums, tagging photos, and searching...
</description></item><item><title>Download FastCopy Pro 5.11.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 10 Oct 2025 15:01:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fastcopy-pro-9404.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fastcopy-pro-9404.html
</guid><description>
FastCopy Pro is file copying and synchronization software designed to provide faster and more efficient file transfer operations than native file copying tools in operating system. It provides various features and optimizations to enhance the speed and reliability of file copying.
It can copy/delete unicode and more than MAX_PATH(260byte) pathname files. Automatically, after copy source and copy destination are HDD under the same physical HDD or evaluated, it will work as follows. Diff...
</description></item><item><title>Download 7 Caps 11.0 + Portable</title><pubDate> Fri, 10 Oct 2025 15:00:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-7-caps-3194.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-7-caps-3194.html
</guid><description>
7 Caps is a very small application that aims to notify you in real time whether the status of the keyboard Num Lock or Caps Lock change in real time. 7 Caps will be a money saver when the indicator light on the keyboard or laptop your current activities help you save or repair, or if you just want to verify functional status. This mode will be useful when entering a passage from a web page on a local documents, for example. But that's not all; you get some custom lightweight allows you to...
</description></item><item><title>Download WSCC Windows System Control Center 10.0.1.1 Commercial</title><pubDate> Fri, 10 Oct 2025 14:59:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wscc-windows-system-control-center-1599.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wscc-windows-system-control-center-1599.html
</guid><description>
WSCC Windows System Control Center can automatically install and update the add-ons are supported. Alternatively, WSCC can use the http protocol to download and run the program. WSCC is portable device, no installation required. Extract content of zip archive downloaded into any folder on your computer.
The interface is very simple and intuitive, thus allowing any type of user how to find his way, regardless of the experience of their previous with the IT world. Besides, it includes a...
</description></item><item><title>Download Quick Access Popup 12.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 10 Oct 2025 14:58:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quick-access-popup-984.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quick-access-popup-984.html
</guid><description>
Quick Access Popup  ( QAP ) is a software that provides quick access to files, files, windows applications and is  shortcut manager , mouse and keyboard.  Quick Access Popup  helps you quickly move between FILE, DOCUMENT, APPS in Windows Explorer or file dialog to quickly launch applications, documents or web pages at once 
To launch the pop-up menu, click the  QAP  icon in the Notifications area, press the Middle mouse button, or press Windows + W (these triggers can be changed under...
</description></item><item><title>Download Trillian 6.6 Build 6</title><pubDate> Fri, 10 Oct 2025 14:58:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-trillian-2638.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-trillian-2638.html
</guid><description>
Trillian is the chat help you sign in to more the registered name of a certain service or you can log on at the same time many services in a working window. It integrates multiple services such as Yahoo! MSN, IRC, AIM and ICQ. In addition, you can manage Email accounts, Facebook and Twitter friends - all in just one application.
Login is easy; just click on the network or the appropriate website and log in as normal. Trillian requires access your data (accepted) and post to friends...
</description></item><item><title>Download 4K Tokkit Pro 25.4.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 10 Oct 2025 14:57:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-tokkit-pro-6753.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-tokkit-pro-6753.html
</guid><description>
4K Tokkit Pro is an application created to bulk download TikTok content., save TikTok videos, captions, entire accounts, hashtags and single videos in high quality. . Watch TikToks offline, browse your TikTok feed without ads, repost clips to other social networks.
Features of 4K Tokkit Pro
	Download videos in bulk from your TikTok account. Save all videos from profile and get TikTok user's profile picture.
	Automatically get updates from your favorite TikTok creators and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Roxio Easy VHS to DVD Plus 4.0.13</title><pubDate> Fri, 10 Oct 2025 14:57:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-roxio-easy-vhs-to-dvd-plus-6772.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-roxio-easy-vhs-to-dvd-plus-6772.html
</guid><description>
Roxio Easy VHS to DVD Plus is premium software that helps you convert your VHS tapes to DVD or digital to enhance and preserve the your home movie. Capture analog video directly from your camcorder or VCR and burn to DVD or convert to popular digital formats for free sharing across devices
Roxio Easy VHS to DVD Plus also offers video trimming, quick editing, color enhancement, adding transitions, noise reduction and stabilizing old footage to Breathe new life into your old videos....
</description></item><item><title>Download Lyric Video Studio 1.3.34</title><pubDate> Fri, 10 Oct 2025 14:56:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lyric-video-studio-13581.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lyric-video-studio-13581.html
</guid><description>
Lyric Video Studio is a powerful, feature-rich video editor specifically designed to create lyric videos, music videos, and visualizers with ease. It integrates simple and effective text tools along with generative AI capabilities to streamline the video creation process. Whether you're a musician launching a killer new track, a content creator, or just love playing with visuals, this app lets you sync your lyrics to your music in just a few clicks. Enter lyrics, drag to sync and you're...
</description></item><item><title>Download Android Studio 2025.1.4.8</title><pubDate> Fri, 10 Oct 2025 14:56:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-android-studio-3890.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-android-studio-3890.html
</guid><description>
Android Studio is an Android development environment, completely new, provides many improvements and new features compared to Eclipse ADT. This software solution will is IDE the official Android when is finishing. This tool provides many tools and features such as editing, layout, rich set of tools to capture usability, compatibility version, performance and other issues, create a lot APK, build system based on Gradle flexibility, extended support for Google Services, integrated support...
</description></item><item><title>Download Basilisk Browser 2025.10.10</title><pubDate> Fri, 10 Oct 2025 14:55:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-basilisk-browser-3923.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-basilisk-browser-3923.html
</guid><description>
Basilisk Browser is a browser based on the XUL free and has many features, provides the interface is well designed and simple manipulation. The program is built based on the tool output and layout of the Goanna and based on the platform XUL merge, similar to Mozilla Firefox. Basilisk Browser was created as a reference program for the development of the platform XUL. You can use this app in replacement for Mozilla Firefox. This utility includes support many types of features needed for...
</description></item><item><title>Download Waterfox 6.6.4 / 2022.11</title><pubDate> Fri, 10 Oct 2025 14:54:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-waterfox-114.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-waterfox-114.html
</guid><description>
Waterfox is a 64-bit version of the foundation Firefox was built and the compiler Intel is optimized for speed and performance on Windows systems.Waterfox does not add any additional features or bling, in fact, it will automatically import all the gadgets and install is have of you, so you will feel like at home when you run it the first time.All the add-on your Firefox will work with Waterfox, however, only support the plug-in more 64-bit, is includes Adobe Flash, Oracle Java and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Stardock Start11 2.5.6 Beta</title><pubDate> Fri, 10 Oct 2025 14:53:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stardock-start11-7029.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stardock-start11-7029.html
</guid><description>
Start11 is an application capable of customizing the Start Menu and Taskbar on Windows 11 and Windows 10. This is an application that allows users to customize Windows 11 to suit their preferences. his personal. Start11 will help you bring the new Start Menu of Windows 11 to Windows 10. And vice versa, Start11 also helps you to bring the Start Menu of Windows 10 to Windows 11.
Start11 also helps users bring some functions of Windows 10 to Windows 11 through customizing the Taskbar such...
</description></item></channel></rss>