<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 13:48:48 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 13:48:48 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro 15.26.0109</title><pubDate> Sat, 10 Jan 2026 16:38:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-videotube-downloader-pro-1276.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-videotube-downloader-pro-1276.html
</guid><description>
ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro is the professional version support download videos and playlists from YouTube, videos from Dailymotion, BBC iPlayer, ITV Player, ABC,  FOX,CBS.com Vimeo, Prosieben, Metacafe, Blip.tv CBC.ca many more video sites. After the video is downloaded, you can convert them to the formats compatible with iPad, iPhone, iPod, MPEG-4, H. 264, MP3, AC3.
ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro - Download videos on Youtube
This is one of the software download the most...
</description></item><item><title>Download Altium Designer 26.2.0.7</title><pubDate> Sat, 10 Jan 2026 16:37:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-altium-designer-01en-625.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-altium-designer-01en-625.html
</guid><description>
Altium Designer is the PCB design software (circuit board) professional helps you connect seamlessly with every aspect of design. Altium Designer is a within the automation software design, PCB and electronics for the motherboard in good and most popular today. It was developed by software company Altium Limited based in Australia.
Features Altium Designer:
	Analyzing the similar circuits using Spice.
	Have the perfect tool with the ability to simulate and debug the code and design...
</description></item><item><title>Download DBF Viewer 2000 8.95</title><pubDate> Sat, 10 Jan 2026 16:37:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbf-viewer-2000-7869.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbf-viewer-2000-7869.html
</guid><description>
DBF Viewer 2000 is a fast, efficient solution for viewing and editing all types of DBF files. It can handle files from dBase, Visual dBase, Foxpro, Visual FoxPro and Clipper, just to name a few, with performance that easily rivals expensive professional database utilities. DBF Viewer 2000 is extremely fast, does any task, just one simple query and cleanup copy to export data at lightning speed.
With DBF Editor's simple, dynamically generated visual dialogs, you can easily view the...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Downloader 10.1.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 10 Jan 2026 16:36:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html
</guid><description>
YTD Youtube Downloader is an application that reliable and intuitive, allowing you to quickly download YouTube videos and save them to your computer. You can also convert the media files to the format desired video or extract audio streams and save separately. YTD Youtube Downloader lets you save your favorite clips of yourself from Youtube, Facebook, Vimeo and Dailymotion to your desktop. The software supports URLS from many web site hosting, multimedia and allows you to download desired...
</description></item><item><title>Download TidyWindow 3.7.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 10 Jan 2026 16:12:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tidywindow-14454.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tidywindow-14454.html
</guid><description>
TidyWindow is a Windows desktop assistant that automates developer PC setup, cleanup, diagnostics, software package installation, registry tweaking, and driver updates—powered by a WPF interface and robust PowerShell 7 automation capabilities in the background.
Key Features
	Essentials Repair Center (docs/essentials.md): Queues selected automation tasks Filter for network, Defender, printing, and Windows Update issues. Each task supports preview run, sequential execution, restore...
</description></item><item><title>Download PortableApps.com Installer 3.9.6</title><pubDate> Sat, 10 Jan 2026 16:10:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-portableappscom-installer-7673.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-portableappscom-installer-7673.html
</guid><description>
PortableApps.com Installer is an easy-to-use multilingual installer that allows you to package your portable applications without writing code. PortableApps.com Installer can be run from a cloud folder, an external drive or a local folder without installing to Windows. It's even better with the PortableApps.com Platform for easy installation and automatic updates.
Features of PortableApps.com Installer
	Proven NSIS Installer Core
	Excellent compression for distribution
	Easy...
</description></item><item><title>Download GPS Photo: With Location &amp;amp; Map 4.2.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 10 Jan 2026 16:09:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-gps-photo-with-location-map-13457.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-gps-photo-with-location-map-13457.html
</guid><description>
Capture memories with precise geolocation and relive them with precise details using the powerful features of the GPS Camera Photo Location app. This Photo GPS Camera With Time Stamp app is designed to enhance your photos with detailed geolocation information and much more. Say goodbye to ordinary photos and enhance your memories with GPS Map Camera Location.
Experience the future of photo organization and geotagging with GPS Photo Location: Timestamp Camera, the perfect Photo GPS...
</description></item><item><title>Download Silent Camera [High Quality] 8.16.8</title><pubDate> Sat, 10 Jan 2026 16:09:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-silent-camera-10536.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-silent-camera-10536.html
</guid><description>
Introducing the best silent camera! Without the shutter sound, photos can be taken in complete silence! It also ranks number 1 among many silent cameras thanks to its high image quality! Take high-quality photos with the silent camera! You won't disturb anyone around you because the shutter sound can't be heard. You can take high-quality photos of any situation, such as your baby's cute sleeping face, your pet's natural behaviors, and words written on a blackboard!
Silent Camera...
</description></item><item><title>Download Solid Explorer File Manager 3.2.13 Build 200355</title><pubDate> Sat, 10 Jan 2026 16:08:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-solid-explorer-file-manager-8924.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-solid-explorer-file-manager-8924.html
</guid><description>
Solid Explorer is a file management application inspired by old file management applications. Solid Explorer is a popular file management app for Android devices that allows users to manage and organize their files and folders in an intuitive and user-friendly interface. It offers many features that make it stand out from other file management apps.
Solid Explorer allows you to navigate to files stored on your device and automatically organize them into collections. You can view,...
</description></item><item><title>Download TickTick:To Do List &amp;amp; Calendar 8.0.0.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 10 Jan 2026 16:08:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ticktick-to-do-list-tasks-8702.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ticktick-to-do-list-tasks-8702.html
</guid><description>
TickTick is a simple and effective task management and to-do list application that helps you schedule, manage time, remind about deadlines and organize your life at work, at home. home and everywhere else. TickTick is here to help you make the most of your day and get things done (gtd). Whether there's an idea you want to capture, a personal goal to achieve, a job to complete, or collaborating with other colleagues, even create a shopping list (with the help of a list creator). book)....
</description></item><item><title>Download VAG DPF 4.44.15</title><pubDate> Sat, 10 Jan 2026 16:08:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-vag-dpf-8892.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-vag-dpf-8892.html
</guid><description>
VAG DPF shows you the most important data related to the DPF particulate filter and its regeneration phases using the ELM327 Bluetooth/WiFi adapter. With this app you can find out whether the filter is actually in the regeneration process, if a regeneration is waiting to be completed, how many kilometers you have traveled since the last regeneration, etc.
Attention! This app only works with VAG (Audi Volkswagen SEAT SKODA) equipped with the engines listed below; For diesel engines not...
</description></item><item><title>Download Duolingo: language lessons 6.61.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 10 Jan 2026 16:07:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-duolingo-language-lessons-8265.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-duolingo-language-lessons-8265.html
</guid><description>
Duolingo is a popular language learning app that offers interactive lessons to help users learn new languages. This application offers many languages for you to choose from, including Spanish, French, German, Italian, Portuguese, Chinese, Japanese and many more.
This app offers an gamified learning experience with interactive lessons, exercises, and quizzes designed to help users learn new words, phrases, and grammar rules. This app is designed to be easy to use and suitable for people...
</description></item><item><title>Download Video Converter, Compressor 17.0.8</title><pubDate> Sat, 10 Jan 2026 16:07:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-video-converter-compressor-13301.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-video-converter-compressor-13301.html
</guid><description>
The fastest video converter and compressor on the market supports almost all video formats: MP4, MKV, AVI, 3GP, MOV, MTS, MPEG, MPG, WMV, M4V, VOB, FLV, etc. This converter and compressor supports converting, compressing, changing resolution, Frame Rate (FPS), bitrate of video files. It can also convert video files to audio formats like MP3, AAC, AC3, OGG, M4A, WAV, etc.
Key Features
	Convert and compress your videos to almost any video and audio format. Choose from predefined 4K to...
</description></item><item><title>Download IPTV Smarters Pro 5.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 10 Jan 2026 16:07:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-iptv-smarters-pro-13727.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-iptv-smarters-pro-13727.html
</guid><description>
IPTV Smarters Pro app is a Media Player app for Android TV, Android phones and Android tablets. Fully customizable and brandable for OTT service providers.
Features
	Xtream Codes API Support
	M3u File / URL Download Support
	Live Streaming, Movies, Series &amp;amp; Catchup IPTV HD TV is broadcasted through our IPTV app
	Support: EPG
	Parental Control
	Built-in powerful IPTV player
	Integrate external players
	More attractive &amp;amp; impressive interface and user-friendly
	Support: Dynamic...
</description></item><item><title>Download Music Folder Player Full 3.1.39</title><pubDate> Sat, 10 Jan 2026 16:06:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-music-folder-player-full-10481.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-music-folder-player-full-10481.html
</guid><description>
Music folder player created for people who don't like to see music displayed based on artist, album, track or playlist. If you like to organize your audio tracks in folders, this might be the right player for you.
Full features of Music Folder Player
	Material Design
	Three different home screen widgets (full version only)
	Continue where you left off. Archive for each folder where you left off
	Show folders as a 'flat' list if you have a small collection
	Show folder hierarchy like...
</description></item><item><title>Download WiFi Mouse Pro 5.7.6</title><pubDate> Sat, 10 Jan 2026 16:06:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wifi-mouse-pro-8925.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wifi-mouse-pro-8925.html
</guid><description>
Convert your phone into a wireless mouse, keyboard and trackpad for your computer, it allows you to control your PC/Mac/Linux easily via local network connection. Media Controller, Presentation Controller and Remote File Explorer are all included in this controller app.
Now you can relax on the sofa and control movies or games in the comfort of your own home, replacing your broken mouse and keyboard with this app.
Features of WiFi Mouse Pro
	Fully simulated mouse
	Built-in support...
</description></item><item><title>Download Librera PRO - Book reader 9.2.36</title><pubDate> Sat, 10 Jan 2026 16:06:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-librera-pro-all-my-books-9008.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-librera-pro-all-my-books-9008.html
</guid><description>
PRO Librera Reader is an easy-to-use and highly configurable reading application that supports most popular document formats, including: PDF, EPUB, EPUB3, MOBI, DjVu, FB2, FB2.zip, TXT, RTF, AZW, AZW3, CBR, CBZ, HTML, XPS, MHT and more. With a simple yet powerful interface, Librera Reader makes reading documents a real pleasure. Librera even has a unique hands-free, auto-scrolling music mode.
Some key features of Librera reader include:
Easily explore documents with optional and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Piktures: All-In-One Gallery 2.24 build 948</title><pubDate> Sat, 10 Jan 2026 16:05:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-piktures-gallery-photo-video-9523.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-piktures-gallery-photo-video-9523.html
</guid><description>
Piktures is a simple photo gallery app with very advanced features. It supports dozens of cloud services like Google Drive and Microsoft Onedrive, your personal cloud server (WebDav), SD Cards, USB drives and even your computer! Piktures allows you to view your photos in grid, mosaic and list views. Organize them the way you like.
Features of Piktures
	Fast: Piktures has its own rendering engine so you can view photos very quickly.
	Secret Space: The secure space protects your most...
</description></item><item><title>Download Habitify: Habit Tracker 32.0.8</title><pubDate> Sat, 10 Jan 2026 16:04:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-habitify-habit-tracker-8612.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-habitify-habit-tracker-8612.html
</guid><description>
Habitify is an easy-to-use and award-winning habit tracker that helps remind and motivate you to stick to your daily habits, track your progress, and reward you for achievements nice. With our minimalist and intuitive design, the Habitify habit tracker is here to make building and monitoring your habits more effective and completely effortless.
Features of Habitify: Habit Tracker
	Habit management: create, organize, perfect and unlearn habits
	Customizable routine and routine area...
</description></item><item><title>Download SayIt: Read with Ears 4.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 10 Jan 2026 16:04:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sayit-read-with-ears-13730.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sayit-read-with-ears-13730.html
</guid><description>
SayIt: Read with Ears is an app designed to enhance the reading experience by converting text to natural speech. It's especially useful for people who want to listen to written content on the go, such as articles, books, documents, or web pages.
Want to say it? Share with SayIt!
	Turn any text selection, article or web page into a Podcast
	Any PDF, EPUB or MOBI (Kindle) eBook into an Audiobook
	Translate instantly into your language
	Learn another language with bilingual...
</description></item><item><title>Download Podcast Republic - Podcast app 26.1.5R</title><pubDate> Sat, 10 Jan 2026 16:03:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-podcast-republic-podcast-app-8131.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-podcast-republic-podcast-app-8131.html
</guid><description>
Podcast Republic is a podcast app that allows users to discover, download and listen to podcasts on their mobile devices. Podcast Republic is a top quality Podcast App on Android with 4+ million downloads, 76k+ authentic reviews, 600k+ podcasts, and 40+ million episodes worldwide. It offers features like automatic downloading, variable playback speed, and the ability to create and manage playlists. Podcast Republic also supports Android Auto and Chromecast, so you can listen to podcasts...
</description></item><item><title>Download Graphing Calculator - Algeo 2.48</title><pubDate> Sat, 10 Jan 2026 16:03:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-graphing-calculator-algeo-8784.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-graphing-calculator-algeo-8784.html
</guid><description>
Algeo is the most beautiful scientific graphing calculator available on the Play Store. It's fast and powerful and you'll never have to carry a large physical TI calculator again. The intuitive interface displays your drawn functions as if you wrote them on paper instead of putting everything on one line. And you don't need an internet connection unlike other graphing calculators, it works offline too! Useful for calculus, physics or solving those x+y equations.
This free app has more...
</description></item><item><title>Download Daily Yoga ®: Yoga for Fitness 8.84.00</title><pubDate> Sat, 10 Jan 2026 16:03:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-daily-yoga-yoga-for-fitness-13391.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-daily-yoga-yoga-for-fitness-13391.html
</guid><description>
Do you want to find both fitness yoga and meditation videos in one app? Daily Yoga is a platform that provides health benefits for both your mind and body with a variety of yoga poses, guided yoga classes, and weight loss yoga challenges. Start your day with yoga, increase flexibility and balance, improve performance in daily activities, maintain good posture and stay healthy!
Features
	Daily Yoga offers different yoga courses and poses for weight loss. There are easy and effective...
</description></item><item><title>Download Square Home 3.4.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 10 Jan 2026 16:02:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-square-home-8744.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-square-home-8744.html
</guid><description>
Square Home is an Android launcher app that allows users to customize their Android device's home screen with various themes, layouts, and widgets. Square Home is the best launcher with Windows 10 metro UI. Easy to use, simple, beautiful and powerful for any phone, tablet and TV box.
	This app uses Device Administrator permissions. If your Android version is lower than 9.0, you should grant permission to perform the launcher's "screen lock" action.
	This app only uses the Accessibility...
</description></item><item><title>Download FTP Rush 3.6.6</title><pubDate> Sat, 10 Jan 2026 16:01:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ftp-rush-6410.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ftp-rush-6410.html
</guid><description>
FTP Rush is a free transfer software for Windows, Mac, Linux, Android and iOS. And it ' s not just the FTP/SFTP client app but also the cloud hosting app (supporting Google Drive, DropBox, OneDrive and Amazon S3). With the Explorer-like interface on the card, you can create multiple tabs on the card for different connections and easily download or load files up through the Pull &amp;amp; Drop. It uses a local computer as a bridge to perform the transfer function between the servers of...
</description></item></channel></rss>