<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:17:51 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:17:51 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download CyberLink PowerDirector Ultimate 2026 v24.1.1402.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 01:58:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-powerdirector-ultimate-425.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-powerdirector-ultimate-425.html
</guid><description>
CyberLink PowerDirector Ultimate is software editor, edit video and make movies on the computer from a variety of templates are made available, complete with effects, transitions, animations, and music. CyberLink PowerDirector 17 is a combination of video editing software with advanced video editing features powerful. Cblowing need to add your clips into the time line and click on 'Production'!
The tool design video in CyberLink PowerDirector have the ability to customize helps you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ashampoo Music Studio 12.0.4</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 01:58:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-music-studio-1207.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-music-studio-1207.html
</guid><description>
Ashampoo Music Studio is software to work with audio files. Includes the process of taking the disc recording CD, DVD and Blu-ray discs module to organize music collections, editing audio files, recording module and the tool to restore audio files broken.
Ashampoo Music Studio
Functions of Ashampoo Music Studio
	Edit audio files quickly
	Cut perfect slices including direct recording
	Convert to any format and listen anywhere
	The most convenient tool to extract CD
	Create a list from...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ratiborus KMS Tools Lite 03.02.2026</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 01:57:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ratiborus-kms-tools-lite-11160.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ratiborus-kms-tools-lite-11160.html
</guid><description>
Ratiborus KMS Tools Lite is a collection of activators from Ratiborus for Windows XP, Vista, 7, 8, 8.1, 10, 11, Windows Server, Office 2010/2013/2016/2019 /2021/2024. It includes several utilities, each with its own set of features, mainly aimed at activating Microsoft Windows and Office products. The program is used to activate Microsoft products such as Windows and Office using Key Management Service (KMS). With a simple, easy-to-use interface that allows users to activate the product...
</description></item><item><title>Download PhraseExpander Professional 5.9.9.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 01:57:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-phraseexpander-professional-10882.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-phraseexpander-professional-10882.html
</guid><description>
PhraseExpander Professional is a versatile software designed to streamline and automate typing tasks, allowing professionals to work more efficiently. Store all common medical terms, formulas, and forms in a single place and pull them up instantly by entering an acronym. It supports creating and managing custom text paragraphs, templates and phrases, which can be activated with keyboard shortcuts or abbreviations, saving time and reducing repetitive typing. This tool is commonly used in...
</description></item><item><title>Download QILING Disk Master Professional 8.7.5</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 01:56:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qiling-disk-master-professional-4826.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qiling-disk-master-professional-4826.html
</guid><description>
QILING Disk Master provides powerful tools recover lost data and restore the broken system in few minutes. There is software to restore data &amp;amp; backup systems, reliable and advanced system for desktop and laptops at homes and businesses. It allows the user to perform the operation backup service and backup the entire / difference / increase in comprehensive.
The features of QILING Disk Master
	Backup and system protection (image)
	Backup and restore files
	Compressed file...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube Downloader 3.9.18 (0202)</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 01:56:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-downloader-279.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube Downloader  is a dedicated software that helps users  downloading youtube videos  Favorites on PC for offline viewing. With MediaHuman YouTube  Downloader  you can download videos from youtube website to your computer with  fast speed , with special software development technology that automatically receives videos from Websites, in addition to the ability to download videos from software websites, can convert downloaded video formats to various formats for the purpose...
</description></item><item><title>Download BeeCut 1.7.11.8</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 01:55:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-beecut-4660.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-beecut-4660.html
</guid><description>
BeeCut is software support to create a stunning video from the footage you have taken with his phone, ready to be posted on the media social or blogs, use this app. BeeCut is a video editing tool, lightweight but rich in features designed to help you enhance the media before its publication or upload. Packing hundreds of filters and templates, tools can be useful for many situations.
The program comes with a modern interface and sleek is also well organized and does not have the ability...
</description></item><item><title>Download Secret Disk Pro 2026 v318</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 01:55:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secret-disk-pro-933.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secret-disk-pro-933.html
</guid><description>
Secret Disk Pro 4 is a software to create a virtual disk can be hidden and password protected to keep your data private and safe. You can store any file and folder on the disk. Disc secret works like a hard disk typically, and is compatible with any any other program that you have installed. You can have more than one disk secret, and you can also choose disk letter.
Secret Disk Pro 4 - Create and secure drive
Secret Disk does not encrypt any files, it just limits access to your files...
</description></item><item><title>Download QILING Disk Master Technician 8.7.5</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 01:54:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qiling-disk-master-technician-4828.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qiling-disk-master-technician-4828.html
</guid><description>
QILING Disk Master Technician is the complete tool to simplify the management partition and move the OS and software backup &amp;amp; recovery for IT admins, technicians and consultants. With simple interface and easy to use, anyone, even users with no technical, can protect all business data important in the last few minutes to ensure business continuity without the need to have experts. In addition, It also support to check the health of the hard disk, edit questions startup permanently...
</description></item><item><title>Download QueueExplorer Professional 5.0.66</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 01:54:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-queueexplorer-professional-4823.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-queueexplorer-professional-4823.html
</guid><description>
QueueExplorer is a tool indispensable to work with queues and messages: understand and manage your system, find the error and fix it. Or you can use QueueExplorer to sort them by any field available. Because of the sort display the messages in another order with them will be handled, QueueExplorer more columns of Ms Ms # # so you can still see what is processed first.
The features of QueueExplorer
Move, copy or delete messages
	Messages can be handled the same as in process explorer,...
</description></item><item><title>Download QILING Disk Master Server 8.7.5</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 01:54:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qiling-disk-master-server-4827.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qiling-disk-master-server-4827.html
</guid><description>
QILING Disk Master Server support, backup, data recovery, along with many attractive features other. QILING Disk Master Server data recovery &amp;amp; backup system reliable and advanced system for desktop and laptops at homes and businesses. It allows the user to perform the operation backup service and backup the entire / difference / increase in comprehensive for your server.
QILING Disk Master Server support to fully recover, the content is not deformed in comparison with document,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tower 11.1.546</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 01:53:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tower-6598.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tower-6598.html
</guid><description>
Tower is software that helps you build better software, over 100,000 developers and designers are more productive with Tower, the most powerful Git client for Mac and Windows.
Tower Features
	Beautiful new features like interactive facility or Quick Actions and tons of improvements
	Undo everything
	Unique Conflict Wizard
	File history
	Rich documents
	Great customer support...
	Tower helps you master version control with Git.
	One-click cloning
	Automatically store and fetch
	Quickly...
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 7.9.6</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 01:16:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-11-7760.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-11-7760.html
</guid><description>
TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 is a program that allows users to discover hidden settings in Windows 11. This application is specially designed for Windows 11, groups many registry settings and distribute them from the easy and secure user interface. With TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 you can move the Windows taskbar to the top and resize the taskbar by editing the registry value. With any application that modifies the registry, we recommend that you have a backup copy...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare PDFelement Pro 12.1.10.4005</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 01:16:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-pdfelement-pro-105.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-pdfelement-pro-105.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare PDFelement Pro support users to convert PDF to office documents for easier use, modify in every situation. Is one of the software conversion material is rated best today, integrated with many features. We recommend that you should use experience software many useful features this.
Wondershare PDFelement Pro - conversion Fie PDF more features, multi-language
Wondershare PDFelement Pro what?
Convert PDF into Word, Excel, PowerPoint...
• Convert PDF and protected PDF into...
</description></item><item><title>Download AITextTune 1.6.9</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 01:15:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aitexttune-12973.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aitexttune-12973.html
</guid><description>
AITextTune is an AI-powered tool designed to enhance and refine text content. It offers features such as improving clarity and coherence, generating summaries, and translating text into multiple languages. Users can easily adjust their writing style from formal to creative. This tool is very flexible and can be used on many different software and platforms.
AITextTune Features
	WRITE PERFECTLY: Improve the clarity and coherence of your writing! Create summaries and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare Recoverit 14.0.16.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 01:14:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-recoverits-374.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-recoverits-374.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare Recoverit is a data recovery software that is easily lost at a rapid rate and is used by many people. You will do what happens if one day your data is suddenly lost due to the virus or deleted it, .. Wondershare Recoverit will provide you with an environment to protect important data.
Wondershare Recoverit has all the scanning processes that are divided into multiple types, from the typical recovery of the deleted files that are deleted to the recovery of missing files due...
</description></item><item><title>Download Astute Graphics Plug-ins Elite Bundle 4.4.3</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 01:14:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-astute-graphics-plug-ins-elite-bundle-5523.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-astute-graphics-plug-ins-elite-bundle-5523.html
</guid><description>
Astute Graphics Plug-ins Elite Bundle is a set of graphics editing tools for Adobe Illustrator. It includes many unique tools like Phantasm, VectorScribe, WidthScribe and many others. Get the complete set of plug-ins and transform your workflow in Illustrator. Add speed, ease, and precision with all our plug-ins and become the Astute Graphics Plug-in Elite Package!
Astute Graphics Plug-ins Elite Bundle Features:
	Correct alignment + selection
	Sketching visual vector
	Instantly...
</description></item><item><title>Download Avast Premium Security 26.1.10738</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 01:13:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avast-premier-antivirus-security-1359.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avast-premier-antivirus-security-1359.html
</guid><description>
Avast! Premier Antivirus is antivirus software famous by combining all the technologies and methods virus advanced. The developer software this anti-virus have invested in all their knowledge about fighting viruses to create one of the software anti-virus best. Program anti-virus this combines all the technology and advanced methods to get the level of computer security highest. This product is ideal for all the Windows operating system.
Avast! Premier Antivirus - antivirus...
</description></item><item><title>Download Logo Design Studio Pro Vector Edition 2.0.5.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 01:12:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-logo-design-studio-pro-vector-edition-2276.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-logo-design-studio-pro-vector-edition-2276.html
</guid><description>
Logo Design Studio is software design logo number 1 best-selling in 17 years! You know your business, we know the logo. In the past years, we have helped thousands of businesses new and existing to create their logo by providing the tools, objects, sources of inspiration and guidance necessary to create a unique logo that is personal and professional. Logo Design Studio Pro software logo design selling number 1 in more than 17 years and we want you to join the action.
Logo Design Studio...
</description></item><item><title>Download iTop Easy Desktop 4.1.0.274</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 01:09:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-itop-easy-desktop-7879.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-itop-easy-desktop-7879.html
</guid><description>
iTop Easy Desktop is a lightweight and easy-to-use desktop manager that organizes desktop icons, files and folders according to your rules, helping you Freed from the tedious arrangement of icons on the screen. It provides various practical features including but not limited to grouping desktop items, awakening live search, and quickly accessing icons and files even across multiple desktop sites. desktop.
Untidy desktop If you're not one to diligently organize your Windows desktop icons...
</description></item><item><title>Download Syncthing 2.0.14</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 01:09:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncthing-2115.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncthing-2115.html
</guid><description>
Syncthing is synchronization service, cloud and open and non-focus allows you to share and sync files with other computers and gives you full control how to share your data and who can access it. Syncthing does not store your data in any other place, there is no server side Tuesday how to join. In addition, all the communication is secured by TLS and every button is determined by the certificate the strength of the encryption. Only computers that have explicitly allowed can connect with...
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 7.9.6</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 01:08:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-10-7759.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-10-7759.html
</guid><description>
TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 is a utility that allows users to discover hidden settings in Windows 10. This application is specially designed for Windows 10, groups many registry settings and provide them from an easy and secure user interface. With TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 you can move the Windows taskbar to the top and resize the taskbar by editing the registry value. With any application that modifies the registry, we recommend that you have a backup copy to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Lyric Video Studio 1.5.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 01:07:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lyric-video-studio-13581.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lyric-video-studio-13581.html
</guid><description>
Lyric Video Studio is a powerful, feature-rich video editor specifically designed to create lyric videos, music videos, and visualizers with ease. It integrates simple and effective text tools along with generative AI capabilities to streamline the video creation process. Whether you're a musician launching a killer new track, a content creator, or just love playing with visuals, this app lets you sync your lyrics to your music in just a few clicks. Enter lyrics, drag to sync and you're...
</description></item><item><title>Download WonderFox HD Video Converter Factory Pro 28.4</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 01:05:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hd-video-converter-factory-pro-1458.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hd-video-converter-factory-pro-1458.html
</guid><description>
WonderFox HD Video Converter Factory Pro is a software powerful video conversion . This program can convert the video files the quality standard of the file SD card, the files HD as HD MP4, HD MKV, HD AVI, HD MTS, HD TRP. This can also in the opposite direction. This software includes more than 100 video formats, while maintaining quality output, faster than 50 times compared to some software. This software also supports VBR or VBR, using this option will keep the original quality of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download MusConv 4.10.451 Lifetime</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 01:04:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html
</guid><description>
MusConv transfers playlists, albums, followed artists and liked songs across a variety of services – Spotify, Apple Music, Amazon Music, YouTube, YouTube Music, iTunes, Deezer, Tidal, SoundCloud, Pandora and more 125 music services!
Features of MusConv Ultimate
	Transfer playlists, albums, followed artists and liked tracks between over 125 music servicesManage playlists (Delete, Merge, Split, Copy...)
	More than 125 music services supported
	Access DAILY updated music charts on...
</description></item></channel></rss>