<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 05:30:07 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 05:30:07 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Right-Click Uninstall 1.1.82</title><pubDate> Sun, 12 Oct 2025 00:07:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-right-click-uninstall-11474.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-right-click-uninstall-11474.html
</guid><description>
Uninstall apps easily
With Right-Click Uninstall, you can easily uninstall a program directly from the program's context menu. You won't have to use Add/Remove Programs or any third-party tools to find out which programs you need to uninstall.
Safe and easy to use
Right-Click Uninstall is a completely free and safe application that allows you to uninstall programs easily. This application is very easy to use thanks to its simple and innovative user interface.
Light &amp;amp;...
</description></item><item><title>Download LibreOffice 25.8.2 / 7.6.7</title><pubDate> Sun, 12 Oct 2025 00:06:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-libreoffice-391.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-libreoffice-391.html
</guid><description>
LibreOffice is editor free for office similar to MS Office and OpenOffice includes word processor, spreadsheet application, presentation tool, database and design diagrams. Here is the app code open source, multi-feature, to offer users many tools to draft documents and handle the office documents efficiently.
The program can open or import most Microsoft Office formats popular, including .doc .ppt and .csv as well as many document formats other. LibreOffice is a tool to be more user...
</description></item><item><title>Download Topaz Video AI Pro 7.1.6 / 1.0.3</title><pubDate> Sun, 12 Oct 2025 00:00:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-video-enhance-ai-3733.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-video-enhance-ai-3733.html
</guid><description>
Topaz Video Enhance AI is a tool to increase video quality with this great technology ONE. Topaz Video Enhance WHO wide open your video to resolutions up to 8K with the details and consistency of motion. Until the present, there is no way to re-create a perfect high resolution video from the footage is low resolution. From the family film to SD low quality to DVD quality and more than that, Video Enhance WHO will convert your video into the footage is upgrade clear with resolutions up to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare Recoverit 14.0.1.4</title><pubDate> Sun, 12 Oct 2025 00:00:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-recoverits-374.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-recoverits-374.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare Recoverit is a data recovery software that is easily lost at a rapid rate and is used by many people. You will do what happens if one day your data is suddenly lost due to the virus or deleted it, .. Wondershare Recoverit will provide you with an environment to protect important data.
Wondershare Recoverit has all the scanning processes that are divided into multiple types, from the typical recovery of the deleted files that are deleted to the recovery of missing files due...
</description></item><item><title>Download AOMEI Partition Assistant Professional 10.9.1 + Technician + Unlimited + Server</title><pubDate> Sat, 11 Oct 2025 23:59:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aomei-partition-assistant-281.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aomei-partition-assistant-281.html
</guid><description>
AOMEI Partition Assistant is partition software hard disk all in one easy to use, offers many features partition manager free. AOMEI Partition Assistant to ensure the full features to create, resize, move, copy, delete, delete, align, format, merge, split partitions.
AOMEI Partition Assistant
AOMEI Partition Manager enables you to expand the available space on hard disk quickly for improve the capacity for the root partition. The instructions move smart can easily support you move the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Chaos V-Ray 7.2 Build 7.20.00 for SketchUp 2021 - 2025</title><pubDate> Sat, 11 Oct 2025 23:58:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vray-for-sketchup-3936.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vray-for-sketchup-3936.html
</guid><description>
V-Ray Next for SketchUp is the tool of Chaos Group for Windows PC, this is a lighting tool and as a professional for architects &amp;amp; designers.V-Ray Next for SketchUp allows you to export everything and everything - from the design models to the 3D scene details most of you. Use V-Ray for SketchUp, you can also have access to over 600 documents actual photo, drag and drop. V-Ray Next for SketchUp is very easy to use and brings great results. You can use it to create everything - from 3D...
</description></item><item><title>Download Active Boot Disk 25.2.1a</title><pubDate> Sat, 11 Oct 2025 23:57:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-active-boot-disk-2509.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-active-boot-disk-2509.html
</guid><description>
Active Boot Disk is a computer operating system complete and the operation on CD / DVD / USB. Active@ Boot Disk does not modify the operating system already installed on the hard drive of the computer. It includes many tools to boot up a computer and boot repair most computer configuration and the problem management system.
Active Boot Disk - boot Disk windows
Software Active Boot Disk is a boot disk can run on the computer have installed the OS. Please note that this disc includes...
</description></item><item><title>Download Chaos V-Ray 7.2 Build 7.20.00 for Rhinoceros 7-9</title><pubDate> Sat, 11 Oct 2025 23:56:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-v-ray-next-for-rhino-1285.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-v-ray-next-for-rhino-1285.html
</guid><description>
V-Ray Next For Rhino is an extension a very powerful and handy for Rhino can be used to improve the process output. V-Ray Next allows you to achieve much achievement in Rhino than ever. It's faster to showcase your designs in the best light of them. And a variety of new tools to help manage and display the sight of you much easier.
V-Ray Next For Rhino
V-Ray Next in for Rhino comes with some speed on the table. Optimize performance, speed up the production up to 50% off. The shader...
</description></item><item><title>Download AOMEI Partition Assistant WinPE 10.9.1 Professional</title><pubDate> Sat, 11 Oct 2025 23:55:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aomei-partition-assistant-technician-winpe-5836.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aomei-partition-assistant-technician-winpe-5836.html
</guid><description>
AOMEI Partition Assistant Technician is specifically designed for IT professionals, system administrators, technicians, and consultants to serve new revenue streams through the provision of charge engineering services to their customers. It is an independent and valuable solid disk partition management tool. In addition, it is available for internal use to manage PC groups and large distributed servers at various locations.
Version AOMEI Partition Assistant Technician includes all of...
</description></item><item><title>Download MainConcept Codec Plugin for DaVinci Resolve 1.7.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 11 Oct 2025 23:55:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mainconcept-codec-plugin-for-davinci-resolve-10638.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mainconcept-codec-plugin-for-davinci-resolve-10638.html
</guid><description>
MainConcept Codec Plugin for DaVinci Resolve includes the entire production chain—from filming, recording, and editing to live streaming—possibly remaining in the same broadcast format. This speeds up your workflow and delivers the reliability that comes with MainConcept's experience powering the digital universe for nearly three decades. Creators can now easily render project timelines from DaVinci Resolve Studio 17 and above to professional camera formats from Sony, Panasonic and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Reportizer 6.5.11.293</title><pubDate> Sat, 11 Oct 2025 23:54:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reportizer-5205.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reportizer-5205.html
</guid><description>
Reportizer is a tools report database. Easily create, modify, and print reports database. Allows to manage collection reports. Support database BDE or ADO. Tested on dBase (DBF), Paradox (DB), Text (TXT), the values are separated by commas (CSV), Oracle, Interbase, Microsoft Access, Microsoft Excel, SQL Server, Visual FoxPro, MySQL, PostgreQuery, HTML.
The design reports visually. Reports can be edited in the report design, intuitive and convenient with the toolbar and powerful tool. For...
</description></item><item><title>Download dslrBooth Photo Booth Software Pro 7.49.2.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 11 Oct 2025 23:53:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dslrbooth-photo-booth-software-666.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dslrbooth-photo-booth-software-666.html
</guid><description>
Photo Booth Software is a software to create, list and combine the images back together in the same theme as travel, haloween. Created by the professional photographer for the operator photo booth at all skill levels, photo booth software dslrBooth built from scratch with the sole purpose of running the photo booth. The software uses the latest technology to provide you and your guests, high quality prints and the ability to share photos and GIF on the means of social media including...
</description></item><item><title>Download Nomad Factory 80s Spaces 2.5.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 11 Oct 2025 23:52:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nomad-factory-80s-spaces-9464.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nomad-factory-80s-spaces-9464.html
</guid><description>
Nomad Factory 80s Spaces is a digital reverb plugin developed by Nomad Factory, a company known for creating audio processing software and plugins for professional audio production. . The 80s Spaces plugin aims to recreate the reverberation and atmosphere characteristics of the 1980s, giving users a nostalgic sound reminiscent of that era.
It's worth noting that Nomad Factory 80s Spaces is a software plugin designed for use in digital audio workstations (DAWs) or audio editing software....
</description></item><item><title>Download Minimal Firewall 2.5</title><pubDate> Sat, 11 Oct 2025 23:52:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minimal-firewall-13877.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minimal-firewall-13877.html
</guid><description>
Minimal Firewall works in conjunction with Windows Firewall to block all unknown connections by default, prompting you to create application-based rules to mitigate malware, telemetry, and data leaks. Completely eliminate applications that call home without your knowledge. Minimal Firewall provides a more secure and integrated approach by interacting directly with the native Windows Firewall, eliminating the need for risky system modifications.
Core Features
	Lockdown Mode: The core...
</description></item><item><title>Download PanFone Data Transfer 1.5.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 11 Oct 2025 23:51:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-panfone-data-transfer-5582.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-panfone-data-transfer-5582.html
</guid><description>
PanFone Data Transfer is this phone-to-phone transfer tool that provides you with an optimal transfer solution between iOS and Android devices. With the help of PanFone Data Transfer software feature you can backup iOS and Android devices to your computer in a few clicks without iTunes or iCloud. PanFone will never overwrite your backup files. You can also restore the backup to any device at any time.
Transferring data from old phone to new phone also allows you to transfer music, videos,...
</description></item><item><title>Download TapinRadio Pro 2.16.11</title><pubDate> Sat, 11 Oct 2025 23:45:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tapinradio-pro-735.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tapinradio-pro-735.html
</guid><description>
TapinRadio Pro is a professional software used to listen to the radio there are many channels to choose from and continuously updated. TapinRadio supports most of the formats internet radio - mp3, wma, ogg, aac. This is a powerful tool for you to capture information in the world and in country in the fastest and simplest.
TapinRadio Pro - Listen To The Radio
Features of TapinRadio Pro
	A lot of stations to choose from
	Supports most of the formats internet radio - mp3, wma, vorbis...
</description></item><item><title>Download KDEnlive 25.08.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 11 Oct 2025 23:44:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kdenlive-3288.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kdenlive-3288.html
</guid><description>
Kdenlive is a video editor open source. The project was started in about 2003. Kdenlive is built on the Qt libraries and the KDE Frameworks. Most of the video processing is done by the MLT Framework, based on many open-source projects other as FFmpeg , frei0r , Movit, ladspa, sox, etc.
KDEnlive - video editing quickly
Our software is designed to meet most needs, from basic video editing to professional work. Kdenlive allows you to use and arrange a number of music and video, each can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Fort Firewall 3.19.9</title><pubDate> Sat, 11 Oct 2025 23:44:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fort-firewall-6439.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fort-firewall-6439.html
</guid><description>
Fort Firewall is a network security system that monitors and controls network traffic and goes based on predefined security rules. A firewall often establishes a barrier between a trusted internal network and untrusted external networks, such as the Internet.
Features of Fort Firewall
	Filter by network address, application group
	Support of representative characters in the name path name
	Application group speed limit
	Access Traffic Statistics
	Display bandwidth
	Based on the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Rocrail Build 6181</title><pubDate> Sat, 11 Oct 2025 23:44:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rocrail-3193.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rocrail-3193.html
</guid><description>
Rocrail is a free software to control the training model for the operating system Linux , Apple macOS , Windows and Raspbian / Armbian . Rocrail bear all responsibility in the control of a railway model, and accessories of them. Trains can be controlled manually or fully controlled by software in automatic mode. A mixed operation, i.e. control a number of ships and other vessels at high speed fully automatic is possible.
Rocrail - control layout for the operating system
With Rocrail,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Kazrog Avalon EQ Bundle 1.0.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 11 Oct 2025 23:42:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kazrog-avalon-eq-bundle-13859.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kazrog-avalon-eq-bundle-13859.html
</guid><description>
Kazrog Avalon EQ Bundle is a plugin package that digitally emulates two legendary Avalon equalizers: the AD2077 master equalizer and the AD2055 parametric equalizer, both discontinued hardware units, renowned for their pristine analog sound quality. This package delivers the full Avalon EQ experience, from mastering precision to powerful program shaping.
Key features include:
	Advanced Analog Modeling: Plugins replicate the unique sonic characteristics of the original hardware with...
</description></item><item><title>Download PlayerPro Music Player 5.39 build 243</title><pubDate> Sat, 11 Oct 2025 23:33:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-playerpro-music-player-9862.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-playerpro-music-player-9862.html
</guid><description>
PlayerPro Music Player is a feature-rich music player application available for Android devices. It is developed by BlastOn SA and offers a comprehensive set of features designed to enhance the music listening experience. PlayerPro features a beautiful, fast and intuitive interface, alongside powerful audio configuration options. In addition, there is a choice of several free plugins to complement it: Skins, DSP Pack...
Features of PlayerPro Music Player
	Browse and play your music in...
</description></item><item><title>Download Zero Cleaner: clear cache 4.1.5</title><pubDate> Sat, 11 Oct 2025 23:33:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-zero-cleaner-clear-cache-10667.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-zero-cleaner-clear-cache-10667.html
</guid><description>
Zero Cleaner is a mobile application that specializes in removing cache files from your device. Cache files are temporary data stored by applications and websites to improve their performance and load times. Over time, cache files can accumulate and take up valuable storage space on your device.
Some key features of Zero Cleaner include:
	Cache Cleaner: The app will scan your device for cache files created by apps and web browsers, allowing you to clear them with just a tap. This...
</description></item><item><title>Download Fast Photo Gallery Pro: F-Stop 5.5.480</title><pubDate> Sat, 11 Oct 2025 23:32:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-f-stop-gallery-8357.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-f-stop-gallery-8357.html
</guid><description>
Replace your bulky storage library with a light, fast (even fun) library that helps you organize all the photos and videos on your device. F-Stop is an alternative image library that gives you professional tools and a clean Material Design interface that makes organizing your photos a breeze.
F Stop Library Features
	Fully optimized for Android 7.0+ including material design
	Instantly search through all your photos to find results based on filename and metadata (tags, ratings, camera...
</description></item><item><title>Download Device Info: System &amp;amp; CPU Info 3.4.0.5</title><pubDate> Sat, 11 Oct 2025 23:32:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-device-info-system-cpu-info-8723.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-device-info-system-cpu-info-8723.html
</guid><description>
Device Information: System &amp;amp; CPU Information is a mobile application that provides users with detailed information about the hardware and software specifications of their device. This app is designed to help users better understand their device's capabilities and performance as well as diagnose any potential issues or problems.
With Device Info: System and CPU Info, users can view information about the processor, memory, storage, battery, sensors, and more. of equipment. This app...
</description></item><item><title>Download Chomp SMS 9.26 build 9092666</title><pubDate> Sat, 11 Oct 2025 23:31:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-chomp-sms-8403.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-chomp-sms-8403.html
</guid><description>
Comes with many great features, especially passcode app lock, privacy options, scheduled SMS sender (reminders, birthday wishes), stopping messages while sending , pin favorites to top, backup, SMS blacklist/blocker, signature, excerpt text, quick reply popup (even on lock screen), multi-select photo gallery, dual sim, better MMS and GROUP messaging, etc...
Plus unlimited customization options for LED color, ringtone, vibration pattern, screen color, font type, font size and wallpaper....
</description></item></channel></rss>