<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 00:10:42 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 00:10:42 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download RegCool 3.0.0.5</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 00:24:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-regcool-42.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-regcool-42.html
</guid><description>
RegCool is a powerful and user-friendly registry editor for Windows operating systems. The registry is an important part of the Windows operating system, containing important settings and configurations that determine how your computer functions. With RegCool, users can easily navigate, edit, and manage registry keys and values, making it a valuable tool for advanced users and IT professionals.
RegCool's main features:
	User-friendly interface: RegCool has a clear and intuitive user...
</description></item><item><title>Download O&amp;amp;O ShutUp10++ 2.2.1024</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 00:24:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-shutup10-1535.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-shutup10-1535.html
</guid><description>
O&amp;amp;O ShutUp10 is software that puts you in full control of today's latest Windows 10 and Windows 11 features, it's up to you to decide what information to pass on Windows 10 or Windows 11. Using a simple user interface, this program disables the parts of Windows 10 and Windows 11 that don't want to receive and send your data. The program is completely free and requires no installation, and once downloaded, you can run it immediately. The program does not install adware and spam software...
</description></item><item><title>Download LibreOffice 26.2.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 00:23:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-libreoffice-391.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-libreoffice-391.html
</guid><description>
LibreOffice is editor free for office similar to MS Office and OpenOffice includes word processor, spreadsheet application, presentation tool, database and design diagrams. Here is the app code open source, multi-feature, to offer users many tools to draft documents and handle the office documents efficiently.
The program can open or import most Microsoft Office formats popular, including .doc .ppt and .csv as well as many document formats other. LibreOffice is a tool to be more user...
</description></item><item><title>Download Office Installer Plus 1.35</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 00:22:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-installer-plus-11616.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-installer-plus-11616.html
</guid><description>
Office Installer Plus is the next version of Ratiborus that helps you download, install, update, uninstall, activate office 2024, 2021, 2019, 2016 and it has added an Office activator to the program. submit. Office Installer+ is considered a useful application that helps users install and manage office applications from Microsoft Office easily and quickly. This application is designed to help users save time and effort when installing popular office applications such as Word, Excel,...
</description></item><item><title>Download JRiver Media Center 35.0.42</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 00:21:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jriver-media-center-110.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jriver-media-center-110.html
</guid><description>
JRiver Media Center can help you strictly manage all your files media and enjoy them in a completely new way. Launching the application for the first time, users will be immediately impressed with the intuitive and eye-catching interface with many interesting features to explore. Most people who have used JRiver Media Center evaluate that the software interface design is youthful and modern.
The software for arranging cover art of music files is also extremely neat, especially Insert...
</description></item><item><title>Download Office Installer by Ratiborus 1.35</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 00:21:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-installer-11545.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-installer-11545.html
</guid><description>
Office Installer is a software program by Ratiborus used to install Microsoft Office on computers or devices. Office is a productivity suite that includes programs like Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Outlook, and more. The installer ensures that all required Microsoft Office files and components are installed, properly configured, and ready for use on the user's computer.
Office Installer allows users to choose which Office applications they want to install, select the installation location,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Aeon Timeline 3.5.39</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 00:20:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aeon-timeline-4952.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aeon-timeline-4952.html
</guid><description>
Aeon Timeline is a tool line-time for creative thinking. Most of the application time line traditional designed to suit a single need: to create attractive screen on time one way. They are present, static, and perfectly aligned with the slide and overhead projector.
With Aeon Timeline, you can split your timeline into logical groups, projects or arcs at the same time. You can model the relationships between events and people, places, and ideas. Aeon calculate ages of people for you. And...
</description></item><item><title>Download Aidfile Recovery Software Professional 3.7.9.5</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 00:20:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aidfile-recovery-software-professional-4316.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aidfile-recovery-software-professional-4316.html
</guid><description>
Aidfile Recovery Software Professional is a software small but powerful will assist you to recover files lost, deleted or damaged. It is ideal to restore data such as videos, files, office, images, folders and many other things. Professional tool this will help you to perform full scan and in-depth hard drive and partition, USB drive, memory card or removable media , to fully restore your data. This software can restore the data file from the file system partition FAT32, NTFS and ExFAT,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Multi Commander 15.8 Build 3135</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 00:13:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-multi-commander-2038.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-multi-commander-2038.html
</guid><description>
Multi Commander is a file manager, multi tab and is an alternative to the Windows Explorer standard. It uses the table layout control dual very popular and effective. Multi Commander has everything you need in daily work with files to increase speed and efficiency.
Multi Commander - file Manager
Multi Commander has all the standard features that any manager files would have, such as copy, move, rename, view. But the strong point of Multi Command is the special feature allows you to...
</description></item><item><title>Download OpenVPN 2.6.18</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 00:12:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-openvpn-4245.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-openvpn-4245.html
</guid><description>
OpenVPN provides the VPN solution flexible to secure communication of your data, whether it is the right to privacy on the Internet, remote access for employees, security, IoT, or for the data center cloud. Solution VPN software, our Server can be deployed in place by standard server or virtual device or on the cloud.
OpenVPN - VPN Solution flexible
Though built with the open source OpenVPN, the solution of our additional functionality to meet the needs of business customers, the...
</description></item><item><title>Download AllMapSoft Universal Maps Downloader 10.234</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 00:07:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-universal-maps-downloader-736.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-universal-maps-downloader-736.html
</guid><description>
AllMapSoft Universal Maps Downloader is software download map images on the computer for offline viewing support many types such as Google Maps, Yahoo maps, Bing maps, OpenStreet Maps, Yandex Maps, Ovi Maps, MapQuest Maps. All the downloaded photos will be saved on disk. You can view downloaded maps by Maps Viewer Or you can combine them into one big bmp, or jpg file tif by Maps Combiner, and also you can export all the tiles into a database format MBTiles.
AllMapSoft Universal Maps...
</description></item><item><title>Download High-Logic FontCreator Professional 15.0.0.3047</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 00:07:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-high-logic-fontcreator-professional-1533.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-high-logic-fontcreator-professional-1533.html
</guid><description>
High-Logic FontCreator Professional allows you to create and edit TrueType fonts and OpenType. It has the powerful drawing tools that typographers and graphic designers require, and an intuitive interface that allows beginners to become productive immediately.
When you create or open a font, FontCreator displays an overview of all available characters. You can only add the characters missing, or select an existing character, and modify its appearance. You can import (scanned) signature...
</description></item><item><title>Download Capture One Pro 16.7.3.3328 + Enterprise</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 00:06:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capture-one-pro-624.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capture-one-pro-624.html
</guid><description>
Capture One Pro is the software solution complete photo editing. With powerful tools to organize, color grading, editing grades, and more, you have full control over the images and process his work. Capture One has been developed with quality images and easy to use. Every tool is designed to give you full control over all aspects of the process editing - preserve, restore and optimize all information from the file RAW of you. Full the tool provides the ability to expand to always achieve...
</description></item><item><title>Download AllMapSoft Google Maps Downloader 8.886</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 00:06:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-google-maps-downloader-2796.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-google-maps-downloader-2796.html
</guid><description>
AllMapSoft Google Maps Downloader is a reliable application aimed at downloading maps from Google at high speed. The result is a set of small images can be combined in a larger map. This can serve in a large variety of projects, from creating a tile map to presentations and tutorials.
Google Maps Downloader successfully fulfills both of those conditions, providing simple means to quickly grab maps at the resolution satisfactory. In addition, it is extremely easy to use and integrated a...
</description></item><item><title>Download MobiKin Assistant for iOS 3.6.26</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 00:05:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mobikin-assistant-for-ios-4865.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mobikin-assistant-for-ios-4865.html
</guid><description>
MobiKin Assistant for iOS is software assistant the world's most powerful apps for iPad users, iPhone and iPod, MobiKin Assistant for iOS allows users to transfer, backup and manage all content on your device just by a simple click. In case of losing data if your iPhone is stolen or accidentally damaged or you just want to share the movies on your iDevice with your friends in other ways you should regularly backup the files on iPhone, iPad or iPod to iTunes . However, there are still many...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sync Breeze Ultimate 17.7.24 + Enterprise + Pro</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 00:05:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sync-breeze-ultimate-enterprise-1462.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sync-breeze-ultimate-enterprise-1462.html
</guid><description>
Sync Breeze Ultimate / Enterprise is software sync files fast, powerful and reliable for the local disk, shared network storage devices, NAS and storage systems business. Users are provided with multiple modes sync files one-way and two-way sync files periodically, sync file real time sync file-level bits, sync files multi-threading, synchronization, files, wallpaper and more.
Sync Breeze Ultimate / Enterprise - synchronize files
App GUI main Sync Breeze Ultimate allows a person to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Coolmuster iOS Assistant 4.6.30</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 00:04:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-ios-assistant-2476.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-ios-assistant-2476.html
</guid><description>
You want to backup data from iPhone / iPad / iPod to computer? You want to import a file from your computer to your iOS device? You want to restore backup on your iDevices? You want to have full control over the data stored on your iDevices? This iOS Assistant pro integrates all these features in a and sure is the best manager for your iOS device.
Coolmuster iOS Assistant - backup for IOS devices
Coolmuster iOS Assistant is a whole program feature allows you to freely backup contacts,...
</description></item><item><title>Download YUMI exFAT 1.0.3.4</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 00:04:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yumi-exfat-7423.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yumi-exfat-7423.html
</guid><description>
YUMI exFAT is a Multiboot USB creator that supports exFAT format and files larger than 4GB. BIOS and USB UEFI boot. YUMI exFAT is compatible with Ventoy. It supports both modern UEFI and Legacy BIOS boot modes. Included is a separate USB Boot creation tool derived from Ventoy/Ventoy2Disk. This variant is also backward compatible with Ventoy. If desired, you can even copy YUMI-exFAT-xxx.exe to the same location as Ventoy2Disk.exe and use the YUMI-exFAT-xxx.exe user interface with...
</description></item><item><title>Download AllmapSoft Google Satellite Maps Downloader 8.415</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 00:04:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-google-satellite-maps-downloader-687.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-google-satellite-maps-downloader-687.html
</guid><description>
AllmapSoft Google Satellite Maps Downloader is software help download map images from google maps on computer for you to get the satellite images from google map. All the downloaded photos will be saved on disk. You can see the map is downloaded by viewer Or you can combine them into the map BMP, big. It supports proxy server. And you can easily get the longitude and latitude of each image tile small download.
You can use offline maps in GIS software such as Global Mapper, QGIS,...
</description></item><item><title>Download AllMapSoft Offline Map Maker 8.365</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 00:03:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-offline-map-maker-656.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-offline-map-maker-656.html
</guid><description>
AllMapSoft Offline Map Maker is software create, organize, offline map from Google Maps, Yahoo maps, Bing maps and Openstreetmap. You can view offline maps downloaded with map viewer offline. And you can zoom out or zoom in the offline map or export map under the file format .BMP with file world xxx.bpw, and can output files xxx.map for OziExplorer. If you want to make a offline map of your city by yourself, it is very useful for you.
Features AllMapSoft Offline Map Maker
	You can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Disk Pulse Ultimate 17.7.24 + Enterprise + Pro</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 00:03:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-disk-pulse-ultimate-1465.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-disk-pulse-ultimate-1465.html
</guid><description>
Disk Pulse Ultimate is a monitoring solution change disk real-time allows one to monitor one or more disks or directories, save reports and statistics monitoring disk changes, the change is detected to the SQL database focus, execute custom commands and send E-Mail notifications when unauthorized changes are detected in the file system important.
Disk Pulse Ultimate - Monitor disc change
DiskPulse provides the ability for users to start / stop the monitoring operation disc change,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Revo Registry Cleaner Pro 2.0.7</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 20:45:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-revo-registry-cleaner-pro-12750.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-revo-registry-cleaner-pro-12750.html
</guid><description>
Revo Registry Cleaner Pro provides complete solutions to advanced Registry cleaning. It uses more than 15 separate scanning categories to identify and completely delete invaluable and redundant registry items that can slow down your system performance. You can customize the cleaning process by specifying the items including and the main exclusion, allowing a more appropriate approach to maintain the integrity of the registration book. In addition, Revo Registry Cleaner has four flexible...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinRAR 7.20 Final</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 20:43:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winrar-127.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winrar-127.html
</guid><description>
WinRAR is a compression utility data advanced supports multiple formats including RAR, ZIP, CAB, ARJ, LZH, ACE, TAR, GZip, UUE, ISO, BZIP2, Z and 7-Zip. It allows you to create, organize and manage archives in a comfortable way and quickly. WinRAR naturally are is a leading software currently in the compression and decompression of data. With the enhanced algorithm is applied, the software allows users to compress bulk files in different formats into synthetic 1 single file to facilitate...
</description></item><item><title>Download GiliSoft Video Editor Pro 18.5</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 20:42:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-video-editor-pro-7065.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-video-editor-pro-7065.html
</guid><description>
GiliSoft Video Editor Pro is the pro version that makes it easy to edit your video files in your own Hollywood style with stunning cinematic quality. With GiliSoft Video Editor Pro you simply select your own video clip, edit it with titles, text, filters, overlays, effects and your videos will come to life.
This software allows you to preview the video before, during and at the end so you can make sure your movie looks good from start to finish, and then export the project file as: MP4,...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDF Annotator 10.0.0.1008</title><pubDate> Wed, 04 Feb 2026 20:42:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-annotator-178.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-annotator-178.html
</guid><description>
PDF Annotator software user open any PDF file and add annotations, using the mouse or pen Tablet PC, directly on the Page of the PDF file. PDF Annotator allows users to perform editing operations on PDF files such as: add notes, edit signature, highlight, insert images or text... From the this useful tool, you can completely modify PDF files as you like in order to meet the different work.
PDF Annotator
With the PDF Annotator the document has annotations can then be saved directly back...
</description></item></channel></rss>