<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 13:50:08 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 13:50:08 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Synchredible Professional 9.110</title><pubDate> Sat, 24 Jan 2026 16:49:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-synchredible-professional-1923.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-synchredible-professional-1923.html
</guid><description>
Synchredible Professional is the most advanced version help synchronize the folder and your drive quickly and easily. Whether it is a single file or an entire drive - Synchredible Professional will synchronize, copy and save them for you. The software guide will assist you to identify the work that is scheduled in advance or be done through the USB connection. This way, you can keep your files in sync - automatically.
In the past years, the advanced technology of the us in Synchredible...
</description></item><item><title>Download FileCenter Professional Suite 12.0.32</title><pubDate> Sat, 24 Jan 2026 16:49:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-filecenter-professional-suite-3407.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-filecenter-professional-suite-3407.html
</guid><description>
FileCenter Professional Suite is a set of tools, file manager and powerful document. FileCenter Professional Suite is a management solution document full and effective designed for small businesses. The program blends organize files and scan easily with the ability to edit and create PDF advanced. In addition, the program also comes with a number of functions and features, such as Search, OCR, restore files, etc. Integrated with cloud services such as OneDrive, Google Drive and Dropbox,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Synchredible 9.110</title><pubDate> Sat, 24 Jan 2026 16:48:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-synchredible-53.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-synchredible-53.html
</guid><description>
Synchredible is an easy to use tool to synchronize folders and files. It provides a wizard interface lets you set up the sync job, select files to exclude, schedule the job to execute automatically, and more.Additional features include support for network and external drives, check CRC32, and more.
Synchredible - synchronization of folders and files
Among other things, you can use the filter for the file type specific data synchronization according to the time or routine deletion of...
</description></item><item><title>Download HTTP Toolkit 1.24.4</title><pubDate> Sat, 24 Jan 2026 16:48:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-http-toolkit-6246.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-http-toolkit-6246.html
</guid><description>
HTTP Toolkit is software that provides the ability to automatically block HTTP and HTTPS traffic from most client applications, including web browsers such as Chrome and Firefox, most CLI tools and auxiliary languages such as Node.js, Python, Ruby etc. You can browse through traffic by marking the content type, status, and source or search by URL, status, and title to find important notifications.
You can check the URL, status, title, and content of each request or feedback, along with...
</description></item><item><title>Download SmartGit 25.1.110</title><pubDate> Sat, 24 Jan 2026 16:47:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-smartgit-13978.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-smartgit-13978.html
</guid><description>
SmartGit is a cross-platform, graphical Git application designed for professional users to simplify and enhance Git version control workflows. SmartGit supports major Git hosting services like GitHub, Bitbucket, GitLab, and Azure DevOps with built-in features to handle pull requests, comments, and code reviews directly in the app.
Why choose SmartGit as your Git Client?
	One for all.
	SmartGit helps new Git users as well as helps experienced developers work more efficiently.
	SmartGit...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tomabo MP4 Downloader Pro 6.1.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 24 Jan 2026 16:47:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tomabo-mp4-downloader-pro-3602.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tomabo-mp4-downloader-pro-3602.html
</guid><description>
Tomabo MP4 Downloader Pro is the app designed exclusively for Windows users to help them download videos from the Internet. In addition, it also increase download speeds by up to 500%, or even more. Tomabo MP4 Downloader Pro, interface design, simple, well-organized, beautifully. Here, users can view a list of videos has download with gravatar, URL, quality, duration and size of them. Software allows download video series at the same time, at the same time, support create a list of clips...
</description></item><item><title>Download Secret Video Downloader 1.1.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 24 Jan 2026 16:40:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secret-video-downloader-13775.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secret-video-downloader-13775.html
</guid><description>
Secret Video Downloader is a free application designed to facilitate easy video downloading from various websites. It leverages the yt-dlp command line program to efficiently grab video content, allowing users to save videos in the highest quality available without complicated installation or configuration. The tool has a minimalist interface focused on simplicity: the user pastes the video URL into the built-in browser, clicks the Download button, and the video is added to the download...
</description></item><item><title>Download ET Optimizer 6.08.20</title><pubDate> Sat, 24 Jan 2026 16:39:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-et-optimizer-9574.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-et-optimizer-9574.html
</guid><description>
ET-Optimizer is a free, open source script to improve your computer's overall performance and optimize it for your workflow through optimized scripting. With this optimization, setup takes little effort. The script is developed from many sources found on the Internet, tested and updated for different versions of the system. The whole script is contained in 1 file, it uses: command prompt, powershell, power plan configuration, startup configuration, registry changes, network interface...
</description></item><item><title>Download Trillium Technology ShowCase Image Center 2.7.0.5</title><pubDate> Sat, 24 Jan 2026 16:38:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-trillium-technology-showcase-image-center-11868.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-trillium-technology-showcase-image-center-11868.html
</guid><description>
Trillium Technology ShowCase Image Center runs on your own hardware, can store millions of images in the original DICOM format, and provides local, in-office, and remote access to studies using ShowCase Premier and ShowCase View software. Use ShowCase Premier or Workstation to access diagnostic quality studies from the Imaging Center, locally, over your LAN, or remotely, over a slower VPN connection. Background distribution is available over an internet connection, reducing waiting time.
</description></item><item><title>Download NTFS Permissions Reporter Enterprise 5.1.639</title><pubDate> Sat, 24 Jan 2026 16:38:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ntfs-permissions-reporter-enterprise-6370.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ntfs-permissions-reporter-enterprise-6370.html
</guid><description>
System administrators are constantly required to check user rights for specific files and folders. This is often a time-consuming work, with multiple NTFS classes and repetitive adjustments over time creating a security maze. NTFS Permissions Reporter Enterprise allows you to confirm the security status of the entire file system quickly and efficiently. All have multiple export formats, command line support, integration scheduling, advanced filtration, and more.
Features of NTFS...
</description></item><item><title>Download apulSoft apUnmask 1.0.6</title><pubDate> Sat, 24 Jan 2026 16:37:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-apulsoft-apunmask-5374.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-apulsoft-apunmask-5374.html
</guid><description>
apulSoft apUnmask is an audio plugin to amplify components of sound psychologically obscured by other components. To achieve this, apUnmask uses parts of the detector algorithm of the opus high quality audio compression codec. Signal components that will be removed by compression will be extracted. They are often inaudible because they are obscured by larger time and frequency components. apUnmask allows to amplify and create masked content and add that content to music.
To configure...
</description></item><item><title>Download Trillium Technology ShowCase Workstation 6.7.0.5</title><pubDate> Sat, 24 Jan 2026 16:37:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-trillium-technology-showcase-workstation-11870.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-trillium-technology-showcase-workstation-11870.html
</guid><description>
Trillium Technology ShowCase Workstation is a standalone DICOM SCU/SCP with all the viewing features of ShowCase Premier but with the following additional features: Query/Retrieve studies from PACS. PACS-based auto-refresh for a dynamic list of studies, e.g. showing today's studies as they appear. Automatically cleans up locally retrieved studies. No more manually managing your local cache folder. Automatically forwards studies to PACS or Imaging Center.
Main features:
	Query/Retrieve...
</description></item><item><title>Download COAA PlanePlotter 6.7.3.9</title><pubDate> Sat, 24 Jan 2026 16:36:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coaa-planeplotter-7840.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coaa-planeplotter-7840.html
</guid><description>
PlanePlotter receives and decodes digital position reports directly from the aircraft and plots them on a chart. Using PlanePlotter, you can see the radar-like display of all aircraft around you transmitting the appropriate digital messages including ACARS, ADS-B and HFDL.
PlanePlotter Features
	PlanePlotter displays a table showing messages received and decoded from direct plane transmissions.
	PlanePlotter stores all digital data it receives and decodes into a log...
</description></item><item><title>Download Operant Peak Spectroscopy 4.00.544</title><pubDate> Sat, 24 Jan 2026 16:36:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-operant-peak-spectroscopy-7976.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-operant-peak-spectroscopy-7976.html
</guid><description>
Operant Peak Spectroscopy for Spectroscopy reads and converts over 60 spectral file formats. It includes library search, spectrum manipulation and many other functions. Mid IR, Near IR, FTIR, Raman, Fluorescence, LIBS, XRF, UV-VIS, Raman and EELS.
Features of Operant Peak Spectroscopy
	Peak can read data from more than 70 spectral file types.
	Convert files in bulk from closed proprietary formats.
	Peak is used worldwide in industry, education, government and military
	Peak has a...
</description></item><item><title>Download QOwnNotes 26.1.11</title><pubDate> Sat, 24 Jan 2026 16:35:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qownnotes-3178.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qownnotes-3178.html
</guid><description>
QOwnNotes is notes bookmark file simple text (GPL) open source application for GNU / Linux , Mac OS X and Windows of Patrizio Bekerle ( pbek on GitHub and IRC) (optional) activity along with the notes application of ownCloud or Nextcloud. QOwnNote store your notes as plain text files and can be synchronized with synchronization function file of ownCloud / Nextcloud. You can also use other apps like Syncthing or Dropbox . Just write out your thoughts as they appear, and edit them if...
</description></item><item><title>Download Picture Window Pro 8.0.546</title><pubDate> Sat, 24 Jan 2026 16:35:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-picture-window-pro-7452.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-picture-window-pro-7452.html
</guid><description>
Picture Window Pro is a powerful image editing tool designed for serious photographers with strict creative and quality standards. Its comprehensive set of photo editing and editing tools let you control and shape every aspect of your images.
Picture Window Pro 8 is a complete rewrite of Picture Window Pro 7. It features non-destructive image editing through a novel interface based on an image tree. It also fully supports large, high-resolution displays and can be used in dual monitor...
</description></item><item><title>Download apulSoft apQualizr 2.7.6</title><pubDate> Sat, 24 Jan 2026 16:34:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-apulsoft-apqualizr-5516.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-apulsoft-apqualizr-5516.html
</guid><description>
apulSoft apQualizr is an audio plugin based on a layered multi-band equalizer on top of a free frequency analyzer with elements of a modular effect system. It features graphic editing of top quality low-latency filters and modular modulation of various filter parameters. It can be used for all standard EQ applications and can produce a variety of modulation and dynamics effects thanks to the included dynamics and lfo modules.
The apQualizr2 filters are based on a unique method of...
</description></item><item><title>Download apulSoft apShaper 1.2.5</title><pubDate> Sat, 24 Jan 2026 16:34:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-apulsoft-apshaper-7045.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-apulsoft-apshaper-7045.html
</guid><description>
apulSoft apShaper is an audio insert effect plugin to add harmonic content to audio signals. It combines a waveshaper with three filter bands and various modulation options - two lfos, a dynamics detector and user-configurable knobs.
apShaper comes with five shaper engines ranging from adding harmonic distortion to freely configurable polygonal wavefolding.
The three filter bands come directly from apulSoft apQualizr2 and offer the same great quality without frequency squeezing at high...
</description></item><item><title>Download Easy Notes - Note Taking Apps 1.3.39.0121</title><pubDate> Sat, 24 Jan 2026 16:33:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-easy-notes-notebook-notepad-8388.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-easy-notes-notebook-notepad-8388.html
</guid><description>
Easy Notes - Great note taking app, Notepad, Notebook, Free Notes is a free easy to use note taking app for notes app. With this easy notebook and notepad app, take quick notes with colorful backgrounds and checklists to organize notes and tasks easily. Use this aesthetic note taker and note taker to add photos or audio to your notes. Easy Notes is a useful notebook and note-taking app for taking notes and organizing work.
Features of Easy Notes - Notebook, Notepad
	Free Notepad and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Solid Explorer File Manager 3.2.16 build 200360</title><pubDate> Sat, 24 Jan 2026 16:33:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-solid-explorer-file-manager-8924.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-solid-explorer-file-manager-8924.html
</guid><description>
Solid Explorer is a file management application inspired by old file management applications. Solid Explorer is a popular file management app for Android devices that allows users to manage and organize their files and folders in an intuitive and user-friendly interface. It offers many features that make it stand out from other file management apps.
Solid Explorer allows you to navigate to files stored on your device and automatically organize them into collections. You can view,...
</description></item><item><title>Download MDScan + OCR 3.9.96</title><pubDate> Sat, 24 Jan 2026 16:33:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-mobile-doc-scanner-mdscan-ocr-8307.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-mobile-doc-scanner-mdscan-ocr-8307.html
</guid><description>
Mobile Doc Scanner (MDS) is an application that allows users to scan, edit and save documents using the Android device's camera. It's designed to work as a portable scanner so you can easily digitize documents, receipts, business cards, and more.
All image processing is done on your device only! No material will be posted online without your wishes! Take photos with your camera, edit them with many advanced features, save to your favorite format and share on social networks, email,...
</description></item><item><title>Download MIUI Hidden Settings Activity 1.6.14</title><pubDate> Sat, 24 Jan 2026 16:32:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-miui-hidden-settings-activity-8889.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-miui-hidden-settings-activity-8889.html
</guid><description>
MIUI hidden settings app is a launcher that works to find and explore all hidden options for mi phones (Miui Rom like Xiaomi Poco, redmi,...) newer operating system, MIUI 10, 11, 12 and also for Android like Samsung, LG, ...
MI Hidden Settings shows all installed settings, allowing you to reveal, unlock and change settings, find and display system and hardware information or discover new features . it uses the system package name of this setting and searches for it in internally...
</description></item><item><title>Download Smart Launcher 6 ‧ Home Screen 6.6 build 002</title><pubDate> Sat, 24 Jan 2026 16:32:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-smart-launcher-8412.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-smart-launcher-8412.html
</guid><description>
Smart Launcher is a mobile app that provides users with a customized home screen and app launcher on their Android devices. It includes features like minimalist interface, automatic app sorting, and gesture controls. The app also includes many customizable settings, such as the ability to change the theme, icon size, and screen layout, as well as the ability to create custom categories for the app.
Smart Launcher Features
	Ambient theme: Smart launcher automatically changes theme...
</description></item><item><title>Download Multi Timer StopWatch 2.13.37</title><pubDate> Sat, 24 Jan 2026 16:32:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-multi-timer-stopwatch-8914.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-multi-timer-stopwatch-8914.html
</guid><description>
Multi Timer is a beautifully designed time management app. Multiple timers can be set, started and run independently at the same time. Stopwatch results can be stored. Use Multi Timer for cooking, sports, machine washing, studying, working, gaming - whatever you like.
Features of Multi Timer StopWatch
	Multiple timers at once: Store the timers you often use for cooking, sports, studying, working, gaming, whatever you want. Start them with just one tap, anytime you need.
	Timer in...
</description></item><item><title>Download All Document Reader - One Read 1.2.8.59</title><pubDate> Sat, 24 Jan 2026 16:31:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-all-document-reader-pdf-word-9127.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-all-document-reader-pdf-word-9127.html
</guid><description>
All Document Reader is a fast and simple all-in-one office application for opening docx files, viewing xlsx files, and reading pdf and pptx documents. This is a lightweight application used to read all office files, such as Word files (DOC, DOCX), Excel spreadsheets (XLS, XLSX), PDFs, PowerPoint slides (PPT, PPTX), TXT, ZIP, RAR, etc. The file viewer application allows you to search, read, and manage all office documents and files using Android.
This smart and compact office file opener...
</description></item></channel></rss>