<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 19:54:45 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 19:54:45 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Google Chrome 142.0.7444.135</title><pubDate> Sun, 09 Nov 2025 16:27:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-chrome-1012.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-chrome-1012.html
</guid><description>
Google Chrome web browser is the most used today. Support surf the web, listen to music, watch movies, play web game effective no jerky lag with the internet connection stable. When you are surfing the web or performing an important task, whether it is operation big or small, work or entertainment, then Chrome has the smart features and the speed you need to make, create and explore on the net.
The latest version of Google Chrome is the third 114. But we are providing for users Google...
</description></item><item><title>Download CapCut PC 7.4.0.3037</title><pubDate> Sun, 09 Nov 2025 16:26:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capcut-pc-9995.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capcut-pc-9995.html
</guid><description>
CapCut PC is a simple video editing tool that you can freely use anywhere. You can create videos on your browser, desktop and laptop, or on your phone. Versatile editing, magical AI tools, team collaboration, and built-in assets. Create videos in a whole new way.
You can edit videos based on editing the timeline, in the process you can add different elements and effects to the video to give the best effect to your work. It is a simple and intuitive set of editing tools and effects that...
</description></item><item><title>Download VueScan Pro 9.8.49</title><pubDate> Sun, 09 Nov 2025 16:24:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vuescan-pro-75.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vuescan-pro-75.html
</guid><description>
VueScan Pro l  is one of the software  Scan quality pictures  First and appeared quite soon,  VueScan Pro  always asserted its No. 1 position on the technology pages, awards as well as user reviews. Through many versions, VueScan Pro 9 is greatly improved in terms of interface and features. Supporting most popular image formats today, this software will help you scan images quickly, easy to use and high quality output. With the color balance mode, you won't have to worry about blurring the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Q-Dir 12.41</title><pubDate> Sun, 09 Nov 2025 16:23:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-q-dir-348.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-q-dir-348.html
</guid><description>
Q-Dir is software to manage the entire file and folder on the computer, allowing to see file in same time 4 different positions (viewport quadro) while still maintaining all the standard features of the Explorer.
It also provides a variety of management features, additional files included the filter file color-coding, layouts and columns can be customized, quick access to file and folder favorites and more.
Other features of Q-Dir , including directory listings (.txt, .doc .html .csv),...
</description></item><item><title>Download ZD Soft Screen Recorder 12.0.6</title><pubDate> Sun, 09 Nov 2025 16:23:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zd-soft-screen-recorder-136.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zd-soft-screen-recorder-136.html
</guid><description>
ZD Soft Screen Recorder supports user taping the game in 2D or 3D, film screen, the content is screened in the multimedia. The Videos are saved in a list and popular formats with best quality.
ZD Soft Screen Recorder is a program recording software screen high performance. It works just like a camera really. A camcorder can record many things in the real world including computer screen, while ZD Soft Screen Recorder can only record computer screen but can do much better than a camcorder...
</description></item><item><title>Download Password Safe 3.70.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 09 Nov 2025 16:22:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-password-safe-72.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-password-safe-72.html
</guid><description>
Password Safe is a password manager securely protects the sensitive login your encryption algorithm HaiFish. It allows you to store all of your passwords in one or more databases are encrypted and access them with a master password.
Password Safe - Password Manager Safe
Password Safe offers many features, including expired passwords, user notes, integrated backup, password policy, custom, history tracking, passwords, automatic login, secure clipboard, import / export, and more.You can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Bitwig Studio 6.0 Beta 6</title><pubDate> Sun, 09 Nov 2025 16:21:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bitwig-studio-3626.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bitwig-studio-3626.html
</guid><description>
Find new standard in the process of individual work. Bitwig Studio excite you good control over his music, give you access to all features of your production. Streamline course creation of you and quickly develop your ideas into the songs, compositions and music full.
Bitwig Studio - Create your own music
Arrange and record, perform and improvise, or do all at the same time. Choose among the many records displayed. Design your sound with the equipment container commitment. Mixing the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Phoenix Customizer 1.1.11 Beta</title><pubDate> Sun, 09 Nov 2025 16:21:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-phoenix-customizer-12580.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-phoenix-customizer-12580.html
</guid><description>
Phoenix Customizer provides you with various settings that allow you to customize your Windows 11 or Windows 10 system. You can easily customize Windows folders with various colors and effects, add a custom taskbar that you can change to your liking, have a floating widget with access to shortcuts, and favorites or modify the Windows context menu.
Main features
	Customize Windows folders: Customize your Windows folder icons easily. It's simple, select the Windows folder for which you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Hasleo Backup Suite WinPE 5.5.2.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 09 Nov 2025 16:20:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hasleo-backup-suite-winpe-11366.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hasleo-backup-suite-winpe-11366.html
</guid><description>
Hasleo Backup Suite is Windows backup and recovery software, integrating backup, restore, and replication features. This software is designed for Windows operating system users and can be used on both Windows PCs and Servers. Hasleo Backup Suite's backup and restore feature can help you back up and restore your Windows operating system, drives, and partitions to protect the security of your Windows operating system and personal data. Hasleo Backup Suite's cloning feature can help you...
</description></item><item><title>Download WindowTop Pro 5.29.0 Beta</title><pubDate> Sun, 09 Nov 2025 16:20:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windowtop-6955.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windowtop-6955.html
</guid><description>
WindowTop is a program that pins windows on Desktop, in other words it sets the window to float above all other program windows, creating transparency for the windows. that window via a dedicated slider, which supports adjusting transparency, changing the color of application windows or similar programs with the dark theme of the Windows 10 operating system, creating contrast and reducing tension straight, painful for the eyes.
Features of WindowTop
	Put window on top
	Set window to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Find.Same.Images.OK 5.81</title><pubDate> Sun, 09 Nov 2025 16:19:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-find-same-images-ok-113.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-find-same-images-ok-113.html
</guid><description>
Find.Same.Images.OK lets find the images identical or similar in the folder of you, even if they were to rotate, change size or change.
Just select one or more folders that you want the program to scan and it will return a list of all the duplicate images or very similar, as indicated by the percent the same and the preview is built.Then, you can select images from the list and then copy, move or delete them.
Find.Same.Images.OK
In addition, there are other options smart option allows...
</description></item><item><title>Download Muziza YouTube Downloader Converter 8.16.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 09 Nov 2025 16:19:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-muziza-youtube-downloader-converter-3972.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-muziza-youtube-downloader-converter-3972.html
</guid><description>
Muziza YouTube Downloader Converter is a tool to create conditions for an attractive interface and many features to help you to download video clips from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion, Instagram and other sites. Muziza YouTube Downloader Converter can also download the video UHD 8K, 5K, 4K, QHD 2K, HD 1080p and 720p from YouTube. The app allows you download only audio stream from YouTube and save as MP3. You don't need to download the entire video file.
Muziza YouTube Downloader...
</description></item><item><title>Download Hybrid 2025.11.08.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 09 Nov 2025 16:18:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hybrid-2233.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hybrid-2233.html
</guid><description>
Hybrid is a multifunctional program that allows you to record videos on media Blu-ray or AVCHD, also you can convert data in formats x264, Xvid, VP8, ac3, ogg, mp3, aac and flac formats mp4, m2ts, mkv, webm. You can download Hybrid below. Please note that after conversion, you can write the result right into the media. That's not all, you also can use the edit program and the card, you can work with subtitles. You will get a large number of installation, a simple interface, in that it's...
</description></item><item><title>Download App Builder 2025.37</title><pubDate> Sun, 09 Nov 2025 16:18:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-app-builder-241.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-app-builder-241.html
</guid><description>
App Builder is a software application developer to help create and design apps, HTML5, web app, web app PWA on both platforms mobile and desktop. App Builder is professional software supports users to create the program HTML5 without writing code. It is very easy to use, suitable with all users who lack of professional knowledge in the field of programming and application design.
App Builder brings to 22 different themes that users can use to design for your app. You can choose 1 or a...
</description></item><item><title>Download Reportizer 6.6.0.1078</title><pubDate> Sun, 09 Nov 2025 16:17:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reportizer-5205.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reportizer-5205.html
</guid><description>
Reportizer is a tools report database. Easily create, modify, and print reports database. Allows to manage collection reports. Support database BDE or ADO. Tested on dBase (DBF), Paradox (DB), Text (TXT), the values are separated by commas (CSV), Oracle, Interbase, Microsoft Access, Microsoft Excel, SQL Server, Visual FoxPro, MySQL, PostgreQuery, HTML.
The design reports visually. Reports can be edited in the report design, intuitive and convenient with the toolbar and powerful tool. For...
</description></item><item><title>Download TubeDownload Pro 6.31.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 09 Nov 2025 16:17:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubedownload-pro-12035.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubedownload-pro-12035.html
</guid><description>
TubeDownload Pro is a professional Windows application for downloading your favorite videos from YouTube and hundreds of other video sites. TubeDownload Pro can increase download speed up to 500% or even more.
Features of TubeDownload Pro
	Download your favorite videos from YouTube and hundreds of other video sites.
	Increase download speed up to 500% or even more.
	Download 720p, 1080p, 2K, 4K and 8K HD videos from YouTube.
	Download entire playlists in just a few clicks.
	Download...
</description></item><item><title>Download Private Windows Script (PrivWindoze) 5.8.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 09 Nov 2025 16:17:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-private-windows-script-12878.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-private-windows-script-12878.html
</guid><description>
Are you concerned about your personal information sent to others? Or do you feel that your Windows settings have many programs that you never use? Private Windows Script (or Privwindoze) provides a comprehensive anti -remote monitoring set designed to enhance your privacy when using Windows operating system.
The main features
	End the positive process. All unnecessary processes are turned off while the scanning program. A small white list is maintained.
	Clean up the positive runonce....
</description></item><item><title>Download Betterbird 140.5.0esr-bb14</title><pubDate> Sun, 09 Nov 2025 16:16:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-betterbird-8318.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-betterbird-8318.html
</guid><description>
Betterbird is a tweaked version of Mozilla Thunderbird, Thunderbird on steroids, if you will. It closely follows Thunderbird's Extended Support Releases (ESRs), thus avoiding the mistakes of other forks that cause it to quickly lose track of upstream Thunderbird, thus opening users to vulnerabilities. security.
Betterbird makes emailing safer, faster and easier than ever with the implementation of industry best features like smart spam filter, built-in spell checker , extension support,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Broot 1.53.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 09 Nov 2025 16:16:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-broot-8588.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-broot-8588.html
</guid><description>
Broot is an open source command line tool for browsing and navigating file systems. Broot provides a fast and intuitive way to navigate the file system with a tree-like interactive interface. It provides various features like searching for files, opening files and folders, copying file paths to clipboard, etc. It also supports customizing keys and color themes.
Features of Broot
	Fast file browsing: Lets you quickly navigate through large directory structures with a tree-like...
</description></item><item><title>Download BulkFileChanger 1.74</title><pubDate> Sun, 09 Nov 2025 16:15:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bulkfilechanger-1988.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bulkfilechanger-1988.html
</guid><description>
BulkFileChanger is software that allows you to change the date of the file (last accessed, modified, created) and attributes for multiple files, even when they are located in different folders. You can create a list of the files will be processed by copy / paste, drag and drop or via path wildcards.
BulkFileChanger - change date and attributes file
Software BulkFileChanger can also be used to call an external program to which it will transfer the file list as a parameter.
</description></item><item><title>Download Audija KickDrum 2.6.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 09 Nov 2025 16:14:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-audija-kickdrum-14117.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-audija-kickdrum-14117.html
</guid><description>
Audija KickDrum is a highly accurate kick drum synthesizer plugin, designed for electronic music producers looking for maximum control and versatility in their bass drum sounds. It features a three-dimensional wavetable engine, detailed harmonic editing, and extensive routing options, making it far superior to a typical drum plugin.
KickDrum Features
	Combine a precise sine oscillator—with a fixed zero-crossing point—and a flexible sampler to layer and analyze kick sounds.
	Shape...
</description></item><item><title>Download MKVToolnix 96.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 09 Nov 2025 02:12:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mkvtoolnix-1129.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mkvtoolnix-1129.html
</guid><description>
MKVToolnix is software that supports video editing, such as cutting or splicing the videos together to create a complete video and unique. MKVToolnix to help you cut the interesting scenes in the video to create the short clips impress others. In addition, you can also stitch multiple videos together to create a single video quality, get big interest from viewers.
MKVToolnix - Cut and connect video
MKVToolnix allows you to customize and manage up the MKV file had to be cut or connect...
</description></item><item><title>Download LosslessCut 3.67.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 09 Nov 2025 02:11:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-losslesscut-1789.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-losslesscut-1789.html
</guid><description>
LosslessCut is the video editor to trim and cut video without loss of quality. Just download the video file and use seal cutter start / stop to only the part you want to cut. Click the crop icon and the highlighted part will be exported to the file new video without any decoding or encoding whatsoever. LosslessCut using ffmpeg (included) to carry all the heavy stuff.
LosslessCut - Cut and edit videos
LosslessCut based on Chromium and uses the video player HTML5, so not all formats are...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDF Annotator 9.0.0.929</title><pubDate> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 16:48:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-annotator-178.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-annotator-178.html
</guid><description>
PDF Annotator software user open any PDF file and add annotations, using the mouse or pen Tablet PC, directly on the Page of the PDF file. PDF Annotator allows users to perform editing operations on PDF files such as: add notes, edit signature, highlight, insert images or text... From the this useful tool, you can completely modify PDF files as you like in order to meet the different work.
PDF Annotator
With the PDF Annotator the document has annotations can then be saved directly back...
</description></item><item><title>Download GoldWave 7.03</title><pubDate> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 16:48:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-goldwave-1577.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-goldwave-1577.html
</guid><description>
GoldWave is a sound editor comprehensive digital be most appreciated. GoldWave ideal for those who work with sound to edit CD, restore, archive, speech analysis, radio and TV, Java and web pages, games or just to entertain. You can use it to do everything from reply elaborately message to content audio CD professional, high quality.
GoldWave - edit digital audio
The work that GoldWave done:
	Play, edit, mix, and analyze audio
	Record audio from cassettes, vinyl records, radio, etc....
</description></item></channel></rss>