<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 03:31:20 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 03:31:20 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Sejda PDF Desktop Pro 7.9.3</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 22:50:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sejda-pdf-desktop-pro-1301.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sejda-pdf-desktop-pro-1301.html
</guid><description>
Sejda PDF Desktop Pro is a professional PDF file action software with full features to help you with PDF tasks. Sejda PDF Desktop is used free of charge in the daily limit. Upgrade of advanced and non-limited features.
Sejda PDF Desktop Pro fully integrate PDF editing features from basic to complex such as document editing, file compression, page removal, inclusion or separation, page publication, PDF conversion. all in the same modern and efficient program.
Features of Sejda PDF...
</description></item><item><title>Download PanoramaStudio Pro 4.1.6.443</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 22:49:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-panoramastudio-pro-1604.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-panoramastudio-pro-1604.html
</guid><description>
PanoramaStudio Pro is software is the complete solution for creating panoramic images as matching images are arranged arbitrary in the panorama. PanoramaStudio Pro creates panoramic images in a row and multiple rows of up to 360x180 spherical full. In addition, this software provides viewer / player application HTML5 interactions are compatible with all web browsers and on multiple systems to display the panoramic image 3D, 360 degree images and image zoom on the site.
PanoramaStudio...
</description></item><item><title>Download PhraseExpress 17.0.130</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 22:49:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-phraseexpress-41.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-phraseexpress-41.html
</guid><description>
PhraseExpress is a useful application that helps users save time when typing frequently used text or commands. This application allows users to create shortcuts to automatically insert text quickly and conveniently.
With PhraseExpress, users can create "templates" for common commands, regular emails, chat messages, or any text they have to retype frequently. Users only need to set up shortcuts for each template and when needed, just type that shortcut and the text will automatically...
</description></item><item><title>Download KMPlayer (KMP) 2025.8.22.13 x64 / 4.2.3.25 x86</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 22:48:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kmplayer-kmp-902.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kmplayer-kmp-902.html
</guid><description>
KMPlayer (KMP) is software watch movies listen to music multi-function for video enthusiasts. KMPlayer development is many types of the format different. KMPlayer has improved on sound quality, images when listening to music and watching movies, the playback speed of video is faster, more codec player is added to the software video decoder is optimized.
KMPlayer also supports a variety of audio formats and video and offers a the interface can be customized with the preview coverflow and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Responsive Site Designer 4.0.3351</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 22:46:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-responsive-site-designer-1491.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-responsive-site-designer-1491.html
</guid><description>
Responsive Site Designer is software website design with Bootstrap and Foundation without the need to code and build quickly. Here is the CSS Framework used by millions of designers and developers. Bootstrap 3 and 4, Foundation 6, and Materialize is the most popular. Design with the frames are tested this good has many advantages.
CSS Framework is used by millions of designers and developers. Bootstrap 3 and 4, Foundation 6, and Materialize is the most popular. Design with the frames are...
</description></item><item><title>Download WonderPen 3.0.0.8056</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 22:46:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tominlab-wonderpen-7753.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tominlab-wonderpen-7753.html
</guid><description>
WonderPen is a writing app for both professional and amateur writers. WonderPen uses a tree directory to organize documents, supports unlimited levels, and can easily manage both short articles and long works. Documents can be exported to various formats such as images, PDF, Word, Epub and web pages. Multiple chapters can be exported as a book in batches.
WonderPen has a built-in full automatic backup function. By default, it will perform a full database backup every 15 minutes. It also...
</description></item><item><title>Download Coolmuster Android Eraser 4.0.19</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 22:45:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-android-eraser-5330.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-android-eraser-5330.html
</guid><description>
Coolmuster Android Eraser is the most ideal privacy protection tool, designed to delete all personal information from your Android device without any recovery. And it ' s completely payable to your Android device on the "Clean Slate" state so you can resell it or donate it in a reliable way.
Compared to the usual delete operation, Coolmuster Android Eraser offers you the most effective scanning and data protection solution to permanently delete everything from Android. Ensure that your...
</description></item><item><title>Download DVR Examiner 3.19.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 22:45:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dvr-examiner-5726.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dvr-examiner-5726.html
</guid><description>
DVR Examiner is a software solution to recover video and metadata from DVR surveillance systems clearly. This “game changer” software can help your team save time and money when recovering video evidence by recovering data directly from the DVR, bypassing password for video recovery, including all deleted videos, from a suspicious DVR.
DVR Examiner is capable of overlaying important metadata such as Channel and Date / Time during preview, allowing you to easily evolve a timeline of...
</description></item><item><title>Download WonderFox HD Video Converter Factory Pro 28.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 22:45:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hd-video-converter-factory-pro-1458.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hd-video-converter-factory-pro-1458.html
</guid><description>
WonderFox HD Video Converter Factory Pro is a software powerful video conversion . This program can convert the video files the quality standard of the file SD card, the files HD as HD MP4, HD MKV, HD AVI, HD MTS, HD TRP. This can also in the opposite direction. This software includes more than 100 video formats, while maintaining quality output, faster than 50 times compared to some software. This software also supports VBR or VBR, using this option will keep the original quality of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download The Dude 7.19.6</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 22:44:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-the-dude-3238.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-the-dude-3238.html
</guid><description>
The Dude is a new application by MikroTik which can dramatically improve the way you manage your network environment. It will automatically scan all devices in the subnet is specified, draw and layout a map of your networks, monitor services of your devices and alert you in case some service has problems.is a new application by MikroTik which can dramatically improve the way you manage your network environment. It will automatically scan all devices in the subnet is specified, draw and...
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 7.2.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 22:44:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-11-7760.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-11-7760.html
</guid><description>
TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 is a program that allows users to discover hidden settings in Windows 11. This application is specially designed for Windows 11, groups many registry settings and distribute them from the easy and secure user interface. With TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 you can move the Windows taskbar to the top and resize the taskbar by editing the registry value. With any application that modifies the registry, we recommend that you have a backup copy...
</description></item><item><title>Download Merge VM Professional 24.01.30</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 22:44:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-merge-vm-professional-12414.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-merge-vm-professional-12414.html
</guid><description>
Merge VM Professional stands out as the top choice in the virtual machine market, known for its unmatched speed and comprehensive compatibility. This advanced VM platform is meticulously designed to meet the complex requirements of modern computing environments.
Why should you choose Merge VM Professional?
	Merge VM Professional embodies virtual machine technology, delivering unparalleled speed, ease of use and compatibility. It is the ideal solution for many applications, including...
</description></item><item><title>Download Calcpad 7.3.9</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 22:43:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-calcpad-12576.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-calcpad-12576.html
</guid><description>
Calcpad is free software for mathematical and engineering calculations. It is a flexible and modern programmable calculator with Html report generator. Calcpad uses a simple programming language that is fast and easy to learn. It does not require any special programming skills, which makes it suitable for engineers without any computer programming background. You can create calculation notes simply by writing your formula and text, enclosed in 'quotation marks'.
The program includes...
</description></item><item><title>Download Golden Software Surfer 30.1.218</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 22:43:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-golden-software-surfer-1531.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-golden-software-surfer-1531.html
</guid><description>
Golden Software Surfer is software to create 3D models and mapping data, such as the modeling of ground cover mapping, and 3D depth of the sea... programs Golden Software Surfer this converts the input XYZ into the 3D map could be printed. One of the advantages of this program compared with other rivals as the technical grid, diverse and high flexibility in changing parameters of the grid.
Golden Software Surfer - Create 3D models and mapping data
In this program, you can enter network...
</description></item><item><title>Download GameEx 19.27</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 22:42:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gameex-3108.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gameex-3108.html
</guid><description>
GameEx is a user interface, the whole interface is designed for the the game emulator and the command line application as GameBase, MAME, PC Games, Daphne, and more. Besides, the software can be used as plugin for Windows Media Center or PC solutions Home Theater complete.
This app will work perfectly with products in arcade and various controls and features to support tablets and touch screen strong. This software has two versions: free version and upgraded version. GameEx is very...
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 7.2.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 22:41:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-10-7759.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-10-7759.html
</guid><description>
TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 is a utility that allows users to discover hidden settings in Windows 10. This application is specially designed for Windows 10, groups many registry settings and provide them from an easy and secure user interface. With TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 you can move the Windows taskbar to the top and resize the taskbar by editing the registry value. With any application that modifies the registry, we recommend that you have a backup copy to...
</description></item><item><title>Download CoffeeCup Web Form Builder 2.10 Build 5577</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 22:41:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coffeecup-web-form-builder-2032.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coffeecup-web-form-builder-2032.html
</guid><description>
CoffeeCup Web Form Builder software form design for simple Website with templates built to suit any equipment, increase the rate of send. When using CoffeeCup Web Form Builder you just drag the input field and the form components other into place - voila, a web form has been born! For the sign-up form, form orders, surveys, invitations, applications, contact requests, subscriptions, and anything you can imagine, you can tackle the unlimited possibilities of how many times you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Giada 1.3.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 22:40:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-giada-2790.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-giada-2790.html
</guid><description>
How it works? Just grab your sample drop it in any channel and start the program using software little this as a loop machine, drum machine, create sequence, the sampling directly or host effects (VST). Giada aims to be a virtual device compact and mobile for Linux, Mac OS X and Windows for production use and live sets.
Giada - audio tool
Tweak your sound with sampling directly from the external source, the quantum direct, edit, broadcast integration, the recording action and the edit...
</description></item><item><title>Download Coolmuster Android Assistant 6.0.85</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 22:35:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-android-assistant-226.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-android-assistant-226.html
</guid><description>
Coolmuster Android Assistant is a lightweight application that allows you to export the data important from your mobile device to your computer for safekeeping just in few clicks.
Coolmuster Android Assistant allows you to browse a number of types of data on your mobile device, you, namely the apps, contacts, SMS, music, photos, videos , and books. In case you can't preview the contents of the desired part, then you can fix this minor inconvenience by access to the child folder of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Danil Pristupov Fork 2.12.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 22:34:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fork-6879.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fork-6879.html
</guid><description>
Fork is a great Git client app that allows you to keep tabs on every file line so you can know who is the last person to make changes. The simple and intuitive design of this app helps the management of all of your warehouses much easier. The Fork interface is extremely friendly to users. There is a long list of repositories, branches, origins, tags and archives on the left side of the screen.
With Fork, you can also search and open any of the repositories quickly, from the top of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cypheros TS-Doctor 4.2.15</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 22:33:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cypheros-ts-doctor-9146.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cypheros-ts-doctor-9146.html
</guid><description>
Cypheros TS-Doctor is a software tool designed to edit and repair MPEG2 and H.264 transport streams. Easily create your own movie library, easy, fast and without loss of picture and sound quality. TS-Doctor is the perfect tool for editing and repairing recordings from Sat, Cable and DVB-T Receivers. This software is specifically designed for use with digital TV recordings and can process recordings from a variety of digital TV sources, including satellite, cable and terrestrial...
</description></item><item><title>Download MobiKin Eraser for Android 5.0.19</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 22:33:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mobikin-eraser-for-android-4880.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mobikin-eraser-for-android-4880.html
</guid><description>
MobiKin Eraser for Android is a tools delete Android data professional, this program allows the user to delete all the system settings, data privacy and existing data, etc. from all types of phone or Android tablet without chance of recovery. After delete, device, your like a completely new device and no one can steal any information from it. (Deleted data by this tool is 100% can't be recovered, so please backup important files on your Android.)
MobiKin Eraser for Android very easy to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Broot 1.49.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 22:32:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-broot-8588.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-broot-8588.html
</guid><description>
Broot is an open source command line tool for browsing and navigating file systems. Broot provides a fast and intuitive way to navigate the file system with a tree-like interactive interface. It provides various features like searching for files, opening files and folders, copying file paths to clipboard, etc. It also supports customizing keys and color themes.
Features of Broot
	Fast file browsing: Lets you quickly navigate through large directory structures with a tree-like...
</description></item><item><title>Download Metafox 2.6.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 22:32:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-metafox-2626.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-metafox-2626.html
</guid><description>
Metafox is a software that will allow you to convert video files of different formats to MKV format in a minimal interface and no trouble. The app was created to give users the features required to convert, while not causing users stress too much with the settings and process in the interface. You can even download the file just by dragging it with the mouse into main window, you don't need to do this through the shell.
Batch processing is present in the program, whereby the developer. In...
</description></item><item><title>Download Infinite Guide 1.0.5</title><pubDate> Mon, 15 Sep 2025 19:39:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-infinite-guide-14153.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-infinite-guide-14153.html
</guid><description>
The perfect companion on your photo editing journey. The panel guides you through every step of the editing process and lets you focus on editing without having to memorize every detail. It's the perfect learning tool and a Photoshop user's best friend. You'll never have to remember all the little details again.
Advanced Machine Learning Algorithms
When editing face photos, many tools often require specific settings based on the size of the photo. With our advanced algorithms, the tool...
</description></item></channel></rss>