<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 03:30:22 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 03:30:22 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Text Editor Pro 34.1.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 13 Oct 2025 01:14:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-text-editor-pro-800.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-text-editor-pro-800.html
</guid><description>
Text Editor Pro is software to handle text, HTML, Perl, Ruby, or Fortran with features syntax highlighting, professional. Text Editor provides syntax highlighting for over 50 scripts and has a simple interface and easy access. In addition, the Text Editor Pro also supports more than 50 programming languages like C ++, COBOL, graph DOT, DSP, DWScript, Fortran, Foxpro, Java, Perl, Python, Ruby, SQL and many other languages.
Text Editor Pro - text Processing professional
The software can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Double Commander 1.1.29</title><pubDate> Sun, 12 Oct 2025 23:13:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-double-commander-7801.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-double-commander-7801.html
</guid><description>
Double Commander is an open source file manager with two panels side by side. The idea is based on Total Commander but with new and different features. Double Commander has multi-rename tool, tabbed interface, custom columns, internal text editor, built-in file viewer, archive support (ZIP, RAR), extensive search functionality, configurable button bar, file activity logging, plug-in support and more.
Features of Double Commander
	Internal text editor (F4) with syntax...
</description></item><item><title>Download Q-Dir 12.38</title><pubDate> Sun, 12 Oct 2025 23:13:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-q-dir-348.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-q-dir-348.html
</guid><description>
Q-Dir is software to manage the entire file and folder on the computer, allowing to see file in same time 4 different positions (viewport quadro) while still maintaining all the standard features of the Explorer.
It also provides a variety of management features, additional files included the filter file color-coding, layouts and columns can be customized, quick access to file and folder favorites and more.
Other features of Q-Dir , including directory listings (.txt, .doc .html .csv),...
</description></item><item><title>Download W10 Digital Activation 1.5.5.5</title><pubDate> Sun, 12 Oct 2025 23:12:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-10-digital-activation-program-5653.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-10-digital-activation-program-5653.html
</guid><description>
Windows 10 Digital Activation Program is a W10 digital license activation program based on s1ave77's HWID Trigger to activate Windows 10 PERMANENTLY with a Digital License.
Using Windows 10 Digital Activation Program to activate Windows 10 is very safe because it does not install anything on the computer system. In short, this is a tool from Ratiborus for activating Windows 10 using a digital license.
The software easily activates all versions of Windows 10 like:
	Windows 10...
</description></item><item><title>Download Beauty Box Photo for Photoshop 6.0.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 12 Oct 2025 23:10:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-beauty-box-for-photoshop-12578.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-beauty-box-for-photoshop-12578.html
</guid><description>
Beauty Box for Photoshop is a powerful skin retouching plugin designed for Adobe Photoshop, aimed at simplifying the process of enhancing your portraits and images. It allows you to quickly and easily erase skin blemishes and wrinkles, even out skin tone and reduce shine – achieving consistent professional results. This plugin uses advanced skin smoothing techniques that enhance the work of photographers of all levels in Adobe Photoshop. Plus, over 30 new presets let you apply a...
</description></item><item><title>Download OkMap Desktop 19.2.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 12 Oct 2025 23:09:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-okmap-desktop-581.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-okmap-desktop-581.html
</guid><description>
OkMap Desktop is interactive software working on the computer with web maps or digital maps bought or scanned. OkMap can also import a data vector from the most common formats and data DEM related to information height.
Through the map you can organize your path by creating waypoints , routesand tracks on the screen your computer, and upload this data to your GPS . OkMap set data high speedautomatic and estimated moving time . Furthermore OkMap provides you also have autorouting and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Flicker Free for After Effects and Premiere Pro 3.0.3</title><pubDate> Sun, 12 Oct 2025 23:09:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-flicker-free-for-after-effects-and-premiere-pro-12635.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-flicker-free-for-after-effects-and-premiere-pro-12635.html
</guid><description>
Flicker Free is a powerful and simple way to remove flicker from your videos. It offers presets for different types of footage, making it easy to remove flicker caused by out-of-sync cameras, time-lapse, or slow-motion video. Flicker Free will work on any size footage and is compatible with many video editing applications such as After Effects, Premiere Pro.
Main features
Remove from LED lights, Time Lapse and more
	Flicker Free was originally designed to eliminate Time-Lapse...
</description></item><item><title>Download Beauty Box Video for After Effects &amp;amp; Premiere Pro 6.0.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 12 Oct 2025 23:08:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-beauty-box-video-for-after-effects-premiere-pro-12591.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-beauty-box-video-for-after-effects-premiere-pro-12591.html
</guid><description>
Digital Anarchy's Beauty Box Video is a powerful skin retouching plugin designed for use in Adobe After Effects and Premiere Pro. This plugin streamlines the process of enhancing skin tones and removing imperfections, allowing editors to achieve professional results with minimal effort.
Beauty Box Video will assist in this digital skin and makeup editing by automatically identifying skin tones and creating masks that limit the smoothing effect on skin areas. Simply apply a video filter,...
</description></item><item><title>Download AllMapSoft Offline Map Maker 8.357</title><pubDate> Sun, 12 Oct 2025 23:07:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-offline-map-maker-656.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-offline-map-maker-656.html
</guid><description>
AllMapSoft Offline Map Maker is software create, organize, offline map from Google Maps, Yahoo maps, Bing maps and Openstreetmap. You can view offline maps downloaded with map viewer offline. And you can zoom out or zoom in the offline map or export map under the file format .BMP with file world xxx.bpw, and can output files xxx.map for OziExplorer. If you want to make a offline map of your city by yourself, it is very useful for you.
Features AllMapSoft Offline Map Maker
	You can...
</description></item><item><title>Download ManicTime Pro 2025.2.3</title><pubDate> Sun, 12 Oct 2025 23:07:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-manictime-18.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-manictime-18.html
</guid><description>
ManicTime is a software automatically collect information about how to use your computer. It records the time of operation of the machine, see the change data in the machine, how much data you share, received on or moved away, what software you use, use at any time
ManicTime allows you to keep up the work of the staff, send progress reports accurately and manage your time better than ever. This type of software can help your business more efficient when it comes to the internal problems...
</description></item><item><title>Download InstaBot Pro 7.2.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 12 Oct 2025 23:06:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-instabot-pro-8820.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-instabot-pro-8820.html
</guid><description>
InstaBot Pro is a piece of software designed to automate your “likes”, finding new followers profiled by similar accounts and Get your followers really interested in your content. Everyone knows now that the success of an instagram account also depends on the interactions and activity level of that particular account in the community.
Features of InstaBot Pro
	GET FOLLOWERS: Export followers of other profiles and/or users based on specific Hashtags.
	AUTO FOLLOW: Automatically...
</description></item><item><title>Download Light Wrap Fantastic 1.3.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 12 Oct 2025 23:01:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-light-wrap-fantastic-12636.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-light-wrap-fantastic-12636.html
</guid><description>
Light Wrap Fantastic enables the creation of better collages by easily allowing users to blend the background with the foreground in such a way that the background's lighting affects the foreground. Basically simulates a backlight. The plugin has all the controls you need to create a realistic light overlay, making the process quick and easy.
Main features
	A plugin for more convincing composite images: Creating convincing green/blue screen composite images is always a...
</description></item><item><title>Download Digital Anarchy Beauty Box Video 6.0.2 for DaVinci Resolve and Nuke (OFX)</title><pubDate> Sun, 12 Oct 2025 23:00:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-digital-anarchy-beauty-box-video-6557.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-digital-anarchy-beauty-box-video-6557.html
</guid><description>
Digital Anarchy Beauty Box Video is a plugins that allows you to automatically determine the skin tone and create a mask that limits the effect of smoothing only to the skin regions. Just apply the filter, to filter the video analysis, set a few smoothing options and to add a display plugin to make the skin editing very easy.
Digital Anarchy Beauty Box Video acts as the digital makeup in the post-production process by combining the detection algorithms and the modern skin smoothing and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Samurai Sharpen Video 1.3.0 for After Effects &amp;amp; Premiere Pro</title><pubDate> Sun, 12 Oct 2025 23:00:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-samurai-sharpen-video-for-after-effects-and-premiere-pro-12634.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-samurai-sharpen-video-for-after-effects-and-premiere-pro-12634.html
</guid><description>
Samurai Sharpen Video is a specialized video sharpening plugin developed by Digital Anarchy, designed to enhance the clarity and detail of video footage without creating unwanted artifacts.
Video footage is often a bit soft, and making improvements to sharpen certain details can make a big difference. Samurai Sharpen lets you do this quickly with tools designed to make it easy for you to isolate specific areas of your footage and sharpen only those areas. This is advanced sharpening...
</description></item><item><title>Download AllMapSoft Universal Maps Downloader 10.227</title><pubDate> Sun, 12 Oct 2025 22:59:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-universal-maps-downloader-736.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-universal-maps-downloader-736.html
</guid><description>
AllMapSoft Universal Maps Downloader is software download map images on the computer for offline viewing support many types such as Google Maps, Yahoo maps, Bing maps, OpenStreet Maps, Yandex Maps, Ovi Maps, MapQuest Maps. All the downloaded photos will be saved on disk. You can view downloaded maps by Maps Viewer Or you can combine them into one big bmp, or jpg file tif by Maps Combiner, and also you can export all the tiles into a database format MBTiles.
AllMapSoft Universal Maps...
</description></item><item><title>Download Beauty Box Photo for Lightroom 6.0.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 12 Oct 2025 22:58:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-beauty-box-for-lightroom-12579.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-beauty-box-for-lightroom-12579.html
</guid><description>
Beauty Box by Digital Anarchy is a powerful skin editing plugin designed for both Adobe Photoshop and Lightroom, for photographers and digital artists who want to improve their images quickly and effective. This digital makeup and skin retouching plugin automatically determines skin tones and creates masks that limit the smoothing effect to skin areas. Just apply a video filter, let it analyze the footage, set a few smoothing options, and let the plugin render to make skin retouching...
</description></item><item><title>Download Flownex Simulation Environment 2025 R3 v9.0.4.6127</title><pubDate> Sun, 12 Oct 2025 22:57:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-flownex-simulation-environment-10276.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-flownex-simulation-environment-10276.html
</guid><description>
Flownex Simulation Environment provides technology that allows you to study how systems will operate in the real world, where fluids are the driving factor. It relays the overall impact of changing specific characteristics on components, allowing customers to comprehensively test all possible system variations in system design and optimization.
	Turbine blade cooling: By combining 1D flow Flownex models with 3D heat transfer models in ANSYS Mechanical or CFX, detailed turbine blade...
</description></item><item><title>Download SQL Backup Master 8.0.985 Enterprise</title><pubDate> Sun, 12 Oct 2025 22:55:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sql-backup-master-6687.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sql-backup-master-6687.html
</guid><description>
SQL Backup Master backup your SQL Server database into any popular cloud hosting service such as Dropbox, OneDrive, Amazon S3, Microsoft Azure, Box and Google Drive. It can also backup the database to the FTP server-or a directory on your local machine, network server or storage device.
The backup of your SQL Server database to the cloud will not be complex or expensive. SQL Backup Master is born by providing an easy way to download copies of your database to one or more of the most...
</description></item><item><title>Download Digital Anarchy Flicker Free OFX 3.0.3 for DaVinci Resolve and Nuke</title><pubDate> Sun, 12 Oct 2025 22:54:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-digital-anarchy-flicker-free-ofx-11150.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-digital-anarchy-flicker-free-ofx-11150.html
</guid><description>
Digital Anarchy Flicker Free OFX is a plugin designed for video editing and compositing software that supports the OFX (OpenFX) standard. It was developed by Digital Anarchy, a software company known for creating various plugins and tools for video editors and visual effects artists.
Flicker Free OFX is specifically designed to solve the problem of flickering or inconsistent lighting in video footage. Flicker can occur in video for a variety of reasons, including changes in lighting...
</description></item><item><title>Download TexSender Pro 8.9.8</title><pubDate> Sun, 12 Oct 2025 22:53:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-texsender-pro-9550.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-texsender-pro-9550.html
</guid><description>
TexSender Pro is a software designed for those who want to send Telegram messages directly from their PC in a simple and efficient way. TexSender requires no API and uses Telegram Web technology to automate various activities like sending messages, adding members to your group, etc. This is more and more popular.
Features of TexSender Pro
	Create and send personalized messages to Telegram contacts or user lists (list of phone numbers or usernames). Messages can be sent with alternate...
</description></item><item><title>Download Easy Gamer Utility Pro 1.3.85</title><pubDate> Sun, 12 Oct 2025 22:53:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easy-gamer-utility-pro-12381.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easy-gamer-utility-pro-12381.html
</guid><description>
Easy Gamer Utility Pro is an easy-to-use program for Windows that can do a lot on your PC to help fix gaming problems, performance problems, and general optimization! The best tool to improve your Windows gaming experience! Is your game laggy and slow? If so, you can use the built-in game accelerator in Easy Gamer Utility, which boosts system performance, makes games run smoother, and increases FPS.
Additionally, this handy utility deletes and cleans unwanted and unnecessary temporary...
</description></item><item><title>Download Digital Anarchy Samurai Sharpen Video OFX 1.3.0 for DaVinci Resolve and Nuke</title><pubDate> Sun, 12 Oct 2025 22:52:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-digital-anarchy-samurai-ofx-11151.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-digital-anarchy-samurai-ofx-11151.html
</guid><description>
Easily enhance your footage with Samurai Sharpen for video. Video footage is often a bit soft, and enhancing it to sharpen certain details can make a difference. Samurai Sharpen lets you do this quickly with tools designed to make it easy for you to isolate specific areas of your footage and sharpen only those areas. It's advanced sharpening technology makes video footage precise and simple.
Built-in masking tools let you protect shadows and highlights from sharpening. This is important...
</description></item><item><title>Download Flicker Free for Media Composer 3.0.3</title><pubDate> Sun, 12 Oct 2025 22:50:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-flicker-free-for-media-composer-14134.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-flicker-free-for-media-composer-14134.html
</guid><description>
Flicker Free is a plugin developed by Digital Anarchy designed to remove flicker from video footage. The plugin easily handles flicker from sources such as LED lights, fluorescent lights, time-lapse videos, archived footage, slow motion, and computer monitor images. Users can apply Flicker Free to their clips in Media Composer by dragging the effect onto the clip and adjusting simple settings as needed, with presets available for different flickering issues.
Remove flicker from LEDs,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Beauty Box Video 6.0.2 for Media Composer</title><pubDate> Sun, 12 Oct 2025 22:49:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-beauty-box-video-for-media-composer-14133.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-beauty-box-video-for-media-composer-14133.html
</guid><description>
Beauty Box Video for Media Composer is a powerful digital makeup and skin retouching plugin designed to automatically detect skin tones in video footage and create masks that apply skin smoothing effects only to skin areas. Usage is simple: after applying the plugin to a clip, you click the "Analyze Frame" button to automatically detect skin tones and create a mask. The plugin then smooths out wrinkles and blemishes, while keeping important facial details sharp, creating a natural and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Samurai Sharpen Video for Media Composer 1.3.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 12 Oct 2025 20:06:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-samurai-sharpen-video-for-media-composer-14226.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-samurai-sharpen-video-for-media-composer-14226.html
</guid><description>
Easily Enhance Your Footage with Samurai Sharpen for Video. Video footage is often a little blurry, and boosting it to sharpen certain details can make a big difference. Samurai Sharpen lets you do this quickly with tools designed to make it easy to isolate specific areas of your footage and sharpen just those areas. This is advanced sharpening technology for video footage, precise and simple.
Sharpen Only Important Features of Video with Edge Detection Algorithm
You often want to...
</description></item></channel></rss>