<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:57:28 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:57:28 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download MSI Dragon Center 2.0.152.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jan 2026 23:14:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-msi-dragon-center-7095.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-msi-dragon-center-7095.html
</guid><description>
MSI Dragon Center is an official control panel for MSI computers that enables you to get the most out of your MSI experience by enhancing per-key RGB lighting, tones, and tones. bar, get information about the cooling system, or change the display. With MSI Dragon Center, you can closely monitor CPU, GPU and RAM performance to optimize your PC's performance while gaming.
Features of MSI Dragon Center:
	Optimize gaming performance with just 1 click.
	Free up memory, prioritize system...
</description></item><item><title>Download EaseUS Fixo Technician 4.2.5 Build 20260109</title><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jan 2026 23:12:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-fixo-9814.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-fixo-9814.html
</guid><description>
Video is corrupted or inaccessible after power failure and sudden blackout, whole system crash, update failure, wrong file handling or some other reason? EaseUS Fixo allows you to repair many different video file formats including MOV, MP4, M2TS, MKV, MTS, 3GP, etc. easier no matter how broken it is.
It can intelligently and intelligently repair damaged and damaged photos from computers or other external storage devices such as USB flash drives, memory cards, SD cards, digital cameras...
</description></item><item><title>Download AI Video FaceSwap 2.0.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jan 2026 23:11:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ai-video-faceswap-12166.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ai-video-faceswap-12166.html
</guid><description>
AI Video FaceSwap is a technology that uses artificial intelligence algorithms to swap or replace faces in videos. It automatically detects and tracks faces in videos, extracts facial features and expressions, then applies another face to those detected regions. This technology allows for realistic manipulation of video, creating entertaining and sometimes humorous effects.
AI algorithm detects and tracks faces in a video sequence. It identifies facial landmarks to understand the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tor Browser 15.0.4</title><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jan 2026 23:11:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tor-browser-1833.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tor-browser-1833.html
</guid><description>
Tor Browser also has full name is Tor Browser Bundle is a web browser give you ability to access the internet safety and security your personal information as well as sensitive documents absolutely. By Tor Browser Bundle will automatically change the IP address on the machine to hide the identity when surfing the web. Tor Browser is free web browser full-featured basic and advanced allows you to leverage the Tor network anonymously without need to make any configuration changes or install...
</description></item><item><title>Download Fast Video Cutter Joiner 6.9.6</title><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jan 2026 23:10:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fast-video-cutter-joiner-7542.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fast-video-cutter-joiner-7542.html
</guid><description>
Fast Video Cutter Joiner is a fast video cutter and joiner with an easy to use interface. It allows users to trim parts of a video quickly while maintaining the quality of the original video. It supports various formats like AVI, MPEG, MP4, WMV, 3GP, FLV...
This tool helps you to cut video files into small parts, to keep only the parts you need and remove unwanted parts like trailers and advertisements in a movie. The clips you cut can then be used for other video productions or for a...
</description></item><item><title>Download Musify 5.2.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jan 2026 23:10:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musify-4422.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musify-4422.html
</guid><description>
Musify is the convert YouTube Music best can download music from more than 1000 website share music to listen to offline without reducing sound quality. Such as: YouTube, Spotify, SoundCloud, Facebook, Instragram, and more. Easily convert music files mp3 to iPhone, iPad, iPod, Samsung and iOS devices and other Android. High speed and high quality. Musify is a YouTube converter is very efficient and fast, support format converting YouTube to MP3. You can batch convert mp3 files at the same...
</description></item><item><title>Download XnView Shell Extension (XnShell) 4.2.5</title><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jan 2026 23:09:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xnview-shell-extension-8025.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xnview-shell-extension-8025.html
</guid><description>
XnView Shell Extension (XnShell) is a powerful shell extension for Windows Explorer that allows you to preview and perform various operations in the context menu of Windows Explorer. It gives you the ability to view thumbnails and general information about the photo, namely file name and size, rotate the image to different angles or based on EXIF data, flip the image as well as copy the current photo to the clipboard to paste the image into other third-party utilities.
When it comes to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ashampoo WinOptimizer 2026 v28.00.20</title><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jan 2026 23:09:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-winoptimizer-870.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-winoptimizer-870.html
</guid><description>
Ashampoo WinOptimizer is a software cleanup, optimize and protect your PC. It frees up disk space, fix errors on computer. WinOptimizer has overcome the shortcomings of Windows and give you a system faster, leaner and leaner. Many features automated features make setting it up a problem is only a few clicks of the mouse most simple.
Ashampoo WinOptimizer - Clean optimize PC
Ashampoo WinOptimizer provides instant access to your system, you can look and feel the way that best suits you....
</description></item><item><title>Download MemoryCleaner 1.9.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jan 2026 23:08:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-memorycleaner-12469.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-memorycleaner-12469.html
</guid><description>
MemoryCleaner is a tool to free up memory on your computer. This is a free app with a simple user interface that makes it easy for users of all skill levels to use. MemoryCleaner uses many functions built into Windows to free up memory without affecting your system. You can also access Memory Cleaner's functions right from the system tray without having to open the program. The cleaning processes are silent and the only time you see a warning is to briefly display the amount of RAM...
</description></item><item><title>Download Argente System Repair 1.0.4.7</title><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jan 2026 23:07:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-argente-system-repair-13813.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-argente-system-repair-13813.html
</guid><description>
Argente System Repair is a lightweight utility designed to diagnose and fix common Windows system problems. It scans your system to identify errors in operating system components, file systems, installation files, and other system components, and then applies targeted fixes to resolve these problems. The tool provides different scan modes, including simple scan, recommended scan, and custom scan, allowing users to customize the repair process according to their needs.
System Repair...
</description></item><item><title>Download 4DDiG Partition Manager 3.9.2.19</title><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jan 2026 23:07:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4ddig-partition-manager-2024-9781.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4ddig-partition-manager-2024-9781.html
</guid><description>
4DDiG Partition Manager is a powerful Windows disk partition software expert in system migration, disk cloning and disk partition management. It can effectively clone your entire disk or partition, providing a reliable solution for data backup.
This is Windows 10 fast system and data transfer solution &amp;amp; 11. 4DDiG Partition Manager can move the system and large files or folders from one disk partition to a larger one with just one click. Or you can use it to move the system and large...
</description></item><item><title>Download MusConv 4.10.446 Lifetime</title><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jan 2026 23:03:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html
</guid><description>
MusConv transfers playlists, albums, followed artists and liked songs across a variety of services – Spotify, Apple Music, Amazon Music, YouTube, YouTube Music, iTunes, Deezer, Tidal, SoundCloud, Pandora and more 125 music services!
Features of MusConv Ultimate
	Transfer playlists, albums, followed artists and liked tracks between over 125 music servicesManage playlists (Delete, Merge, Split, Copy...)
	More than 125 music services supported
	Access DAILY updated music charts on...
</description></item><item><title>Download FrontFace Lockdown Tool 5.5.4</title><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jan 2026 22:58:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-frontface-lockdown-tool-6281.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-frontface-lockdown-tool-6281.html
</guid><description>
FrontFace Lockdown Tool is software that allows you to protect and lock any Windows PC to use as a public kiosk terminal, digital signage application or other non-monitoring use. The program allows you to disable multiple features and functionality of Windows to prevent users from making changes to the operating system. This includes options to hide the system tray, turn off the Machine and Log out, disable the Windows key and Task Manager, prevent changes in the password, turn off the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Perfinity dotNET Runtime Analyzer 9.0.15</title><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jan 2026 22:58:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfinity-dotnet-runtime-analyzer-10650.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfinity-dotnet-runtime-analyzer-10650.html
</guid><description>
Perfinity dotNET Runtime Analyzer is a powerful line-level pattern analyzer that provides functionality to identify performance bottlenecks in applications. In contrast to the classic .NET profiler, it allows users to analyze processes using native code. Therefore, performance issues caused by native code can be identified, for example, from 3rd party libraries like the .NET runtime.
In addition, the tool supports event tracking to maximize user experience. File I/O activity, network...
</description></item><item><title>Download EverNote 10.171.1.44382</title><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jan 2026 22:44:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-evernote-3261.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-evernote-3261.html
</guid><description>
EverNote is the all in one tool allows you to track notes, todo items, memos, outlines, excerpts, websites, ideas and other things and automatically synchronize them between multiple computers and mobile devices (iPhone, Android, etc.). You can choose to sort their notes into categories, password protect them, export them to XML and more. EverNote supports a number of pattern notes allow you to add to-do list, spreadsheet like Excel to calculate costs (automatic sum), notes, phone, contact...
</description></item><item><title>Download DupliScan 1.0.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jan 2026 20:06:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dupliscan-14487.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dupliscan-14487.html
</guid><description>
DupiScan is a privacy-friendly tool for detecting and managing duplicate files. All analysis is performed locally on your device — no cloud, no data transfer required.
Features of DupliScan
	Fast scanning of folders and drives
	Reliable duplicate detection by comparing hash codes
	Option to automatically ignore empty files
	Clear and structured display of all duplicate groups
	Efficient processing of datasets
	Securely delete selected duplicate files
DupiScan helps you free up...
</description></item><item><title>Download Alfred Xavier Eclipse PDF 1.0.7</title><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jan 2026 20:01:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-alfred-xavier-eclipse-pdf-14486.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-alfred-xavier-eclipse-pdf-14486.html
</guid><description>
Eclipse PDF is a modern, lightweight PDF reader designed for maximum comfort and security. Unlike traditional PDF applications, Eclipse PDF focuses on your vision and your data. Switch between Dark, Sepia, and Warm reading modes, fine-tune brightness and contrast, and enjoy a clean, distraction-free design.
Eclipse PDF works completely offline, ad-free, requires no login, and collects no data — your documents are always secure on your device. Whether you're studying, working, or...
</description></item><item><title>Download Network Password Decryptor 11.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jan 2026 19:56:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-network-password-decryptor-14485.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-network-password-decryptor-14485.html
</guid><description>
Network Password Decryptor is a free tool that instantly recovers network authentication passwords stored on your system. Besides network authentication passwords, it can also recover passwords stored by other Windows applications such as Outlook, Windows Live Messenger, Remote Desktop, etc.
These network passwords are stored in encrypted form and even administrators cannot view them. Furthermore, some types of passwords cannot be decrypted even by administrators because they require...
</description></item><item><title>Download Logitech Options 10.26.14</title><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jan 2026 19:50:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-logitech-options-14484.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-logitech-options-14484.html
</guid><description>
The goal is to make things easier and more efficient. How you do it is up to you. The Logi Options+ app lets you customize all supported devices, including mice, keyboards, lighting, webcams, touchpads, presentation controls, and the MX Creative Console. Get more done with the easy-to-use Options+ app.
Device Management
Software monitors battery life and provides notifications when the battery is low or device statuses like Caps Lock. It supports configurations for different...
</description></item><item><title>Download Garmin Express 7.28</title><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jan 2026 17:34:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-garmin-express-1579.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-garmin-express-1579.html
</guid><description>
Garmin Express is a tool developed by the company Garmin to enable you to manage equipment on your GPS from the computer. You can use this app to map updates, register the device, update software and even to create a backup. Garmin Express also allows you to install voices and vehicles for free, as well as download instructions for use product.
Garmin Express - Manage GPS devices
You can automatically update the map by only one click, so you always have accurate information when you go...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Acrobat Reader DC 2025.001.21078</title><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jan 2026 17:25:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-acrobat-reader-3707.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-acrobat-reader-3707.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Acrobat Reader DC is a system of application software and Web services developed by Adobe Systems to view, create, manipulate, print and manage PDF files. With Adobe Acrobat Reader DC, you can create, export, edit, and track PDF files from anywhere - and maintain connection with the recent set of files on all your devices.
Adobe Acrobat Reader current DC is connected with Adobe Document Cloud - help working on the computers and mobile devices becomes easier than ever before. This is...
</description></item><item><title>Download DesktopPic 2.0.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jan 2026 17:23:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktoppic-7444.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktoppic-7444.html
</guid><description>
DesktopPic allows you to display or watermark images on your Windows desktop wallpaper. Display one or more pictures in a resizable, movable window with no borders or captions, so all you see is the photo. This will give the illusion of the image being part of your wallpaper, but it's really just another window. Any icons on the desktop in the same area as the image will be masked. Bitmap image formats, such as PNG (recommended), JPG, BMP and animated GIF are supported.
Features of...
</description></item><item><title>Download TidyWindow 3.8.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jan 2026 17:12:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tidywindow-14454.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tidywindow-14454.html
</guid><description>
TidyWindow is a Windows desktop assistant that automates developer PC setup, cleanup, diagnostics, software package installation, registry tweaking, and driver updates—powered by a WPF interface and robust PowerShell 7 automation capabilities in the background.
Key Features
	Essentials Repair Center (docs/essentials.md): Queues selected automation tasks Filter for network, Defender, printing, and Windows Update issues. Each task supports preview run, sequential execution, restore...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinBin2Iso 6.61</title><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jan 2026 17:11:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winbin2iso-1777.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winbin2iso-1777.html
</guid><description>
WinBin2Iso is a small program and simple application that allows you to convert the file .bin format .iso. WinBin2Iso support files larger than 2 gigabytes and does not require installation. The interface is quite simple WinBin2Iso only 1 window embodying the features of the software, you can choose the button WinBin2Iso to convert images bin to iso then choose select folder containing source files and output, all the settings are done in just a few seconds for you to implement features of...
</description></item><item><title>Download DBF Recovery 4.64</title><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jan 2026 17:10:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbf-recovery-7931.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbf-recovery-7931.html
</guid><description>
DBF Recovery is software that gives users the ability to restore a damaged database back to its original condition without the expertise required to complete that task. It fixes headers and data structures in an automated process that doesn't involve user interaction. With DBF Recovery, you will truly have a lean, honest DBF repair machine without any functionality.
Features of DBF Recovery
	Quick and simple to use DBF file repair software.
	Repair almost any DBF...
</description></item></channel></rss>