<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:08:17 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:08:17 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Q-Dir 12.37</title><pubDate> Wed, 08 Oct 2025 23:50:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-q-dir-348.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-q-dir-348.html
</guid><description>
Q-Dir is software to manage the entire file and folder on the computer, allowing to see file in same time 4 different positions (viewport quadro) while still maintaining all the standard features of the Explorer.
It also provides a variety of management features, additional files included the filter file color-coding, layouts and columns can be customized, quick access to file and folder favorites and more.
Other features of Q-Dir , including directory listings (.txt, .doc .html .csv),...
</description></item><item><title>Download PhotoPad Image Editor Pro 14.44</title><pubDate> Wed, 08 Oct 2025 23:41:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photopad-image-editor-572.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photopad-image-editor-572.html
</guid><description>
PhotoPad Image Editor is a software to help edit photos and supports lots of features like edit, cut, rotate, resize and flip digital photos. With PhotoPad Image Editor, you can freely perform the basic editing for their images and also can add some neat effect. It has the option to create a photo collage and mosaic images from your photos, and you can also add text and captions. If you prefer, you can complete your masterpiece by adding the frame or contour is simple.
The main features...
</description></item><item><title>Download Windows 11 Enterprise 25H2 v26200.6725 NoTPM Multilingual Preactivated</title><pubDate> Wed, 08 Oct 2025 23:41:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-11-pro-enterprise-untouched-6672.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-11-pro-enterprise-untouched-6672.html
</guid><description>
Windows 11 is the latest version of the Windows operating system released, with new interfaces and other new features such as the new Microsoft Store, the new source of personalized data supported by AI and the best browser performance in the segment from Microsoft Edge, the chat from Microsoft Teams is integrated in the taskbar and more!
Attention when installing Windows 11 Pro Enterprise: The settings environment and Windows installation is to upgrade from the Windows 10 20H2 ISO,...
</description></item><item><title>Download SysNucleus WebHarvy 7.8.0.244</title><pubDate> Wed, 08 Oct 2025 23:40:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sysnucleus-webharvy-881.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sysnucleus-webharvy-881.html
</guid><description>
SysNucleus WebHarvy is software to extract data website such as Text, image, URL &amp;amp; email from the website and save the content... WebHarvy is a tool which scans website intuitive. Absolutely no need to write any scripts or code to scrape data. You will use the browser built-in of WebHarvy to navigate the website.
WebHarvy automatically identifies patterns of data occurring in web pages. So if you need a list of items (name, address, email, price etc) from a website, you do not need to...
</description></item><item><title>Download MultiBoot 2k10 DVD/USB/HDD 7.40 Unofficial</title><pubDate> Wed, 08 Oct 2025 23:40:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-multiboot-2k10-6897.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-multiboot-2k10-6897.html
</guid><description>
MultiBoot 2k10 is a system administrator's boot disk, the main purpose of which is to prepare the hard disk, as well as install the operating system, including designing and unpacking. system image, data recovery after various failures. In addition, the disc will be useful for cleaning the system from many malicious programs, as well as for testing a variety of computer components, with the provision of detailed reports. All the programs in this set are combined under a single installer...
</description></item><item><title>Download IK Multimedia AmpliTube 5 MAX v5.10.7</title><pubDate> Wed, 08 Oct 2025 23:39:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ik-multimedia-amplitube-1317.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ik-multimedia-amplitube-1317.html
</guid><description>
IK Multimedia AmpliTube 4 Complete is a music studio guitar and bass for Mac / PC works as a standalone application and as a plugin for DAW. AmpliTube recreates the entire signal chain guitar / bass from musical instruments to recording equipment, and made it a very practical and intuitive. But it's also doing it in ways you never dreamed possible. If you're not familiar with the use of the computer to get the guitar tone great, then you will be treated. If you are a master of sound...
</description></item><item><title>Download WavePad Sound Editor Master 20.45</title><pubDate> Wed, 08 Oct 2025 23:38:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wavepad-sound-editor-1149.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wavepad-sound-editor-1149.html
</guid><description>
WavePad Sound Editor is editor software and improve the quality of sound create recordings music best quality. WavePad is mootij in the editor software sound good for the computer are configured midrange and low. Because WavePad very compact only about 4MB of space is you already own the software editor sounds good.
WavePad Sound Editor - Side audio quality
WavePad help you edit audio created the Nightcore quality. WavePad Sound Editor there are many options is very impressive as add...
</description></item><item><title>Download PTC Creo View 12.1.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 08 Oct 2025 23:38:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ptc-creo-view-1726.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ptc-creo-view-1726.html
</guid><description>
PTC Creo View allows users to share information 3D CAD internally and with partners and suppliers outside the organization. Does not need software to create data or CAD skills for professional use. PTC Creo View support drawings and documents from many different sources. With Creo View, you are on the go for faster and quality reviews design, improved collaboration, and better products with lower cost.
PTC Creo View
The main features of PTC Creo View
	Data management products:...
</description></item><item><title>Download PTC Creo Illustrate 12.1.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 08 Oct 2025 23:37:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ptc-creo-illustrate-1740.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ptc-creo-illustrate-1740.html
</guid><description>
With the software product development Creo, you can bring your product from idea to prototype digital and do so with efficiency, accuracy and a measure of grace. Our software is intuitive and all work together. PTC Inc., the company specializes in software design, 2D &amp;amp; 3D, management product life cycle (PLM) solutions and managed services, has released Illustrate 6.0.0 incorporate the ability to illustrate with 3D CAD data link to provide specific information about configuration for...
</description></item><item><title>Download Global Mapper Pro 26.2.0 Build 100725</title><pubDate> Wed, 08 Oct 2025 23:36:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-global-mapper-3563.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-global-mapper-3563.html
</guid><description>
Global Mapper is a GIS application affordable and easy-to-use application that provides access to a great variety of spatial data sets and provides just the right level functionality to satisfy both GIS experts and experience users started. Also similar to a tool management data space independently and as an integral component of a GIS system enterprise-wide, Global Mapper is the tool mandatory for anyone working with maps or spatial data.
Global Mapper - GIS application
Global Mapper...
</description></item><item><title>Download DeskSoft EarthView 7.13.11</title><pubDate> Wed, 08 Oct 2025 23:36:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desksoft-earthview-184.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desksoft-earthview-184.html
</guid><description>
With software DeskSoft EarthView you can easily create wallpapers to your computer or select screen saver of your favorite. the program can change day and night, the clouds will also change according to weather conditions current on one or another part of the earth, you can see the lights of the city.
Features of DeskSoft EarthView can be interesting, because of DeskSoft EarthView support for day and night, you can view atmospheric phenomena, light city can see, the cloud is displayed,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Vivaldi Browser 7.6.3797.63</title><pubDate> Wed, 08 Oct 2025 23:35:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vivaldi-159.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vivaldi-159.html
</guid><description>
Vivaldi is a browser designed for users who have power and offer the option to customize high. You can choose the location of the tabs and the address bar, put the hotkeys for the common tasks and many other features. Also, Vivaldi also provides a number of improvements such as Tab Stacks to group multiple open tabs into a tab, leads to interface less cluttered. Can notes and added a screenshot of a web page while browsing, storing an attachment, and add the URL to easily sort and locate...
</description></item><item><title>Download Vivaldi for macOS 7.6.3797.63</title><pubDate> Wed, 08 Oct 2025 23:35:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/mac/download-vivaldi-for-macos-3443.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/mac/download-vivaldi-for-macos-3443.html
</guid><description>
The Vivaldi for MacOS browser does not track users and offers more features than any other modern browser. Managed by Jon von Tetzchner (co-founder of Opera browser), Vivaldi for MacOS is driven by the real needs of today's users and ensures that they have the best tools to browse and get work done.
Vivaldi for MacOS - Modern web browser
Users can adjust Vivaldi to suit their browsing needs them without limiting customization options. Vivaldi takes the browser to the next level with a...
</description></item><item><title>Download TeamViewer 15.70.5 + Portable</title><pubDate> Wed, 08 Oct 2025 23:35:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-teamviewer-528.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-teamviewer-528.html
</guid><description>
TeamViewer is software that functions to connect and control the remote computer, the ability to connect with any system anywhere from all over the place. This is a support tool users is very convenient. TeamViewer to help users control remote computer becomes much more simple, help you interact and collaborate with others in the exchange and share of information, instruction manual, application software or fix the computer.
TeamViewer as a revolution of computer science. when you have...
</description></item><item><title>Download Lansweeper 12.5.6.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 08 Oct 2025 23:34:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lansweeper-2011.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lansweeper-2011.html
</guid><description>
Lansweeper is an application to manage IT assets and the scanning device is connected to the network. This software can scan and identify all network devices have workstation IP and Windows, Linux and Mac and indexing for them. Deep Scan Engine this software uses a set of protocols to detect and receive data from any device connected to the network. All data received can be stored in database SQL Compact or SQL Server.
Lansweeper - Scan system Internet
Software Lansweeper design open...
</description></item><item><title>Download ReclaiMe Pro Build 4195</title><pubDate> Wed, 08 Oct 2025 23:34:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reclaime-pro-11440.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reclaime-pro-11440.html
</guid><description>
ReclaiMe Pro is a software application specially developed to help you recover data from hard drives and create disk images. The installation process goes quite smoothly, and once complete, you'll see a very simple user interface, including some shortcut buttons and a panel to view all connected logical drives. Additionally, it can be used very easily by any type of person, regardless of their previous experience with computers.
ReclaiMe Pro Features
	All-in-one highly configurable...
</description></item><item><title>Download Flyby11 1.30.513</title><pubDate> Wed, 08 Oct 2025 23:33:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-flyby11-12467.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-flyby11-12467.html
</guid><description>
Flyby11 is a simple patcher that removes annoying restrictions that prevent you from installing Windows 11 (24H2) on unsupported hardware. Do you have an old PC? No TPM, Secure Boot or your processor is not supported? Flyby11 allows you to install Windows 11 24H2. There are no complicated steps. Just run the tool and you'll be running Windows 11 on your outdated machine in no time.
Technical overview
Flyby11 takes advantage of a feature of the Windows 11 setup process that uses the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Flyoobe 1.30.513</title><pubDate> Wed, 08 Oct 2025 23:33:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oobelux-13956.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oobelux-13956.html
</guid><description>
Flyoobe was born out of the frustration many users felt with the Windows 11 setup experience. Whether it was the mandatory online account, the endless "Next, next, next..." screens, or the incomplete configuration options when you finally reached the desktop, the current setup lacked focus on what users really wanted.
Why choose Flyoobe?
	Simplifies the Windows 11 setup process right out of the box.
	Allows easy local account creation without need to hunt for hidden options.
	Includes...
</description></item><item><title>Download Remote Desktop Manager Enterprise 2025.3.15</title><pubDate> Wed, 08 Oct 2025 23:33:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-remote-desktop-manager-enterprise-242.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-remote-desktop-manager-enterprise-242.html
</guid><description>
Remote Desktop Manager Enterprise software is the complete management of remote connections and virtual machines from a single location, at the same time access support data online and cloud storage. Remote Desktop Manager supports multiple types of connections, not only connections for the protocol connect remote computer Remote Desktop Protocol (RDP).
Remote Desktop Manager easily add, edit, delete, share, organize and find your remote connection of you quickly. Compatible with...
</description></item><item><title>Download Doxillion Document Converter Plus 11.36</title><pubDate> Wed, 08 Oct 2025 23:32:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-doxillion-document-converter-plus-2928.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-doxillion-document-converter-plus-2928.html
</guid><description>
Doxillion Document Converter Plus is a lightweight app and comprehensive, allowing you to convert documents to many different file formats, provides intuitive interface and easy to use. The program also quick, which allows converting documents within minutes, with just a click of the mouse. It also allows you to convert multiple documents at once, saving time and effort.
Doxillion Document Converter Plus supports multiple file formats, including DOC, DOCX, PDF, RTF, TXT, WPS and HTML....
</description></item><item><title>Download MusConv 4.10.425 Lifetime</title><pubDate> Wed, 08 Oct 2025 23:32:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html
</guid><description>
MusConv transfers playlists, albums, followed artists and liked songs across a variety of services – Spotify, Apple Music, Amazon Music, YouTube, YouTube Music, iTunes, Deezer, Tidal, SoundCloud, Pandora and more 125 music services!
Features of MusConv Ultimate
	Transfer playlists, albums, followed artists and liked tracks between over 125 music servicesManage playlists (Delete, Merge, Split, Copy...)
	More than 125 music services supported
	Access DAILY updated music charts on...
</description></item><item><title>Download SoftPerfect RAM Disk 25.10</title><pubDate> Wed, 08 Oct 2025 23:31:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-softperfect-ram-disk-4359.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-softperfect-ram-disk-4359.html
</guid><description>
SoftPerfect RAM Disk is a program disk, RAM performance is designed to help you have a disk on the computer is stored completely in memory. Because memory is much faster than physical hard disk, should store temporary data on disk in fast memory to achieve higher performance. Whether your job is what, keep reading to find out if a RAM disk can offer you what. The program creates a virtual disk located in the computer RAM accessible in Windows Explorer and other applications, allowing you...
</description></item><item><title>Download QuickMemoryTestOK 5.25</title><pubDate> Wed, 08 Oct 2025 23:31:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quickmemorytestok-3327.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quickmemorytestok-3327.html
</guid><description>
QuickMemoryTestOK is a free utility to check RAM of your PC. QuickMemoryTestOK will be useful when you buy a PC have 16, 32, 64, 128, etc., RAM GB. For example, for most users, the part of this often never be used or handled. For this reason, should undergo a test to ensure that no area is error in main memory. QuickMemoryTestOK can also be used to check your Windows PC if there is any behavior in high memory that may be the cause of a system error other serious not.
QuickMemoryTestOK -...
</description></item><item><title>Download SkyDemon 4.2.0.104</title><pubDate> Wed, 08 Oct 2025 23:31:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-skydemon-6442.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-skydemon-6442.html
</guid><description>
SkyDemon is designed to make the flight planning less tedious and more interesting, by bringing the best aviation summary information directly to your reach in real time when you explore the charts. Planning a journey, summaring yourself about potential hazards, prepare for flight and analysis of your path. Direct summary data includes NOTAM, airport documentation and maps, TAF, METAR and wind forecast at altitude.
Features of SkyDemon
	Planning a route with SkyDemon simply by...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tracktion Software F-em 1.2.8</title><pubDate> Wed, 08 Oct 2025 23:30:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tracktion-software-f-em-10720.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tracktion-software-f-em-10720.html
</guid><description>
Tracktion Software F-em is one of the most powerful FM Synthesizers ever created, leveraging state-of-the-art CPU resources for matrix processing of 11 freely configurable operators . It's a combined four-heartbeat synthesizer that can function as an FM, VA, and Sample-based instrument, with the added bonus of dual multi-mode filters, a complex effects section, and a polar modulation matrix flexible period.
Features of Tracktion Software F-em
	4 layers, each layer has 4 effect...
</description></item></channel></rss>