<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 15:39:21 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 15:39:21 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download MusConv 4.10.429 Lifetime</title><pubDate> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 18:03:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html
</guid><description>
MusConv transfers playlists, albums, followed artists and liked songs across a variety of services – Spotify, Apple Music, Amazon Music, YouTube, YouTube Music, iTunes, Deezer, Tidal, SoundCloud, Pandora and more 125 music services!
Features of MusConv Ultimate
	Transfer playlists, albums, followed artists and liked tracks between over 125 music servicesManage playlists (Delete, Merge, Split, Copy...)
	More than 125 music services supported
	Access DAILY updated music charts on...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter 3.9.17 (3010)</title><pubDate> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 18:03:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-to-mp3-converter-1744.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-to-mp3-converter-1744.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter is the software support download youtube video and convert video to mp3 format fast and most simple. MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter allows you download and convert videos from YouTube and other websites to MP3 format by pasting the YouTube URL into the application. When you paste the URL, the program will display thumbnails for videos and you have the option to customize the title information, artist and album before you begin the process of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Photo Supreme 2025.3.3.8125</title><pubDate> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 18:02:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photo-supreme-430.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photo-supreme-430.html
</guid><description>
Photo Supreme is a software product management professional pictures of idimager. With Photo Supreme you can arrange, manage back stock photo archive of yourself and share them with you here and relatives easily via Email or Facebook. Photo Supreme provides users method to sort images effective, logical, as well as edit and share your photos with friends and relatives in the family. Especially the Photo Supreme allows to work with multiple image formats and support mounting support,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Robin YouTube Video Downloader Pro 6.17.6</title><pubDate> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 17:59:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-video-downloader-pro-2828.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-video-downloader-pro-2828.html
</guid><description>
YouTube Video Downloader Pro is a Windows application professional to download and convert videos from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion and thousands of video sharing sites, other. It accelerates your download up to 5 times. YouTube Video Downloader Pro allows you to download multiple videos at the same time. It also allows you to pause, resume and cancel a download at any time.
YouTube Video Downloader Pro - Download online videos on social networks
Features of YouTube Video Downloader...
</description></item><item><title>Download ElectraSoft Speed Dial 25.10.31</title><pubDate> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 17:59:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-electrasoft-speed-dial-5967.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-electrasoft-speed-dial-5967.html
</guid><description>
ElectraSoft Speed Dial is used as a contact book to store detailed information about all your friends and acquaintats, allowing you to quickly find the number of phones you need and dial that number without having to look into your contacts. The main interface of the application displays a structured table, where all contacts are displayed, along with their short description. It can store a maximum of five phone numbers for each contact number and five different notes, too enough for any...
</description></item><item><title>Download Android Studio 2025.2.1.7</title><pubDate> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 17:59:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-android-studio-3890.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-android-studio-3890.html
</guid><description>
Android Studio is an Android development environment, completely new, provides many improvements and new features compared to Eclipse ADT. This software solution will is IDE the official Android when is finishing. This tool provides many tools and features such as editing, layout, rich set of tools to capture usability, compatibility version, performance and other issues, create a lot APK, build system based on Gradle flexibility, extended support for Google Services, integrated support...
</description></item><item><title>Download AnyDesk 9.6.4</title><pubDate> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 17:58:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anydesk-1321.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anydesk-1321.html
</guid><description>
AnyDesk is software computer control remote, easy connection with remote computer management and manipulation on the computer. After installing the AnyDesk up 2 the computer then you can easily use the software to provide technical support for a friend or family member or you have access to your computer while you away from home or office.
AnyDesk - control your computer remotely
The process of using very simple software, want to allow access to his computer, only need to provide for...
</description></item><item><title>Download ElectraSoft Mouse Button Control 25.10.31</title><pubDate> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 17:58:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-electrasoft-mouse-button-control-5973.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-electrasoft-mouse-button-control-5973.html
</guid><description>
ElectraSoft Mouse Button Control is a small software program that helps you customize specific settings associated with your mouse. This software tool allows you to convert the middle mouse button to a double click, the arrow keys of the mouse-moving keyboard, as well as the number 7 keyboard (home page) to move the left mouse button down/up, 9 (page up) to move the right button down/up and 5 (middle) to move the middle button down/up.
Summary, ElectraSoft Mouse Button Control is a...
</description></item><item><title>Download File Viewer Plus 6.1.0.60</title><pubDate> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 17:57:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-file-viewer-plus-6043.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-file-viewer-plus-6043.html
</guid><description>
File Viewer Plus 4 opens more than 400 file formats. See dozens of common types of files, such as Office documents, PDF and photo files, all with a program. Play hundreds of audio and video file formats with a built-in multimedia browser. Compress the archive file with the file compression solution. You can also open file formats that are less popular with File Viewer Plus. See the Microsoft Project and Visio documentation. Open source code files that mark the syntax. Open the email...
</description></item><item><title>Download ElectraSoft First Alert Service Monitor 25.10.31</title><pubDate> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 17:57:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-electrasoft-first-alert-service-monitor-5983.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-electrasoft-first-alert-service-monitor-5983.html
</guid><description>
ElectraSoft First Alert Service Monitor is a fully feature network/Internet service monitoring solution. Monitoring Internet protocols such as HTTP, FTP, SMTP, etc. Options include: visual interface, ease of view of all services, some warning options, service dependencies, run as an NT service and many other features. Always be warned if any of your Internet/network services meet the incident, with the First Warning Service Trace.
If one of your services stops responding, you will be...
</description></item><item><title>Download ElectraSoft FaxMail for Windows 25.10.31</title><pubDate> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 17:57:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-electrasoft-faxmail-for-windows-5968.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-electrasoft-faxmail-for-windows-5968.html
</guid><description>
ElectraSoft FaxMail for Windows is a lightweight software designed to help you send and receive a fax through the modem, email or via the Internet. The fax to which can be transferred to an email address is specified as a TIFF or PDF file. During installation, it is necessary to configure a variety of settings, including the modem connection properties, and the owner information. Then, the app is integrated into Windows ' automatic boot sequence, so the app will automatically launch...
</description></item><item><title>Download ElectraSoft Multi Clipboard 25.10.31</title><pubDate> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 17:56:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-electrasoft-multi-clipboard-5970.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-electrasoft-multi-clipboard-5970.html
</guid><description>
ElectraSoft Multi Clipboard is a reliable and comprehensive application designed to help you save your memory tray for thousands of bits of information, whenever you need to use them. The app displays thirty-three buttons on each page and because a project can have any number of pages, you can save all the data you want and keep it handy, for use in the future. Each node can be renamed separately and in this way, you will not forget the information they contain, which can be quickly...
</description></item><item><title>Download 7 Caps 12.0 + Portable</title><pubDate> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 17:56:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-7-caps-3194.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-7-caps-3194.html
</guid><description>
7 Caps is a very small application that aims to notify you in real time whether the status of the keyboard Num Lock or Caps Lock change in real time. 7 Caps will be a money saver when the indicator light on the keyboard or laptop your current activities help you save or repair, or if you just want to verify functional status. This mode will be useful when entering a passage from a web page on a local documents, for example. But that's not all; you get some custom lightweight allows you to...
</description></item><item><title>Download KiCad 9.0.6</title><pubDate> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 17:55:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kicad-10384.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kicad-10384.html
</guid><description>
KiCad is a unique software product that allows you to open, create and develop electronic circuits for subsequent visualization of printed circuit board designs in interactive views . It allows you to develop complex circuit diagrams using an electronic components database and test signal integrity. It includes free applications, facilities, templates, and open libraries.
Using KiCad, users will be able to create truly professional printed circuit board layouts, beautifully designed...
</description></item><item><title>Download Valentina Studio Pro 16.2.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 17:55:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-valentina-studio-pro-2122.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-valentina-studio-pro-2122.html
</guid><description>
Valentina Studio Pro is the best way to transform your data into meaningful information; create, manage, query and explore MySQL, Postgre MariaDB, MS SQL Server and SQLite database.
Valentina Studio Pro
Features of Valentina Studio Pro
SCHEMA EDITING &amp;amp; MAPPING
	Manage multiple databases in tabs and views that can be attached is
	Create / Drop / alter / Browse Tables, fields, index, trigger, constraints, links, views, stored procedures, properties, Sequences, Types, ...
	Edit the...
</description></item><item><title>Download ElectraSoft FaxMail Network for Windows 25.10.31</title><pubDate> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 17:54:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-electrasoft-faxmail-network-for-windows-5971.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-electrasoft-faxmail-network-for-windows-5971.html
</guid><description>
ElectraSoft FaxMail Network for Windows can turn your computer into a fax machine, which allows you to easily send and receive fax messages from your PC or from a network computer through the modem. Its most important advantage is the ability to automatically relay fax messages that have received a specific e-mail address, which can be useful for any entrepreneur who is unable to access the office fax machine while moving.
The app operates like a fax server, which connects to one or...
</description></item><item><title>Download LibreWolf 144.0.2-1</title><pubDate> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 17:54:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-librewolf-11967.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-librewolf-11967.html
</guid><description>
LibreWolf is a customized and independent version of Firefox, with the main goals being user privacy, security and freedom. LibreWolf is designed to provide increased protection against tracking and fingerprinting techniques and includes a number of security enhancements. This is achieved through our security and privacy oriented settings and patches. LibreWolf also aims to remove all telemetry, data collection and annoyances, as well as disable anti-free features like DRM.
LibreWolf...
</description></item><item><title>Download Disk Savvy Ultimate 17.4.24 + Enterprise + Pro</title><pubDate> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 17:53:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-disk-savvy-ultimate-1290.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-disk-savvy-ultimate-1290.html
</guid><description>
Disk Savvy Ultimate is the analysis disk space visualization and powerful reporting, comprehensive operation management file and export options. This is the Disk Savvy Ultimate get bottle service for free on taiwebs.com software is the analyze disk space usage has the ability to analyze disks, network shares, NAS devices and storage systems business. Users are provided with more ability to analyze disk usage and classification of files, allows one to have is the ability to display more in...
</description></item><item><title>Download ElectraSoft FaxAmatic 25.10.31</title><pubDate> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 17:52:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-electrasoft-faxamatic-5969.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-electrasoft-faxamatic-5969.html
</guid><description>
ElectraSoft FaxAmatic is a software application that allows users to send and receive fax messages from their computers. This can be done because the program will integrate fax into your Windows environment, allowing you to create a fax and send them over the Internet, e-mail or modem.
There are many tabs from which you can choose to take certain actions (The Configuration Format, Create Fax, Fax Fax, Event Trace, etc.) and all of them are filled with information. Of course, you will...
</description></item><item><title>Download Valentina Server 16.2.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 17:52:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-valentina-server-10771.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-valentina-server-10771.html
</guid><description>
Valentina Server is software that provides reports from all major databases or with its own advanced object-relational database system. It will combine an enterprise reporting server and two database servers into a single solution. You get all the technical features of Valentina Server in terms of usage, more connections and live technical support.
Features of Valentina Server
	Enterprise report server turns data into highly formatted reports in the form of multimedia web pages, text,...
</description></item><item><title>Download ElectraSoft Pcx-Dcx Fax Viewer 25.10.31</title><pubDate> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 17:52:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-electrasoft-pcx-dcx-fax-viewer-5972.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-electrasoft-pcx-dcx-fax-viewer-5972.html
</guid><description>
ElectraSoft Pcx-Dcx Fax Viewer is a simple and lightweight software that allows you to view fax messages and .dcx files in an undistracted environment. The app is a bit obsolete and is easy to install. You can start with this app pretty quickly because it goes through a common and unsurprising installation process.
From the File menu, you can open, copy, delete or print fax documents, while from the Edit menu, you can convert files from the .dcx format to .pcx, as well as to TIFF, TIF...
</description></item><item><title>Download Flyby11 1.42.600</title><pubDate> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 17:51:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-flyby11-12467.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-flyby11-12467.html
</guid><description>
Flyby11 is a simple patcher that removes annoying restrictions that prevent you from installing Windows 11 (24H2) on unsupported hardware. Do you have an old PC? No TPM, Secure Boot or your processor is not supported? Flyby11 allows you to install Windows 11 24H2. There are no complicated steps. Just run the tool and you'll be running Windows 11 on your outdated machine in no time.
Technical overview
Flyby11 takes advantage of a feature of the Windows 11 setup process that uses the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Flyoobe 1.42.600</title><pubDate> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 17:51:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oobelux-13956.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oobelux-13956.html
</guid><description>
Flyoobe was born out of the frustration many users felt with the Windows 11 setup experience. Whether it was the mandatory online account, the endless "Next, next, next..." screens, or the incomplete configuration options when you finally reached the desktop, the current setup lacked focus on what users really wanted.
Why choose Flyoobe?
	Simplifies the Windows 11 setup process right out of the box.
	Allows easy local account creation without need to hunt for hidden options.
	Includes...
</description></item><item><title>Download AI FaceSwap 2.6.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 15:11:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ai-faceswap-11511.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ai-faceswap-11511.html
</guid><description>
AI FaceSwap uses artificial intelligence (AI) algorithms to swap faces between two or more people in an image or camera. This technology leverages deep learning techniques, especially convolutional neural networks (CNN), to accurately detect and manipulate facial features.
The algorithm identifies important facial landmarks such as eyes, nose, mouth, etc. to understand the structure and orientation of each face. The faces are then aligned to ensure that the corresponding facial features...
</description></item><item><title>Download AI Video Watermark Remover Pro 1.0.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 31 Oct 2025 15:09:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ai-video-watermark-remover-pro-14264.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ai-video-watermark-remover-pro-14264.html
</guid><description>
Easily remove any watermark from your videos with AI Video Watermark Remover Pro, the ultimate desktop solution for clean, professional video content. Powered by advanced AI inpainting technology, our app will intelligently recreate the area behind logos, text overlays, timestamps, and any distracting watermarks, giving you a flawless, flawless video.
Unlike online tools that require you to upload sensitive files, AI Video Watermark Remover Pro does all processing 100% offline on your...
</description></item></channel></rss>