<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 21:31:17 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 21:31:17 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download WinTools.one Professional / Home 25.11.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 16 Nov 2025 23:43:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wintoolsone-10808.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wintoolsone-10808.html
</guid><description>
WinTools.one is a program designed to help both regular and advanced users as well as computer engineers fine-tune the MS Windows operating system. It allows you to increase the performance of the operating system, maintain its performance at a high level, fix operating system errors, free up space on the computer's hard drive and control the operation of installed programs. In addition, the program allows you to store and protect your secret and confidential information, as well as work...
</description></item><item><title>Download Allavsoft Video Downloader Converter 3.28.5.9439</title><pubDate> Sun, 16 Nov 2025 23:43:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allavsoft-video-downloader-converter-248.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allavsoft-video-downloader-converter-248.html
</guid><description>
Allavsoft Video Downloader Converter software supports download movies, music videos, playlist, sport videos from video sharing website for free like Facebook, Youtube and over 100 video sharing sites.
Allavsoft is many users favorite thanks to the combined features simultaneous transmission of multiple videos and speed limit download video. Besides, the program also supports pause and resume data transmission, to help you interfere with the process of transmitting download data to...
</description></item><item><title>Download reaConverter Pro 8.0.156</title><pubDate> Sun, 16 Nov 2025 23:42:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html
</guid><description>
reaConverter Pro is software image processing feature with batch conversion and image editing periodically becomes simple. eaConverter also provide command line utilities allow you to process images automatically, thus helping you shorten the time for other work.
reaConverter Pro integrated powerful tool of Uber with many great features. It provides advanced solutions to process and adjust images. Management of the conversion process the base image with the latest version of...
</description></item><item><title>Download AllMapSoft Google Hybrid Maps Downloader 8.443</title><pubDate> Sun, 16 Nov 2025 23:42:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-google-hybrid-maps-downloader-6479.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-google-hybrid-maps-downloader-6479.html
</guid><description>
AllMapSoft Google Hybrid Maps Downloader  is a tool that can automatically download a Google combined map image to your PC. It can download small squares and save them to your hard disk. Once downloaded, you can view the map offline with its Maps Viewer tool, or you can combine the small images into one large map image. If you want to make your own city map, it is very useful for you.
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Media Encoder 2025 v25.6.0.098 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Sun, 16 Nov 2025 23:41:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-0010-adobe-media-encoder-1360.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-0010-adobe-media-encoder-1360.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Media Encoder 2024 is a professional audio and video converter that allows you to encode audio and video files into various distribution formats for applications different uses and audiences. Such video and audio formats are characterized by a high degree of compression. By downloading this program on taiwebs.com, you can export videos in formats supported by various devices, from DVD players and websites to mobile phones, portable media players and High Definition and High...
</description></item><item><title>Download Reportizer 6.6.1.405</title><pubDate> Sun, 16 Nov 2025 23:40:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reportizer-5205.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reportizer-5205.html
</guid><description>
Reportizer is a tools report database. Easily create, modify, and print reports database. Allows to manage collection reports. Support database BDE or ADO. Tested on dBase (DBF), Paradox (DB), Text (TXT), the values are separated by commas (CSV), Oracle, Interbase, Microsoft Access, Microsoft Excel, SQL Server, Visual FoxPro, MySQL, PostgreQuery, HTML.
The design reports visually. Reports can be edited in the report design, intuitive and convenient with the toolbar and powerful tool. For...
</description></item><item><title>Download AllMapSoft Google Maps Terrain Downloader 7.203</title><pubDate> Sun, 16 Nov 2025 23:40:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-google-maps-terrain-downloader-6476.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-google-maps-terrain-downloader-6476.html
</guid><description>
AllMapSoft Google Maps Terrain Downloader  is a tool that can automatically download Google topographic map images to your PC. It can download small squares and save them to your hard disk. Once downloaded, you can view the map offline with its Maps Viewer tool, or you can combine the small images into one large map image. If you want to make your own city map, it is very useful for you.
</description></item><item><title>Download ArmorTools Professional / Home 25.11.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 16 Nov 2025 23:40:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-armortools-7726.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-armortools-7726.html
</guid><description>
ArmorTools is a set of tools that extend the capabilities of the MS Windows operating system in the field of security and protection of user confidential information. ArmorTools allows you to create secure virtual disks encrypted with AES128/AES256 algorithms, encrypting files and folder contents using any file as a password.
ArmorTools erases the user's work traces on the computer, deletes the history of accessing websites, deletes confidential information without the possibility of...
</description></item><item><title>Download dbForge SQL Complete Enterprise 2025.2.109</title><pubDate> Sun, 16 Nov 2025 23:39:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbforge-sql-complete-pro-7827.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbforge-sql-complete-pro-7827.html
</guid><description>
dbForge SQL Complete Pro is an advanced solution for SQL database development, management and administration. Available as an add-in for Visual Studio and SSMS, this tool provides great autocompletion.Write, beautify, refactor your SQL code and give your productivity a huge boost with features included in SQL Complete.
dbForge SQL Complete Pro provides a wide range of code completion features that save users from having to memorize long and complex object names, column names, SQL...
</description></item><item><title>Download LuBan 3D 03.11.2025</title><pubDate> Sun, 16 Nov 2025 23:39:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-luban-3d-10427.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-luban-3d-10427.html
</guid><description>
LuBan 3D is creative design software that helps designers and manufacturers create their innovative products quickly. LuBan automatically creates 3D models in a variety of forms, such as lithophane, stacks, hashes, slabs, reliefs, modules, and wireframes. The resulting model can be fabricated by 3D printing, laser cutting and CNC milling. Model parts can be fabricated using laser cutting and 3D printing. LuBan does not depend on specific fabrication methods; instead, it can communicate...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe After Effects 2025 v25.6.0.101 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Sun, 16 Nov 2025 23:36:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-after-effects-0003-2793.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-after-effects-0003-2793.html
</guid><description>
Adobe After Effects is a powerful digital visual effects, motion graphics, and compositing application developed by Adobe Inc. The software is widely used in the film, television, and video game industries to animate and enhance video content.
After Effects allows users to create stunning motion graphics and visual effects by animating text, images, and video clips. Its capabilities include keying, tracking, compositing, and basic audio editing, making it a versatile tool for...
</description></item><item><title>Download XtraTools Pro 25.11.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 16 Nov 2025 23:35:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xtratools-pro-7168.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xtratools-pro-7168.html
</guid><description>
XtraTools Pro is a universal tool for MS Windows system optimization that takes care of all aspects of your computer like optimizing the registry and removing unnecessary program to establish network connection and increase RAM speed. It is a compact tool with an intuitive interface that gives you complete control over the boot process, memory monitoring and a huge set of system settings that control your computer. The current version of the software provides the following tools: Folder...
</description></item><item><title>Download JRiver Media Center 35.0.21</title><pubDate> Sun, 16 Nov 2025 17:59:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jriver-media-center-110.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jriver-media-center-110.html
</guid><description>
JRiver Media Center can help you strictly manage all your files media and enjoy them in a completely new way. Launching the application for the first time, users will be immediately impressed with the intuitive and eye-catching interface with many interesting features to explore. Most people who have used JRiver Media Center evaluate that the software interface design is youthful and modern.
The software for arranging cover art of music files is also extremely neat, especially Insert...
</description></item><item><title>Download Minimal Firewall 2.5.5</title><pubDate> Sun, 16 Nov 2025 17:59:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minimal-firewall-13877.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minimal-firewall-13877.html
</guid><description>
Minimal Firewall works in conjunction with Windows Firewall to block all unknown connections by default, prompting you to create application-based rules to mitigate malware, telemetry, and data leaks. Completely eliminate applications that call home without your knowledge. Minimal Firewall provides a more secure and integrated approach by interacting directly with the native Windows Firewall, eliminating the need for risky system modifications.
Core Features
	Lockdown Mode: The core...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Downloader 9.18.6</title><pubDate> Sun, 16 Nov 2025 17:58:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html
</guid><description>
YTD Youtube Downloader is an application that reliable and intuitive, allowing you to quickly download YouTube videos and save them to your computer. You can also convert the media files to the format desired video or extract audio streams and save separately. YTD Youtube Downloader lets you save your favorite clips of yourself from Youtube, Facebook, Vimeo and Dailymotion to your desktop. The software supports URLS from many web site hosting, multimedia and allows you to download desired...
</description></item><item><title>Download Watchdog Anti-Malware Premium / Business 4.3.450</title><pubDate> Sun, 16 Nov 2025 17:58:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-watchdog-anti-malware-7110.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-watchdog-anti-malware-7110.html
</guid><description>
Watchdog Anti-Malware is an anti-malware with many highly rated tools to help keep your computer safe. Watchdog Anti-Malware will help you with Advanced Malware Detection and Removal, Browser Hijacker Removal, Effective Rootkit and Bootkit Detection and Removal, Real-Time Protection, Anti-ransomware Protection Module.
Watchdog Anti-Malware is extremely optimized and lightweight. Software engineers designed it to work efficiently without having to tweak confusing settings. Just start...
</description></item><item><title>Download CalendarTask (formerly DesktopCal) 3.26.256.8191</title><pubDate> Sun, 16 Nov 2025 17:57:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopcal-1831.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopcal-1831.html
</guid><description>
CalendarTask (formerly DesktopCal) is a simple desktop calendar that blends into your desktop without blocking access to your desktop icons. You can double-click on a date to quickly add notes and also jump to specific dates in the past or future.
CalendarTask - Computer calendar
CalendarTask can use your current wallpaper or loop through images from your folder and update your desktop every few minutes. The program helps you make appointments, make plans... Not only that, the Screen...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Dimension 4.1.6.4632 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Sun, 16 Nov 2025 17:56:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-dimension-cc-254.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-dimension-cc-254.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Dimension CC 2019 is software for designing 2D and 3D to easily create 3D images are of high quality, made to combine the resources intuitive 2D and 3D in one product the actual environment. Purpose introduction of Adobe Dimension is to provide to developers the tools necessary to integrate assets in 2D and 3D without having to study the application complex and specialized. In other words, the program allows you to quickly and simple and creative image other combined 2D and 3D...
</description></item><item><title>Download XRECODE3 1.174 Final</title><pubDate> Sun, 16 Nov 2025 17:56:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xrecode-iii-2915.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xrecode-iii-2915.html
</guid><description>
"Xrecode II" is the switch and grab the audio allows you to convert from mp2, mp3, ac3, aiff, wma, amr, ogg, ape, flac, cue, mpc, wv, tak, mid, cue, m4b, tta, wav, dts , wav (rf64), m4a, mp4, ra, shn, rm, avi, aac, mpg, vob, mka, mkv, flv, Mov, swf, ofr, divx, wmv, spx, mp3, m4v, 3gp, m2v, 3g2, m4v, m2ts, ts, adts, tak, xm, mod, it, s3m, alac, umx, mtm, mlp to m4a, ape, flac, mp4 (using NeroAAC), raw, ogg, wav, wav (rf64) , wma, mpc, WavPack, mp2, ofr, Speex, ac3, tak, aiff, snd, Shorten...
</description></item><item><title>Download XYplorer 28.00.0600 Beta</title><pubDate> Sun, 16 Nov 2025 17:55:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-533.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-533.html
</guid><description>
XYplorer - File Manager for Windows is software that supports users to manage files on the Window quickly and to arrange the folder tidy. XYplorer features tabbed browsing, search, files, powerful, preview, flexible, highly customizable interface, dual frame options and a variety of unique ways to automate effective tasks often repeat. It's fast, lightweight, and portable.
Features XYplorer
	XYplorer is a file manager mobile. It does not require any settings, store all configuration...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinCatalog 2024.15.0.1115</title><pubDate> Sun, 16 Nov 2025 17:54:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wincatalog-615.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wincatalog-615.html
</guid><description>
WinCatalog 2018 is a software cataloguer multi-function for the disk, file, folder, and any objects not files. Not always easy to track the location of a number of files in your computer, especially if you have a huge collection of CD and DVD. If you are one of those users, then surely there will be appropriate tools to work with such a task. WinCatalog is a software utility designed to help you find documents and data from your computer by building an index that allows you immediate...
</description></item><item><title>Download Power-user Premium 1.7.64.224</title><pubDate> Sun, 16 Nov 2025 17:53:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-power-user-premium-3149.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-power-user-premium-3149.html
</guid><description>
Power-user is a plugin for software, Microsoft Excel, PowerPoint and Word help you to provide more visual content so you can create the spreadsheet attractive. It contains templates, icons, tables, drawings and charts, modern, professional, allows you to build professional looking documents. You can add custom content to your project just by a click of the mouse and surprise clients and colleagues with your skills on Excel, PowerPoint and Word.
Power-user Premium - Plugin Excel,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Power-user for PowerPoint and Excel 1.7.64.224</title><pubDate> Sun, 16 Nov 2025 17:53:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-power-user-for-powerpoint-and-excel-522.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-power-user-for-powerpoint-and-excel-522.html
</guid><description>
Power-user for PowerPoint and Excel is a utility providing you with a library of templates, icons, charts, maps and diagrams for spreadsheet and presentation. With Power-user for PowerPoint and Excel, you will attract the attention of your audience with stunning graphics will certainly impress.
Power-user comes with a collection of 2,000 icons to illustrate your slides. The icons are vector shapes so you can resize them without distortion and color back as you with. With Power-user, you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tomabo MP4 Downloader Pro 5.9.5</title><pubDate> Sun, 16 Nov 2025 17:53:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tomabo-mp4-downloader-pro-3602.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tomabo-mp4-downloader-pro-3602.html
</guid><description>
Tomabo MP4 Downloader Pro is the app designed exclusively for Windows users to help them download videos from the Internet. In addition, it also increase download speeds by up to 500%, or even more. Tomabo MP4 Downloader Pro, interface design, simple, well-organized, beautifully. Here, users can view a list of videos has download with gravatar, URL, quality, duration and size of them. Software allows download video series at the same time, at the same time, support create a list of clips...
</description></item><item><title>Download Reuschtools CopyWin 4.73</title><pubDate> Sun, 16 Nov 2025 17:53:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reuschtools-copywin-14136.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reuschtools-copywin-14136.html
</guid><description>
Reuschtools CopyWin is a versatile program designed to copy the contents of your Windows drive, including all files and programs, to another drive, USB or MicroSD card. This is especially useful for upgrading or replacing storage hardware, as it simplifies the migration process. The tool does not require installation; it can be used by running the executable file, but requires administrative rights to operate. CopyWin also offers features like incremental backups after the initial backup,...
</description></item></channel></rss>