<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 05:27:58 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 05:27:58 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Calibre 8.11.1 + Portable</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Sep 2025 02:58:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-calibre-1669.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-calibre-1669.html
</guid><description>
Calibre  is an eBook library management application that allows you to manage your eBook collection, convert eBooks between different formats, Sync with popular e-reading devices and read your e-books with included viewer. You can sort books by author, title, date and other details, download meta information and book covers, add personalized tags and comments, and view your images in the cover display.
Collection of essential tools for adding metadata editing books or managing your...
</description></item><item><title>Download ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro 15.25.0924</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Sep 2025 02:56:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-videotube-downloader-pro-1276.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-videotube-downloader-pro-1276.html
</guid><description>
ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro is the professional version support download videos and playlists from YouTube, videos from Dailymotion, BBC iPlayer, ITV Player, ABC,  FOX,CBS.com Vimeo, Prosieben, Metacafe, Blip.tv CBC.ca many more video sites. After the video is downloaded, you can convert them to the formats compatible with iPad, iPhone, iPod, MPEG-4, H. 264, MP3, AC3.
ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro - Download videos on Youtube
This is one of the software download the most...
</description></item><item><title>Download By Click Downloader 2.4.26</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Sep 2025 02:55:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-by-click-premium-193.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-by-click-premium-193.html
</guid><description>
YouTube By Click Premium is a high quality powerful video downloader including YouTube downloader, YouTube Converter, YouTube Chrome Downloader, Facebook Video Downloader, Downloader Vimeo, Dailymotion Downloader and supports many other video sites.
YouTube By Click
YouTube By Click Features
	YouTube by Click can download and convert files to MP3, MP4, FLV, AVI, WMV, 3GP, WAV and WEBM formats.
	Download all supported qualities, including HD.
	YouTube By Click downloads entire YouTube...
</description></item><item><title>Download Windows To Go Upgrader Enterprise 4.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Sep 2025 02:55:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-to-go-upgrader-enterprise-2848.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-to-go-upgrader-enterprise-2848.html
</guid><description>
Windows To Go Upgrader Enterprise is a feature of Windows 8 and 8.1 Enterprise, also in Windows 10 Enterprise and Education, which allows you to boot from external drives based on USB, can be hard drive or flash drive. Because it is only a part of the Enterprise version Windows To Go can not upgrade directly to newer Windows versions, requires a clean installation instead.
Windows To Go Upgrader Enterprise - boot Disk windows
A software that can help you upgrade your Windows To Go...
</description></item><item><title>Download Chaos Enscape 4.12.0.204</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Sep 2025 02:54:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-enscape-3d-4125.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-enscape-3d-4125.html
</guid><description>
Enscape 3D is the tool support simulation 3D for the software Revit, SketchUp, Rhino, ArchiCAD. With real-time technology of Enscape 3D your project is displayed in the form of walk-3D is fully displayed, can be navigated and explored from every angle, at every moment of the day. With direct link between Enscape 3D and CAD programs, you can track all updates for his plan immediately. More Enscape to your work to give yourself more time to create and innovate. Enscape 3D offers many options...
</description></item><item><title>Download iCare Data Recovery Pro 9.0.1.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Sep 2025 02:53:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-icare-data-recovery-pro-424.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-icare-data-recovery-pro-424.html
</guid><description>
iCare Data Recovery Pro is recovery software data including files, deleted documents, photos, mp3 files and zip files, folders deleted or even hard drive failure.  Besides, iCare Data Recovery helps you restore the file system errors such as boot sector, bad MBR, bad partition table, bad MFT, bad.
When using windows operating systems will arise a lot of problems occur such as : Virus attack lost file as the boot sector is destroyed, MBR, partition, format confusion, error, software...
</description></item><item><title>Download Exif Pilot 6.27.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Sep 2025 02:48:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-exif-pilot-3900.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-exif-pilot-3900.html
</guid><description>
Exif Pilot is a tool that small and simple will help you to easily edit the EXIF data contained in digital photos of you. Using this tool, you will be able to view and manage multiple types of data, such as IPTC, EXIF, GPS, XMP, etc. the program also allows you to create data EXIF, IPTC and GPS. The new card also can be added to your photo. Exif Pilot allows you to import and export data, IPTC and EXIF from / to files, MS Excel, CSV and XML. The program allows you to add, delete and edit...
</description></item><item><title>Download Aiseesoft FoneLab for Android 6.0.16</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Sep 2025 02:48:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aiseesoft-fonelab-for-android-3929.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aiseesoft-fonelab-for-android-3929.html
</guid><description>
Aiseesoft FoneLab for Android is one of the software Android data recovery best. Aiseesoft FoneLab for Android is recovery software data great for Android users that helps you recover text messages, deleted messages, attached, lost, contacts lost, call history and Photos, Photo, Videos, Music, documents on Android phone, tablet and your SD card. Regardless of whether you lost files due to mistakenly deletion, root, upgrade, format the memory card, attack of virus or due to you crashing,...
</description></item><item><title>Download eDocPrinter PDF Pro 10.37 Build 10377</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Sep 2025 02:43:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-edocprinter-pdf-pro-3915.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-edocprinter-pdf-pro-3915.html
</guid><description>
eDocPrinter PDF Pro is an application to create PDF files from applications in Windows 2000, Windows XP and above. eDocPrinter PDF Pro works as a printer under windows environment, hence users can print from any application window using the device printing GDI. Extremely easy to work with this tool, because it installs on your system as a virtual printer and lets you convert documents to PDF in an easy way. eDocPrinter PDF Pro comes with advanced functions that can meet the requirements of...
</description></item><item><title>Download FotoJet Photo Editor 1.3.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Sep 2025 02:38:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fotojet-photo-editor-8002.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fotojet-photo-editor-8002.html
</guid><description>
FotoJet Photo Editor is a powerful and easy-to-use photo editor that allows anyone to become a photo editing expert in no time. It allows you to not only edit photos and apply amazing filters easily, but also add overlays, frames, text, clipart, and more. to embellish your images in a simple way. Whether you are a novice or a professional, FotoJet Photo Editor fulfills all your photo editing desires.
Features of FotoJet Photo Editor
	Automatically enhance your photos with a simple...
</description></item><item><title>Download Picture Window Pro 8.0.531</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Sep 2025 02:38:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-picture-window-pro-7452.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-picture-window-pro-7452.html
</guid><description>
Picture Window Pro is a powerful image editing tool designed for serious photographers with strict creative and quality standards. Its comprehensive set of photo editing and editing tools let you control and shape every aspect of your images.
Picture Window Pro 8 is a complete rewrite of Picture Window Pro 7. It features non-destructive image editing through a novel interface based on an image tree. It also fully supports large, high-resolution displays and can be used in dual monitor...
</description></item><item><title>Download iCare Format Recovery 8.0.1.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Sep 2025 02:38:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-icare-format-recovery-590.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-icare-format-recovery-590.html
</guid><description>
iCare Format Recovery software supports users to recover, data recovery, file lost quickly. iCare Format Recovery is easy to use even for the novice with this software to recover data, we can say this is a pretty good choice for everyone.
iCare Format Recovery gives you information, preview the recovered file to make the processing faster. iCare Format Recovery owned utilities, file search, provide you with functions to quickly find furniture, file recovery, iCare Format Recovery format...
</description></item><item><title>Download Draftable Desktop 25.9.300</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Sep 2025 02:33:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-draftable-desktop-3749.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-draftable-desktop-3749.html
</guid><description>
Draftable Desktop is comparison tool documents the fastest. Compare over 300 pages in a few seconds. Draftable Desktop 2.0 is now available - faster and stronger than ever! See all the changes in your documents, locally and online. Take your work to the next level. Compare secret and private do not use the internet and your documents never leave your computer. Specifically, Draftable Desktop compatible with .xls, .xlsx, .xlsxm. With Office 2013, 2016 or 365, you can compare text in...
</description></item><item><title>Download Playnite 10.39</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Sep 2025 02:32:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-playnite-6972.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-playnite-6972.html
</guid><description>
Playnite is an open-source video game library manager and manager with support for third-party libraries such as Steam, GOG, Origin, Battle.net and Uplay. Includes supporting the game, providing a unified interface for your game. With Playnite, you can comfortably enter the game from Steam, Battle.net, Origin, GOG and Uplay services, including uninstalled games.
You have three options to view when using Playnite. You also have the custom game option or add any game or program with...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wi-Fi Filter Tool 1.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Sep 2025 02:32:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wi-fi-filter-tool-10401.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wi-fi-filter-tool-10401.html
</guid><description>
Your Windows computer will show you a list of available WiFi networks around you. But if there are too many Wi-fi addresses displayed, it will make it difficult for you to choose a suitable Wi-fi for your computer. You can remove one or all of them from the list of Network Profiles or your available networks but it does not have a graphical interface and is only done using the Administrator Command Prompt:
1. Only whitelist Wi-Fi connections that you want
netsh wlan add filter...
</description></item><item><title>Download iCare SD Memory Card Recovery 4.0.1.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Sep 2025 02:31:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-icare-sd-memory-card-recovery-5894.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-icare-sd-memory-card-recovery-5894.html
</guid><description>
You can easily lose the file on multiple storage devices and it ' s absolutely not your fault. The drives may be corrupted or items may have been deleted due to confusion. Regardless of the case, iCare SD Memory Card Recovery can help you recover them from the USB flash drive and the broken SD memory card. After a scan operation, the application will display an organized set of navigation. On one side, you find a list of folders to navigate comfortably, while the second table is where...
</description></item><item><title>Download Viber for PC 26.3.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Sep 2025 02:26:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-viber-2406.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-viber-2406.html
</guid><description>
Viber is a software of instant messaging, based on VoIP protocols, multi-platform due to the Viber Media development for smart phones used to send sms and make calls over the internet. Along with text messaging, users can exchange images, video and audio.
Viber - software news message, chat online
This is a program that is quite popular is mainly designed for mobile phones, but now we are talking about the version for Windows, so immediately. It will allow you to send messages to other...
</description></item><item><title>Download FotoJet Collage Maker 1.3.7</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Sep 2025 02:25:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fotojet-collage-maker-8003.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fotojet-collage-maker-8003.html
</guid><description>
FotoJet Collage Maker is a FotoJet collage maker that has 800+ stunning collage layouts and templates, including birthday collages, wedding collages, baby collages, family collages, love collages, and more, all designed to help you create online collages quickly and easily.
Thanks to FotoJet Collage Maker, everyone can become a professional designer delivering impressive results with this powerful graphic design tool! Whenever you feel inspired, you can always create amazing designs...
</description></item><item><title>Download FotoJet Designer 1.4.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Sep 2025 02:25:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fotojet-designer-568.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fotojet-designer-568.html
</guid><description>
FotoJet Designer is an enterprise software design, brand design, logo with easy visual effects without losing costs. If it is about the design of Banner, the most professional logo is probably one of the most likely to mention Adobe Photoshop-One of the top software currently. But the use of Adobe Photoshop is very difficult for new people. Therefore, the choice of FotoJet Designer is the optimal solution for you.
With FotoJet Designer, you can absolutely design the logo, banner,...
</description></item><item><title>Download FTPie Pro 2025.9.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Sep 2025 02:24:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ftpie-pro-12319.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ftpie-pro-12319.html
</guid><description>
FTPie Pro is a powerful FTP and Cloud application that integrates seamlessly with Google Docs and Microsoft 365 Apps. This program will integrate seamlessly with Google Docs and Microsoft 365 applications, support many different cloud storage services, making file management on different platforms easy.
Features of FTPie Pro
	File Transfer: Easily transfer, upload and manage files between your PC, cloud storage and FTP
	Embedded app: Manage files easily with FTPie's built-in viewer...
</description></item><item><title>Download Revo Registry Cleaner Free 2.0.0 + Portable</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Sep 2025 02:24:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-revo-registry-cleaner-free-12717.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-revo-registry-cleaner-free-12717.html
</guid><description>
Revo Registry Cleaner Free is a powerful tool designed to clean, tune and optimize the Windows Registry. Explore the powerful Registry Cleaner with over 15 scanning categories to find and remove invalid and unnecessary Registry entries. Customize your cleaning routine with custom key inclusions/exclusions and 4 different deep scan modes.
In addition, it also supports custom backups for user-specified keys as well as full Registry backups providing peace of mind as they ensure the safety...
</description></item><item><title>Download CopyQ 12.0.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Sep 2025 02:23:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-copyq-1368.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-copyq-1368.html
</guid><description>
CopyQ is software clipboard manager for windows that helps you easily copy, save, text, clipboard. CopyQ absolutely free on taiwebs.com it allows you to save more than one default entry to the clipboard is limited to Windows. Each time you copy or cut something, it will be saved to the clipboard expansion of CopyQ , both files and text can all be saved.
CopyQ - clipboard Manager
Features of CopyQ
	Support for Linux, Windows and OS X 10.9+
	Store text, HTML, image or any customized...
</description></item><item><title>Download SysTools DBX to PST Converter 8.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Sep 2025 02:23:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-systools-dbx-to-pst-converter-8286.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-systools-dbx-to-pst-converter-8286.html
</guid><description>
SysTools DBX to PST Converter is a software tool that allows users to convert DBX (Outlook Express) files to PST (Microsoft Outlook) format. This can be useful for individuals or organizations that need to access their email data from a damaged or corrupted Outlook Express installation, or for those who want to import their email data into Microsoft Outlook. The software can convert multiple DBX files into a single PST file, or it can create a separate PST for each DBX file. It also...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sinevibes Complete Effects Bundle 2025.9</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Sep 2025 02:22:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sinevibes-collection-7149.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sinevibes-collection-7149.html
</guid><description>
Explore Sinevibes' innovative music technologies with their unique audio effects. Get seven of Sinevibes' powerful effects Albedo, Blend v2, Corrosion v2, Droplet v2, Dipole v2, Dispersion v2, Eternal v2, Luminance v2 and Whirl v2 in a single bundle.
Sinevibes Collection 2024 included:
	Albedo: v1.1.2
	Blend v2: v2.1.3
	Corrosion v2: v2.0.3
	Dipole v2: v2.1.1
	Dispersion v2: v2.0.2
	Droplet v2: v2.0.3
	Eternal v2: v2.1.0
	Hollow: v1.0.1
	Integer: v1.0.0
	Luminance v2: v2.1.0
	Rerun...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft Teams 1.8.00.26073</title><pubDate> Tue, 30 Sep 2025 02:21:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-teams-6904.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-teams-6904.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft Teams is a system that provides chat, meetings, notes and attachments. Whether you're working with teammates on a project or planning a weekend away with loved ones, Microsoft Teams helps bring people together so they can get things done. It's the only app that has chats, meetings, files, tasks, and calendars in one place, so you can easily connect with people and make plans come true.
Features of Microsoft Teams:
	Meeting safely with teammates, family, and friends.
	Live...
</description></item></channel></rss>