<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 15:43:26 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 15:43:26 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Minimal Firewall 2.6.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 17:37:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minimal-firewall-13877.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minimal-firewall-13877.html
</guid><description>
Minimal Firewall works in conjunction with Windows Firewall to block all unknown connections by default, prompting you to create application-based rules to mitigate malware, telemetry, and data leaks. Completely eliminate applications that call home without your knowledge. Minimal Firewall provides a more secure and integrated approach by interacting directly with the native Windows Firewall, eliminating the need for risky system modifications.
Core Features
	Lockdown Mode: The core...
</description></item><item><title>Download Unicodia 3.0.3</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 17:37:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-unicodia-8521.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-unicodia-8521.html
</guid><description>
Unicodia is free, open source software that can be used as an alternative character map for your Windows machine. The interface contains everything you need, allowing you to easily cycle through all the available ASCII symbols and copy them to the clipboard. Uncicodia is a great alternative to your standard Unicode characters and is filled with symbols/characters that make it useful for a number of different uses.
Features of Unicodia
	In Windows 10/11 — all characters of Unicode 15...
</description></item><item><title>Download Flyby11 2.1.790</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 17:36:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-flyby11-12467.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-flyby11-12467.html
</guid><description>
Flyby11 is a simple patcher that removes annoying restrictions that prevent you from installing Windows 11 (24H2) on unsupported hardware. Do you have an old PC? No TPM, Secure Boot or your processor is not supported? Flyby11 allows you to install Windows 11 24H2. There are no complicated steps. Just run the tool and you'll be running Windows 11 on your outdated machine in no time.
Technical overview
Flyby11 takes advantage of a feature of the Windows 11 setup process that uses the...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDF-XChange Editor Plus 10.7.6.404</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 17:34:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-xchange-editor-plus-645.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-xchange-editor-plus-645.html
</guid><description>
PDF-XChange Editor Plus is the editor, PDF viewer, compact, fast with many features, add-ons, professional. When using the PDF-XChange Editor Plus, easy for users to create, view, edit, annotate, OCR and digital signing PDF files, plus much more.
PDF-XChange Editor is a PDF editing full-featured. With the help of it, you can edit, fix, add, or delete text easily. Graphics can also be moved, resized or removed.
Features PDF-XChange Editor Plus
Edit documents
	Use a variety of editing...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinRAR 7.20 Beta 2 / 7.13 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 17:33:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winrar-127.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winrar-127.html
</guid><description>
WinRAR is a compression utility data advanced supports multiple formats including RAR, ZIP, CAB, ARJ, LZH, ACE, TAR, GZip, UUE, ISO, BZIP2, Z and 7-Zip. It allows you to create, organize and manage archives in a comfortable way and quickly. WinRAR naturally are is a leading software currently in the compression and decompression of data. With the enhanced algorithm is applied, the software allows users to compress bulk files in different formats into synthetic 1 single file to facilitate...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wise Duplicate Finder Pro 2.1.9.71</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 17:33:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wise-duplicate-finder-pro-544.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wise-duplicate-finder-pro-544.html
</guid><description>
Wise Duplicate Finder Pro is a software supports to find and delete file duplicates based on file name, size and content of file a most accurate way. Besides, Wise Duplicate Finder Pro trigger help the user to find and delete the file, empty, backup and data recovery ensure you can recover data deleted at any time.
In addition, you can use more Wise Disk Cleaner to completely remove junk files from his system.
Features Wise Duplicate Finder Pro
	Provide filter, search for files...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDF-XChange Pro 10.7.6.404</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 17:32:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-xchange-editor-pro-3422.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-xchange-editor-pro-3422.html
</guid><description>
PDF-XChange Editor Pro is an application to manipulate and create PDF versatile, offering a wide range of useful features and powerful will help you to easily work with PDF files. This application is very flexible and allows you to easily create and modify PDF files. PDF-XChange Editor Pro provides a powerful set of tools and flexibility to work with PDF files, such as editor PDF-XChange new, utilities series, OFFice2PDF and the Addin tool Bar allows you to easily convert multiple file...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Acrobat Pro DC 2025.001.20937 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 17:31:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-001en-adobe-acrobat-pro-458.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-001en-adobe-acrobat-pro-458.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Acrobat Pro DC is a comprehensive software that helps you create and edit the PDF&amp;nbsp;document, or create form, sign, protect PDF, connect, split PDF, export PDF to various formats. The Acrobat Pro DC is the latest version of Adobe with improvements in the interface with the polished ribbon bar and the ability to create and handle pdf files as well as its male versions.
The highlight of the Acrobat Pro DC is probably the ability to connect, store documents on the cloud, you can...
</description></item><item><title>Download SIW Technicians 2025 v15.11.1119 + Enterprise</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 17:30:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-siw-technicians-3584.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-siw-technicians-3584.html
</guid><description>
SIW Technicians is an information tool complex system, for Microsoft Windows, check your PC and collect detailed data about the properties and system settings and displays it in a way very easy to understand. SIW Technicians can create a report file (JSON, HTML, TXT, CSV or XML) and you can use that file in batch mode (for Inventory computer inventory of hardware and software, asset inventory, security audit, license Management software, configuration Management server).
SIW Technicians...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ashampoo Backup Pro 27.5.15</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 17:29:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-backup-pro-716.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-backup-pro-716.html
</guid><description>
Ashampoo Backup Pro is software to backup and restore data professional to save the file, the important data for your computer. Ashampoo Backup Pro will remove the fear of viruses, ransomware, or hardware errors. Ashampoo® Backup Pro offers you various options to backup individual files or entire disk partitions on any storage media or on the cloud. User friendly, intuitive, fast. Even in case an error occurs the entire system, application integrated emergency can bring your...
</description></item><item><title>Download RE:VisionFX Color Genius Plus 2025.11</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 17:29:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-revisionfx-color-genius-plus-14070.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-revisionfx-color-genius-plus-14070.html
</guid><description>
RE:VisionFX Color Genius Plus is a one-click, AI-powered video enhancement tool designed to automatically color correct and enhance videos. It is available as a standalone application and a plugin for various video editing software such as After Effects, Premiere Pro, Resolve, and others.
Key Features
	Simple drag-and-drop interface with in/out point settings, intensity, and color balance adjustments.
	Automatically restore highlights, improve contours and depth, enhance skin tones,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Flyoobe 2.1.790</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 16:53:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oobelux-13956.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oobelux-13956.html
</guid><description>
Flyoobe was born out of the frustration many users felt with the Windows 11 setup experience. Whether it was the mandatory online account, the endless "Next, next, next..." screens, or the incomplete configuration options when you finally reached the desktop, the current setup lacked focus on what users really wanted.
Why choose Flyoobe?
	Simplifies the Windows 11 setup process right out of the box.
	Allows easy local account creation without need to hunt for hidden options.
	Includes...
</description></item><item><title>Download Soda PDF Desktop Pro 14.0.527.23106</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 16:34:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-soda-pdf-home-808.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-soda-pdf-home-808.html
</guid><description>
Soda PDF Pro  is intuitive PDF software that helps you to easily process and create PDF files from more than 300 different formats. Soda PDF is built to help you power through any PDF task. Convert to a wide range of file types. Edit the content of your document. Create custom forms. Annotate your files. Send and track contracts for electronic signatures.
Soda PDF Pro: Create PDF file
Features of Soda PDF Pro
	Read your PDFs and digital publications in 3D with unique page-turning...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Premiere Pro 2025 v25.6.1.002 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 16:33:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-premiere-pro-0021-1361.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-premiere-pro-0021-1361.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Premiere Pro is the leading video editing software for film, TV, and the web. Creative tools, integration with other Adobe apps and services, and the power of Adobe Sensei help you turn footage into finished movies and videos in a seamless workflow. It offers high-quality video editing at 4K x 4K resolution and beyond, with 32-bit color, in both RGB and YUV color spaces. Edit audio samples, support for VST audio plug-ins (plug-ins), and 5.1 surround sound tracks. The Premiere Pro...
</description></item><item><title>Download SepPDF 3.95</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 16:33:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-seppdf-924.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-seppdf-924.html
</guid><description>
SepPDF is a standalone tool simple allows you to split PDF document and create a PDF file for each page. SepPDF has a simple interface only provides access to a few configuration settings. The file can be added to the list by using the function drag and drop support of Wap or function built-in browser.
Advantages of SepPDF is the speed split pdf file was quite fast, with the capacity to compact software does not affect the operation performance of CPU as well as the performance of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Privacy Eraser Free 6.24.2 Build 5410</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 16:32:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-privacy-eraser-free-9160.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-privacy-eraser-free-9160.html
</guid><description>
Privacy Eraser is a software tool that helps protect user privacy by securely erasing or deleting unwanted data from their computer or device. This tool is designed to delete browsing history, cookies, cache, temporary files and other sensitive information that may be stored on the computer.
Privacy Eraser can be used to clear browsing history of popular web browsers such as Google Chrome, Mozilla Firefox and Microsoft Edge. It can also clear the history and cache of other applications,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Disk Drill Enterprise 6.1.1162.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 16:32:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-disk-drill-enterprise-6875.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-disk-drill-enterprise-6875.html
</guid><description>
Disk Drill Enterprise is software that allows you to recover files from hard drives and USB devices, external hard drives, memory cards, iPhone and iPad, drive formats like NTFS, FAT, exFAT, HFS + Mac drive, EXT2/3/4. The software provides fast scan and deep scan mode, depending on the user's needs, to save time and achieve the highest efficiency.
Features of Disk Drill Enterprise
	Users simply need one click to activate Disk Drill.
	Support to scan the entire drive and rejoin lost...
</description></item><item><title>Download Claris FileMaker Pro 22.0.4.406</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 16:31:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-filemaker-pro-advanced-487.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-filemaker-pro-advanced-487.html
</guid><description>
FileMaker Pro Advanced is software via internet easy manager database, contacts, projects and inventory data, and generate reports. FileMaker Pro will help users to build database customize and design them to fit with the activities and profile of their business. More than a million people around the world use platform FileMaker every day to complete the work faster and more efficient in work.
Features on FileMaker Pro Advanced
Anywhere access
	Use one unified platform to create the...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDF Architect Pro + OCR 9.1.83.23106</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 16:31:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-architect-pro-ocr-6381.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-architect-pro-ocr-6381.html
</guid><description>
PDF Architect  is professional software that provides PDF creation and editing features according to your needs. Our PDF editor keeps you up to date with forward-looking features. Take complete control of your PDF files with our PDF editor. Modify text, images, and pages, and convert PDF to Word and Excel and more.
It has many advanced options and features for customizing, securing, and collaborating PDF files. All necessary features are included in this for better user experience. This...
</description></item><item><title>Download RollBack Rx Server 4.9 Build 2711286639</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 16:30:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rollback-rx-server-5643.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rollback-rx-server-5643.html
</guid><description>
RollBack Rx Server is a powerful Windows Server backup and restore utility that allows IT professionals the ability to instantly backup, be able to quickly restore mission-critical systems back to real any number of restore points. It helps you to quickly and easily securely update sandbox and service patches with a fail-safe approach to system recovery. You can recover files and folders from any corrupted snapshots or system state.
RollBack Rx Server Features
	Fully supports active...
</description></item><item><title>Download Secure Delete Professional 2025 v214</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 16:30:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secure-delete-professional-4991.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secure-delete-professional-4991.html
</guid><description>
Secure Delete Professional is very simple tool but very effective to delete files and folders in a secure way. After using this tool, the files and folders selected will not be available for recovery. We have attached a number of security options so you can choose the security level that you need (this reflects the processing speed).
You can use this application in 3 ways. First, you can drag and drop the file or folder that you want to delete securely to the main window of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Serato Studio 2.4.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 16:29:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-serato-studio-2352.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-serato-studio-2352.html
</guid><description>
Serato Studio's beat making software intuitive for DJ and producer. Spend less time to block the barrier and more time in creative flow. Serato Studio is an audio workstation new digital (DAW), developed for those who have experience in the field of DJ. It reflects the essence of DJ software and make it become the ideal for any user in this field, it doesn't matter if you just decided to create music, or have experienced. This application has the working environment very friendly for...
</description></item><item><title>Download Photo Lab PRO Picture Editor 3.13.76</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 16:29:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-photo-lab-pro-picture-editor-8225.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-photo-lab-pro-picture-editor-8225.html
</guid><description>
Photo Lab PRO Picture Editor is a powerful photo editing application that allows users to enhance and transform their photos with a variety of filters, effects and frames. Enhance your photos with over 640 beautiful frames, effects, filters or montages! Photo Lab PRO is an easy, fast and fun photo editor. You don't have to be a Photoshop expert to make every photo funny and every portrait beautiful.
Features of Photo Lab PRO Picture Editor
	Photo effects: Photo Lab PRO offers a...
</description></item><item><title>Download AZIP Master: ZIP RAR Extractor 4.2.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 16:28:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-azip-master-zip-rar-extractor-9785.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-azip-master-zip-rar-extractor-9785.html
</guid><description>
AZIP Master is a file manager application, zip file reader, creates archives in ZIP or 7Z file format. Unzip multiple archive file formats: unZIP (unzip ZIP files) unRAR (unzip RAR files), etc. Being a stable application - AZIP Master is an attractive choice for mobile users globally.
AZIP Master Features: ZIP RAR Extractor
	Decompress multiple files at once
	️Create a packaged 7Z ZIP archive
	️Quick decompression: open compressed files with the ZIP RAR 7Z file decompression...
</description></item><item><title>Download Zero Cleaner: clear cache 25.11.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 16:28:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-zero-cleaner-clear-cache-10667.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-zero-cleaner-clear-cache-10667.html
</guid><description>
Zero Cleaner is a mobile application that specializes in removing cache files from your device. Cache files are temporary data stored by applications and websites to improve their performance and load times. Over time, cache files can accumulate and take up valuable storage space on your device.
Some key features of Zero Cleaner include:
	Cache Cleaner: The app will scan your device for cache files created by apps and web browsers, allowing you to clear them with just a tap. This...
</description></item></channel></rss>