<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:45:18 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:45:18 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download WinScan2PDF 9.51 + Portable</title><pubDate> Wed, 31 Dec 2025 17:20:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winscan2pdf-2117.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winscan2pdf-2117.html
</guid><description>
WinScan2PDF is a simple tool that allows you to scan documents from scanner and save them as PDF files. The program also supports multi-page scanning, then will be combined into one PDF document. Useful if your scanning software does not provide PDF conversion.
WinScan2PDF - Scan document to computer
WinScan2PDF allows users to perform scans the entire text or document at the same time to serve for the saved PDF format. Not only that, you also can choose the page any of a text to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Realtek Ethernet Controller All-In-One Drivers 11.27.1229.2025</title><pubDate> Wed, 31 Dec 2025 17:19:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-realtek-ethernet-controller-all-in-one-drivers-6485.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-realtek-ethernet-controller-all-in-one-drivers-6485.html
</guid><description>
Realtek Ethernet All-In-One Controller Driver is the software driver for the Realtek Ethernet cards. It is a program used to communicate from the Windows PC OS to the device. This software is required in most cases for the hardware device to function properly. In most cases, drivers come with Windows or can be found by going to Windows Update in Control Panel and checking for updates as well as downloaded from the Realtek support website.
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare Filmora 15.1.2.17051</title><pubDate> Wed, 31 Dec 2025 17:17:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-filmora-2025-31.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-filmora-2025-31.html
</guid><description>
In early November 2020 Wondershare came up with a new version called Wondershare Filmora 13 with two new ways to edit: Action Cam Tool (Lens distortion correction, Clean up your audio, Control speed new) and Instant Cutter (Cut or merge clips quickly, Export instantly).
Wondershare Filmora 13  allows you to add your favorite tracks to your videos, creating a more stylish, romantic film reel, with a rich music library besides Users can manually add their favorite songs to the editing...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter 3.9.18 (3012)</title><pubDate> Wed, 31 Dec 2025 17:17:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-to-mp3-converter-1744.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediahuman-youtube-to-mp3-converter-1744.html
</guid><description>
MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter is the software support download youtube video and convert video to mp3 format fast and most simple. MediaHuman YouTube to MP3 Converter allows you download and convert videos from YouTube and other websites to MP3 format by pasting the YouTube URL into the application. When you paste the URL, the program will display thumbnails for videos and you have the option to customize the title information, artist and album before you begin the process of...
</description></item><item><title>Download GoodSync Enterprise 12.9.21.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 31 Dec 2025 17:13:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-goodsync-enterprise-163.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-goodsync-enterprise-163.html
</guid><description>
GoodSync Enterprise is a software that saves files and files easily and is reliable. It automatically analyts, synchronize and backup your email, family photos, contacts, MP3, financial documentation and other important files-between desktop computers, laptops, servers, external drives and Windows Mobile devices as well as remotely via FTP , SFTP, WebDAV and more. The GoodSync synchronized software combines bulletproof reliability with an extremely easy interface to compare, synchronize...
</description></item><item><title>Download foobar2000 2.25.4</title><pubDate> Wed, 31 Dec 2025 17:12:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-foobar2000-1812.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-foobar2000-1812.html
</guid><description>
foobar2000 is the media player for media formats MP3, WAV, OGG and other formats multimedia other. It has no bells and whistles, however, under the hood, the program offers quite many features, including format, title and layout of the interface can be customized, convert WAV, Equalizer, Resampler, note cards, MP3, playlists, music album, CD, drag / drop and more. It also includes all the standard features like shuffle, random play, etc.
foobar2000 - The media player
foobar2000 running...
</description></item><item><title>Download iFunia Video Converter 5.0.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 31 Dec 2025 17:12:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ifunia-video-converter-10020.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ifunia-video-converter-10020.html
</guid><description>
iFunia Video Converter is a versatile video converter that supports more than 600 video and audio formats, including 4K/5K UHD video. It can extract audio from video and convert for popular devices and software. The application also has advanced editing functions, built-in media player and fast conversion speed. In addition, iFunia Video-Converter includes a DVD creator that can burn video to DVD with menus, subtitles and background music.
The application supports various DVD menu...
</description></item><item><title>Download O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro 22.1.230 / Server</title><pubDate> Wed, 31 Dec 2025 17:05:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-diskimage-pro-218.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-diskimage-pro-218.html
</guid><description>
O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro is software backup data comprehensive and effective is provided to protect the data of the computer system, it creates images for individual drives or the entire system that still does not affect your system.
O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro allows the user to backup the entire computer or drive, the and files whenever you want even while the computer is being used. Or can use O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro to create a copy chinh sac of computer disk drives, can be used instead of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinNTSetup 5.4.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 31 Dec 2025 17:04:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winntsetup-4062.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winntsetup-4062.html
</guid><description>
WinNTSetup is a simple utility and reliable give you the ability to customize easy to install Windows before installing the system on your machine. The app allows you to create your version of MS Windows, customized just by few mouse clicks. WinNTSetup is a tool targeted to experienced users. This app allows you to select the source WIM, ISO, or ESD. The program allows you to view the list of Windows versions supported by the selected file of you. Utility offers many improvements rich can...
</description></item><item><title>Download AutoHideMouseCursor 5.99</title><pubDate> Wed, 31 Dec 2025 17:03:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-autohidemousecursor-4104.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-autohidemousecursor-4104.html
</guid><description>
AutoHideMouseCursor is a Microsoft Windows application mobile mini allows you to hide the cursor, if the mouse is not active for a period of time. With AutoHideMouseCursor you can automatically hide the mouse cursor with the timer can be customized this is utility desktop perfect when the cursor is too annoying to them, such as when used with the application handling the text because often when you add pointers, text and cover text.
AutoHideMouseCursor - Hide mouse cursor
User...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sante PACS Server PG 4.4.3</title><pubDate> Wed, 31 Dec 2025 17:02:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sante-pacs-server-pg-7540.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sante-pacs-server-pg-7540.html
</guid><description>
Sante PACS Server PG is an HTTP server (web) for DICOM files and a recorder and In CD/DVD with high performance and reliability. It provides connectivity with all the DICOM (CT, MR, US, CR, NM, XA, MG, DX, etc.). The review of the DICOM image can be done with the Sante PACS Viewer.
Integrated web servers can be used as a free cloud server for DICOM files!
</description></item><item><title>Download Pulsar Audio Pulsar Echorec 1.7.11</title><pubDate> Wed, 31 Dec 2025 17:01:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pulsar-audio-pulsar-echorec-9183.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pulsar-audio-pulsar-echorec-9183.html
</guid><description>
Pulsar Audio Pulsar Echorec is a software emulation of the iconic echo/delay device of the same name produced by the Italian brand Binson in the 1960s. The sound of This platter delay was different from the tape delay used at the time and largely contributed to the sonic signatures of many '70s bands: Pink Floyd, The Shadows, Jimmy Page, etc.
Features of Pulsar Audio Pulsar Echorec
	Best software emulation of Binson Echorec 2
	Vintage Echorec devices are known for their saturation,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Pulsar Audio Pulsar 1178 1.5.11</title><pubDate> Wed, 31 Dec 2025 17:00:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pulsar-audio-pulsar-1178-9167.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pulsar-audio-pulsar-1178-9167.html
</guid><description>
Pulsar Audio Pulsar 1178 is an audio plug-in (VST/VST3/AU/AAX) that meticulously reproduces the original 1178 hardware compressor in color and compression characteristics of the original 1178 hardware compressor. it, while adding some extra features, making it a very flexible compressor for tracking and mixing. It has added all the features you'd expect from a modern, versatile plug-in, including full sidechain EQ for additional control, optional saturation stages for warmth and...
</description></item><item><title>Download AnySQL Maestro Professional 16.12.0.20</title><pubDate> Wed, 31 Dec 2025 17:00:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anysql-maestro-professional-2983.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anysql-maestro-professional-2983.html
</guid><description>
AnySQL Maestro Professional is the name of a software management database. This software is a useful tool and useful in the management, control and development database. Software in front of you, with support for multiple tool database such as SQL Server, MySQL, Access, etc., can help you manage data. Managing your data also includes the ability to edit, sort, sort, and filter.
AnySQL Maestro Professional - Manage and develop database
Software AnySQL Maestro Professional can also help...
</description></item><item><title>Download O&amp;amp;O BlueCon Tech Edition WinPE 23.0.14008</title><pubDate> Wed, 31 Dec 2025 16:59:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-bluecon-admin-edition-4037.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-bluecon-admin-edition-4037.html
</guid><description>
O&amp;amp;O BlueCon Admin Edition offers a set of powerful tools for users, administrators and service technicians so that the system is broken can be operated back without install ago. The user interface is based on Windows help the use of O&amp;amp;O BlueCon Admin Edition becomes easy to rate need less time for training. O&amp;amp;O BlueCon Admin Edition is at the side of an administrator during the course of a daily routine as well as whenever disaster happens.
O&amp;amp;O BlueCon Admin Edition -...
</description></item><item><title>Download Pulsar Audio Pulsar Smasher 1.5.11</title><pubDate> Wed, 31 Dec 2025 16:59:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pulsar-audio-smasher-3823.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pulsar-audio-smasher-3823.html
</guid><description>
Pulsar Audio Smasher is a custom modification not seen of the circuit the classic compressor Urei 1176, a single recipe that we stumbled across while tweaking the other algorithms. Hardware compressor 1176 original offers a choice of four rates, but the studio engineer was soon discovered that the press all of them at the same time lead to sound distortion, explosion and very high compression. This is the mode "all buttons in mode," or "You" that Pulsar Audio Smasher is designed...
</description></item><item><title>Download Pulsar Audio Pulsar Primavera 1.2.11</title><pubDate> Wed, 31 Dec 2025 16:58:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pulsar-audio-pulsar-primavera-11662.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pulsar-audio-pulsar-primavera-11662.html
</guid><description>
Pulsar Primavera is a 6-in-1 reverb plugin that includes equipment heard on countless hits throughout the ages. Known for their unique, warm, characterful and natural tone, these reverbs created a sonic identity that lasted from the 50s to the 70s and is back in vogue today.
It is a complete reverb chain plugin with built-in saturation, filter, presence and fade controls. Get that signature “twang” sound within seconds and test out next-generation features built into the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Pulsar Audio Vocal Studio 1.0.21</title><pubDate> Wed, 31 Dec 2025 16:58:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pulsar-audio-vocal-studio-13849.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pulsar-audio-vocal-studio-13849.html
</guid><description>
Pulsar Audio Vocal Studio is an all-in-one vocal processing plugin designed to deliver professional vocal mixes quickly and intuitively by combining many essential vocal production tools into a single interface. It offers a comprehensive channel array with preamp, compression, EQ, gating, de-essing, reverb, delay, saturation and a suite of creative effects.
Key Features:
	Tri-Mode Preamp: Choose between Solid State, Tube and Germanium saturation models with adjustable drive for warmth...
</description></item><item><title>Download AutoHideDesktopIcons 6.61</title><pubDate> Wed, 31 Dec 2025 16:57:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-autohidedesktopicons-1747.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-autohidedesktopicons-1747.html
</guid><description>
AutoHideDesktopIcons allows you to automatically hide the icons on his screen after some seconds of inactivity, certain to your screen is not cluttered and your wallpaper in full view. The program works very similar to the screen saver, but instead of making the desktop look your beautiful eyes, it makes it look clean.
AutoHideDesktopIcons - Hides icons on the Desktop
Must say that AutoHideDesktopIcons is software features auto hide and show on the computer screen. It has a lot of apps...
</description></item><item><title>Download Pulsar Audio Pulsar 8200 1.2.11</title><pubDate> Wed, 31 Dec 2025 16:57:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pulsar-audio-pulsar-8200-9385.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pulsar-audio-pulsar-8200-9385.html
</guid><description>
Pulsar Audio has announced the release of Pulsar 8200, a faithful emulation of the legendary GML 8200 designed by George Massenburg, inventor of parametric EQ. Besides emulating the sound of the original device, Pulsar Audio has incorporated all the features you would expect from a modern EQ plugin, such as filtering, tilt, sub and air band, editing visual curves, eliminators, auto-increment, etc. .
Like the original machine, the plugin offers tight and powerful bass, vibrant highs, and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Pulsar Audio MP-EQ 2.0.6</title><pubDate> Wed, 31 Dec 2025 16:56:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pulsar-audio-mp-eq-14261.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pulsar-audio-mp-eq-14261.html
</guid><description>
Pulsar MP-EQ is an emulation of the legendary analog equalizer used in most mastering studios worldwide. Engineered from the best passive equalizers of the past 70 years, its fully parallel architecture delivers a unique and musical frequency response compared to digital equalizers of the same setup. Thanks to this design, the frequency bands interact naturally, resulting in a more musical overall response.
Key Features
Modern EQ Version
For the first time, a plugin allows you to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Pulsar Audio IPA 25 1.0.17</title><pubDate> Wed, 31 Dec 2025 16:56:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pulsar-audio-ipa-25-14071.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pulsar-audio-ipa-25-14071.html
</guid><description>
Pulsar Audio's IPA 25 is a classic VCA compressor emulation plugin, specifically inspired by the API 2500, providing a flexible multi-VCA dynamics system with modern control options for the engineer.
Key Features
	Faithful VCA modeling delivers classic tone with advanced control beyond the hardware limits.
	Modular signal flow and intuitive controls, allowing allows users to switch between different VCA circuits for more diverse sounds.
	Multi-circuit design: Provides both native...
</description></item><item><title>Download Pulsar Audio VM-Comp 2.0.6</title><pubDate> Wed, 31 Dec 2025 16:55:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pulsar-audio-vm-comp-14262.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pulsar-audio-vm-comp-14262.html
</guid><description>
Pulsar Audio VM-Comp is a software plugin that faithfully emulates the legendary yet modern mu variable tube compressor/limiter, originally called Pulsar Mu. It is designed primarily for mixing and mastering but is also versatile enough for monitoring.
Key Features
	Faithful emulation of a modern yet legendary mu variable tube compressor/limiter with smooth and transparent gain control.
	Signature "glue" compression effect, ideal for bus, mix and master.
	Unique Structure Preservation...
</description></item><item><title>Download Trellix Stinger (McAfee Stinger) 13.0.0.583</title><pubDate> Wed, 31 Dec 2025 16:53:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mcafee-stinger-202.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mcafee-stinger-202.html
</guid><description>
McAfee Stinger is a free utility that functions to scan, check and remove the hazards and obstacles as virus or malware for Windows, whether they are hiding deep into the system.
In addition, due to the ability to search for the correct folder, or the data at risk contains viruses to scan instead you have to remove a long time waiting for antivirus software to scan all system on your computer. Thus speed of work of the McAfee Stinger faster and somewhat more accurate.
Themselves McAfee...
</description></item><item><title>Download The Dude 7.20.6</title><pubDate> Wed, 31 Dec 2025 16:49:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-the-dude-3238.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-the-dude-3238.html
</guid><description>
The Dude is a new application by MikroTik which can dramatically improve the way you manage your network environment. It will automatically scan all devices in the subnet is specified, draw and layout a map of your networks, monitor services of your devices and alert you in case some service has problems.is a new application by MikroTik which can dramatically improve the way you manage your network environment. It will automatically scan all devices in the subnet is specified, draw and...
</description></item></channel></rss>