<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 01:44:52 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 01:44:52 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download MathType 7.10.1.458</title><pubDate> Wed, 05 Nov 2025 00:11:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mathtype-478.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mathtype-478.html
</guid><description>
MathType software is to compose mathematical formulas, symbols, math for office applications such as mathematical equations, to handle text, web pages, desktop publishing, desktop presentations, elearning, and for TeX documents, LaTeX and MathML. MathType would be a great help for work as well as your learning.
When integrate MathType into the office software, you easily create the logo or any formula in Math will save a lot of time, work efficiency is highly increased.
Teachers,...
</description></item><item><title>Download CyberLink PowerDirector Ultimate 2026 v24.0.1030.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 05 Nov 2025 00:10:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-powerdirector-ultimate-425.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-powerdirector-ultimate-425.html
</guid><description>
CyberLink PowerDirector Ultimate is software editor, edit video and make movies on the computer from a variety of templates are made available, complete with effects, transitions, animations, and music. CyberLink PowerDirector 17 is a combination of video editing software with advanced video editing features powerful. Cblowing need to add your clips into the time line and click on 'Production'!
The tool design video in CyberLink PowerDirector have the ability to customize helps you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Lyric Video Studio 1.3.48</title><pubDate> Wed, 05 Nov 2025 00:10:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lyric-video-studio-13581.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lyric-video-studio-13581.html
</guid><description>
Lyric Video Studio is a powerful, feature-rich video editor specifically designed to create lyric videos, music videos, and visualizers with ease. It integrates simple and effective text tools along with generative AI capabilities to streamline the video creation process. Whether you're a musician launching a killer new track, a content creator, or just love playing with visuals, this app lets you sync your lyrics to your music in just a few clicks. Enter lyrics, drag to sync and you're...
</description></item><item><title>Download CapCut PC 7.3.0.2974 / 7.4.0.3032 Beta 8</title><pubDate> Wed, 05 Nov 2025 00:09:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capcut-pc-9995.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capcut-pc-9995.html
</guid><description>
CapCut PC is a simple video editing tool that you can freely use anywhere. You can create videos on your browser, desktop and laptop, or on your phone. Versatile editing, magical AI tools, team collaboration, and built-in assets. Create videos in a whole new way.
You can edit videos based on editing the timeline, in the process you can add different elements and effects to the video to give the best effect to your work. It is a simple and intuitive set of editing tools and effects that...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ashampoo Backup Pro 27.4.45</title><pubDate> Wed, 05 Nov 2025 00:08:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-backup-pro-716.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-backup-pro-716.html
</guid><description>
Ashampoo Backup Pro is software to backup and restore data professional to save the file, the important data for your computer. Ashampoo Backup Pro will remove the fear of viruses, ransomware, or hardware errors. Ashampoo® Backup Pro offers you various options to backup individual files or entire disk partitions on any storage media or on the cloud. User friendly, intuitive, fast. Even in case an error occurs the entire system, application integrated emergency can bring your...
</description></item><item><title>Download MedCalc 23.4.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 05 Nov 2025 00:07:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-medcalc-1536.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-medcalc-1536.html
</guid><description>
MedCalc is a statistical software for biomedical research can analyze many performance curve system with a set of rich functionality, chart types and advanced module. MedCalc was designed to meet the needs and requirements of the study nature and aims to analyze the statistical calculations of the project. This software provides the tools and means essential to analyze the characteristic curve of the system (ROC), drawing data and perform the statistical calculations.
MedCalc -...
</description></item><item><title>Download Worksheet Crafter Premium Edition 2025.2.7.191 + Premium Content Pack</title><pubDate> Wed, 05 Nov 2025 00:07:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-worksheet-crafter-premium-edition-3922.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-worksheet-crafter-premium-edition-3922.html
</guid><description>
Worksheet Crafter Premium Edition helps you to create the form of teaching, worksheet and quiz grade perfect for elementary school students &amp;amp; your special in just a few clicks. Create a spreadsheet of your own in a few clicks. It is interesting to use, tested by 1000 teacher, and as familiar as Microsoft Word. Moreover, Worksheet Crafter Premium Edition has improved the ability to use the equation editor by adding support undo / redo for better editing. In addition, when choosing a...
</description></item><item><title>Download ExpanDrive 2025.10.31</title><pubDate> Wed, 05 Nov 2025 00:06:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-expandrive-609.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-expandrive-609.html
</guid><description>
ExpanDrive is software sync cloud storage strong support BackBlaze B2, Google Team Drive, SMB / CIFS and new interface and easy user search file version, share links and much more.  ExpanDrive mapped network drives for macOS and Micosoft Windows connect with all the provide major cloud storage such as Dropbox, Google Drive, Google Team Drive, Amazon Drive, Box, OneDrive, OneDrive for Business, Sharepoint, Openstack Swift , BackBlaze B2, Amazon S3 or SFTP servers, FTP or WebDAV on your own...
</description></item><item><title>Download DroidKit 2.3.7.20251104</title><pubDate> Wed, 05 Nov 2025 00:06:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-droidkit-6578.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-droidkit-6578.html
</guid><description>
DroidKit is data recovery software for your mobile device, it will quickly scan your phone memory and save photos, WhatsApp chats and files, messages Messages, contacts and more essential data up to 13 categories, covering almost everything you need every day. All Android phones and tablets are supported. Without rooting your device. No tech skills required. No need to wait many days. You can get back what you've lost with just a few simple clicks, instantly.
Besides, DroidKit also has...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ultracopier 3.0.1.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 05 Nov 2025 00:05:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-supercopier-2121.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-supercopier-2121.html
</guid><description>
SuperCopier is a replacement for advanced copy command Windows standard. Supercopier support pause and resume the copy operation is ongoing, install copy speed can adjust, automatically rename the old file, and more.
You can view a detailed list of queue copy and optionally move files up or down in the list, add additional files and also can delete or ignore the category when needed. This can be especially useful when you copy large number of files.
Supercopier - copy...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adlice Protect (formerly RogueKiller) 16.5.1.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 05 Nov 2025 00:05:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rogueKiller-171.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rogueKiller-171.html
</guid><description>
RogueKiller is a tool anti-malware independent can assist advanced users with the removal of a number of difficulties in the removal of malware, in security software rogue special.
The program can terminate processes, malware has to know to you can delete them manually or use the tool clear of the Tuesday to complete the work. RogueKiller can also restore HOSTS file as well as your DNS settings and Proxy, which is often modified by rogue applications.
RogueKiller
When you run...
</description></item><item><title>Download A4ScanDoc 2.0.9.27</title><pubDate> Wed, 05 Nov 2025 00:04:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-a4scandoc-4421.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-a4scandoc-4421.html
</guid><description>
A4ScanDoc is a software solution useful provide you with a set of features reasonable and support the document feeder and two-sided printing, at the same time provides a fast scanning engine handy based on the profile of users to create. It is very easy to use, and it has a minimalist interface, while somewhat outdated, has intuitive layout. However, the application does not provide materials to help first-time users.
A4ScanDoc - Scan and print documents
When one or more documents have...
</description></item><item><title>Download Video Shaper 6.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 05 Nov 2025 00:04:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-video-shaper-pro-5705.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-video-shaper-pro-5705.html
</guid><description>
Video Shaper Pro is lightweight and easy-to-use video conversion software that allows you to convert and burn video files, extract audio tracks from video files, preview video and apply visual effects .
Features of Video Shaper Pro
	Convert video to AVI, MOV, MKV, WMV, VCD, DVD, MP4
	Extract audio and save it as MP3, WAV, OGG, FLAC, WMA
	Burn video files to CD, DVD or Blu-ray Disc
	Preview video files and save snapshots
	Command line support
	Supports batch conversion and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Blumentals WeBuilder 2025 v18.4.0.271</title><pubDate> Wed, 05 Nov 2025 00:03:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blumentals-webuilder-1572.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blumentals-webuilder-1572.html
</guid><description>
Blumentals WeBuilder is a powerful app to edit the HTML code, CSS, JavaScript, PHP and ASP in an environment simple and user friendly. WeBuilder is a versatile application for web developers to edit code.
The application Blumentals WeBuilder this supports the programming languages HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, Ruby, Python, ASP, SSI and Perl. The integrated tool of this software allows you to verify, re-use and redirect your code and expand them according to how efficient and complex....
</description></item><item><title>Download AllMapSoft Yandex Maps Downloader 5.832</title><pubDate> Wed, 05 Nov 2025 00:03:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-yandex-maps-downloader-4915.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-yandex-maps-downloader-4915.html
</guid><description>
AllMapSoft Yandex Maps Downloader is a tool that can automatically download images Yandex Maps on your PC. It can download the small cells and save them to your hard disk, including the normal map, satellite map, hybrid map. After downloading, you can view the map offline tool map viewer or you can combine the small images into one image large map. If you want to make a map of their city, it is very useful for you.
The features of AllMapSoft Yandex Maps Downloader
	Lightweight and...
</description></item><item><title>Download HTMLPad 2025 v18.4.0.271</title><pubDate> Wed, 05 Nov 2025 00:02:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-htmlpad-2997.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-htmlpad-2997.html
</guid><description>
HTMLPad is a HTML editor, JavaScript, and CSS smart, be so many experts and learners in over 50 countries trust. Full of features and comprehensive options, HTMLPad allows you to make, edit, re-use, verify, navigate and use the HTML code, CSS and JavaScript faster and simpler than ever. HTMLPad include CSS studio and editor JavaScript strong bring you the best value.
HTMLPad - editor, HTML, CSS, JavaScript
Features of HTMLPad
	Quick and lightweight loads much faster than any other...
</description></item><item><title>Download DeskSoft EarthView 7.13.14</title><pubDate> Wed, 05 Nov 2025 00:02:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desksoft-earthview-184.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desksoft-earthview-184.html
</guid><description>
With software DeskSoft EarthView you can easily create wallpapers to your computer or select screen saver of your favorite. the program can change day and night, the clouds will also change according to weather conditions current on one or another part of the earth, you can see the lights of the city.
Features of DeskSoft EarthView can be interesting, because of DeskSoft EarthView support for day and night, you can view atmospheric phenomena, light city can see, the cloud is displayed,...
</description></item><item><title>Download True Burner 10.6</title><pubDate> Wed, 05 Nov 2025 00:01:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-true-burner-3876.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-true-burner-3876.html
</guid><description>
True burner is software burn and copy CD, DVD, Blu-ray free. It is ideal for users wishing to record the disc usually as backup, creating or copying data, audio, MP3 music, DVD-Video and burn disc images. Free, easy to install, it allows you to save your files to disc quickly and provides flexible interface, clean to help you complete the task scored much faster.
True Burner - Burn and copy CD, DVD
The features of True Burner
	Free for personal use and commercial
	File size install...
</description></item><item><title>Download Opera GX (Gaming Browser) 123.0.5669.43</title><pubDate> Wed, 05 Nov 2025 00:01:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-gx-3170.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-gx-3170.html
</guid><description>
Opera GX is a special version of the Opera browser is built to complement gamers avid. Browser this game comes with the unique features to help users make maximum use of both the game and their browser. Opera GX is built specifically to support the game. This browser includes the unique features to help users have the best experience when gaming and surfing the web.
Opera GX - special browser for gamers
GX Control allows you to set a limit on the level of use RAM, CPU and network where...
</description></item><item><title>Download AllMapSoft OpenstreetMap Downloader 6.625</title><pubDate> Wed, 05 Nov 2025 00:00:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-openstreetmap-downloader-4916.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-openstreetmap-downloader-4916.html
</guid><description>
AllMapSoft OpenstreetMap Downloader is a tool that can automatically download images OpenstreetMap on your PC. It can download the small cells and save them to your hard disk, including the regular classroom, transpot and cycle, opensea, etc. After downloading, you can view the map offline tool Maps Viewer or you can combine the small images into one image large map. If you want to make a map of their city, it is very useful for you.
The features of AllMapSoft OpenstreetMap...
</description></item><item><title>Download Blumentals Rapid PHP 2025 v18.4.0.271</title><pubDate> Wed, 05 Nov 2025 00:00:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blumentals-rapid-php-2996.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blumentals-rapid-php-2996.html
</guid><description>
Blumentals Rapid PHP is an editor PHP powerful and fast mixing function of the Environment integrated development PHP complete along with the speed of the Notepad. This is a comprehensive software that will support you coding CSS, HTML, PHP, JavaScript and other programming languages. Rapid PHP provides a set of advanced tools to validate, reuse, debugging, navigate and format your code. This software allows you to save valuable time and increase productivity by writing code in a way...
</description></item><item><title>Download AllMapSoft Bing Maps Downloader 7.535</title><pubDate> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 23:59:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-bing-maps-downloader-6063.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allmapsoft-bing-maps-downloader-6063.html
</guid><description>
AllMapSoft Bing Maps Downloader is a tool that can automatically download Bing Maps down your PC. It can download small squares and save them into your hard disk, including the usual map, satellite map, hybrid map. After downloading, you can view the offline map with its Viewer Maps tool, or you can combine small images into a large map image. If you want to make a map of your own city, it is very useful for you.
Features of AllMapSoft Bing Maps Downloader
	Light software and easy to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Blumentals Rapid CSS 2025 v18.4.0.271</title><pubDate> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 23:59:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blumentals-rapid-css-2995.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blumentals-rapid-css-2995.html
</guid><description>
Blumentals Rapid CSS is an application that will allow you to write CSS code to create, design or edit web sites modern. Tool allows you to edit the code manually, or use the edit style sheet automatically. The program provides many useful features, including the check CSS, the code-checking, auto-completion and preview many browser. This utility is designed to ease your work, save time and increase your productivity.
Blumentals Rapid CSS - Write, edit CSS
Rapid CSS is a lightweight...
</description></item><item><title>Download WebBrowserPassView 2.18</title><pubDate> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 23:58:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-webbrowserpassview-2000.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-webbrowserpassview-2000.html
</guid><description>
WebBrowserPassView is a tool to recover password allows you to view all information site login and password are stored in the browser Internet Explorer, Firefox, Opera, Vivaldi, and Google Chrome. WebBrowserPassView can be used to recover the password is lost / forgotten for any website (including sites like Facebook, Yahoo, Google and GMail) as long as the password is your browser storing.
WebBrowserPassView - Recover passwords browsers
It can recover all passwords stored by web...
</description></item><item><title>Download Everything 1.4.1.1030</title><pubDate> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 19:35:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-everything-385.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-everything-385.html
</guid><description>
Everything is a search tool on the desktop that lets you find files and folders instantly by entering the name software or certain applications. The interesting thing for Everything that can be indexed for the whole of your computer in a few seconds and automatically updates the index.
The software is split into two main controls: the search box and the results page. When you first run Everything it will create an index of all the files and folders on your machine. Unless you have...
</description></item></channel></rss>