<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 15:37:16 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 15:37:16 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Google Chrome 140.0.7339.186</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Sep 2025 17:41:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-chrome-1012.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-chrome-1012.html
</guid><description>
Google Chrome web browser is the most used today. Support surf the web, listen to music, watch movies, play web game effective no jerky lag with the internet connection stable. When you are surfing the web or performing an important task, whether it is operation big or small, work or entertainment, then Chrome has the smart features and the speed you need to make, create and explore on the net.
The latest version of Google Chrome is the third 114. But we are providing for users Google...
</description></item><item><title>Download CyberLink PowerDirector Ultimate 2026 v24.0.0916.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Sep 2025 17:40:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-powerdirector-ultimate-425.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-powerdirector-ultimate-425.html
</guid><description>
CyberLink PowerDirector Ultimate is software editor, edit video and make movies on the computer from a variety of templates are made available, complete with effects, transitions, animations, and music. CyberLink PowerDirector 17 is a combination of video editing software with advanced video editing features powerful. Cblowing need to add your clips into the time line and click on 'Production'!
The tool design video in CyberLink PowerDirector have the ability to customize helps you...
</description></item><item><title>Download ACDSee Photo Studio Professional 2026 v19.0.0.3354</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Sep 2025 17:39:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-acdsee-photo-studio-professional-5542.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-acdsee-photo-studio-professional-5542.html
</guid><description>
ACDSee Photo Studio Professional is a complete photo editor and photo manager. It was developed for professional and advanced amateur photographers who need full control over their workflow .ACDSee Photo Studio Professional 2020 offers state-of-the-art RAW processing for non-destructive photo editing RAW image conversion and conversion.
With the Manage, View, Develop, Edit and Online modes, it is the only solution that allows photographers to perform all the essential tasks of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Office Timeline Plus 11.27.00.00 Expert / Pro / Pro+ Edition</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Sep 2025 17:38:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-timeline-2106.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-timeline-2106.html
</guid><description>
Office Timeline is an add-on very useful and powerful software for Microsoft PowerPoint. With add-ons, you can create PowerPoint documents look more beautiful. With add-ons, you can add the time Line on the project by yourself. Application time for the composition and different segments of the document, your PowerPoint will not only increase the beauty for your work, but also for customers and your manager. The people who created this product is also believe that add-ons this is the only...
</description></item><item><title>Download Topaz Gigapixel AI 8.4.4</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Sep 2025 17:38:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-ai-gigapixel-1318.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-ai-gigapixel-1318.html
</guid><description>
Topaz ONE Gigapixel is the first app and only use the power of artificial intelligence to enhance your photos, add natural details, for great results. Use technology to learn deep, AIGigapixel ™ can zoom in and fill in the details that the products change in size other are not included. The traditional method this created blurred image, a non-realistic and do not have the detail present in the image have high resolution.
Topaz A.I. Gigapixel - enhance image quality
The content of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Draftable Desktop 25.9.200</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Sep 2025 17:37:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-draftable-desktop-3749.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-draftable-desktop-3749.html
</guid><description>
Draftable Desktop is comparison tool documents the fastest. Compare over 300 pages in a few seconds. Draftable Desktop 2.0 is now available - faster and stronger than ever! See all the changes in your documents, locally and online. Take your work to the next level. Compare secret and private do not use the internet and your documents never leave your computer. Specifically, Draftable Desktop compatible with .xls, .xlsx, .xlsxm. With Office 2013, 2016 or 365, you can compare text in...
</description></item><item><title>Download Psiphon 186.20250917</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Sep 2025 17:37:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-psiphon-7347.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-psiphon-7347.html
</guid><description>
Psiphon is a firewall bypass tool by Psiphon Inc. Uses VPN, SSH and HTTP Proxy technology to give you uncensored access to Internet content. Your Psiphon app automatically learns about new hotspots to maximize your chances of bypassing censorship.
The way the software works is that Psiphon constantly changes the proxy, so the user's IP address is also constantly changing, the server will not detect the user's real address, so you can feel free. roof. access to websites and software...
</description></item><item><title>Download Google Earth Pro 7.3.6.10441</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Sep 2025 17:37:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-earth-pro-1118.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-earth-pro-1118.html
</guid><description>
Google Earth Pro is the upgraded version of Google Earth helps track earth map and share the information with others. Google has released the new version of the software package called Google Earth. The application is designed to operate with the same service, which allows you to view satellite images of planet earth in 3D mode using OpenGL technology. There is a search function by address, by subject. The seventh version has a simple interface as well as the ability to display a number of...
</description></item><item><title>Download dslrBooth Photo Booth Software Pro 7.48.0917.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Sep 2025 17:36:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dslrbooth-photo-booth-software-666.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dslrbooth-photo-booth-software-666.html
</guid><description>
Photo Booth Software is a software to create, list and combine the images back together in the same theme as travel, haloween. Created by the professional photographer for the operator photo booth at all skill levels, photo booth software dslrBooth built from scratch with the sole purpose of running the photo booth. The software uses the latest technology to provide you and your guests, high quality prints and the ability to share photos and GIF on the means of social media including...
</description></item><item><title>Download ACDSee Photo Studio Ultimate 2026 v19.0.0.4295</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Sep 2025 17:36:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-acdsee-photo-studio-ultimate-1244.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-acdsee-photo-studio-ultimate-1244.html
</guid><description>
ACDSee Photo Studio Ultimate 2019 is the perfect combination between support layers, supports image processing is GPU accelerated, supports transparency with all the function adjust the picture from edit mode. ACDSee is a program function is designed for both professional photographers and amateurs. ACDSee lets you work with digital photos, RAW images, and supports more than 100 image file formats. The program also provides batch processing quickly a large number of files with visual...
</description></item><item><title>Download iDefender 5.1.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Sep 2025 17:27:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idefender-13959.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idefender-13959.html
</guid><description>
iDefender is an advanced security solution designed for the home, providing both a High-Performance Intrusion Prevention System (HIPS) and Real-Time Endpoint Detection and Response (EDR). This integrated system protects against potential threats, ensuring the safety and integrity of your devices by proactively monitoring and responding to suspicious activity.
Why iDefender?
Ransomware Prevention
	Detects and blocks ransomware in real time to protect important files from malicious...
</description></item><item><title>Download Classroom Spy Professional 5.4.9</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Sep 2025 17:26:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-classroom-spy-professional-916.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-classroom-spy-professional-916.html
</guid><description>
Classroom Spy Professional is a software classroom management effective. Manage and track activities of all the computers of students remotely. Plus, you can share your screen with the activity record of the student, the computer controls for performance, limit the use of the Internet, the application blocks and more.
Classroom Spy Professional - software classroom management
The main features of Classroom Spy Professional
	Display live images of the remote computer.
	You can control...
</description></item><item><title>Download Prevent Restore Pro 2025 v113</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Sep 2025 17:26:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-prevent-restore-pro-1473.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-prevent-restore-pro-1473.html
</guid><description>
Prevent Restore Pro is software prevent restore files deleted in any drive: external hard drives and hard drives mounted in hard drive, SSD, Flash drives, except CD-ROM and CD-RW. The software uses many security algorithms can be used to get data.Our program includes some of the most reliable and accepted as standard.
Prevent Restore Pro - Prevent restore files deleted
The features of Prevent Restore Pro
Mode to clean up quickly
	In this mode, the program will not overwrite the free...
</description></item><item><title>Download Daemon Tools Lite 12.3.0.2358</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Sep 2025 17:25:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-daemon-tools-lite-3391.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-daemon-tools-lite-3391.html
</guid><description>
DAEMON Tools Lite is based on two key features, simulation of virtual disks and building the file disk image as iso. DAEMON Tools Lite can emulate up to 4 virtual drives, DVD, CD or Blu-ray on your computer. The virtual units will be present in your system the same as the unit. After you select the virtual drive you want, you will choose a disc image (nrg, iso, mdf, bin, cue, etc.) that you want to mount. Visit My Computer at the device have The mobile storage and you will find the disk...
</description></item><item><title>Download Directory List and Print Pro 4.35</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Sep 2025 17:25:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-list-and-print-pro-481.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-list-and-print-pro-481.html
</guid><description>
Directory List and Print Pro is software that provides function lists and support printing content, quick, simple. In addition, the file list can be formatted, filtered, saved to several file formats and also further processed (delete / copy / move files). By copying to the clipboard the list can be exported into other programs or opened directly in Word and Excel.
The features Directory List and Print basic
	Choose the folders listed in a tree structure.
	Select the folder by...
</description></item><item><title>Download NxFilter 4.7.3.6</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Sep 2025 17:24:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nxfilter-50.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nxfilter-50.html
</guid><description>
NxFilter is a server filter DNS have the ability to filter Internet traffic based on domain names and content types. In addition, it can use check package DNS to protect your network from malware and botnet activity.
NxFilter is installed on a single computer, where it acts as a proxy server, DNS. To route Internet traffic through NxFilter, you will need to change the DNS settings on all the machines that you want to protect to use the IP address of the individual NxFilter (instead of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Visual Studio Code 1.104.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Sep 2025 17:24:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-visual-studio-code-3182.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-visual-studio-code-3182.html
</guid><description>
Visual Studio Code is the encryption tool of Microsoft has met most of the needs of the developer. Environment this encoding was introduced to compete with other products such as Sublime and Nodepad ++ . Microsoft, in its new product, has not been released in many years, has provided many features in a simple environment. In addition to the familiar with a dozen programming languages, the syntax and get to know coding language as soon as be encrypted and allows for syntax highlighting, it...
</description></item><item><title>Download Watchdog Anti-Virus 1.8.640</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Sep 2025 17:23:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-watchdog-anti-virus-7711.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-watchdog-anti-virus-7711.html
</guid><description>
Real-time protection is one of the best network protections you can implement for your devices and networks. Watchdog Anti-Virus compares any potential threats against a database of known malware such as viruses and Trojans and stops them from tracking before they can cause harm. harmful.
Watchdog Anti-Virus stores information about virus variants in the cloud and not on your device so as not to slow down your PC. Our cloud-based antivirus protects you by interacting with threat...
</description></item><item><title>Download Grub2Win 3.0.0.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Sep 2025 17:23:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-grub2win-3177.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-grub2win-3177.html
</guid><description>
Grub2Win is a open source program to dual boot Windows and Linux safely. Grub2Win boot code the GNU Grub version 2.04. Everything is in a folder of 20 MB on Windows drive C: On the EFI system, a few small modules to be installed into the EFI partition of your.
Grub2Win - Boot system, Windows
Using GUI Windows and simple instructions you can install Grub2Win quickly and safely. Notice the boot time and help can be displayed in multiple languages. After installing interface, it's easy to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Watchdog Anti-Malware Premium / Business 4.3.440</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Sep 2025 17:22:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-watchdog-anti-malware-7110.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-watchdog-anti-malware-7110.html
</guid><description>
Watchdog Anti-Malware is an anti-malware with many highly rated tools to help keep your computer safe. Watchdog Anti-Malware will help you with Advanced Malware Detection and Removal, Browser Hijacker Removal, Effective Rootkit and Bootkit Detection and Removal, Real-Time Protection, Anti-ransomware Protection Module.
Watchdog Anti-Malware is extremely optimized and lightweight. Software engineers designed it to work efficiently without having to tweak confusing settings. Just start...
</description></item><item><title>Download AVS Image Converter 7.1.2.42</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Sep 2025 17:22:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs-image-converter-4021.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs-image-converter-4021.html
</guid><description>
AVS Image Converter is a comprehensive application and have the ability to allow you to switch quickly and easily the digital images of yourself between many formats, including RAW, JPEG, GIF, TGA, PNG, PDF, TIFF, RAS, JPEG 2000. and many other types . The application comes with a variety of presets to change image size will allow you to easily resize your photos to the different print formats. You can also use the presets this to adjust their images for slideshows can be shared on social...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tails 7.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Sep 2025 17:21:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tails-3241.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tails-3241.html
</guid><description>
Tails is a live operating system that you can boot on almost any computer from a USB memory stick or DVD. Tails does this by using the distribution classic Gnome of Linux. The top navigation bar allows you quick access to "Applications" and "Places" so you can easily access what you need quickly and easily and not lost.
Tails - independent operating System for security
Menu "apps" provide shortcuts for bundled software, including graphics, audio and video, office, system tools, and...
</description></item><item><title>Download PentaLogix CAMMaster 11.24.60</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Sep 2025 17:21:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pentalogix-cammaster-5559.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pentalogix-cammaster-5559.html
</guid><description>
CAMMaster Designer is CAM software of choice by the Designer for the most demanding jobs. Experience the industry's best CAD companion to get your work done. The disinfection process is fast with all the features available in this package. Exploiting Netlist and DRC sets industry standards. Basically, CamMaster provides many functions depending on the relevant needs of the user. It also provides nearly five free technical support. Furthermore, net list comparison and class comparison make...
</description></item><item><title>Download RDS Advanced Security Ultimate 7.4.9.17</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Sep 2025 17:20:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rds-advanced-security-ultimate-13846.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rds-advanced-security-ultimate-13846.html
</guid><description>
RDS Advanced Security Ultimate is comprehensive cybersecurity software designed to protect Remote Desktop Services (RDS) infrastructure from a wide range of cyber threats, including brute force attacks, ransomware, unauthorized logins, and malicious IP addresses. This software provides advanced, multi-layered security features to protect RDS servers and ensure secure remote access.
Key Features:
	Hacker IP Protection: Blocks millions of malicious IP addresses daily with a...
</description></item><item><title>Download Rainbow Analyst add-in Professional 25.09</title><pubDate> Thu, 18 Sep 2025 17:20:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rainbow-analyst-add-in-professional-11122.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rainbow-analyst-add-in-professional-11122.html
</guid><description>
Rainbow Analyst add-in Professional is a powerful tool designed to enhance data analysis in Microsoft Excel. This add-on provides many advanced features and visualizations to help users gain valuable insights from their data.
One of the key features of Rainbow Analyst is the ability to create color-coded reports and charts. Users can assign specific colors to different data values, making it easier to identify patterns, trends, and outliers. This visual representation of data enhances...
</description></item></channel></rss>