<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 13:50:14 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 13:50:14 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download DVDFab 13.0.4.7</title><pubDate> Mon, 18 Aug 2025 16:48:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dvdfab-67.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dvdfab-67.html
</guid><description>
DVDFab All-In-One is a multi-purpose combo of nearly all powerful DVDFab products-DVD replication, Ripper DVD, Blu-ray Ripper, Blu-ray Ripper, Copy UHD, Blu-ray to DVD, DVD to Blu-ray Transaction, DVD Creator, Blu-ray Creator, video conversion, Cinavia DVD removal, Windows DVD removal, DRM elimination for Apple, Screen Recorder and Editor for iOS, Hi-Fi Sound and File Transfer. It provides a complete solution to all of your DVD/Blu-ray/video problems and the perfect execution.
DvDFab -...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cent Browser 5.2.1168.76</title><pubDate> Mon, 18 Aug 2025 16:48:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cent-browser-3301.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cent-browser-3301.html
</guid><description>
Cents Browser is the improved version of web browser Chrome popular integrate countless features, including download the lazy, the tab bar can scroll, optimize memory automatically, mouse gestures and more options the other tab. Application small and efficient, this will significantly improve the browsing experience of your website and make it safer and more comfortable.
Cent Browser - web browser improvements new
This web browser based on the code and tools of Google Chrome and offers...
</description></item><item><title>Download Autodesk AutoCAD 2026.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 18 Aug 2025 16:47:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-autodesk-autocad-2025-0002-4077.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-autodesk-autocad-2025-0002-4077.html
</guid><description>
Autodesk AutoCAD design software is computer-aided (CAD) which the architects, engineers and construction professionals rely on to create the 2D and 3D drawings accurately. Autodesk AutoCAD will allow you to design and shape the world around you using the powerful features and flexibility of it. Speed documentation, share ideas seamlessly, and explore ideas more intuitively in 3D. With thousands of add-ons available, AutoCAD offers maximum flexibility, is customized for the specific needs...
</description></item><item><title>Download Autodesk AutoCAD LT 2026.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 18 Aug 2025 16:46:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-autodesk-autocad-lt-0001-7351.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-autodesk-autocad-lt-0001-7351.html
</guid><description>
AutoCAD LT 2024 is designed for the development and detailing of 2D drawings. The program automates most of the phases of the project. A complete set of 2D commands allows you to create drawings, modify them, and publish working documents for projects. can easily transfer files to other professionals. Additionally, you can customize the program's user interface to fit your needs.
Features of AutoCAD LT
	Create and edit 2D drawings.
	Annotate drawings with text, dimensions, paths, and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Agisoft Metashape Professional 2.2.2 Build 20976</title><pubDate> Mon, 18 Aug 2025 16:45:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-agisoft-metashape-professional-1731.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-agisoft-metashape-professional-1731.html
</guid><description>
Agisoft Metashape (formerly PhotoScan) is a software product independently perform image processing and digital data creation, 3D space used in GIS applications, material cultural heritage and the production visual effects as well as the indirect measurement of the different subjects scale. Technical digital photography is deployed wisely is applied with the method of computer vision led to the system processor, smart auto, on the one hand, can be managed by a new person in the field of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Aescripts BRAW Studio 3.3.9</title><pubDate> Mon, 18 Aug 2025 16:45:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aescripts-braw-studio-6395.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aescripts-braw-studio-6395.html
</guid><description>
Aescripts BRAW Studio  includes established plugins, including brand new .braw format that will be imported into Adobe CC (Premiere Pro, Media Encoder and After Effects). In Premiere Pro, you can load the Blackmagic RAW parameters in our new BRAW Studio Power Settings Panel. This panel provides durability properties and useful utilities, such as editing NTSC timecode and importing your footage metadata (Dashboard UI is provided at Window - &amp;amp; gt menu. ; Extensions). On After Effects,...
</description></item><item><title>Download G-Business Extractor 7.6.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 18 Aug 2025 16:44:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-g-business-extractor-10863.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-g-business-extractor-10863.html
</guid><description>
Google Maps is the source where you can find millions of business leads sorted by category and location.
You can search by target keywords in your location. This software will search and find business information such as website, email address, phone number, fax, etc. G-Business Extractor is a powerful tool that helps you find business leads from Google Maps. This is the best Google Maps Scraper tool that can extract data from the most important business categories.
Features of...
</description></item><item><title>Download SeekFast 5.6 Build 2</title><pubDate> Mon, 18 Aug 2025 16:43:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-seekfast-7524.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-seekfast-7524.html
</guid><description>
SeekFast has the ability to quickly search for specific text in all documents on your computer. SeekFast then sorts the results in a way that makes it easy to find the text you're looking for, see its context, and open the file that contains it. All you have to do is select a folder to search for and enter search words or phrases - you'll get all the sentences they appear in within seconds. This is especially useful if you need to find something quickly.
SeekFast uses state-of-the-art...
</description></item><item><title>Download Private Windows Script (PrivWindoze) 5.6.6</title><pubDate> Mon, 18 Aug 2025 16:38:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-private-windows-script-12878.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-private-windows-script-12878.html
</guid><description>
Are you concerned about your personal information sent to others? Or do you feel that your Windows settings have many programs that you never use? Private Windows Script (or Privwindoze) provides a comprehensive anti -remote monitoring set designed to enhance your privacy when using Windows operating system.
The main features
	End the positive process. All unnecessary processes are turned off while the scanning program. A small white list is maintained.
	Clean up the positive runonce....
</description></item><item><title>Download Easy System Utility Pro 1.1.48</title><pubDate> Mon, 18 Aug 2025 16:36:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easy-system-utility-pro-12380.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easy-system-utility-pro-12380.html
</guid><description>
Easy System Utility Pro is a powerful, all-in-one program designed for Windows 10 and 11 users. This versatile tool should be your primary choice to improve your computing experience ! This is the complete version with additional and enhanced features. It will help you easily determine your computer's hardware specifications with a system overview. You can view the operating system, CPU model, GPU, Memory, Motherboard, Network and even drivers.
It also supports launching programs,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Total Extractor Pro 3.6.4</title><pubDate> Mon, 18 Aug 2025 16:36:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-total-extractor-pro-12563.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-total-extractor-pro-12563.html
</guid><description>
Total Email Phone Extractor is software designed to quickly and accurately search for email addresses and phone numbers directly from major search engines (Google and Bing). Data is extracted in real time, while scanning results are obtained based on the keywords used. To get more email addresses and/or phone numbers, you can use more keywords and choose more sources at once (Google, Bing, Linkedin, Twitter, Instagram, etc.). There are no limits to the keywords you can use.
Information...
</description></item><item><title>Download HashiCorp Vault Enterprise 1.20.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 18 Aug 2025 16:35:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hashicorp-vault-enterprise-8618.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hashicorp-vault-enterprise-8618.html
</guid><description>
HashiCorp Vault Enterprise is a secret management solution that provides organizations with a centralized platform to store, manage and control access to sensitive information, such as passwords, certificates, and API keys.
HashiCorp Vault Enterprise provides organizations with a powerful solution to manage their secrets. The platform's combination of secret management, encryption, and role-based access control makes it a valuable tool for organizations looking to secure their sensitive...
</description></item><item><title>Download Easy System Utility 1.1.48</title><pubDate> Mon, 18 Aug 2025 16:31:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easy-system-utility-10906.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easy-system-utility-10906.html
</guid><description>
Easy System Utility is a powerful, all-in-one program designed for Windows 10 and 11 users. This versatile tool will be your main choice for your computing experience. better! You can see your operating system, CPU model, GPU, Memory, Motherboard, Network, and drivers all in one place, saving you time. Easy System Utility's interface is arranged in a tabbed menu, allowing you to access features.
You can analyze files first, then easily clean and delete them from your PC or laptop. You...
</description></item><item><title>Download Danil Pristupov Fork 2.11.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 18 Aug 2025 16:31:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fork-6879.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fork-6879.html
</guid><description>
Fork is a great Git client app that allows you to keep tabs on every file line so you can know who is the last person to make changes. The simple and intuitive design of this app helps the management of all of your warehouses much easier. The Fork interface is extremely friendly to users. There is a long list of repositories, branches, origins, tags and archives on the left side of the screen.
With Fork, you can also search and open any of the repositories quickly, from the top of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download QuickSoundSwitcher 1.7.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 18 Aug 2025 16:23:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quicksoundswitcher-14033.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quicksoundswitcher-14033.html
</guid><description>
QuickSoundSwitcher is a lightweight, open-source Windows utility designed to quickly and easily manage audio input and output devices. It allows users to switch between multiple audio devices (e.g. speakers, headphones, microphones) and control the volume directly from the system tray without navigating to complex Windows settings.
The program also provides an application volume mixer, allowing for volume adjustment and muting for individual programs. This tool is especially useful for...
</description></item><item><title>Download Easy Gamer Utility Pro 1.3.81</title><pubDate> Mon, 18 Aug 2025 16:22:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easy-gamer-utility-pro-12381.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easy-gamer-utility-pro-12381.html
</guid><description>
Easy Gamer Utility Pro is an easy-to-use program for Windows that can do a lot on your PC to help fix gaming problems, performance problems, and general optimization! The best tool to improve your Windows gaming experience! Is your game laggy and slow? If so, you can use the built-in game accelerator in Easy Gamer Utility, which boosts system performance, makes games run smoother, and increases FPS.
Additionally, this handy utility deletes and cleans unwanted and unnecessary temporary...
</description></item><item><title>Download HashiCorp Consul Enterprise 1.21.4</title><pubDate> Mon, 18 Aug 2025 16:22:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hashicorp-consul-enterprise-8616.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hashicorp-consul-enterprise-8616.html
</guid><description>
HashiCorp Consul Enterprise is a software solution for service discovery, configuration management, and network segmentation. It provides organizations with a centralized platform to manage and secure their infrastructure and applications across multi-cloud and multi-datacenter environments.
HashiCorp Consul Enterprise provides organizations with a powerful solution to manage and secure their infrastructure and applications. The platform's combination of service discovery, configuration...
</description></item><item><title>Download Estrattoredati Social Phone Extractor 7.1.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 18 Aug 2025 13:41:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-estrattoredati-social-phone-extractor-14059.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-estrattoredati-social-phone-extractor-14059.html
</guid><description>
Social Phone Extractor is a powerful (and popular) software that allows users to extract phone numbers (including WhatsApp numbers) from various social media platforms. With this tool, users can quickly and easily extract phone numbers from platforms such as Facebook, Twitter/X.com, LinkedIn, TikTok and Instagram.
This software tool is designed to simplify the process of extracting phone numbers, making it an extremely useful tool for businesses and individuals who need phone numbers...
</description></item><item><title>Download Estrattoredati Spider Annunci 8.4.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 18 Aug 2025 13:35:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-estrattoredati-spider-annunci-14058.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-estrattoredati-spider-annunci-14058.html
</guid><description>
Estrattoredati Spider Annunci is a powerful software capable of scraping major Italian online classifieds websites to extract important information such as mobile phone numbers, landline numbers, listing descriptions, listing photos, advertiser names and even email addresses (if clearly displayed in the listing description), etc.
Key Features
	Extract mobile phone numbers, landline numbers, email addresses (if present in the ad description) ad), advertiser name, ad description and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Estrattoredati Social Email Extractor 7.1.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 18 Aug 2025 13:30:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-estrattoredati-social-email-extractor-14057.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-estrattoredati-social-email-extractor-14057.html
</guid><description>
Estrattoredati Social Email Extractor is a tool designed to quickly and efficiently extract email addresses from various social media platforms such as Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn and Instagram. Users can perform targeted searches to collect emails in bulk from these platforms.
Features of Estrattoredati Social Email Extractor
	Quickly extract email addresses from social media platforms like Facebook, LinkedIn, Twitter, and Instagram.
	Supports keyword and targeted profile searches to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Display Driver Uninstaller (DDU) 18.1.3.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 18 Aug 2025 01:02:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-display-driver-uninstaller-1999.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-display-driver-uninstaller-1999.html
</guid><description>
Display Driver Uninstaller (DDU) help to easily completely remove the packages and drivers graphics cards AMD, NVIDIA and Intel from your system without leaving any rest whatsoever. Display Driver Uninstaller will automatically detect your current GPU and allows you to delete drivers, registry and files related only by the click of a button. It will also prevent Windows automatically re-install drivers when you reboot your computer, leaving you a drivers graphics common until you install...
</description></item><item><title>Download BrightVPN 1.560.626</title><pubDate> Mon, 18 Aug 2025 01:01:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-brightvpn-8960.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-brightvpn-8960.html
</guid><description>
BrightVPN is a virtual private network (VPN) service that provides users with a private and secure internet browsing experience. The service uses encryption and tunneling protocols to protect users' online activities and personal data from being intercepted or tracked by third parties.
BrightVPN frees you from restrictions or censorship by unblocking any website from 150+ countries, connecting you to the Internet for free from anywhere. In addition, Bright VPN protects your internet...
</description></item><item><title>Download RapidRAW 1.3.9</title><pubDate> Mon, 18 Aug 2025 00:52:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rapidraw-13957.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rapidraw-13957.html
</guid><description>
RapidRAW is a modern, high-performance, open-source RAW photo editor, designed to deliver a fast and clean editing experience with a lightweight footprint (under 30MB). Built with performance and usability in mind, the software is aimed at photographers who want a simple, efficient, and fun workflow without compromising performance.
Key Features
	GPU-accelerated processing: Uses a custom WGSL shader to process all image adjustments on the GPU, allowing for smooth, responsive editing...
</description></item><item><title>Download PeaZip 10.6.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 18 Aug 2025 00:51:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-peazip-1800.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-peazip-1800.html
</guid><description>
PeaZip is an Archive Utility And Compressed open-source, support multiple compression formats. It lets you create 7Z, ARC, BZ2, GZ, PAQ / ZPAQ, PEA, QUAD / BALZ, TAR, UPX, and ZIP, and enables you to open and extract 133 format additional storage, including RAR. PeaZip has the ability to open and extract over 150 file formats compressed downloads, have the ability to create and switch between multiple file formats, different background on an interface intuitive and easy to use. In...
</description></item><item><title>Download Fort Firewall 3.19.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 18 Aug 2025 00:51:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fort-firewall-6439.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fort-firewall-6439.html
</guid><description>
Fort Firewall is a network security system that monitors and controls network traffic and goes based on predefined security rules. A firewall often establishes a barrier between a trusted internal network and untrusted external networks, such as the Internet.
Features of Fort Firewall
	Filter by network address, application group
	Support of representative characters in the name path name
	Application group speed limit
	Access Traffic Statistics
	Display bandwidth
	Based on the...
</description></item></channel></rss>