<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 14:31:40 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 14:31:40 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Ratiborus KMS Tools 11.02.2026</title><pubDate> Wed, 11 Feb 2026 17:05:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ratiborus-kms-tools-78.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ratiborus-kms-tools-78.html
</guid><description>
Ratiborus KMS Tools: All-in-one activator from Ratiborus for Windows XP, Vista, 7, 8, 8.1, 10.11, Server 2008, 2008 R2, 2012, 2012 R2, Office 2010/2013/2016/2019/2021. Ratiborus KMS Tools is a small tool Compact used to activate Windows copyright with full features, with all versions like Windows 7, 8, 10, 11 easily.
Programs include:
AAct Network Portable
AAct Portable
ConsoleAct Portable
Defender Tools
Garbage Collector x86_x64
KMSAuto Lite Portable
KMSAuto Net 2016 Portable
KMSCleaner...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinRAR 7.20 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Wed, 11 Feb 2026 17:05:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winrar-127.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winrar-127.html
</guid><description>
WinRAR is a compression utility data advanced supports multiple formats including RAR, ZIP, CAB, ARJ, LZH, ACE, TAR, GZip, UUE, ISO, BZIP2, Z and 7-Zip. It allows you to create, organize and manage archives in a comfortable way and quickly. WinRAR naturally are is a leading software currently in the compression and decompression of data. With the enhanced algorithm is applied, the software allows users to compress bulk files in different formats into synthetic 1 single file to facilitate...
</description></item><item><title>Download Light Image Resizer 7.5.1.151</title><pubDate> Wed, 11 Feb 2026 17:02:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-light-image-resizer-945.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-light-image-resizer-945.html
</guid><description>
Light Image Resizer or also known as VSO Image Resizer. This is a software support thumbnail resolution images or move images in your hard drive. Light Image Resizer helps people store photos and digital images on their PC and who want to resize, compress, convert, create copies, import or organize photos. Light Image Resizer is integrated into Windows Explorer, right-click on your pictures and start working on your photos.
Light Image Resizer - miniature high-resolution photos and sort...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinScan2PDF 9.55 + Portable</title><pubDate> Wed, 11 Feb 2026 16:56:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winscan2pdf-2117.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winscan2pdf-2117.html
</guid><description>
WinScan2PDF is a simple tool that allows you to scan documents from scanner and save them as PDF files. The program also supports multi-page scanning, then will be combined into one PDF document. Useful if your scanning software does not provide PDF conversion.
WinScan2PDF - Scan document to computer
WinScan2PDF allows users to perform scans the entire text or document at the same time to serve for the saved PDF format. Not only that, you also can choose the page any of a text to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Visual Studio Code 1.109.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 11 Feb 2026 16:20:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-visual-studio-code-3182.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-visual-studio-code-3182.html
</guid><description>
Visual Studio Code is the encryption tool of Microsoft has met most of the needs of the developer. Environment this encoding was introduced to compete with other products such as Sublime and Nodepad ++ . Microsoft, in its new product, has not been released in many years, has provided many features in a simple environment. In addition to the familiar with a dozen programming languages, the syntax and get to know coding language as soon as be encrypted and allows for syntax highlighting, it...
</description></item><item><title>Download FocusWriter 1.9.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 11 Feb 2026 16:20:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-focuswriter-372.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-focuswriter-372.html
</guid><description>
FocusWriter is a word processing software text editor for in process work is not distracted, focused work. FocusWriter is a program that are lightweight are designed to avoid the distractions of the app processing complex text cause. You can create multiple work environments completely personalize using background images, colors and font type you choose, thereby creating an environment to inspire imagination.
The toolbar of FocusWriter provides access to the features to handle common...
</description></item><item><title>Download ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro 15.26.0210</title><pubDate> Wed, 11 Feb 2026 16:18:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-videotube-downloader-pro-1276.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-videotube-downloader-pro-1276.html
</guid><description>
ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro is the professional version support download videos and playlists from YouTube, videos from Dailymotion, BBC iPlayer, ITV Player, ABC,  FOX,CBS.com Vimeo, Prosieben, Metacafe, Blip.tv CBC.ca many more video sites. After the video is downloaded, you can convert them to the formats compatible with iPad, iPhone, iPod, MPEG-4, H. 264, MP3, AC3.
ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro - Download videos on Youtube
This is one of the software download the most...
</description></item><item><title>Download Edraw Max Ultimate 15.1.4.1481</title><pubDate> Wed, 11 Feb 2026 16:18:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-edraw-max-1121.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-edraw-max-1121.html
</guid><description>
Edraw Max is software draw professional looking diagrams help simplify creating diagrams, organization charts, network diagrams, business presentations, building plans, mind mapping, illustration, science, fashion designs, UML diagrams , workflows, program structure diagrams, web design diagrams, electrical engineering, directional maps, diagrams, databases, and more.
Edraw Max - Draw professional looking diagrams
EdrawSoft Edraw Max use software mapping best suits what you know and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Minimal Firewall 2.6.7</title><pubDate> Wed, 11 Feb 2026 16:18:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minimal-firewall-13877.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minimal-firewall-13877.html
</guid><description>
Minimal Firewall works in conjunction with Windows Firewall to block all unknown connections by default, prompting you to create application-based rules to mitigate malware, telemetry, and data leaks. Completely eliminate applications that call home without your knowledge. Minimal Firewall provides a more secure and integrated approach by interacting directly with the native Windows Firewall, eliminating the need for risky system modifications.
Core Features
	Lockdown Mode: The core...
</description></item><item><title>Download Youtube Downloader HD 5.9.9.7</title><pubDate> Wed, 11 Feb 2026 16:17:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-downloader-hd-3122.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-downloader-hd-3122.html
</guid><description>
Youtube Downloader HD is the best application to download and save Youtube videos. And it's completely free :) You can also convert the downloaded video into various formats easily. Youtube Downloader HD is the download at video free. Download at your videos easily and convert to AVI video format or into MP4 video format (compatible with iPad, iPhone). You can download high quality videos, high definition videos and Full HD from YouTube.
Youtube Downloader HD - Download Youtube videos...
</description></item><item><title>Download Rhinoceros 8.28.26041.11001</title><pubDate> Wed, 11 Feb 2026 16:17:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rhinoceros-179.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rhinoceros-179.html
</guid><description>
Rhinoceros is design software 3D easy to learn, easy to use and has range of application in various industries. Rhinoceros (or Rhino, Rhino3D) is a graphics software CAD and 3D developed by Robert McNeel &amp;amp; Associates, a private company established in the year 1980. Rhinoceros is developed according to the algorithm NURBS mathematical model, algorithm, focus on the correct presentation of curves and surfaces mathematics in computer graphics (in contrast to the application polygon...
</description></item><item><title>Download EF Commander 26.02.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 11 Feb 2026 16:16:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ef-commander-92.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ef-commander-92.html
</guid><description>
EF Commander is an application specialized software can help you to manage your files effectively can help you full control over the files and folders, suitable for both beginners to experts with interface according to the card format Tab. The application supports ID3 tags, enhanced sound quality and use less resources with the format OGG/ Vorbis, FLAC, WMA and WAV and other formats can be heard on Winamp,...
EF Commander - a file manager effectively 
With EF Commander : When starting...
</description></item><item><title>Download Synchredible Professional 9.112</title><pubDate> Wed, 11 Feb 2026 16:16:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-synchredible-professional-1923.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-synchredible-professional-1923.html
</guid><description>
Synchredible Professional is the most advanced version help synchronize the folder and your drive quickly and easily. Whether it is a single file or an entire drive - Synchredible Professional will synchronize, copy and save them for you. The software guide will assist you to identify the work that is scheduled in advance or be done through the USB connection. This way, you can keep your files in sync - automatically.
In the past years, the advanced technology of the us in Synchredible...
</description></item><item><title>Download RAM Saver Professional 26.2.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 11 Feb 2026 16:16:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ram-saver-pro-565.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ram-saver-pro-565.html
</guid><description>
RAM Saver Pro is a professional software optimize RAM is for system stable operation with high performance. RAM Saver Pro aims to provide all the tools necessary to increase the amount of free memory, at any time, also monitor and check the RAM.
When using RAM Saver Pro, you will be allowed to access its main menu by right-clicking on the tray icon. Also, if you want to display the main panel of the program you just double-click the icon. In addition, from the main interface of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download CapCut PC 8.1.1.3417</title><pubDate> Wed, 11 Feb 2026 16:15:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capcut-pc-9995.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capcut-pc-9995.html
</guid><description>
CapCut PC is a simple video editing tool that you can freely use anywhere. You can create videos on your browser, desktop and laptop, or on your phone. Versatile editing, magical AI tools, team collaboration, and built-in assets. Create videos in a whole new way.
You can edit videos based on editing the timeline, in the process you can add different elements and effects to the video to give the best effect to your work. It is a simple and intuitive set of editing tools and effects that...
</description></item><item><title>Download TickTick Premium 8.0.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 11 Feb 2026 16:14:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ticktick-premium-7770.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ticktick-premium-7770.html
</guid><description>
TickTick Premium is a task management application that helps users stay organized, it is very suitable for educators and students with many incentives. TickTick turns your Windows PC device into a flexible, easy-to-use and highly efficient office platform. Join millions of people to capture ideas, organize their lives, and do something creative every day.
Whether there are work related tasks or personal goals, TickTick is here to help you manage all your to-dos. With five different...
</description></item><item><title>Download Android Studio 2025.3.1.7</title><pubDate> Wed, 11 Feb 2026 16:14:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-android-studio-3890.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-android-studio-3890.html
</guid><description>
Android Studio is an Android development environment, completely new, provides many improvements and new features compared to Eclipse ADT. This software solution will is IDE the official Android when is finishing. This tool provides many tools and features such as editing, layout, rich set of tools to capture usability, compatibility version, performance and other issues, create a lot APK, build system based on Gradle flexibility, extended support for Google Services, integrated support...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft .NET Desktop Runtime 10.0.3</title><pubDate> Wed, 11 Feb 2026 16:11:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-net-desktop-runtime-5748.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-net-desktop-runtime-5748.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft .NET Desktop Runtime allows you to run existing Windows desktop applications. This release includes the .NET Runtime, which requires no separate installation. The Microsoft .NET Desktop Runtime redistributable package installs the .NET Desktop Runtime and related files needed to run many applications that use this programming language.
This is Microsoft's comprehensive and consistent programming model for building applications with stunningly intuitive user experiences,...
</description></item><item><title>Download QOwnNotes 26.2.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 11 Feb 2026 16:10:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qownnotes-3178.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qownnotes-3178.html
</guid><description>
QOwnNotes is notes bookmark file simple text (GPL) open source application for GNU / Linux , Mac OS X and Windows of Patrizio Bekerle ( pbek on GitHub and IRC) (optional) activity along with the notes application of ownCloud or Nextcloud. QOwnNote store your notes as plain text files and can be synchronized with synchronization function file of ownCloud / Nextcloud. You can also use other apps like Syncthing or Dropbox . Just write out your thoughts as they appear, and edit them if...
</description></item><item><title>Download ProtonVPN 4.3.12</title><pubDate> Wed, 11 Feb 2026 16:09:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-protonvpn-10433.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-protonvpn-10433.html
</guid><description>
ProtonVPN app for Windows is the best way to stay safe and private while surfing the internet. It is open source, easy to use, and packed with useful security features. ProtonVPN will secure your connection by routing your traffic through multiple servers to protect you against advanced network-based attacks.
It helps keep your IP address safe if something goes wrong with your VPN connection. If your VPN connection fails, the kill switch feature will prevent your device from connecting...
</description></item><item><title>Download Markdown Monster 4.1.4.3</title><pubDate> Wed, 11 Feb 2026 16:08:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-markdown-monster-2640.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-markdown-monster-2640.html
</guid><description>
Markdown Monster is the edit and view Markdown allows you to edit Markdown by syntax highlighting and fast text input. Live preview can collapse, synchronized allows you to see the output of when you enter. You can easily embed images, links, emoticons and code in text form or by using the support UI lightness of we to simplify many operations. You can also paste and drag images directly into the editor.
Markdown Monster is a solution comprehensive software designed to solve almost any...
</description></item><item><title>Download TechSmith Snagit 2026 v26.0.1.9849</title><pubDate> Wed, 11 Feb 2026 16:08:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-techsmith-snagit-01en-280.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-techsmith-snagit-01en-280.html
</guid><description>
TechSmith Snagit software screen capture anything on your screen, then easily add text arrows or effects and save the snapshot to a file or share it immediately by e-mail or IM. With TechSmith Snagit you can capture and share the article, photo or Web page directly from your screen.
TechSmith Snagit
TechSmith Snagit help you can take a photo screen in the form of roll, panoramic shooting, shooting photos of and easy photo editing after shooting. Besides it is feature - video recording...
</description></item><item><title>Download Directory Opus Pro 13.21.3 Beta</title><pubDate> Wed, 11 Feb 2026 16:07:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-opus-pro-779.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-opus-pro-779.html
</guid><description>
Directory Opus Pro is a software replacement for Explorer with traditional strength and function more than any manager other files. Directory Opus Pro full support for high DPI screen (for example 4K and 5K) with the rename dialog is redesigned, with new features. Besides being a recording macro only allows you to perform mass renaming complex that don't need regular expressions. In addition, Directory Opus Pro also enhances the ability to script.Better handling of renaming recursive and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Diffchecker 6.8.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 11 Feb 2026 16:07:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-diffchecker-5025.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-diffchecker-5025.html
</guid><description>
Diffchecker is a application compare text, images and powerful file to desktop of your. Available for Windows, macOS. Compare text files, documents, PDF. Compare photos, graphics. Because Diffchecker Desktop running entirely on your computer, so it does not have to communicate with our servers to create your difference. This means that there is no other way in addition you can view your sensitive data, you.
Diffchecker Desktop run offline, that means you can use it anytime, anywhere and...
</description></item><item><title>Download VovSoft Sound Recorder 3.3</title><pubDate> Wed, 11 Feb 2026 16:06:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-sound-recorder-10245.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-sound-recorder-10245.html
</guid><description>
VovSoft Sound Recorder helps you record sound from an input device (microphone) and from an output device (loop recording) by leveraging WASAPI. It is made to quickly capture the microphone or sound emitted by your desktop or laptop even if you don't connect any speakers.
Features of VovSoft Sound Recorder
	Save full record
	Save the silent trimmed recording
	Save split record
</description></item></channel></rss>