<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 16:13:09 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 16:13:09 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Glary Utilities Pro 6.38.0.42</title><pubDate> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 17:25:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-utilities-pro-76.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-utilities-pro-76.html
</guid><description>
Glary Utilities Pro is a collection of tools and system utilities to fix, speed up, maintain and protect your computer. Glary Utilities Pro allows you to clean junk files, system downloads, as well as the subscriptions are not valid and Internet traces (that support the plug-in more for the 45+ program outside). You can also manage and delete add-ons of the browser, analyze the use of disk and find the file duplicate.
Glary Utilities Pro - optimized system
Key features Glary Utilities...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare UniConverter 17.2.1.497</title><pubDate> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 17:25:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-uniconverter-4808.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-uniconverter-4808.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare UniConverter ( old name is Wondershare Video Converter Ultimate) which allows you to convert the video format. You can cut, splice, move, or add effects, subtitles a easy way. When using software you easily cut, splice, move, as well as add the effects, the subtitles to the video.... Or can switch the clods SD, HD video to any format popular for use with iPod (Classic, Nano and Touch), iPhone, Apple TV, Zune, PSP, Pocket PC...
Wondershare UniConverter helps convert formats...
</description></item><item><title>Download Directory Opus Pro 13.21.2 Beta</title><pubDate> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 17:24:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-opus-pro-779.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-opus-pro-779.html
</guid><description>
Directory Opus Pro is a software replacement for Explorer with traditional strength and function more than any manager other files. Directory Opus Pro full support for high DPI screen (for example 4K and 5K) with the rename dialog is redesigned, with new features. Besides being a recording macro only allows you to perform mass renaming complex that don't need regular expressions. In addition, Directory Opus Pro also enhances the ability to script.Better handling of renaming recursive and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare Filmora 15.2.5.17803</title><pubDate> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 17:13:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-filmora-2025-31.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-filmora-2025-31.html
</guid><description>
In early November 2020 Wondershare came up with a new version called Wondershare Filmora 13 with two new ways to edit: Action Cam Tool (Lens distortion correction, Clean up your audio, Control speed new) and Instant Cutter (Cut or merge clips quickly, Export instantly).
Wondershare Filmora 13  allows you to add your favorite tracks to your videos, creating a more stylish, romantic film reel, with a rich music library besides Users can manually add their favorite songs to the editing...
</description></item><item><title>Download Absolute Uninstaller 6.0.1.19</title><pubDate> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 17:12:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-absolute-uninstaller-6676.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-absolute-uninstaller-6676.html
</guid><description>
Absolute Uninstaller is a free software that provides a more friendly way with users to delete unneeded applications and improve your computer efficiency. With Absolute Uninstaller, you can remove multiple programs at the same time, search for the app, delete the entries or restore them, change the program attribute, check the program support information, see the command line, automatically correct the unvalid entries, backup and restore the installation information and publish the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Glary Quick Startup 6.0.1.19</title><pubDate> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 17:12:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-startup-manager-1340.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-startup-manager-1340.html
</guid><description>
Quick StartUp is software that helps you track and control programs and automated services that run when the computer system starts. StartUp Manager brings a simple solution to removing programs that do not need to run with your system and your system resources.
Startup Delayer is also software that allows you to monitor and control startup processes with windows, from which optimizing and reducing the launch time of the PC. When you use this software, users easily shut down the...
</description></item><item><title>Download LINQPad Premium 9.6.6</title><pubDate> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 17:12:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-linqpad-premium-7181.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-linqpad-premium-7181.html
</guid><description>
LINQPad is a software utility targeting .NET Framework and .NET Core development. It is used to interactively query SQL databases using LINQ, as well as to write C# code interactively without an IDE. LINQPad will be where C# code can be rapidly prototyped outside of Visual Studio. It can also be used to code in VB.NET, SQL and F#.
With LINQPad, you can interactively query databases using a modern query language: LINQ. LINQPad includes a tool optimized for on-the-fly context creation of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Dll Export Finder 1.5.9</title><pubDate> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 17:11:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dll-export-finder-11579.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dll-export-finder-11579.html
</guid><description>
Dll Export Finder will find functions exported by dll in a specified directory. This is the tool you need if you don't remember which dll contains the export function you're looking for. Created from a standard window with a classic interface, the interface allows you to create a scan scope by including any drive or folder, apply file filters by type as well as enter the required file name. take into account.
The results reveal the function, filename, and undecorated filename, along...
</description></item><item><title>Download LieberLieber Software LemonTree 4.2.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 17:10:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lieberlieber-software-lemontree-12724.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lieberlieber-software-lemontree-12724.html
</guid><description>
LieberLieber Software has expanded its LemonTree product into a comprehensive family of tools designed for model management and version control, especially for teams working with Enterprise Architect. This evolution reflects the growing demand for advanced model management solutions.
LemonTree Overview
LemonTree was launched over six years ago and has since evolved into a product family consisting of several key components:
	LemonTree.Desktop: Provides diff/merge functionality for...
</description></item><item><title>Download Chief Architect Premier X17 v27.3.2.5</title><pubDate> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 16:31:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chief-architect-premier-1243.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chief-architect-premier-1243.html
</guid><description>
Chief Architect Premier is a program that is almost ideal for interior design, successfully combined interface, user friendly, easy to use and library cliparts rich. After download at on taiwebs.com you will not need to draw each line in a long time and tedious, and is a master in the mouse only exact - thanks to the option to connect the walls, foundation and frame of home appear in just a few seconds.
Chief Architect Premier - interior design
The program Chief Architect Premier...
</description></item><item><title>Download K-Lite Codec Pack Update 19.4.8</title><pubDate> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 16:31:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-update-5145.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-update-5145.html
</guid><description>
K-Lite Codec Pack Update is the update of the set of codecs and related tools. Codec stands for Compressor-decompressor. Codec is necessary to encode and decode (play) audio and video. K-Lite Codec Pack Update is designed as a user-friendly solution with users to play all movie files your. With Codec Pack K-Lite, you can play 99% of all the movies found on your computer. A number of packages codec is not friendly with computers, as they tend to slow down Windows, break down multimedia...
</description></item><item><title>Download EmEditor Pro 26.0.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 16:30:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-emeditor-pro-69.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-emeditor-pro-69.html
</guid><description>
EmEditor Pro - the professional version of editor text powerful for programmers, web developers and ordinary users with illumination of syntax and Unicode support. The features of the editor such as search and replace in files using regular expressions, automatic code detect, bookmark link and address email, block selection mode, configure the button bar, menu, font and elements color. With each language you can set separate configuration.
EmEditor Pro - text Editor professional
The...
</description></item><item><title>Download Antivirus Removal Tool 2026.02 (v.1)</title><pubDate> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 16:29:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-antivirus-removal-tool-4936.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-antivirus-removal-tool-4936.html
</guid><description>
Antivirus Removal Tool is removal tool virus was designed to detect and remove completely software anti-virus. It will help you determine the current setting and the past, and it will give you the uninstall specialized official. They are designed by the manufacturer program anti-virus to delete completely all the files, drivers, services, and registration records were left by the programs that they create.
The features of the Antivirus Removal Tool
	Determine program anti-virus is...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinTools.net Professional / Premium / Classic 26.2.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 16:29:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wintoolsnet-304.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wintoolsnet-304.html
</guid><description>
WinTools.net is an optimal tool working performance of the operating system and delete the unnecessary program from the hard drive and control the start-up process of Windows.
WinTools.net integrates many useful tools, to support increased processing speed and ability, stable operation for the computer include: Clean Uninstaller, Scan Files, Scan Registry, Start Up, Tweak UI, Net Tweaker, The Privacy. Scan Files are often used to scan the hard drive periodically, search for junk files or...
</description></item><item><title>Download Disable Windows Defender 3.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 16:28:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-disable-windows-defender-14217.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-disable-windows-defender-14217.html
</guid><description>
Usually, we need to disable Windows Defender to prevent it from deleting known files due to false positives. Sometimes, it can slow down your computer or interrupt your work. In such cases, you can easily disable it and enable it again later with just one click. We can also disable this feature (Real-time Monitoring) using the Defender Settings panel, but it will be automatically enabled after a period of time. This tool ensures that this feature is 100% disabled. It also disables all...
</description></item><item><title>Download Atlantis Word Processor 5.0.1.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 16:28:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-atlantis-word-processor-585.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-atlantis-word-processor-585.html
</guid><description>
Atlantis Word Processor is a word processor app with features format, standard text, autocorrect, and spell check.  Atlantis is a word processor in accordance with most of the tasks handled daily text. The interface is very easy to use and offers the toolbars, hotkeys and sound effects thanh can customize (can turn off). It includes a clip library for quick access to the text or images used regular preview, font format and many other features aimed at improving the process of your...
</description></item><item><title>Download AutoHotkey 2.0.20</title><pubDate> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 16:27:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-autohotkey-44.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-autohotkey-44.html
</guid><description>
AutoHotkey is a utility automation script allows you to automate almost any task on your PC by running applications or documents and / or sending keystrokes and mouse clicks. The program supports several advanced features allows you to create complex with flow control, the command math, variables and expressions, functions, file, message boxes, and more.
You can even create a form to enter data to customize the user interface and menu bar. AutoHotkey can learning curve initially and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Helium Music Manager Premium 17.4.568</title><pubDate> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 16:27:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-helium-music-manager-premium-164.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-helium-music-manager-premium-164.html
</guid><description>
Helium Music Manager is a music manager that can rip, tag, play, browse, search, rename, burn and synchronize your music with the mobile. You can control your music collection with Helium Music Manager. Stop using time looking for the file on your computer or looking through CDS, vinyl records and tapes - instead, simply enjoy and explore your music! Helium Music Manager can replace the ripper, the player, tag editor and related software to audio your other.
Helium Music Manager...
</description></item><item><title>Download Luanti 5.15.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 16:27:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-luanti-13986.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-luanti-13986.html
</guid><description>
Luanti, formerly known as Minetest, is a free and open source voxel game engine, written primarily in C++. It uses a modified version of the Irrlicht Engine and allows users to create games and mods using the Lua programming language.
Player Features
	Choose from a Variety of Games: There are a variety of games to choose from. You can survive in harsh environments, build creatively, or fight other players. Just load the game or connect to the server.
	Huge map: With 62,000 × 62,000...
</description></item><item><title>Download ToDoList 9.1.11.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 16:26:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-todolist-1637.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-todolist-1637.html
</guid><description>
ToDoList is an application note and task management with multiple options, set up help you to easily split and track the progress of the work. Todolist helps millions of people feel in control of their lives more and be the leader in a number of organizations inspired the world to believe. Todolist keep all to-dos of I in one place and perfectly integrated with the other tools that I use. It helps me turn everything faster.
ToDoList - management software job
Every day you have to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Metasequoia 4.9.0e</title><pubDate> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 16:26:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tetraface-inc-metasequoia-1479.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tetraface-inc-metasequoia-1479.html
</guid><description>
Metasequoia is software designed three-dimensional model and create the characters the same person or animal, requires some knowledge in this field and most important is a set of tools suitable for the job. For those who have created a number of innovative 3D solutions dedicated software different and need to work with them without have to re-install each program, a utility like Metasequoia can be the right choice.
Tetraface Inc Metasequoia - designed three-dimensional model
This app...
</description></item><item><title>Download VovSoft File Checksum Calculator 2.4</title><pubDate> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 16:25:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-file-checksum-calculator-6961.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-file-checksum-calculator-6961.html
</guid><description>
VovSoft File Checksum Calculator is an independent utility that creates and verify the cryptography hash in MD5, SHA-1, and SHA-256. Cryptography hash functions are often used to protect against harmful changes to protected data in many software, Internet, and security applications, including digital signatures and other forms of authentication.
</description></item><item><title>Download Dragonrise Games YoloX 1.7.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 16:25:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dragonrise-games-yolox-11598.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dragonrise-games-yolox-11598.html
</guid><description>
Use YoloX to change your game crosshair.Including color inversion, sound sensor, motion sensor, heat safety and other features never seen before.Development your target with the next revolution in crosshair technology!
YoloX Features
	Effect: Invert colors and other effects.
	Animation: Separate animations for primary fire, secondary fire, and jump.
	Sound sensor: Animated response to game sounds. Now you can listen to your own music without missing any key sounds.
	Motion sensor:...
</description></item><item><title>Download Certificate Manager 19.1.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 16:24:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-certificate-manager-13958.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-certificate-manager-13958.html
</guid><description>
Certificate Manager provides an in-depth overview of your current certificates, allowing you to easily access detailed information. It also provides functions for both exporting existing certificates and importing new certificates, enhancing your certificate management capabilities.
Application certificates are often overlooked by most users until problems arise during application installation. For the average end user, there is little reason to focus on application certificates....
</description></item><item><title>Download Pulsar Modular P915 MEDUSA 2.0.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 09 Feb 2026 16:24:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pulsar-modular-p915-medusa-10584.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pulsar-modular-p915-medusa-10584.html
</guid><description>
Pulsar Modular P915 MEDUSA is the main signal booster of the synthesizer. With a solid hardware build in hand, a software model can begin. Careful characterization and measurement of the hardware, along with a software model that retains the unique structure of the Moog FFB with its two-stage design, resulted in a software model that faithfully matches and follows the model. initial. Adding some additional features, such as the ability to direct the output of each cell to the left or...
</description></item></channel></rss>