<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 13:45:57 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 13:45:57 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download QuickSoundSwitcher 1.9.4</title><pubDate> Mon, 13 Oct 2025 16:45:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quicksoundswitcher-14033.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quicksoundswitcher-14033.html
</guid><description>
QuickSoundSwitcher is a lightweight, open-source Windows utility designed to quickly and easily manage audio input and output devices. It allows users to switch between multiple audio devices (e.g. speakers, headphones, microphones) and control the volume directly from the system tray without navigating to complex Windows settings.
The program also provides an application volume mixer, allowing for volume adjustment and muting for individual programs. This tool is especially useful for...
</description></item><item><title>Download CyberLink PowerDirector Ultimate 2026 v24.0.1009.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 13 Oct 2025 16:43:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-powerdirector-ultimate-425.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-powerdirector-ultimate-425.html
</guid><description>
CyberLink PowerDirector Ultimate is software editor, edit video and make movies on the computer from a variety of templates are made available, complete with effects, transitions, animations, and music. CyberLink PowerDirector 17 is a combination of video editing software with advanced video editing features powerful. Cblowing need to add your clips into the time line and click on 'Production'!
The tool design video in CyberLink PowerDirector have the ability to customize helps you...
</description></item><item><title>Download ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro 15.25.1012</title><pubDate> Mon, 13 Oct 2025 16:42:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-videotube-downloader-pro-1276.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-videotube-downloader-pro-1276.html
</guid><description>
ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro is the professional version support download videos and playlists from YouTube, videos from Dailymotion, BBC iPlayer, ITV Player, ABC,  FOX,CBS.com Vimeo, Prosieben, Metacafe, Blip.tv CBC.ca many more video sites. After the video is downloaded, you can convert them to the formats compatible with iPad, iPhone, iPod, MPEG-4, H. 264, MP3, AC3.
ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro - Download videos on Youtube
This is one of the software download the most...
</description></item><item><title>Download Telegram for Desktop 6.2.3</title><pubDate> Mon, 13 Oct 2025 16:42:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-telegram-3376.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-telegram-3376.html
</guid><description>
Telegram is an instant messaging service and voice over IP services on the cloud platform. Client application Telegram is available for Android, iOS, Windows Phone, Windows NT, macOS, and Linux. Users can send messages and exchange photos, videos, stickers, audio and files of any kind.
Telegram - Messaging and free phone calls
Telegram seamless sync across all your devices and can be used on desktop, tablet and phone. You can send unlimited amount of messages, photos, videos and files...
</description></item><item><title>Download Agisoft Metashape Professional 2.3.0 Build 21427</title><pubDate> Mon, 13 Oct 2025 16:36:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-agisoft-metashape-professional-1731.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-agisoft-metashape-professional-1731.html
</guid><description>
Agisoft Metashape (formerly PhotoScan) is a software product independently perform image processing and digital data creation, 3D space used in GIS applications, material cultural heritage and the production visual effects as well as the indirect measurement of the different subjects scale. Technical digital photography is deployed wisely is applied with the method of computer vision led to the system processor, smart auto, on the one hand, can be managed by a new person in the field of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cutting Optimization Pro 5.18.15</title><pubDate> Mon, 13 Oct 2025 16:36:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cutting-optimization-pro-6573.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cutting-optimization-pro-6573.html
</guid><description>
Cutting Optimization Pro is a cutting software used to obtain the optimal cut layout for one-dimensional (1D) and two-dimensional (2D) pieces. The software also allows you to define and process complex products, such as desks, tables, cabinets, cabinets, bookshelves... Cutting Optimization Pro can be used to cut rectangular panels made of glass, wood, metal, plastic or any other material used in industrial applications.
Features of Cutting Optimization Pro
	Optimize 1D and 2D in the...
</description></item><item><title>Download FanControl v244</title><pubDate> Mon, 13 Oct 2025 16:35:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fancontrol-5749.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fancontrol-5749.html
</guid><description>
FanControl is a highly customizable fan control software for Windows. Stay in control of every aspect of your PC's GPU and CPU fan with the help of this highly customizable fan control app.
Features of FanControl
	Save, edit and load multiple configurations
	Multiple temperature sources (CPU, GPU, motherboard, hard drive, ".sensor" files)
	Custom fan curve
	Fine tune fan control response with steps,% start,% stop, response time and delay
	Mix different curves and sensors...
</description></item><item><title>Download Stardock Start11 2.5.6.1 Beta</title><pubDate> Mon, 13 Oct 2025 16:35:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stardock-start11-7029.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stardock-start11-7029.html
</guid><description>
Start11 is an application capable of customizing the Start Menu and Taskbar on Windows 11 and Windows 10. This is an application that allows users to customize Windows 11 to suit their preferences. his personal. Start11 will help you bring the new Start Menu of Windows 11 to Windows 10. And vice versa, Start11 also helps you to bring the Start Menu of Windows 10 to Windows 11.
Start11 also helps users bring some functions of Windows 10 to Windows 11 through customizing the Taskbar such...
</description></item><item><title>Download AD Stream Recorder 5.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 13 Oct 2025 16:34:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ad-stream-recorder-2419.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ad-stream-recorder-2419.html
</guid><description>
AD Stream Recorder is a recording program for Windows. It can digitize, visualize and record any signal connected to your sound card as well as audio live streaming includes Internet radio, free the player media popular into MP3 and WAV formats. A application small and powerful for users to record audio from any source. You can select the format of the output file and specify the desired quality, as well as where to save the file.
AD Stream Recorder - Record streaming audio
Visualize...
</description></item><item><title>Download Monkeys Audio 11.62</title><pubDate> Mon, 13 Oct 2025 16:34:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-monkeys-audio-949.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-monkeys-audio-949.html
</guid><description>
Monkey\'s Audio is software that compresses digital music without loss of quality. Supports high quality WAV files and CD ripping. Monkeys Audio will compress .wav tracks into .ape files to reduce their size without loss of sound quality, decompress .ape, convert files, check file integrity and manage tags.
Unlike traditional methods like MP3 and OGG, which permanently remove quality to save space, Monkey\'s Audio only creates perfect copies with the same sound quality as the originals....
</description></item><item><title>Download CSV Editor Pro 32.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 13 Oct 2025 16:34:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-csv-editor-pro-2039.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-csv-editor-pro-2039.html
</guid><description>
CSV Editor Pro is the professional choice for working with the CSV file. Is packed with an arsenal of features and tools, it can help you save a lot of time and effort. CSV Editor Pro supports sort, filter, edit multi-line search and replace, draw graphs, copy, unicode, print, and more. Although the interface is simple and intuitive, a file detailed help is provided. Download the trial fully functional today.
CSV Editor Pro - edit the CSV file
Features of CSV Editor Pro
	Works with...
</description></item><item><title>Download Fors Pivot 1.2.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 13 Oct 2025 16:33:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fors-pivot-13894.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fors-pivot-13894.html
</guid><description>
Fors Pivot is a newly released software synthesizer specializing in FM (Frequency Modulation) synthesis. This is a three-operator FM synthesizer designed to balance flexibility and simplicity, making it capable of complex tones while remaining fast and easy to program.
Key features of the Fors Pivot include:
	Three operators with a unique continuous routing system for the top modulator output, avoiding the need for predefined algorithms, allowing for more exploratory sound design.
	A...
</description></item><item><title>Download MultiMax 3.34.00</title><pubDate> Mon, 13 Oct 2025 16:32:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-multimax-7404.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-multimax-7404.html
</guid><description>
MultiMax is a program that can be used to create many types of processing that can make music smoother or stronger, depending on what you want. it does. MultiMax can take your music WAV files and process them for a gentle AGC action that will adjust the overall volume of each file.
MultiMax is a multi-band audio limiter/compressor that can produce smooth and powerful sound from WAV files extracted from music CDs. It divides the audio frequency range into 6 bands, optimizing the sound...
</description></item><item><title>Download Secret Video Downloader 1.0.3</title><pubDate> Mon, 13 Oct 2025 16:32:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secret-video-downloader-13775.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secret-video-downloader-13775.html
</guid><description>
Secret Video Downloader is a free application designed to facilitate easy video downloading from various websites. It leverages the yt-dlp command line program to efficiently grab video content, allowing users to save videos in the highest quality available without complicated installation or configuration. The tool has a minimalist interface focused on simplicity: the user pastes the video URL into the built-in browser, clicks the Download button, and the video is added to the download...
</description></item><item><title>Download FabulousMP3 3.06.00</title><pubDate> Mon, 13 Oct 2025 16:32:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fabulousmp3-9238.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fabulousmp3-9238.html
</guid><description>
FabulousMP3 is a multi-band compressed audio processor that can be used to edit and enhance the audio properties of your MP3 and WAV files. It emulates a professional broadcast processor and offers a number of presets that make your music richer and more powerful, or use manual adjustments to achieve the sound you like.
Features of FabulousMP3
	FabulousMP3 supports many audio formats, including WAV, MP3, WMA, AAC, FLAC, and more.
	The software allows you to convert audio files to MP3...
</description></item><item><title>Download Novabench 5.6.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 13 Oct 2025 16:31:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-novabench-5406.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-novabench-5406.html
</guid><description>
Novabench is a calculator benchmarking utility for Microsoft Windows and macOS. The program tests the performance of computer components and assigns exclusive scores, with higher scores indicating better performance. An online archive is available where scores can be compared. You can calibrate your PC in just a few minutes by testing CPU and GPU speed, Direct3D 11 / Metal graphics performance, OpenCL calculation, memory transfer rate, and disk read and write speed.
Once the tests are...
</description></item><item><title>Download Psiphon 186.20251012</title><pubDate> Mon, 13 Oct 2025 16:30:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-psiphon-7347.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-psiphon-7347.html
</guid><description>
Psiphon is a firewall bypass tool by Psiphon Inc. Uses VPN, SSH and HTTP Proxy technology to give you uncensored access to Internet content. Your Psiphon app automatically learns about new hotspots to maximize your chances of bypassing censorship.
The way the software works is that Psiphon constantly changes the proxy, so the user's IP address is also constantly changing, the server will not detect the user's real address, so you can feel free. roof. access to websites and software...
</description></item><item><title>Download Antivirus Removal Tool 2025.10 (v.1)</title><pubDate> Mon, 13 Oct 2025 16:03:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-antivirus-removal-tool-4936.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-antivirus-removal-tool-4936.html
</guid><description>
Antivirus Removal Tool is removal tool virus was designed to detect and remove completely software anti-virus. It will help you determine the current setting and the past, and it will give you the uninstall specialized official. They are designed by the manufacturer program anti-virus to delete completely all the files, drivers, services, and registration records were left by the programs that they create.
The features of the Antivirus Removal Tool
	Determine program anti-virus is...
</description></item><item><title>Download HE - Hardware Read and Write Utility 1.25.10.13</title><pubDate> Mon, 13 Oct 2025 16:02:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-he-hardware-read-and-write-utility-4287.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-he-hardware-read-and-write-utility-4287.html
</guid><description>
HE - Hardware Read and Write Utility is a powerful utility intended for hardware engineer, engineer, BIOS developer, driver, engineer, QA engineers, performance test engineers, diagnostic, etc., this utility access almost all the computer hardware, including PCI (PCI Express), index / Data, PCI, memory, index memory / Data space I / O, Index I / O / Data, Super I / O, DIMM SPD, CPU The registers MSR, screen, SMART, physical area of the hard drive identification data, ATA, dump tables ACPI...
</description></item><item><title>Download SD Maid 2/SE - System Cleaner 1.5.2-rc0</title><pubDate> Mon, 13 Oct 2025 16:01:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sd-maid-2se-system-cleaner-10472.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sd-maid-2se-system-cleaner-10472.html
</guid><description>
SD Maid 2/SE - System Cleaner is a reliable helper for your Android, keeping the device clean &amp;amp; orderly. SD Maid SE has optional features that use the AccessibilityService API to automate tedious actions. Using the AccessibilityService API, SD Maid SE can click buttons for you to perform cross-app operations, for example, clear cache. SD Maid SE does not use the AccessibilityService API to collect information.
No one is perfect and neither is Android
	Apps you deleted will leave...
</description></item><item><title>Download Smart Launcher 6 ‧ Home Screen 6.5 build 049</title><pubDate> Mon, 13 Oct 2025 16:01:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-smart-launcher-8412.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-smart-launcher-8412.html
</guid><description>
Smart Launcher is a mobile app that provides users with a customized home screen and app launcher on their Android devices. It includes features like minimalist interface, automatic app sorting, and gesture controls. The app also includes many customizable settings, such as the ability to change the theme, icon size, and screen layout, as well as the ability to create custom categories for the app.
Smart Launcher Features
	Ambient theme: Smart launcher automatically changes theme...
</description></item><item><title>Download Pulsar Music Player Pro 1.13.8 build 286</title><pubDate> Mon, 13 Oct 2025 16:01:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pulsar-music-player-pro-9602.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pulsar-music-player-pro-9602.html
</guid><description>
Pulsar Music Player has long been one of the best music players on Android. It is an ad-free offline audio player. Its beautiful user interface matches every detail of material design principles. Pulsar contains almost every feature needed to satisfy all your musical needs, including: seamless playback, lyrics display, interlacing, playback speed adjustment, tag editing, Last recording .fm, Chromecast, voice command, Android Auto, equalizer, music visualizer, equalizer, ReplayGain, sleep...
</description></item><item><title>Download Anti Spy Detector - Spyware 6.7.3</title><pubDate> Mon, 13 Oct 2025 16:00:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-anti-spy-scanner-spyware-8753.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-anti-spy-scanner-spyware-8753.html
</guid><description>
Anti-spy scanner &amp;amp; Spyware is an Android app that scans your device for spyware and other harmful applications that can compromise your privacy and security. This is a useful tool for users who want to ensure their devices are not infected with spyware or other malware that could collect sensitive information or cause other harm.
Anti Spy has been developed to scan Android devices to detect potential spies effectively. Thanks to artificial intelligence (AI), real-time signature...
</description></item><item><title>Download AI Chat: Chatbot &amp;amp; Assistant v81</title><pubDate> Mon, 13 Oct 2025 16:00:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ai-chat-chatbot-assistant-12922.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ai-chat-chatbot-assistant-12922.html
</guid><description>
Experience the power of GPT-4o technology with AI Chatbot, a comprehensive solution for intelligent conversations. Designed with advanced artificial intelligence, bringing convenience to those who value intelligence and efficiency. We bring you a groundbreaking AI Chatbot that enhances your writing skills integrated with AI Keyboard, which speeds up your responses by up to 5x
See what AI Chatbot can do for you
	AI Image Generator from instant requests and get images instantly
	Analyze...
</description></item><item><title>Download Audials Play Pro Radio + Podcast 10.5.4-0</title><pubDate> Mon, 13 Oct 2025 16:00:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-audials-play-pro-radio-podcast-8420.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-audials-play-pro-radio-podcast-8420.html
</guid><description>
Audials Pro is the only Radio App for smartphones and tablets that can easily find the right to receive the desired Hits Radio station with the Audials Network to satisfy music requests from thousands of radio stations Internet is monitored.
Features of Audials Play Pro for Android
	Find the best radio station for your music: Simply enter your favorite artist or select a music genre, country or local station near you. The Audials Radio app will find Internet radio for you.
	Your radio...
</description></item></channel></rss>