<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 20:05:57 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 20:05:57 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download VLC Media Player 3.0.22</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 22:43:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vlc-media-player-63.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vlc-media-player-63.html
</guid><description>
VLC Media Player is a multimedia player supporting many audio formats and video (MPEG-1, MPEG-2, MPEG-4, DivX, mp3, ogg, etc.) without the need for additional codecs , as well as DVDS, VCDS, and various streaming protocols different online.It also comes with a server, streaming allows you to stream media in unicast or multicast from your network.
VLC Media Player 
VLC Media Player provides a simple interface, with simple buttons control the playback standard and make the most of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Zero Install 2.28.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 22:42:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zero-install-1632.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zero-install-1632.html
</guid><description>
Zero Install is a system, install the software distribution cross africa focus. Other features include full support for shared libraries (with the SAT for resolution dependent), share between users, and integration with the package manager original foundation. Zero Install supports both binary packages and source and works on Linux systems , OS X , Unix and Windows. It is completely open source.
Zero Install - System software installation
Zero Install also has a number of interesting...
</description></item><item><title>Download Revo Uninstaller Pro 5.4.5</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 22:39:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-revo-uninstaller-pro-35.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-revo-uninstaller-pro-35.html
</guid><description>
Revo Uninstaller Pro is software that helps you to uninstall unnecessary software and easily remove unwanted programs installed on your personal computer. Revo Uninstaller Pro gives you the convenience to optimize your device, as well as get rid of all the program files you don't need and slow down your computer.
Traces such as registry entries or program files and folders may remain. Now with Revo Uninstaller Pro, you can be sure that you can clean your system of all these residues,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Revo Uninstaller Pro Portable 5.4.5</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 22:39:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-revo-uninstaller-pro-portable-4370.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-revo-uninstaller-pro-portable-4370.html
</guid><description>
Revo Uninstaller Pro Portable helps you to uninstall the program and delete the unwanted program is installed on your PC the easy way! Even if you have problems uninstalling and cannot uninstall them from control panel, Programs and features of Windows. Revo Uninstaller is an alternative agile and stronger for optional Programs and features of Windows. It has the very powerful feature to uninstall and remove programs.
Revo Uninstaller Pro Portable - Uninstall software
With complex...
</description></item><item><title>Download Syncthing 2.0.12</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 22:38:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncthing-2115.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncthing-2115.html
</guid><description>
Syncthing is synchronization service, cloud and open and non-focus allows you to share and sync files with other computers and gives you full control how to share your data and who can access it. Syncthing does not store your data in any other place, there is no server side Tuesday how to join. In addition, all the communication is secured by TLS and every button is determined by the certificate the strength of the encryption. Only computers that have explicitly allowed can connect with...
</description></item><item><title>Download Revo Registry Cleaner Pro 2.0.5</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 22:38:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-revo-registry-cleaner-pro-12750.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-revo-registry-cleaner-pro-12750.html
</guid><description>
Revo Registry Cleaner Pro provides complete solutions to advanced Registry cleaning. It uses more than 15 separate scanning categories to identify and completely delete invaluable and redundant registry items that can slow down your system performance. You can customize the cleaning process by specifying the items including and the main exclusion, allowing a more appropriate approach to maintain the integrity of the registration book. In addition, Revo Registry Cleaner has four flexible...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDQ Inventory 19.6.2.0 Enterprise</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 22:37:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdq-inventory-1468.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdq-inventory-1468.html
</guid><description>
PDQ Inventory is a software application to manage your system. This software will be able to manage your system by scanning the Windows operating system of you to provide information hardware, software, and configuration for the Windows operating system in your your tools. The tools available in this software helps you can scan the computer correctly.
In addition, the software PDQ Inventory can give you very detailed information. This software application is one of the management...
</description></item><item><title>Download AOMEI Partition Assistant Professional 10.9.2 + Technician + Unlimited + Server</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 22:37:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aomei-partition-assistant-281.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aomei-partition-assistant-281.html
</guid><description>
AOMEI Partition Assistant is partition software hard disk all in one easy to use, offers many features partition manager free. AOMEI Partition Assistant to ensure the full features to create, resize, move, copy, delete, delete, align, format, merge, split partitions.
AOMEI Partition Assistant
AOMEI Partition Manager enables you to expand the available space on hard disk quickly for improve the capacity for the root partition. The instructions move smart can easily support you move the...
</description></item><item><title>Download ZW3D 2026 SP1</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 22:35:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zwcad-zw3d-1782.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zwcad-zw3d-1782.html
</guid><description>
ZWSOFT solution provider CAD creation for the industry, the AEC and MCAD announced that the official version of the solution to top of the brand, ZWCAD ZW3D is now available. ZWCAD ZW3D official is provided by a hybrid technology completely new, and it couples the familiar interface with support systems, 64bit so that users can do more, faster, easier and better.
ZWCAD ZW3D
The features and functions of ZW3D
Notable upgrades
	Is optimization and innovation, the assembly proceed to a...
</description></item><item><title>Download DaVinci Resolve Studio 20.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 22:35:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-davinci-resolve-studio-1072.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-davinci-resolve-studio-1072.html
</guid><description>
DaVinci Resolve Studio is professional video editing and color grading software developed by Blackmagic Design. This is an enhanced version of the free DaVinci Resolve software, providing additional features and capabilities for professional video editing, color correction, and post-production.
One of the outstanding features of DaVinci Resolve Studio is its powerful color correction capabilities. It provides a comprehensive set of tools and features for advanced color correction,...
</description></item><item><title>Download XnViewMP 1.9.6</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 22:34:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xnview-mp-1074.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xnview-mp-1074.html
</guid><description>
XnViewMP "XnView MP" is the enhanced version of XnView Classic. This is the view and convert images multi-platform powerful, compatible with more than 500 image formats, different today. XnView MP easily export images to about 70 file format is different. Similar to XnConvert, XnView MP also features integrated switch at the same time batch file to help you process photos faster. XnView is another version of the photo viewer but with the ability to support formats more limited.
XnView...
</description></item><item><title>Download AOMEI Partition Assistant WinPE 10.9.2 Professional</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 22:34:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aomei-partition-assistant-technician-winpe-5836.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aomei-partition-assistant-technician-winpe-5836.html
</guid><description>
AOMEI Partition Assistant Technician is specifically designed for IT professionals, system administrators, technicians, and consultants to serve new revenue streams through the provision of charge engineering services to their customers. It is an independent and valuable solid disk partition management tool. In addition, it is available for internal use to manage PC groups and large distributed servers at various locations.
Version AOMEI Partition Assistant Technician includes all of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Acrobat Reader DC 2025.001.20982</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 22:33:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-acrobat-reader-3707.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-acrobat-reader-3707.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Acrobat Reader DC is a system of application software and Web services developed by Adobe Systems to view, create, manipulate, print and manage PDF files. With Adobe Acrobat Reader DC, you can create, export, edit, and track PDF files from anywhere - and maintain connection with the recent set of files on all your devices.
Adobe Acrobat Reader current DC is connected with Adobe Document Cloud - help working on the computers and mobile devices becomes easier than ever before. This is...
</description></item><item><title>Download WizFlow Flowcharter Professional 7.48.2218</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 22:32:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wizflow-flowcharter-professional-3604.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wizflow-flowcharter-professional-3604.html
</guid><description>
WizFlow Flowcharter Professional is a tool for drawing diagrams and diagram easy-to-use, feature-rich, abundant for Windows. WizFlow lets you define "styles" shape using more than a hundred shapes and arrow heads to be determined first. Save your styles in the template to set the method of mapping your own. WizFlow comes with the template complete diagram to help you get started. WizFlow can create flowcharts and diagrams similar with minimal effort. When you draw a diagram of WizFlow...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDQ Deploy 19.6.2.0 Enterprise</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 22:32:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdq-deploy-1469.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdq-deploy-1469.html
</guid><description>
PDQ Deploy Enterprise is an application to keep the Windows PC and the programs installed on it. Software PDQ Deploy helps you to connect multiple patch or a windows app (.exe, .msi) with multiple operating systems. The deployment software can be install, delete, run script, reboot, copy the file, sliding mode, send messages, etc.
PDQ Deploy Enterprise
Features of PDQ Deploy Enterprise
	Send notifications (alerts) via email
	Run the script as popular as .vbs, .reg .bat and .ps1
	Run...
</description></item><item><title>Download MedCalc 23.4.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 22:31:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-medcalc-1536.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-medcalc-1536.html
</guid><description>
MedCalc is a statistical software for biomedical research can analyze many performance curve system with a set of rich functionality, chart types and advanced module. MedCalc was designed to meet the needs and requirements of the study nature and aims to analyze the statistical calculations of the project. This software provides the tools and means essential to analyze the characteristic curve of the system (ROC), drawing data and perform the statistical calculations.
MedCalc -...
</description></item><item><title>Download Chess Assistant Pro 26 v12.00 Build 0</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 22:31:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chess-assistant-pro-1506.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chess-assistant-pro-1506.html
</guid><description>
Chess Assistant Pro is a unique tool to manage the game and database, chess, playing chess through the Internet, analyzing games or playing chess against the computer. Chess Assistant 19 includes the program, the martial play, the flag mode, the opening Encyclopedia, a system powerful search mode, Tree unique database of about 7.077.000 games in total.
Chess Assistant Pro - help play chess
Houdini 6 PRO, chess program strongest in the world, continue to surge the impression created by...
</description></item><item><title>Download Free Download Manager 6.31.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 22:30:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-download-manager-3105.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-download-manager-3105.html
</guid><description>
Free Download Manager is free application download manager, Free Download Manager will significantly increase downloads by splitting the files into several smaller parts and then downloads at the same time. Speed your download will be significantly increased. Manager download free can also continue to download at broken or not responding, so you don't need start downloading from the beginning after occasionally interrupted.
Free Download Manager - Manage and speed up downloads
You can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Agisoft Metashape Professional 2.3.0 Build 21711</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 22:30:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-agisoft-metashape-professional-1731.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-agisoft-metashape-professional-1731.html
</guid><description>
Agisoft Metashape (formerly PhotoScan) is a software product independently perform image processing and digital data creation, 3D space used in GIS applications, material cultural heritage and the production visual effects as well as the indirect measurement of the different subjects scale. Technical digital photography is deployed wisely is applied with the method of computer vision led to the system processor, smart auto, on the one hand, can be managed by a new person in the field of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Blackmagic Design Fusion Studio 20.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 22:29:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blackmagic-design-fusion-studio-2750.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blackmagic-design-fusion-studio-2750.html
</guid><description>
Blackmagic Design Fusion Studio is the world's most advanced compositing software for visual effects artists, broadcast and motion graphics designers, and 3D animators. For the past 30 years, Fusion has been used on thousands of Hollywood blockbuster films and television shows. Fusion features a powerful node-based interface that lets you quickly and easily create sophisticated effects by connecting different types of image processing tools together! You get a wide range of tools,...
</description></item><item><title>Download FRITZ 20.6</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 22:29:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fritz-14060.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fritz-14060.html
</guid><description>
FRITZ 20 is more than just a chess engine – it’s a training revolution for aspiring players and professionals. Whether you’re taking your first steps into the world of professional chess training, or are already playing at tournament level, FRITZ 20 will help you train more efficiently, intelligently and personally than ever before.
Simulate playing styles at the highest level
FRITZ 20 analyzes your next opponent – and plays just like them!
Use the style analysis feature in...
</description></item><item><title>Download QuickMemoryTestOK 5.27</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 22:28:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quickmemorytestok-3327.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quickmemorytestok-3327.html
</guid><description>
QuickMemoryTestOK is a free utility to check RAM of your PC. QuickMemoryTestOK will be useful when you buy a PC have 16, 32, 64, 128, etc., RAM GB. For example, for most users, the part of this often never be used or handled. For this reason, should undergo a test to ensure that no area is error in main memory. QuickMemoryTestOK can also be used to check your Windows PC if there is any behavior in high memory that may be the cause of a system error other serious not.
QuickMemoryTestOK -...
</description></item><item><title>Download FontViewOK 9.19</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 22:28:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fontviewok-1337.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fontviewok-1337.html
</guid><description>
FontViewOK is a simple tool that helps show your location and can install any fonts in list of it. To view (display) the font is not installed on Windows, you can also thanks to the help of Font View OK. Launch FontViewOK on the program screen, click the select folder Button From. Then just select the category to which the display font.
FontViewOK - Support install fonts
Many users install available font on Windows operating system of them and want tocompare the font visually on...
</description></item><item><title>Download Hit'n'Mix RipX DeepAudio 8.0.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 22:27:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hitnmix-ripx-deepaudio-9448.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hitnmix-ripx-deepaudio-9448.html
</guid><description>
RipX DeepAudio includes the world's leading audio separation DeepRemix, along with DeepCreate MIDI/MPE, a sound and sample song creation system, and then adds processing tools advanced audio and original cleanup into the workflow, so you can create the highest quality extracted audio, and refine/create sounds with unprecedented levels of detail.
With RipX DeepAudio, users can isolate and extract specific parts of a song, remix tracks, or create entirely new compositions from existing...
</description></item><item><title>Download EDGE Diagrammer 7.48.2218</title><pubDate> Tue, 02 Dec 2025 22:27:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-edge-diagrammer-9462.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-edge-diagrammer-9462.html
</guid><description>
EDGE Diagrammer is a software application used to create graphical diagrams, especially in the field of systems engineering. The term "EDGE" stands for "Enhanced Diagram Graphics Environment". It provides a user-friendly interface and a set of tools for designing and documenting complex systems, processes, and workflows.
EDGE Diagrammer is all you need for block diagrams, flowcharts, organization charts, family trees, data flow diagrams and more. Free extension packs are available to...
</description></item></channel></rss>