<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 09:27:47 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 09:27:47 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download XnViewMP 1.9.9</title><pubDate> Mon, 12 Jan 2026 23:13:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xnview-mp-1074.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xnview-mp-1074.html
</guid><description>
XnViewMP "XnView MP" is the enhanced version of XnView Classic. This is the view and convert images multi-platform powerful, compatible with more than 500 image formats, different today. XnView MP easily export images to about 70 file format is different. Similar to XnConvert, XnView MP also features integrated switch at the same time batch file to help you process photos faster. XnView is another version of the photo viewer but with the ability to support formats more limited.
XnView...
</description></item><item><title>Download LAV Filters 0.81</title><pubDate> Mon, 12 Jan 2026 23:12:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lav-filters-7279.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lav-filters-7279.html
</guid><description>
LAV Filters offers you a comprehensive package that includes a multi-format splitter, audio codec and video decoder. Visually named LAV Splitter, LAV Audio, and LAV Video, the components work together to enable playback of any file format in a DirectShow compatible player.
Based on the FFmpeg multimedia package and its built-in libraries, LAV Splitter aims to provide you with a dedicated tool for splitting various types of media files into their underlying streams and allowing Blu-Ray...
</description></item><item><title>Download ReShade 6.7.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 12 Jan 2026 23:11:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-450-3227.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-450-3227.html
</guid><description>
ReShade is an open Source tool help improve the look of the old games on modern video cards as well as allow additional display technology / new video over on the old game doesn't support the technology that.
ReShade, technically, is a tool processing general for the games and video software. Imagine you see your favorite game yourself with the obscure-around, effects market the true depth or color correction. Function ReShade by showing in an automatic way and general access to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Zoom Player Max 22.0.1.2201</title><pubDate> Mon, 12 Jan 2026 23:11:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zoom-player-max-104.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zoom-player-max-104.html
</guid><description>
Zoom Player MAX help you to see the film on DVD, Blu-ray, Flash movies and HD format with high quality and the ability to display subtitles in English very well. The advantage of software is that takes up very little system resources to play the movie with quick speed, change the wallpaper options while viewing movies.
Zoom Player MAX is the movies, browse high-quality photos on the computer with the advantages such as compact size, quick start, built-in codec. The application supports...
</description></item><item><title>Download reaConverter Pro 8.0.179</title><pubDate> Mon, 12 Jan 2026 23:10:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html
</guid><description>
reaConverter Pro is software image processing feature with batch conversion and image editing periodically becomes simple. eaConverter also provide command line utilities allow you to process images automatically, thus helping you shorten the time for other work.
reaConverter Pro integrated powerful tool of Uber with many great features. It provides advanced solutions to process and adjust images. Management of the conversion process the base image with the latest version of...
</description></item><item><title>Download FotoJet Collage Maker 1.4.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 12 Jan 2026 23:10:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fotojet-collage-maker-8003.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fotojet-collage-maker-8003.html
</guid><description>
FotoJet Collage Maker is a FotoJet collage maker that has 800+ stunning collage layouts and templates, including birthday collages, wedding collages, baby collages, family collages, love collages, and more, all designed to help you create online collages quickly and easily.
Thanks to FotoJet Collage Maker, everyone can become a professional designer delivering impressive results with this powerful graphic design tool! Whenever you feel inspired, you can always create amazing designs...
</description></item><item><title>Download MeinPlatz 8.55</title><pubDate> Mon, 12 Jan 2026 23:10:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-meinplatz-1860.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-meinplatz-1860.html
</guid><description>
MeinPlatz is a free software provides an easy and fast way to scan the hard disk to find the disk space lost. After the search is complete, results can be exported to XLS, HTM, CSV and TXT. MeinPlatz "My-Place" also has a print function with preview feature integrated print and frame rate change, and is also a magnifying glass the small screen.
MeinPlatz - Scan disk
The new features of MeinPlatz
	General optimization and general improvements as well as update the file language in...
</description></item><item><title>Download Quick Clipboard Editor 3.2.0.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 12 Jan 2026 23:09:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quick-clipboard-editor-9421.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quick-clipboard-editor-9421.html
</guid><description>
Quick Clipboard Editor is free software that provides direct access to the text stored in your clipboard, allowing you to quickly modify it to meet your needs. meet your needs before pasting the text into the app you want. It allows you to quickly retrieve previous clips from your clipboard history, find and replace specific words or phrases, insert new content into each line, trim unwanted pieces of text, keep or remove lines or characters based on different criteria, arrange text using...
</description></item><item><title>Download Red Gate SmartAssembly Professional 8.4.2.6717</title><pubDate> Mon, 12 Jan 2026 23:09:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-red-gate-smartassembly-1593.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-red-gate-smartassembly-1593.html
</guid><description>
Red Gate SmartAssembly is a tool that helps protect your application against reverse engineering or modifications prevent side Tuesday access to source code. This comprehensive solution protects the data card of you and more likely to report errors. This program makes files difficult can disassemble and injection code does not use, to help engineer can reverse and understand the core structure of the code. With your smartphone, you will have many features to tamper with the code as the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Starry Night Pro Plus 8.1.1.2098</title><pubDate> Mon, 12 Jan 2026 23:09:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-starry-night-pro-plus-1953.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-starry-night-pro-plus-1953.html
</guid><description>
Starry Night Pro Plus 8 is astronomical software for those who love to explore the universe, the stars, the planet in the milky way, a way sharp. Application has been refitted inside and out to best meet the needs of amateur astronomers, modern! With a database of gorgeous new object, integrated with the cloud service, and tons of new smart features, Starry Night 8 sets you up for success more than ever! Discover a new object, updates, 36.000, be cross-reference database built from the...
</description></item><item><title>Download 2BrightSparks SyncBackPro 11.3.134</title><pubDate> Mon, 12 Jan 2026 23:08:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-2brightsparks-syncbackpro-812.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-2brightsparks-syncbackpro-812.html
</guid><description>
SyncBackPro is a backup utility, restore and synchronize professional and enhanced with many advanced features. With SyncBackPro you can copy any file whether it is locked or is open, which usually isn't possible to copy in these conditions. But this feature works only on window XP or higher version of window. Backup with SyncBackPro is a process that is very fast and it can handle the number of files is not limited.
2BrightSparks SyncBackPro - backup, restore data
The main features of...
</description></item><item><title>Download RegCool 3.0.0.3</title><pubDate> Mon, 12 Jan 2026 23:04:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-regcool-42.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-regcool-42.html
</guid><description>
RegCool is a powerful and user-friendly registry editor for Windows operating systems. The registry is an important part of the Windows operating system, containing important settings and configurations that determine how your computer functions. With RegCool, users can easily navigate, edit, and manage registry keys and values, making it a valuable tool for advanced users and IT professionals.
RegCool's main features:
	User-friendly interface: RegCool has a clear and intuitive user...
</description></item><item><title>Download AnyTrans for iOS 8.9.14.20260112</title><pubDate> Mon, 12 Jan 2026 23:04:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anytrans-for-ios-755.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anytrans-for-ios-755.html
</guid><description>
AnyTrans for iOS is content manager essential fully managed iPhone, Android and content of your cloud. Including all mobile devices, all cloud drives from your iPhone, iPad, iPod touch to phones and tablets. From local disk to cloud storage. AnyTrans has protected them all, providing you convenient management for all data and your files, regardless of whether they are stored where.
AnyTrans is the one stop solution to meet all the management needs of your data. For the first time, you can...
</description></item><item><title>Download FotoJet Designer 1.4.5</title><pubDate> Mon, 12 Jan 2026 23:03:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fotojet-designer-568.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fotojet-designer-568.html
</guid><description>
FotoJet Designer is an enterprise software design, brand design, logo with easy visual effects without losing costs. If it is about the design of Banner, the most professional logo is probably one of the most likely to mention Adobe Photoshop-One of the top software currently. But the use of Adobe Photoshop is very difficult for new people. Therefore, the choice of FotoJet Designer is the optimal solution for you.
With FotoJet Designer, you can absolutely design the logo, banner,...
</description></item><item><title>Download SDF Viewer 2.0.3</title><pubDate> Mon, 12 Jan 2026 22:59:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sdf-viewer-14251.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sdf-viewer-14251.html
</guid><description>
SDF Viewer is a smart and handy tool, powerful enough for database professionals, yet easy to use and affordable. Create, view and edit SQL Server Compact Edition (SQLCE) version 3.1, 3.5 and 4.0 databases.
A simple way to create, view, edit or export data in SQLCE databases on your Windows Mobile or Pocket PC device, right on your desktop. Run SQL commands on your SQLCE database and see results instantly.
Features of SDF Viewer
	Runs on Windows 7 SP1, 8, 10, and 11
	Works with SQL...
</description></item><item><title>Download Black NotePad 2.3.2.30</title><pubDate> Mon, 12 Jan 2026 22:59:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-black-notepad-1154.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-black-notepad-1154.html
</guid><description>
Black NotePad is software write notes replacement for traditional NotePad with many different color schemes. Black NotePad provides a table of white color on a black background by default and allows you to quickly switch between 5 different color schemes from the toolbar.
Black NotePad - Write notes NotePad
In addition to foreground color and background color, you can also switch between the font type just by the click of a button. The color scheme and font options can be user...
</description></item><item><title>Download RapidRAW 1.4.8</title><pubDate> Mon, 12 Jan 2026 22:58:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rapidraw-13957.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rapidraw-13957.html
</guid><description>
RapidRAW is a modern, high-performance, open-source RAW photo editor, designed to deliver a fast and clean editing experience with a lightweight footprint (under 30MB). Built with performance and usability in mind, the software is aimed at photographers who want a simple, efficient, and fun workflow without compromising performance.
Key Features
	GPU-accelerated processing: Uses a custom WGSL shader to process all image adjustments on the GPU, allowing for smooth, responsive editing...
</description></item><item><title>Download Private Windows Script (PrivWindoze) 5.8.8</title><pubDate> Mon, 12 Jan 2026 22:58:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-private-windows-script-12878.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-private-windows-script-12878.html
</guid><description>
Are you concerned about your personal information sent to others? Or do you feel that your Windows settings have many programs that you never use? Private Windows Script (or Privwindoze) provides a comprehensive anti -remote monitoring set designed to enhance your privacy when using Windows operating system.
The main features
	End the positive process. All unnecessary processes are turned off while the scanning program. A small white list is maintained.
	Clean up the positive runonce....
</description></item><item><title>Download FotoJet Photo Editor 1.3.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 12 Jan 2026 22:57:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fotojet-photo-editor-8002.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fotojet-photo-editor-8002.html
</guid><description>
FotoJet Photo Editor is a powerful and easy-to-use photo editor that allows anyone to become a photo editing expert in no time. It allows you to not only edit photos and apply amazing filters easily, but also add overlays, frames, text, clipart, and more. to embellish your images in a simple way. Whether you are a novice or a professional, FotoJet Photo Editor fulfills all your photo editing desires.
Features of FotoJet Photo Editor
	Automatically enhance your photos with a simple...
</description></item><item><title>Download CrawlRhino SEO Crawler PRO 1.1.13</title><pubDate> Mon, 12 Jan 2026 22:49:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-crawlrhino-seo-crawler-pro-14273.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-crawlrhino-seo-crawler-pro-14273.html
</guid><description>
Ensuring your website is properly indexed and has optimal SEO aspects can be more difficult than you think, but luckily, web crawlers like CrawlRhino SEO Crawler can professionally assist you. This application allows you to perform website crawls to analyze site structure, find broken links, duplicate entries, as well as perform in-depth SEO audits and generate reports that can be used to improve performance and resolve upcoming issues.
How CrawlRhino SEO Crawler Works
CrawlRhino SEO...
</description></item><item><title>Download Keyword Researcher Pro 13.259</title><pubDate> Mon, 12 Jan 2026 22:44:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-keyword-researcher-pro-2749.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-keyword-researcher-pro-2749.html
</guid><description>
Keyword Researcher Pro is a scan tool auto-complete easy-to-use of Google. After being activated, it simulates a human user, and repeatedly enter thousands of queries into Google. Each time enter a partial phrase, Google will try to predict entire phrases that could be anything. We simply save this prediction. And, as it turns out, when you do this for all the letters of the alphabet (a-Z).
Keyword Researcher Pro - Support SEO keyword, Website
Keyword Researcher Pro is the only SEO...
</description></item><item><title>Download KS DB Merge Tools for SQLite Pro 1.23.3</title><pubDate> Mon, 12 Jan 2026 22:41:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ks-db-merge-tools-for-sqlite-pro-10406.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ks-db-merge-tools-for-sqlite-pro-10406.html
</guid><description>
KS DB Merge Tools for SQLite Pro is a software utility that provides a convenient way for you to compare databases and monitor their changes. It not only allows you to explore the contents of SQLite databases but also helps you identify differences and apply filters to detect modifications to tables, indexes, triggers and views .
Features of KS DB Merge Tools for SQLite Pro
	Compare and merge SQLite databases
	Run SQL queries and export data to Excel
	Compare, synchronize and merge...
</description></item><item><title>Download USB Drive Letter Manager (USBDLM) 5.7.5</title><pubDate> Mon, 12 Jan 2026 22:33:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-usb-drive-letter-manager-3382.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-usb-drive-letter-manager-3382.html
</guid><description>
USB Drive Letter Manager is a lightweight software written for use in Windows it will give you full control over the assigned drive letter of the system for the USB drive. The application will run as a system service, independent of the privileges of the user that logged in. Thanks to this feature, you will be able to easily change the drive letter without admin privileges.
USB Drive Letter Manager - control the drive of Windows system
USB Drive Letter Manager automatically solves...
</description></item><item><title>Download CrawlRhino SEO Monitor 1.0.7</title><pubDate> Mon, 12 Jan 2026 22:32:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-crawlrhino-seo-monitor-14292.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-crawlrhino-seo-monitor-14292.html
</guid><description>
CrawlRhino SEO Monitor is a professional desktop monitoring solution designed for digital agencies, SEO consultants, and businesses that depend on stable website performance.
It continuously tracks your site's uptime, downtime, and important SEO tag changes — including titles, meta descriptions, H1 headings, robots directives, and canonicals — so you can immediately identify any issues that could impact rankings or user experience.
Core Features of CrawlRhino SEO...
</description></item><item><title>Download ASDIP Wood 3.3.2.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 12 Jan 2026 22:32:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-asdip-wood-11830.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-asdip-wood-11830.html
</guid><description>
ASDIP Wood is structural engineering software used by engineers to design wood elements, such as biaxial columns, continuous beams, and out-of-plane shear walls. This structural design software is based on the latest NDS regulations. Load combination according to ASCE 7 and CSA A23.3. ASDIP WOOD significantly simplifies time-consuming calculations for structural engineering design.
Main benefits of ASDIP Wood
	Quickly model your specific parts using a simple and efficient graphical...
</description></item></channel></rss>