<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 15:43:53 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 15:43:53 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download OsmAnd+ — Maps &amp;amp; GPS Offline 5.2.7</title><pubDate> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 16:46:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-osmand-maps-gps-offline-8245.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-osmand-maps-gps-offline-8245.html
</guid><description>
OsmAnd+ (OSM Automatic Navigation Directions) is a mapping and navigation application with access to free, global, and high-quality OpenStreetMap (OSM) data. Enjoy voice and optical navigation, view POIs (points of interest), create and manage GPX routes, use contour visualization and elevation information, choose between driving modes, cyclists, pedestrians, OSM editing, etc.
This is a mobile navigation app that uses OpenStreetMap (OSM) data to provide users with detailed maps and...
</description></item><item><title>Download WiFi Pro FTP Server 2.2.7</title><pubDate> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 16:46:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wifi-pro-ftp-server-8831.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wifi-pro-ftp-server-8831.html
</guid><description>
Convert your Android phone/tablet into an FTP Server! Use this cool app to host your own FTP Server on your phone/tablet. Use FTP Server to transfer files, photos, movies, songs, etc. to/from your Android device using an FTP client like FileZilla.
Features of WiFi Pro FTP Server Pro
	Full-fledged FTP server with configurable port numbers
	Supports FTP over TLS/SSL (FTPS)
	Configurable anonymous access
	Configurable home directory (mount point)
	Configurable username/password
	Avoid...
</description></item><item><title>Download WiFi Direct + 10.0.21</title><pubDate> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 16:45:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wifi-direct-10153.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wifi-direct-10153.html
</guid><description>
Wi-Fi Direct is a Wi-Fi standard for peer-to-peer wireless connections that allows two devices to establish a direct Wi-Fi connection without the need for an intermediate wireless access point, router, or Internet connection.
Features of WiFi Direct +
	Fast
	Completely free, no intrusive ads.
	Supports all file transfers.
	Supports multiple file transfers.
	Supports folder transfer.
	Supports file transfer to and from external sdcard.
	Tested on many devices.
	Advanced file chooser.
</description></item><item><title>Download Add Text: Text on Photo Editor 12.6.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 16:44:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-add-text-text-on-photo-editor-10483.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-add-text-text-on-photo-editor-10483.html
</guid><description>
Add Text app is an all-in-one tool for creating text. You can add text to photos, gradients, solid colors, or transparent backgrounds.
Highlights
	Besides text, add other overlays: photos, shapes, stickers, and saved text styles
	Design parts of text separately: supported in Format, Color, Stroke, Markup tools
	3D Text Tools: 3D Rotation, 3D Depth, Perspective
	In addition to 800+ fonts, add an unlimited number of custom fonts (including emoji fonts)
	Change text size, line wrapping,...
</description></item><item><title>Download StbEmu (Pro) 2.0.17.03</title><pubDate> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 16:44:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-stbemu-pro-9840.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-stbemu-pro-9840.html
</guid><description>
StbEmu is an application for Android 5.0+, allowing downloading IPTV web portals, designed to run on IPTV STB (Set-Top-Box), on devices running Android, such as phones, tablets tablets and TV boxes. Currently, the application supports simulation of many STBs created by the Ukrainian company Infomir, such as MAG 250, MAG 270 or MAG 322.
StbEmu (Pro) for IPTV: Remember that this application is configured for a demo IPTV portal for testing purposes. If you want to use the app, you must...
</description></item><item><title>Download BlackPlayer EX 20.64 build 413</title><pubDate> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 16:44:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-blackplayer-ex-9732.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-blackplayer-ex-9732.html
</guid><description>
BlackPlayer Exclusive - The ultimate MP3 player. BlackPlayer EX removes Ads to focus on what matters most, the music. Includes a ton of additional premium features. Of course all the great features of the standard BlackPlayer are included in this player. Create your own look with customization available in the Settings menu.
Features of BlackPlayer EX
	Light themes!
	6 additional fonts, including the option to use System fonts.
	11 color accents.
	8 additional now playing...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaMonkey 2.1.1.1285</title><pubDate> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 16:43:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-mediamonkey-8211.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-mediamonkey-8211.html
</guid><description>
MediaMonkey APK is a media player and management application for Android devices. MediaMonkey lets you organize and play music, podcasts, and audiobooks on your device. It supports multiple audio formats and has a built-in equalizer, sleep timer, and customizable interface.
MediaMonkey can also sync your music library with other devices, including Windows and Mac computers, and allows you to create playlists and play music on a variety of devices. This app is a great way to organize and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Equalizer &amp;amp; Bass Booster - XEQ 31.3.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 16:43:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-equalizer-bass-booster-xeq-10095.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-equalizer-bass-booster-xeq-10095.html
</guid><description>
This XEQ app is a powerful yet easy-to-use Music Equalizer with Bass Boost, Volume Boost, Auto Volume Boost and 3D Virtualizer effects, which can improve the sound quality of your device. your Android device.
This is the only equalizer fx app you will ever need for your smartphone. With this feature, you can not only equalize the bass boost, but also increase the normal sound volume of your Android phone, add virtual 3D effects, save custom presets, automatically recall presets of audio...
</description></item><item><title>Download X-plore File Manager 4.45.02</title><pubDate> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 16:42:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-x-plore-file-manager-8781.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-x-plore-file-manager-8781.html
</guid><description>
X-plore File Manager is a file management application for Android devices that allows users to browse, manage and organize files and folders on the device's storage as well as on network storage services and clouds. Developed by Lonely Cat Games, X-plore File Manager offers a number of advanced features, making it a popular choice among users who need a powerful and flexible file management solution.
Features of X-plore File Manager
	Two-pane tree view
	Root, FTP, SMB1 / SMB2, Sqlite,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Zero Cleaner: clear cache 25.11.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 16:42:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-zero-cleaner-clear-cache-10667.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-zero-cleaner-clear-cache-10667.html
</guid><description>
Zero Cleaner is a mobile application that specializes in removing cache files from your device. Cache files are temporary data stored by applications and websites to improve their performance and load times. Over time, cache files can accumulate and take up valuable storage space on your device.
Some key features of Zero Cleaner include:
	Cache Cleaner: The app will scan your device for cache files created by apps and web browsers, allowing you to clear them with just a tap. This...
</description></item><item><title>Download Screen Recorder - AZ Recorder 6.7.9</title><pubDate> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 16:42:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-screen-recorder-az-recorder-8402.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-screen-recorder-az-recorder-8402.html
</guid><description>
AZ Screen Recorder is the best app to record your Lollipop screen. It requires NO root access, no time limit, no watermark, no ads and very easy to use with one action to start and stop recording. This screen recording app will let you create beautiful screencasts by providing all the features you need in a simple and elegant user experience design.
AZ Screen Recorder allows you to record your screen to HD and FullHD videos, and it is the only screen recording app on the Android market...
</description></item><item><title>Download Battery Guru: Battery Info 2.4.1 build 638</title><pubDate> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 16:41:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-battery-guru-battery-health-8651.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-battery-guru-battery-health-8651.html
</guid><description>
Battery Guru displays battery usage information, measures battery capacity (mAh), shows estimates, and helps you change your charging habits with helpful tips to extend battery life and increase battery life up 200%.
Features of Battery Guru for Android
	Batteries have a limited lifespan, each time you charge your device, the battery wears out, reducing its total (design) capacity.
	Now you can reduce wear and tear, spend less time tethering your device to the charger, and get the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Nova Launcher 81003 (8.1.3) Beta</title><pubDate> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 16:40:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-nova-launcher-10503.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-nova-launcher-10503.html
</guid><description>
Nova Launcher is a powerful, customizable, and flexible home screen replacement. Nova brings advanced features to enhance your home screen but remains a great, user-friendly choice for everyone. Whether you want to completely overhaul your home screen or are looking for a cleaner, faster home screen launcher, Nova is the answer.
Nova Launcher Features
	Latest features: Nova brings the latest Android launcher features to all other phones.
	Custom icon themes: Nova supports thousands of...
</description></item><item><title>Download DIGI Clock Widget Plus 3.6.0 build 25806</title><pubDate> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 16:40:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-digi-clock-widget-plus-8539.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-digi-clock-widget-plus-8539.html
</guid><description>
DIGI Clock Widget Plus is an ad-free version of "DIGI Clock Widget" - highly customizable digital time and date widgets:
	2x1 widget - small
	4x1 widget - wide option in seconds
	4x2 widget - large
	5x2 widget - for tablets and especially for Galaxy Note
	6x3 widget - for tablet.
Features of DIGI Clock Widget Plus
	preview widget during setup (on Android ICS+)
	choose widget click action: tap widget to load alarm app, install widget or any installed app
	allows you to individually...
</description></item><item><title>Download Digital Compass 17.8</title><pubDate> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 16:39:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-digital-compass-13590.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-digital-compass-13590.html
</guid><description>
This app is a smart compass with high accuracy and a great tool for outdoor activities. This compass app allows you to easily determine the direction you are facing. This app is built using the device's gyroscope, accelerometer, magnetometer, gravity sensor to determine the direction. Make sure your device has an accelerometer and magnetometer sensor or it will not work.
Features
	Show current location (longitude, latitude, address)
	Show altitude
	Show magnetic field strength
	Show...
</description></item><item><title>Download Block WiFi &amp;amp; IP Tools 1.6</title><pubDate> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 16:39:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-block-wifi-ip-tools-14055.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-block-wifi-ip-tools-14055.html
</guid><description>
Block WiFi &amp;amp; IP Tools is a powerful WiFi analysis and IP toolkit that helps you monitor, manage, and secure your home WiFi network in real-time. Discover all connected devices, block unknown users, boost network performance, and protect your internet from intruders — all from your mobile device.
Whether you're experiencing slow network or suspicious devices, Block WiFi &amp;amp; IP Tools is the solution. IP Tools gives you full control over your WiFi network with advanced features...
</description></item><item><title>Download Smart AudioBook Player 11.5.9</title><pubDate> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 16:38:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-smart-audiobook-player-8181.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-smart-audiobook-player-8181.html
</guid><description>
Smart AudioBook Player is a type of application that allows users to listen to audiobooks on their mobile devices. This app is designed to improve the listening experience by providing features such as automatic bookmarking, adjustable playback speed, and sleep timer. The program is specially designed to play audio books. Let's say you have audiobooks and have copied them to your phone.
Smart AudioBook Player Features
	Supports Chromecast.
	Control playback speed.
	Categorize books...
</description></item><item><title>Download EOBD Facile: OBD2 Car Scanner 3.80.1127</title><pubDate> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 16:37:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-eobd-facile-obd2-car-scanner-8698.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-eobd-facile-obd2-car-scanner-8698.html
</guid><description>
Run diagnostics on your car with your Android Smartphone or tablet and discover why the engine light is on... no need to check the manufacturer's manual! Connect the ELM 327 interface to your car's OBD2 port and run the app: you will be able to read engine and transmission error codes and view data from your vehicle in real time.
EOBD Facile features for Android
	View engine and transmission fault codes (also known as DTCs) and see what they mean (over 11,000 definitions...
</description></item><item><title>Download Auto Text: Schedule Messages 5.8.4</title><pubDate> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 16:37:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-auto-text-auto-send-message-8447.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-auto-text-auto-send-message-8447.html
</guid><description>
Auto Text: Auto send WA &amp;amp; SMS is a feature or application that allows users to automatically send pre-written text messages at a specific time or in response to a request. specific activation. This feature can be useful in many situations, such as sending reminders, sending messages to loved ones at a specific time, or sending messages in response to certain events, such as calls to or location-based triggers.
Auto Text features: Auto send WA &amp;amp; SMS
	Automatically send happy...
</description></item><item><title>Download Unit Converter Pro 2.6.5</title><pubDate> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 16:36:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-unit-converter-pro-9060.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-unit-converter-pro-9060.html
</guid><description>
Pro Unit Converter is the 6th set of the Smart Tools® collection. This app includes currency exchange rates (money, bitcoin). It has no ads and ads are replaced with useful texts. There are many unit conversion applications on the market. However, most are inconvenient and difficult to use because of poor and complicated user interfaces.
Features of Unit Converter Pro
	Basic: length (distance), area, weight (mass), volume (capacity)
	Life: exchange rates, temperature, time, speed,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cinema FV-5 2.2.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 16:36:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-cinema-fv-5-9801.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-cinema-fv-5-9801.html
</guid><description>
Cinema FV-5 is a professional video camera app for mobile devices that puts professional manual controls at your fingertips. Designed for professional and enthusiast filmmakers and videographers, with this video camera app, you can capture the best footage with top-notch controls for flawless post-production. The only limit is your imagination and creativity!
Features of Cinema FV-5
	Adjust all the image sensor parameters you only think professional video cameras have: exposure...
</description></item><item><title>Download BetterSleep: Sleep tracker 25.19.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 16:35:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-bettersleep-sleep-tracker-8274.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-bettersleep-sleep-tracker-8274.html
</guid><description>
BetterSleep is a sleep tracking app that helps users track and improve their sleeping habits. The app uses the phone's sensors to track movement and sounds during sleep, then provides users with detailed sleep reports and analysis. It also includes features such as a sleep log, smart alarm, and white noise generation to help users fall asleep and wake up more refreshed. Additionally, BetterSleep allows users to set sleep goals, track their progress, and receive personalized...
</description></item><item><title>Download Podcast Player App - Castbox 11.23.0-251022111</title><pubDate> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 16:35:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-podcast-player-app-castbox-8386.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-podcast-player-app-castbox-8386.html
</guid><description>
The best podcast app and podcast player to find, save, download and listen to your favorite podcasts, FM, radio and audiobooks. Castbox is an easy-to-use podcast player for podcast lovers, offering a super clean layout and an easy-to-navigate interface. With a diverse catalog of podcasts to choose from, you can stream or download your favorite podcasts anywhere, anytime for free.
Access over 95 million audio content including podcasts, audiobooks, FM radio, and more. in 27 different...
</description></item><item><title>Download Fitify: Fitness, Home Workout 1.111</title><pubDate> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 16:32:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-fitify-fitness-home-workout-8397.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-fitify-fitness-home-workout-8397.html
</guid><description>
Fitify is a mobile app that offers users a variety of workout routines and workouts, including bodyweight exercises with weights, resistance bands, and kettlebells as well as stretching exercises and start up. It also includes features like progress tracking, creating custom workout plans, and setting fitness goals. The app also includes many customizable settings, such as the ability to choose between different types of exercises, such as strength, cardio, and flexibility, as well as...
</description></item><item><title>Download Digital Clock &amp;amp; World Weather 8.90.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 04 Nov 2025 16:32:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-digital-clock-world-weather-13567.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-digital-clock-world-weather-13567.html
</guid><description>
A feature-rich weather app with support for 4x2 widgets. Check the time and weather from your home screen customize the widget using one of the provided skins and make your screen look the way you want.
The weather app supports the following:
	Current weather conditions, 7-day weather and 12-hour weather
	Useful weather information (current temperature, chance of rain and snow, wind speed and direction, atmospheric pressure, etc.)
	Extended daily forecast (7 to 15 days, depending on...
</description></item></channel></rss>