<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 03:34:20 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 03:34:20 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download DefenderUI 1.46</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Dec 2025 17:36:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-defenderui-6893.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-defenderui-6893.html
</guid><description>
DefenderUI greatly improves the usability and unlocks many hidden Windows Security features in Windows 10 and 11. DefenderUI puts you in full control of your settings. Microsoft Defender security features. It is easy to use, it has different security profiles, and it features one-click access to both basic and advanced security settings. With its help, Microsoft Defender is no longer a background antivirus but a full-featured security tool with various settings and options.
There are...
</description></item><item><title>Download WDAC Lockdown 1.46</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Dec 2025 17:36:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wdac-lockdown-13875.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wdac-lockdown-13875.html
</guid><description>
WDAC is a security feature in Windows that can filter which applications are allowed to run code on the local system. Only software authorized by the user can execute code while the WDAC service is running, making it a whitelist-based filter for the operating system. Aimed at streamlining WDAC management and enhancing its default functionality, WDAC Lockdown provides users with the means to create custom policies and whitelist configurations, while also providing additional security...
</description></item><item><title>Download HomeBank 5.9.6</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Dec 2025 17:35:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-homebank-1160.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-homebank-1160.html
</guid><description>
HomeBank is a software personal accounting helps you manage finances, track expenses and manage your budget. HomeBank can nerd the interface is quite simple but the program back offers all the features that most people need to manage personal finance their.
HomeBank - Manage personal finance
In addition, you can import your bank statements from the file OFX / QFX, customize the type of spending and income, set a limit personal budget and create a custom report (with chart) to know you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Topaz Photo Pro 1.1.0 Final</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Dec 2025 17:30:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-photo-ai-8105.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-photo-ai-8105.html
</guid><description>
What is Topaz Photo AI?
Topaz Photo AI is a professional software that automatically adjusts for your image quality needs. Simply import images into Topaz Photo AI and it will use specially trained AI models to first detect unique details, clarity, and resolution issues before applying the intelligently adjusts to maximize your image quality.
For users experienced with Topaz Labs image quality applications, it combines the functionality of DeNoise AI, Sharpen AI and Gigapixel AI into...
</description></item><item><title>Download CareUEyes Pro 2.5.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Dec 2025 17:30:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-careueyes-783.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-careueyes-783.html
</guid><description>
CareUEyes is software that protects the eye by adjusting the light as normal, intelligent auto. CareUEyes can automatically filter blue light and make your screen come up naturally, comfortable to your eyes not feel tired.
CareUEyes providing notice of rest to help you not work too long at a time It is very important to rest often and not just your eyes benefit from them. This app can make sure you don't forget to rest at all times, by displaying the notification on the screen in a...
</description></item><item><title>Download FreeFileSync Donation Edition 14.6</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Dec 2025 17:29:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-freefilesync-donation-edition-13970.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-freefilesync-donation-edition-13970.html
</guid><description>
FreeFileSync Donation Edition is a special version of the FreeFileSync file synchronization software for donors who financially support projects. It is used to compare and synchronize folders, create and manage backups of all your important files. Instead of copying every file each time, FreeFileSync determines the difference between the source and destination folders and transfers only the minimum amount of data necessary.
FreeFileSync version with additional functionality and...
</description></item><item><title>Download System Mechanic Pro 26.0.0.10 + Standard</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Dec 2025 17:28:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-system-mechanic-434.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-system-mechanic-434.html
</guid><description>
System Mechanic Pro is tool cleanup and repair errors on the system and restore hard drive and operating speed window.  System Mechanic helps you to clean your entire computer system, delete the unnecessary files, detect and repair the incident occurred due to virus attack or due to mistakenly deleted system files.
System Mechanic offers many useful features such as Registry cleaning, defragmenting computer memory, protect your privacy while accessing the Internet. With programs this...
</description></item><item><title>Download System Mechanic Ultimate Defense 26.0.0.10</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Dec 2025 17:28:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-system-mechanic-ultimate-defense-1974.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-system-mechanic-ultimate-defense-1974.html
</guid><description>
System Mechanic Ultimate Defense is software provides tracking features anti browser and protect your online privacy, management, encryption and secure password protection, anti-virus certified, VB100, detect and remove malware on demand, technology, erase hard drive military grade, award-winning optimize PC, software, file recovery advanced.
Malware threats is growing fast now because of almost a million new viruses, worms, trojan horses, rootkits and other types of spyware, and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Batch XLS and XLSX Converter 2025.17.1219.2705</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Dec 2025 17:21:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-batch-xls-and-xlsx-converter-6064.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-batch-xls-and-xlsx-converter-6064.html
</guid><description>
Batch XLS and XLSX Converter is software to convert Excel XLS to XLSX and XLSX to XLS easily. Batch XLS and XLSX Converter supports the search for multiple files in a strong way. Conversion tool XLS and XLSX for Excel. Batch XLS and XLSX Converter supports the project and the line. Batch XLS and XLSX Converter has a friendly GUI that should be used very easily. Support for the Batch XLS &amp;amp; XLSX Converter Drag and Explorer Context.
Batch XLS and XLSX Converter supports efficient...
</description></item><item><title>Download Bitwig Studio 6.0 Beta 11</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Dec 2025 17:20:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bitwig-studio-3626.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bitwig-studio-3626.html
</guid><description>
Find new standard in the process of individual work. Bitwig Studio excite you good control over his music, give you access to all features of your production. Streamline course creation of you and quickly develop your ideas into the songs, compositions and music full.
Bitwig Studio - Create your own music
Arrange and record, perform and improvise, or do all at the same time. Choose among the many records displayed. Design your sound with the equipment container commitment. Mixing the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Batch DOC to TXT Converter 2025.17.1219.2435</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Dec 2025 17:20:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-batch-doc-to-txt-converter-7561.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-batch-doc-to-txt-converter-7561.html
</guid><description>
Batch DOC to TXT Converter is a tool to batch convert Word to TXT, DOC/DOCX to TXT documents easily. Batch DOC TO TXT Converter supports searching multiple files powerfully. A TXT publisher for Word. Batch DOC to TXT Converter has a friendly interface that makes it very easy to use. In addition, it also supports you to batch convert to save time.
Features of Batch DOC to TXT Converter
	Convert Word DOC/DOCX to text easily.
	Batch convert DOC to TXT with GUI with powerful search...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ekahau AI Pro 11.8.8</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Dec 2025 17:19:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ekahau-ai-pro-7947.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ekahau-ai-pro-7947.html
</guid><description>
Ekahau AI Pro is powerful Wi-Fi planning software and AI design for the most reliable, best performing wireless networks, now including 6GHz. Ekahau AI Pro is the Wi-Fi design software top choice for IT professionals for business-critical Wi-Fi design and implementation projects.
Use the new Channel Planner and Network Simulator to show recommended improvements to your existing network design, or start a redesign with the complete AI Automated Planner completely new and discover optimal...
</description></item><item><title>Download DP Animation Maker 3.5.45</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Dec 2025 17:19:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dp-animation-maker-2860.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dp-animation-maker-2860.html
</guid><description>
DP Animation Maker - 2D animation software smart allows you to turn static images into motion directly. The world is a living, breathing from your still images with minimal effort. DP Animation Maker lets you make natural scenes burst with vibrancy and bring out the motion to people and objects.
DP Animation Maker - Create and edit animated GIF
Animation Maker has the tools rich that you need to put all the pieces together. When you select pictures of yourself, it's easy to move from...
</description></item><item><title>Download StruSoft FEM-Design Suite 24.00.005</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Dec 2025 17:19:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-strusoft-fem-design-suite-7996.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-strusoft-fem-design-suite-7996.html
</guid><description>
FEM-Design Suite is a software for designing concrete, steel and timber structures according to EU standards. It features a unique user-friendly working environment based on familiar CAD tools that make structural modeling and editing simple and intuitive. The fast and easy nature of FEM-Design makes it ideal for all types of construction tasks from single element design to global stable analysis of large structures and making it become the best practical tool for structural...
</description></item><item><title>Download Batch CHM to DOC Converter 2025.17.1219.3604</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Dec 2025 17:18:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-batch-chm-to-word-converter-5412.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-batch-chm-to-word-converter-5412.html
</guid><description>
Batch CHM to Word Converter is a CHM to Word Document batch converter which can convert HTML Help to Word DOC and DOCX easily. Batch CHM to Word Converter supports searching multiple files in a powerful way. Compressed HTML Help Converter for Windows. Batch CHM to Word Converter supports project and command line. Batch CHM to Word Converter has a friendly GUI so it's very easy to use. Batch support CHM TO Word DOC Converter Drag and Explorer Context.
Batch CHM to Word Converter supports...
</description></item><item><title>Download VovSoft - Vov Screen Recorder 4.5</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Dec 2025 17:18:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-screen-recorder-5507.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-screen-recorder-5507.html
</guid><description>
VovSoft Screen Recorder is a handy tool for taking screenshots of your computer, ie recording the activities happening on the screen. Using Vov Screen Recorder, you can record your screen to create program videos, compile product demo videos for some customers, record gameplay to post on social networks or record any other screen activity to share with friends or stakeholders or to upload video streaming services such as YouTube. Vov Screen Recorder can capture a specific area or full...
</description></item><item><title>Download JangaFX LiquiGen 1.0.5</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Dec 2025 17:17:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jangafx-liquigen-14152.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jangafx-liquigen-14152.html
</guid><description>
JangaFX LiquiGen is a real-time fluid simulation software designed to create fluid simulations such as water, liquids, and dynamic fluid effects. The software uses GPU acceleration to enable near real-time fluid simulation and mesh generation with advanced features such as a PIC/FLIP solver that can simulate swirling water effects including spray, foam, and bubbles. LiquiGen supports the simulation of viscous fluids like honey and oil, reproducing complex behaviors like rolling and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Batch CHM to PDF Converter 2025.17.1219.2273</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Dec 2025 17:17:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-batch-chm-to-pdf-converter-5067.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-batch-chm-to-pdf-converter-5067.html
</guid><description>
Batch CHM to PDF Converter is a conversion tool, batch CHM to PDF can convert HTML help to document and PDF files in an easy way. Batch CHM to PDF Converter supports powerful search for lots of files. The convert HTML help to be compressed for Windows. Batch CHM to PDF Converter supports project and command line. Batch CHM to PDF Converter has user friendly GUI so used very easily. Batch CHM to PDF Converter Drag and Explorer Context supported.
Batch CHM to PDF Converter supports...
</description></item><item><title>Download CrawlRhino SEO Crawler PRO 1.1.11</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Dec 2025 17:16:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-crawlrhino-seo-crawler-pro-14273.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-crawlrhino-seo-crawler-pro-14273.html
</guid><description>
Ensuring your website is properly indexed and has optimal SEO aspects can be more difficult than you think, but luckily, web crawlers like CrawlRhino SEO Crawler can professionally assist you. This application allows you to perform website crawls to analyze site structure, find broken links, duplicate entries, as well as perform in-depth SEO audits and generate reports that can be used to improve performance and resolve upcoming issues.
How CrawlRhino SEO Crawler Works
CrawlRhino SEO...
</description></item><item><title>Download LuBan 3D 11.12.2025</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Dec 2025 17:16:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-luban-3d-10427.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-luban-3d-10427.html
</guid><description>
LuBan 3D is creative design software that helps designers and manufacturers create their innovative products quickly. LuBan automatically creates 3D models in a variety of forms, such as lithophane, stacks, hashes, slabs, reliefs, modules, and wireframes. The resulting model can be fabricated by 3D printing, laser cutting and CNC milling. Model parts can be fabricated using laser cutting and 3D printing. LuBan does not depend on specific fabrication methods; instead, it can communicate...
</description></item><item><title>Download JangaFX IlluGen 1.1.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Dec 2025 17:15:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jangafx-illugen-13967.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jangafx-illugen-13967.html
</guid><description>
IlluGen is the world's first tool specifically built for VFX and real-time technical content creation. When creating special effects for games, we spend a lot of time fine-tuning cinematic tools to fit our unique content creation workflow. Visual effects are essential to delivering gameplay to players, but we rarely get direct support for the tools we need. We felt it was time to give real-time FX artists the tool of their dreams.
Summarize your workflow
IlluGen was built to summarize...
</description></item><item><title>Download Batch Access Database Compactor 2025.17.1219.2631</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Dec 2025 17:15:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-batch-access-database-compactor-5068.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-batch-access-database-compactor-5068.html
</guid><description>
Batch Access Database Compactor is a software to help optimize and help compact and repair database access in an easy way. Batch Access Database Compactor can compress and repair Access database without installing Office. Batch Access Database Compactor supports project and command line. Batch Access Database Compactor has friendly GUI so used very easily. Batch Access Database Compactor Drag and Explorer Context supported.
Batch Access Database Compactor supports a compression tool...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tomabo MP4 Downloader Pro 6.0.9</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Dec 2025 17:15:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tomabo-mp4-downloader-pro-3602.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tomabo-mp4-downloader-pro-3602.html
</guid><description>
Tomabo MP4 Downloader Pro is the app designed exclusively for Windows users to help them download videos from the Internet. In addition, it also increase download speeds by up to 500%, or even more. Tomabo MP4 Downloader Pro, interface design, simple, well-organized, beautifully. Here, users can view a list of videos has download with gravatar, URL, quality, duration and size of them. Software allows download video series at the same time, at the same time, support create a list of clips...
</description></item><item><title>Download Batch XLS to PDF Converter 2025.17.1219.2077</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Dec 2025 17:14:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-batch-xls-to-pdf-converter-5077.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-batch-xls-to-pdf-converter-5077.html
</guid><description>
Batch XLS to PDF Converter is a tool to batch convert Excel to PDF, XLS / XLSX to PDF can convert Excel XLS / XLSX to PDF format (portable document) in an easy way. Batch XLS to PDF Converter supports powerful search for lots of files. Batch XLS to PDF Converter supports project and command line. Batch XLS to PDF Converter has user friendly GUI so used very easily. Batch XLS to PDF Converter Drag and Explorer Context supported.
Batch XLS to PDF Converter supports conversion tool...
</description></item><item><title>Download Batch PPT TO PDF Converter 2025.17.1219.3937</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Dec 2025 17:14:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-batch-ppt-to-pdf-converter-5058.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-batch-ppt-to-pdf-converter-5058.html
</guid><description>
Batch PPT TO PDF Converter is a tool to batch convert PowerPoint PPT / PPTX to PDF can convert PowerPoint PPT (X) to PDF format (portable document) in an easy way. Batch PPT TO PDF Converter supports powerful search for a lot of files. A publisher PDF for PowerPoint.
Batch PPT TO PDF Converter supports project and command line. Batch PPT TO PDF Converter has user friendly GUI so used very easily. Batch PPT TO PDF Converter Drag and Explorer Context supported. Batch PPT TO PDF Converter...
</description></item></channel></rss>