<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:48:10 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:48:10 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Privacy Eraser Pro 6.25.0.5456</title><pubDate> Thu, 25 Dec 2025 23:22:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-privacy-eraser-1141.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-privacy-eraser-1141.html
</guid><description>
Privacy Eraser is the cleanup for computer help to clear the tracks, junk files and traces of recent activity of the computer. Privacy Eraser support the popular web browsers like Internet Explorer, Mozilla Firefox, Google Chrome, Safari and Opera. The program can quickly erase the browser cache, cookies, browsing history, website history, website URL entered, form data, auto complete, file index.dat, file swapping, temporary directory and the position in other common.
Privacy Eraser -...
</description></item><item><title>Download 4K Video Downloader Plus 25.4.4</title><pubDate> Thu, 25 Dec 2025 23:21:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-video-downloader-617.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-video-downloader-617.html
</guid><description>
4K Video Downloader Plus is software support downloads video, audio and subtitles from YouTube with high quality up to 4K. Download process video is very simple: just copy the video link from your browser and click Paste Url. Done! If you want that video on your iPad, iPhone or other device, we have protected you.
The feature on 4K Video Downloader Plus
	Download entire playlists and channels from YouTube and save them in MP4, MKV, M4A, MP3, FLV, 3G, create a file .m3u for...
</description></item><item><title>Download Coolutils Total PDF Converter 6.5.0.154</title><pubDate> Thu, 25 Dec 2025 23:21:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-total-pdf-converter-830.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-total-pdf-converter-830.html
</guid><description>
Coolutils Total PDF Converter is software to convert PDF convert PDF files to HTML, DOC (Word), text, Excel, PostScript, CSV or image files. The advantage of Coolutils Total PDF Converter is the fast, easy-to-handle, accurate, does not require Adobe Acrobat, supports many target format and have the option of batch (can convert hundreds of PDF files as well as the single file). Added to this, registered users get command line support to manage the utility with maximum...
</description></item><item><title>Download Soda PDF Desktop Pro 14.0.538.23117</title><pubDate> Thu, 25 Dec 2025 23:20:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-soda-pdf-home-808.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-soda-pdf-home-808.html
</guid><description>
Soda PDF Pro  is intuitive PDF software that helps you to easily process and create PDF files from more than 300 different formats. Soda PDF is built to help you power through any PDF task. Convert to a wide range of file types. Edit the content of your document. Create custom forms. Annotate your files. Send and track contracts for electronic signatures.
Soda PDF Pro: Create PDF file
Features of Soda PDF Pro
	Read your PDFs and digital publications in 3D with unique page-turning...
</description></item><item><title>Download RegRun Reanimator 17.90.2025.1224</title><pubDate> Thu, 25 Dec 2025 23:20:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-regrun-reanimator-1205.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-regrun-reanimator-1205.html
</guid><description>
RegRun Reanimator is a software supports to Remove Trojan / adware / spyware and rootkits, as well as the types of other malicious software. RegRun Reanimator is not just a set of standard tools, but also have a reporting feature in-depth. This can create a detailed report about the current state of your PC, including applications, drivers, codecs, browser settings, extensions, Explorer, network settings, link file the details, Windows services, startup programs, scheduled tasks, running...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sublime Merge 2 Build 2121</title><pubDate> Thu, 25 Dec 2025 23:13:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sublime-merge-3957.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sublime-merge-3957.html
</guid><description>
Sublime Merge is the name of the application software and of course very useful for the programmer. In fact, the software in front of you is a text editor and the code light on the mass, and of course is strong. When using this software, you can view and edit multiple page text and his code at the same time and edit and complete them. User interface with great editing tools will give you experience coding very interesting.
Sublime Merge - source Editor and write the Code
Software...
</description></item><item><title>Download 3DP Chip 25.12.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 25 Dec 2025 23:13:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-3dp-chip-2282.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-3dp-chip-2282.html
</guid><description>
3DP Chip is software commonly used in the update of the version latest driver for your computer. The advantage of this software is completely free, compact and easy to use. 3DP Chip will help the hardware always works in the best state, with the 3DP Chip, you can know the driver has been outdated, then let the software automatically searches for the latest version and installed for your system.
3DP Chip - Download and update driver
With the 3DP Chip you can learn everything about the...
</description></item><item><title>Download CoolUtils PDF Combine 8.1.0.69/5</title><pubDate> Thu, 25 Dec 2025 23:12:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-pdf-combine-14316.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-pdf-combine-14316.html
</guid><description>
Need a utility that can combine multiple PDF files into a single PDF file? PDF Combine can do it easily. Looking for a program that is easy to use and has enough options to meet your needs? PDF Combine is the most efficient and convenient program available on the market.
Combine PDF from CoolUtils easily
	Combine different pages of invoices, bank statements, contracts or e-books
	Allows you to select as many PDF files as you want
	Combine files by folder or common name.
	Preserves the...
</description></item><item><title>Download AB Download Manager 1.8.3</title><pubDate> Thu, 25 Dec 2025 23:06:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ab-download-manager-12399.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ab-download-manager-12399.html
</guid><description>
With this application, you can easily download files from anywhere. Enjoy fast, free downloads with seamless browser extension support. It is built to be a desktop application that allows you to manage and organize your downloads better than before.
AB Download Manager features
	Simple and modern UI: Simple UI and dark mode by default
	Faster download speeds: Download files using multiple connections to increase your download speed by up to 500%
	Download Queue: Create and manage your...
</description></item><item><title>Download Quick CPU 6.1.0.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 25 Dec 2025 23:05:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quick-cpu-5144.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quick-cpu-5144.html
</guid><description>
Quick CPU (Core Parking Manager v3) is an application designed to tweak and monitor the performance settings of the CPU such as Core Parking, Frequency Scaling and Turbo Boost, as well as made other adjustments. Below you will find all information about how it works, how to interpret the data and install the application and how to perform these adjustments.
Features of Quick CPU
	Performance graphs for each core. Show if the core is Active or not adjust the size for the CPU...
</description></item><item><title>Download iFoneTool EasyDown 2.3.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 25 Dec 2025 20:18:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ifonetool-easydown-14405.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ifonetool-easydown-14405.html
</guid><description>
iFoneTool EasyDown is a download software for Windows that allows you to save videos and music from platforms like YouTube, TikTok, Spotify, and many others, with features such as batch downloading and support for high-quality formats. It's compatible with major platforms including YouTube, NicoNico, Apple Music, Spotify, TikTok, and Twitter. It supports batch downloading of playlists, channels, individual songs, albums, podcasts, and more. High quality, lossless downloads, fast saving of...
</description></item><item><title>Download VSave 2.3.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 25 Dec 2025 20:10:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vsave-14404.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vsave-14404.html
</guid><description>
VSave is a video saving and editing app that lets you download videos from cloud storage services, import videos from your camera or library, and convert or edit video formats and attributes. It's compatible with major platforms including YouTube, NicoNico, Apple Music, Spotify, TikTok, Twitter, and other video, audio, and social media websites. It supports downloading playlists, shows, channels, individual songs, and entire albums. Save content permanently in high quality without data...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare PDFelement Pro 12.1.4.3916</title><pubDate> Thu, 25 Dec 2025 16:11:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-pdfelement-pro-105.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-pdfelement-pro-105.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare PDFelement Pro support users to convert PDF to office documents for easier use, modify in every situation. Is one of the software conversion material is rated best today, integrated with many features. We recommend that you should use experience software many useful features this.
Wondershare PDFelement Pro - conversion Fie PDF more features, multi-language
Wondershare PDFelement Pro what?
Convert PDF into Word, Excel, PowerPoint...
• Convert PDF and protected PDF into...
</description></item><item><title>Download Topaz Photo Pro 1.1.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 25 Dec 2025 16:10:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-photo-ai-8105.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-photo-ai-8105.html
</guid><description>
What is Topaz Photo AI?
Topaz Photo AI is a professional software that automatically adjusts for your image quality needs. Simply import images into Topaz Photo AI and it will use specially trained AI models to first detect unique details, clarity, and resolution issues before applying the intelligently adjusts to maximize your image quality.
For users experienced with Topaz Labs image quality applications, it combines the functionality of DeNoise AI, Sharpen AI and Gigapixel AI into...
</description></item><item><title>Download iWatermark Pro 2 v4.0.34</title><pubDate> Thu, 25 Dec 2025 16:09:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iwatermark-pro-1908.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iwatermark-pro-1908.html
</guid><description>
iWatermark Pro is great tool to stamp copyright image, create own mark on the digital image to protect the image copyright. iWatermark Pro works as a digital app independently of the browser other photos, such as Lightroom, Picasa and ACDSee. iWatermark Pro is designed to save time photographers, it support stamped a series of images at a time to save your work.
iWatermark Pro - stamped images copyright
The features of iWatermark Pro
	Stamped copyright the entire images folder at the...
</description></item><item><title>Download ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro 15.25.1223</title><pubDate> Thu, 25 Dec 2025 16:08:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-videotube-downloader-pro-1276.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-videotube-downloader-pro-1276.html
</guid><description>
ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro is the professional version support download videos and playlists from YouTube, videos from Dailymotion, BBC iPlayer, ITV Player, ABC,  FOX,CBS.com Vimeo, Prosieben, Metacafe, Blip.tv CBC.ca many more video sites. After the video is downloaded, you can convert them to the formats compatible with iPad, iPhone, iPod, MPEG-4, H. 264, MP3, AC3.
ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro - Download videos on Youtube
This is one of the software download the most...
</description></item><item><title>Download Marvelous Designer Enterprise 2025.2.143</title><pubDate> Thu, 25 Dec 2025 16:08:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-marvelous-designer-1339.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-marvelous-designer-1339.html
</guid><description>
Marvelous Designer is one of the program best designed to help the 3D design and fashion design. A simulation system revolutionary use of physics. Now, you can create the correct clothes only using Marvelous Designer without help of the other CAD app. Marvelous Designer supports polylines, draw the curved lines connected for free. Any amendments and / or modifications will be displayed immediately on the model clothing 3D in real time.
Marvelous Designer - fashion design
The main...
</description></item><item><title>Download LostMyPassword 1.02</title><pubDate> Thu, 25 Dec 2025 16:07:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lostmypassword-14028.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lostmypassword-14028.html
</guid><description>
LostMyPassword is a tool for Windows that allows you to recover a lost password if it was stored by a software installed on your system. LostMyPassword can extract passwords from popular programs, including web browsers (Chrome, Firefox, Microsoft Edge, Brave, Internet Explorer, Opera, etc.), POP3/IMAP/SMTP passwords stored by email software (Microsoft Outlook, Thunderbird, Windows Mail), Dialup/VPN passwords stored by Windows operating system, remote computer login passwords stored by...
</description></item><item><title>Download 7+ Taskbar Tweaker 5.15.4 / 5.15.3.1 Beta</title><pubDate> Thu, 25 Dec 2025 16:07:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-7-taskbar-tweaker-1863.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-7-taskbar-tweaker-1863.html
</guid><description>
7+ Taskbar Tweaker is a software utility that helps Taskbar on Windows 7 and Windows 8 develop more features, allows users Taskbar more flexible. 7+ Taskbar Tweaker will help the user to completely hide the Start button, watch the hour of the clock displayed on the Taskbar, delete the gaps between the icons. 7+ Taskbar Tweaker allows to automatically hide the Taskbar on Windows to maximize screen space or hide menu Start Menu or Start Screen, turn off the sound on the system or adjust the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Total Uninstall Professional 7.6.2.367</title><pubDate> Thu, 25 Dec 2025 16:06:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-total-uninstall-professional-727.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-total-uninstall-professional-727.html
</guid><description>
Total Uninstall Professional  is an advanced software installation and removal aid that accurately analyzes existing installations. Total Uninstall creates a snapshot of your system before installing a new program. It will then take a snapshot once the installation is complete. It then compares the two snapshots and shows all changes in the graphical tree view, highlighting all registry values ​​and / or files added, changed, or deleted. Total Uninstall saves the changes and, if you...
</description></item><item><title>Download FastKeys Pro 6.05</title><pubDate> Thu, 25 Dec 2025 16:06:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fastkeys-219.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fastkeys-219.html
</guid><description>
FastKeys is a compact tool used to create the shortcut, assign a shortcut key to specify the string stands for the text often use and manage mouse gestures. Users can specify the mouse manipulation to increase the performance of the work or simply replace a string or use an acronym.
FastKeys trigger to allow for expansion of abbreviations for texts used frequently in any application and save time typing. Enter a few letters and automates the task of repeating in a professional manner....
</description></item><item><title>Download Avid Media Composer 25.12 Dongle BackUp</title><pubDate> Thu, 25 Dec 2025 16:05:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avid-media-composer-5432.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avid-media-composer-5432.html
</guid><description>
Avid Media Composer is the industry's most proven video editing software, trusted by professional editors in every segment of filmmaking, television, broadcast and online streaming. Designed for handling large volumes of various file-based media, Media Composer provides accelerated HD and high-resolution workflow, real-time collaboration, and powerful media management, Eliminate time-consuming tasks so you can concentrate on telling a great story.
Media Composer 2020 is packed with a lot...
</description></item><item><title>Download Full Discography 1.8.7</title><pubDate> Thu, 25 Dec 2025 16:04:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-full-discography-7509.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-full-discography-7509.html
</guid><description>
Full Discography is a program to discover all the releases of your favorite artists! Listen to every song your favorite artist ever made! Get to know all Albums &amp;amp; Single click by artist.
Features of Full Discography
	Discover all the releases by your favorite artists!
	Listen to every song your favorite artist ever made!
	Recognize All Albums &amp;amp; Single click by artist.
	Discover all the missing releases from your music collection.
	Get notified when your favorite artist...
</description></item><item><title>Download Gilisoft Total Repair 11.5.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 25 Dec 2025 16:04:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-total-repair-12836.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-total-repair-12836.html
</guid><description>
Total Repair Toolkit is an all-in-one system maintenance tool that integrates smart diagnosis, in-depth repair, and performance optimization. It has a one-click smart repair engine that can automatically resolve over 500 common problems such as system lag, game crashes, and file corruption. Meanwhile, it provides a professional manual repair module to meet advanced requirements.
Gilisoft Total Repair Features
	Application error repair based on a large DLL library
	In-depth diagnosis...
</description></item><item><title>Download Smart File Renamer 1.6.8</title><pubDate> Thu, 25 Dec 2025 16:04:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-smart-file-renamer-7510.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-smart-file-renamer-7510.html
</guid><description>
Smart File Renamer is software to rename multiple files easily! It supports hundreds of renaming scenarios and is loved by happy users aged 14 to 80. Rename 1000 files in less than a second!
Features of Smart File Renamer
	Quickly rename 1000 files in less than a second!
	Rename multiple files in one click!
	Rename photos by country, date, or EXIF ​​tag!
	Rename audio files by music tags easily!
	Rename preselected file categories with one click.
	Support Dark and Light...
</description></item></channel></rss>