<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 15:43:41 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 15:43:41 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Disable Windows Defender 2.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 04 Jan 2026 17:43:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-disable-windows-defender-14217.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-disable-windows-defender-14217.html
</guid><description>
Usually, we need to disable Windows Defender to prevent it from deleting known files due to false positives. Sometimes, it can slow down your computer or interrupt your work. In such cases, you can easily disable it and enable it again later with just one click. We can also disable this feature (Real-time Monitoring) using the Defender Settings panel, but it will be automatically enabled after a period of time. This tool ensures that this feature is 100% disabled. It also disables all...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ant Download Manager Pro 2.16.5 Build 92283</title><pubDate> Sun, 04 Jan 2026 17:39:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ant-download-manager-pro-137.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ant-download-manager-pro-137.html
</guid><description>
Ant Download Manager Pro is software support download has the same features as IDM, even it has many prominent features, more user friendly more and have speed download data incredible. Ant Download Manager is a Internet content downloader quickly with support download at video! Function: fully Integrated with the web browsers most popular: Internet Explorer 8+, Mozilla Firefox 32 +, Google Chrome 31+ and the copies of them (Pale Moon, Opera, Vivaldi, Slimjet, ComodoDragon, etc.). you...
</description></item><item><title>Download CyberLink PowerDirector Ultimate 2026 v24.0.1302.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 04 Jan 2026 17:38:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-powerdirector-ultimate-425.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-powerdirector-ultimate-425.html
</guid><description>
CyberLink PowerDirector Ultimate is software editor, edit video and make movies on the computer from a variety of templates are made available, complete with effects, transitions, animations, and music. CyberLink PowerDirector 17 is a combination of video editing software with advanced video editing features powerful. Cblowing need to add your clips into the time line and click on 'Production'!
The tool design video in CyberLink PowerDirector have the ability to customize helps you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Easy English Platinum 11.0.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 04 Jan 2026 17:38:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easy-english-platinum-10850.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easy-english-platinum-10850.html
</guid><description>
Designed by university language experts, Easy English Platinum is an interactive learning system proven to teach you English quickly and easy. With progressive learning lessons, voice recognition technology, and immersive learning, you'll have everything you need to master English. Build your vocabulary, practice real-world conversations, and perfect your pronunciation.
This program will put you in real-life situations where you interact with native speakers to learn faster. Enter your...
</description></item><item><title>Download reaConverter Pro 8.0.175</title><pubDate> Sun, 04 Jan 2026 17:37:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html
</guid><description>
reaConverter Pro is software image processing feature with batch conversion and image editing periodically becomes simple. eaConverter also provide command line utilities allow you to process images automatically, thus helping you shorten the time for other work.
reaConverter Pro integrated powerful tool of Uber with many great features. It provides advanced solutions to process and adjust images. Management of the conversion process the base image with the latest version of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Telegram for Desktop 6.4.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 04 Jan 2026 17:37:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-telegram-3376.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-telegram-3376.html
</guid><description>
Telegram is an instant messaging service and voice over IP services on the cloud platform. Client application Telegram is available for Android, iOS, Windows Phone, Windows NT, macOS, and Linux. Users can send messages and exchange photos, videos, stickers, audio and files of any kind.
Telegram - Messaging and free phone calls
Telegram seamless sync across all your devices and can be used on desktop, tablet and phone. You can send unlimited amount of messages, photos, videos and files...
</description></item><item><title>Download Allavsoft Video Downloader Converter 3.28.8.9497</title><pubDate> Sun, 04 Jan 2026 17:37:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allavsoft-video-downloader-converter-248.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allavsoft-video-downloader-converter-248.html
</guid><description>
Allavsoft Video Downloader Converter software supports download movies, music videos, playlist, sport videos from video sharing website for free like Facebook, Youtube and over 100 video sharing sites.
Allavsoft is many users favorite thanks to the combined features simultaneous transmission of multiple videos and speed limit download video. Besides, the program also supports pause and resume data transmission, to help you interfere with the process of transmitting download data to...
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 7.6.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 04 Jan 2026 17:36:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-11-7760.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-11-7760.html
</guid><description>
TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 is a program that allows users to discover hidden settings in Windows 11. This application is specially designed for Windows 11, groups many registry settings and distribute them from the easy and secure user interface. With TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 you can move the Windows taskbar to the top and resize the taskbar by editing the registry value. With any application that modifies the registry, we recommend that you have a backup copy...
</description></item><item><title>Download NirLauncher Package 1.30.22</title><pubDate> Sun, 04 Jan 2026 17:36:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nirlauncher-152.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nirlauncher-152.html
</guid><description>
NirLauncher is a package of more than 200 freeware utilities developed by Nirsoft, the NirLauncher application is provided free of charge for easy selection, use by feature classification. . Popular Nirsoft Utilities (many of them listed separately on taiwebs.com) NirLauncher includes network tools, password recovery tools, security cleaners, system utilities, programming tools, command line utilities and more.
NirLauncher's Versatile Utility
With this NirLauncher utility, users can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Top Process Monitor 11.5</title><pubDate> Sun, 04 Jan 2026 17:36:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-top-process-monitor-2753.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-top-process-monitor-2753.html
</guid><description>
Top Process Monitor is a small utility that allows you to view the processes are using most CPU, memory and other important components in your system. It can be easily installed and configured, even by inexperienced users. The interface of the application is based on a small frame that you can move to any location on the screen. So, you can check the current CPU, along with the application and the total stream is included.
Top Process Monitor - View operation, the CPU, computer...
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 7.6.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 04 Jan 2026 17:35:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-10-7759.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-10-7759.html
</guid><description>
TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 is a utility that allows users to discover hidden settings in Windows 10. This application is specially designed for Windows 10, groups many registry settings and provide them from an easy and secure user interface. With TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 you can move the Windows taskbar to the top and resize the taskbar by editing the registry value. With any application that modifies the registry, we recommend that you have a backup copy to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Any Video Downloader Pro 10.1.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 04 Jan 2026 17:35:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-video-downloader-pro-3731.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-video-downloader-pro-3731.html
</guid><description>
Any Video Downloader Pro is software support you can download video HD 720p, 1080p, 2K, 4K and 8K from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion, Vimeo, Metacafe and thousands of video sharing sites, other. It is a tool to speed up multi-threading can speed up your download faster up to 5 times. This helpful program support download at the same time. Any Video Downloader Pro lets you download multiple videos at the same time. Moreover, it allows you to pause and resume downloads if you need more...
</description></item><item><title>Download DriverStore Explorer 0.12.135</title><pubDate> Sun, 04 Jan 2026 17:34:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-driverstore-explorer-2892.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-driverstore-explorer-2892.html
</guid><description>
DriverStore Explorer RAPR is software for dealing with drivers Windows more easily. The supported operations include enumeration, adding driver package (stage), add and install, delete and delete force from the store drivers.
DriverStore Explorer - drivers
The features of the DriverStore Explorer
	Listed / Listed all the packages are held in the store current drivers.
	Export the list as CSV.
	Added package drivers catalog drivers (called staging)
	Install &amp;amp; Add driver package...
</description></item><item><title>Download Picture Window Pro 8.0.542</title><pubDate> Sun, 04 Jan 2026 17:34:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-picture-window-pro-7452.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-picture-window-pro-7452.html
</guid><description>
Picture Window Pro is a powerful image editing tool designed for serious photographers with strict creative and quality standards. Its comprehensive set of photo editing and editing tools let you control and shape every aspect of your images.
Picture Window Pro 8 is a complete rewrite of Picture Window Pro 7. It features non-destructive image editing through a novel interface based on an image tree. It also fully supports large, high-resolution displays and can be used in dual monitor...
</description></item><item><title>Download thilmera7 0b184 Rev.8</title><pubDate> Sun, 04 Jan 2026 17:33:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thilmera7-2918.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thilmera7-2918.html
</guid><description>
thilmera7 is an application capable of performing this task and perform it quite well. This is an app that tracks real-time which you can put anywhere on the screen of his computer application and to forward detailed information about memory, disk, network, CPU, GPU, processes, sound and other aspects miscellaneous.
All the controls and options for the application is provided from the context menu right-click. There you can find the table 'properties' from where you can switch and see all...
</description></item><item><title>Download Snap2HTML 2.51</title><pubDate> Sun, 04 Jan 2026 17:31:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-snap2html-4267.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-snap2html-4267.html
</guid><description>
Snap2HTML is a lightweight utility and simple, can grasp the structure of the folder stored on the local drive of you and save them in HTML format. The HTML file created by this program use advanced techniques to bring the feel of a real software, like Windows Explorer, allowing you to see a tree with the folder can click to access the content of them. A search feature integrated file also available. The HTML files created can be easily shared.
Snap2HTML - folder structure as...
</description></item><item><title>Download FonePaw Data Recovery 3.8</title><pubDate> Sun, 04 Jan 2026 17:30:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fonepaw-data-recovery-1206.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fonepaw-data-recovery-1206.html
</guid><description>
FonePaw Data Recovery allows you to easily and quickly proceed to scan the entire PC to recover different file formats from your hard disk, can work with images, documents, audio, video and other files. It will help even if you have deleted software.
FonePaw Data Recovery - data recovery
FonePaw Data Recovery can fully operate with the corrupted files on the hard drive, regardless of what happened with them and how you or other people delete them, everything can be put back, even when...
</description></item><item><title>Download Easy French Platinum 11.0.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 04 Jan 2026 17:30:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easy-french-platinum-10849.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easy-french-platinum-10849.html
</guid><description>
Easy French Platinum is a proven interactive learning system that can teach you French quickly and easily. With progressive learning lessons, voice recognition technology, and immersive learning, you'll have everything you need to master French. Build your vocabulary, practice real-world conversations, and perfect your pronunciation.
Easy French Platinum will immerse you in real-life situations where you interact with native speakers to learn faster. Enter your specific language goals...
</description></item><item><title>Download App Builder 2026.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 04 Jan 2026 17:29:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-app-builder-241.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-app-builder-241.html
</guid><description>
App Builder is a software application developer to help create and design apps, HTML5, web app, web app PWA on both platforms mobile and desktop. App Builder is professional software supports users to create the program HTML5 without writing code. It is very easy to use, suitable with all users who lack of professional knowledge in the field of programming and application design.
App Builder brings to 22 different themes that users can use to design for your app. You can choose 1 or a...
</description></item><item><title>Download Easy German Platinum 11.0.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 04 Jan 2026 17:29:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easy-german-platinum-10846.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easy-german-platinum-10846.html
</guid><description>
Easy German Platinum is a proven interactive learning system that helps you teach German quickly and easily. With progressive learning lessons, voice recognition technology, and immersive learning, you'll have everything you need to become fluent in German. Build your vocabulary, practice real-world conversations, and perfect your pronunciation.
It puts you in real-life situations where you interact with native speakers to learn faster. Enter your specific language goals to personalize...
</description></item><item><title>Download OneCommander Pro 3.105.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 04 Jan 2026 17:28:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-one-commander-4232.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-one-commander-4232.html
</guid><description>
One Commander is a file manager for Microsoft Windows with function improved user interface and navigation experience, system file and manipulating the files. Utilities use the tree view to sort the folder, subfolders, and files your, make sure that the current location of you always clear. It supports multiple tabs, allowing you to easily switch between them and access the folder you need.
One Commander - a filemanager for Windows
Depending on the format of the files, some files can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Syncovery Premium 11.11.14.144</title><pubDate> Sun, 04 Jan 2026 17:28:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncovery-pro-enterprise-232.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncovery-pro-enterprise-232.html
</guid><description>
Syncovery Pro Enterprise is a great application used to back up data and to synchronize personal computers, servers, laptops, notepads and storage online. The software comes with support for FTP and secure FTP servers, SSH, WebDAV, Amazon S3, http, update the part file, ZIP compression, data encryption, and schedule automatic backups.
Syncovery Pro Enterprise have the ability to freely select files and folders across the whole folder hierarchy in tree view and supports email...
</description></item><item><title>Download Rocrail Build 6461</title><pubDate> Sun, 04 Jan 2026 17:27:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rocrail-3193.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rocrail-3193.html
</guid><description>
Rocrail is a free software to control the training model for the operating system Linux , Apple macOS , Windows and Raspbian / Armbian . Rocrail bear all responsibility in the control of a railway model, and accessories of them. Trains can be controlled manually or fully controlled by software in automatic mode. A mixed operation, i.e. control a number of ships and other vessels at high speed fully automatic is possible.
Rocrail - control layout for the operating system
With Rocrail,...
</description></item><item><title>Download VovSoft OCR Reader 4.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 04 Jan 2026 17:27:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-ocr-reader-7875.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-ocr-reader-7875.html
</guid><description>
VovSoft OCR Reader is an image-based text recognition program that converts images of typed, handwritten or printed text into machine-encoded text. , whether from a scanned document or an image of a document. VovSoft OCR Reader can easily digitize scanned image files and documents on your laptop or desktop computer. This application uses the Tesseract OCR engine, which supports more than 100 languages. It uses a neural network-based OCR (LSTM) engine that focuses on line recognition, but...
</description></item><item><title>Download Database Tour Pro 11.6.0.950</title><pubDate> Sun, 04 Jan 2026 17:26:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-database-tour-pro-5321.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-database-tour-pro-5321.html
</guid><description>
Database Tour Pro application is a comprehensive software that allows you to organize all the database is connected his. It provides support for Borland Database Engine (BDE) and Microsoft ActiveX Data Objects (ADO), SQL scripts, reports, along with conversion and data export, among others.
It contains a browser object for the function, package, triggers, folders, users, roles, profiles, sequences, work, style, Java, exception, link, database, general properties, table, schema, and...
</description></item></channel></rss>