<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 03:30:55 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 03:30:55 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Wondershare UniConverter 17.0.5.439</title><pubDate> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 00:59:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-uniconverter-4808.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-uniconverter-4808.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare UniConverter ( old name is Wondershare Video Converter Ultimate) which allows you to convert the video format. You can cut, splice, move, or add effects, subtitles a easy way. When using software you easily cut, splice, move, as well as add the effects, the subtitles to the video.... Or can switch the clods SD, HD video to any format popular for use with iPod (Classic, Nano and Touch), iPhone, Apple TV, Zune, PSP, Pocket PC...
Wondershare UniConverter helps convert formats...
</description></item><item><title>Download StartAllBack 3.9.16.5330</title><pubDate> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 00:58:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-startallback-6857.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-startallback-6857.html
</guid><description>
With the official release of Windows 11, chances are that most of you want to try it out. As the name suggests, StartAllBack is a small, lightweight tool that can help you enjoy the power of the new operating system while keeping the look and feel, especially because main work area, desktop of Windows 7, Windows 10 as taskbars and start menu styles.
StartAllBack is specially designed for Windows 11 and will not work on any older operating systems. If you want to get the start menu back...
</description></item><item><title>Download Office Timeline Plus 12.05.00.00 Expert / Pro / Pro+ Edition</title><pubDate> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 00:58:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-timeline-2106.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-timeline-2106.html
</guid><description>
Office Timeline is an add-on very useful and powerful software for Microsoft PowerPoint. With add-ons, you can create PowerPoint documents look more beautiful. With add-ons, you can add the time Line on the project by yourself. Application time for the composition and different segments of the document, your PowerPoint will not only increase the beauty for your work, but also for customers and your manager. The people who created this product is also believe that add-ons this is the only...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare Recoverit 14.0.4.4</title><pubDate> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 00:57:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-recoverits-374.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-recoverits-374.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare Recoverit is a data recovery software that is easily lost at a rapid rate and is used by many people. You will do what happens if one day your data is suddenly lost due to the virus or deleted it, .. Wondershare Recoverit will provide you with an environment to protect important data.
Wondershare Recoverit has all the scanning processes that are divided into multiple types, from the typical recovery of the deleted files that are deleted to the recovery of missing files due...
</description></item><item><title>Download WYSIWYG Web Builder 20.3.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 00:57:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wysiwyg-web-builder-177.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wysiwyg-web-builder-177.html
</guid><description>
WYSIWYG Web Builder : The construction of the website from scratch using HTML code isn't a pleasant process, even when you know what you are doing. The website can be built using WYSIWYG Web Builder with using the element similar to the package published on the desktop: text and images placed in frames and tables on the page, so very little surprised when most of the efforts to make the web become a experience user-friendly than. the controls do you use to build your pages.
WYSIWYG Web...
</description></item><item><title>Download Drive SnapShot 1.50.0.1749</title><pubDate> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 00:51:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-drive-snapshot-701.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-drive-snapshot-701.html
</guid><description>
Drive SnapShot is a backup software, Restore disk, including operating system, installed programs, your data and all security attributes - while windows is running and you continue to work. With Drive SnapShot you backup partition or hard drive and it can also create disk image of your system. If a disaster occurs (a virus, trojan or the fixed hard disk), the recover complete and accurate your system will be able to accomplish after only a few minutes. The image file can be mounted as...
</description></item><item><title>Download Realtek Ethernet Controller All-In-One Drivers 11.27.1028.2025</title><pubDate> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 00:43:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-realtek-ethernet-controller-all-in-one-drivers-6485.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-realtek-ethernet-controller-all-in-one-drivers-6485.html
</guid><description>
Realtek Ethernet All-In-One Controller Driver is the software driver for the Realtek Ethernet cards. It is a program used to communicate from the Windows PC OS to the device. This software is required in most cases for the hardware device to function properly. In most cases, drivers come with Windows or can be found by going to Windows Update in Control Panel and checking for updates as well as downloaded from the Realtek support website.
</description></item><item><title>Download Blumentals WeBuilder 2025 v18.4.0.272</title><pubDate> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 00:42:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blumentals-webuilder-1572.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blumentals-webuilder-1572.html
</guid><description>
Blumentals WeBuilder is a powerful app to edit the HTML code, CSS, JavaScript, PHP and ASP in an environment simple and user friendly. WeBuilder is a versatile application for web developers to edit code.
The application Blumentals WeBuilder this supports the programming languages HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, Ruby, Python, ASP, SSI and Perl. The integrated tool of this software allows you to verify, re-use and redirect your code and expand them according to how efficient and complex....
</description></item><item><title>Download Calibre 8.14.0 + Portable</title><pubDate> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 00:42:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-calibre-1669.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-calibre-1669.html
</guid><description>
Calibre  is an eBook library management application that allows you to manage your eBook collection, convert eBooks between different formats, Sync with popular e-reading devices and read your e-books with included viewer. You can sort books by author, title, date and other details, download meta information and book covers, add personalized tags and comments, and view your images in the cover display.
Collection of essential tools for adding metadata editing books or managing your...
</description></item><item><title>Download Pazu StreamGet All-In-One Video Downloader 2.8.6</title><pubDate> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 00:41:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pazu-streamget-all-in-one-video-downloader-12037.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pazu-streamget-all-in-one-video-downloader-12037.html
</guid><description>
StreamGet All-In-One Video Downloader is the ultimate downloading solution for you. It supports downloading any movies and shows from the most popular streaming sites including Netflix, Prime Video, Disney Plus, Max, Hulu, and Apple TV Plus. The downloader is continuously updated to support more platforms in the future.
Download movies and shows from various streaming platforms to MP4/MKV on your Windows device and enjoy them anywhere you want.
Features of Pazu StreamGet All-In-One...
</description></item><item><title>Download Blumentals Rapid CSS 2025 v18.4.0.272</title><pubDate> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 00:41:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blumentals-rapid-css-2995.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blumentals-rapid-css-2995.html
</guid><description>
Blumentals Rapid CSS is an application that will allow you to write CSS code to create, design or edit web sites modern. Tool allows you to edit the code manually, or use the edit style sheet automatically. The program provides many useful features, including the check CSS, the code-checking, auto-completion and preview many browser. This utility is designed to ease your work, save time and increase your productivity.
Blumentals Rapid CSS - Write, edit CSS
Rapid CSS is a lightweight...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDFgear 2.1.13</title><pubDate> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 00:40:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdfgear-9049.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdfgear-9049.html
</guid><description>
PDFgear is a PDF reader and editor that combines PDF editing functionality with an AI (artificial intelligence) assistant powered by ChatGPT. The user-friendly product PDFgear offers options that you cannot find in Adobe Acrobat. It's great that you can change the color of your comments with simple clicks.
PDFgear is a full-featured PDF editor that basically helps me do everything I need: edit, convert, form, signature, etc. The interface is intuitive and familiar, and all the features...
</description></item><item><title>Download PerfectTablePlan Professional 7.1.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 00:40:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfecttableplan-2563.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfecttableplan-2563.html
</guid><description>
PerfectTablePlan is a part of interesting to help you easily create a database of guest details. When you start planning, you must make sure that the first thing you know is the number and status of guests. The software allows you to manage carefully the details so nobody is confused and everyone's happy. You can only import a CSV file and vCard if you already have contacts on your computer. If this is not the case, the edit integration allows you to add the individual, couple, family or...
</description></item><item><title>Download Blumentals Rapid PHP 2025 v18.4.0.272</title><pubDate> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 00:39:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blumentals-rapid-php-2996.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blumentals-rapid-php-2996.html
</guid><description>
Blumentals Rapid PHP is an editor PHP powerful and fast mixing function of the Environment integrated development PHP complete along with the speed of the Notepad. This is a comprehensive software that will support you coding CSS, HTML, PHP, JavaScript and other programming languages. Rapid PHP provides a set of advanced tools to validate, reuse, debugging, navigate and format your code. This software allows you to save valuable time and increase productivity by writing code in a way...
</description></item><item><title>Download HTMLPad 2025 v18.4.0.272</title><pubDate> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 00:39:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-htmlpad-2997.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-htmlpad-2997.html
</guid><description>
HTMLPad is a HTML editor, JavaScript, and CSS smart, be so many experts and learners in over 50 countries trust. Full of features and comprehensive options, HTMLPad allows you to make, edit, re-use, verify, navigate and use the HTML code, CSS and JavaScript faster and simpler than ever. HTMLPad include CSS studio and editor JavaScript strong bring you the best value.
HTMLPad - editor, HTML, CSS, JavaScript
Features of HTMLPad
	Quick and lightweight loads much faster than any other...
</description></item><item><title>Download Brave Browser 1.84.135</title><pubDate> Sat, 08 Nov 2025 00:38:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-brave-browser-2874.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-brave-browser-2874.html
</guid><description>
Brave Browser is a browser based on Chromium, the basic principle is that operation fast and privacy of users. The program can block pop-up windows and other ads, plus it blocked the mechanism for monitoring the online activities of your. Therefore, you can purchase and safely browse the website you are interested in without having to worry about the fact that your activity will be monitored and then you will be shown the necessary advertising or service provider of parties...
</description></item><item><title>Download AnkhTech Windows 11 Tiny 25H2 Build 26200.6584</title><pubDate> Fri, 07 Nov 2025 21:54:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ankhtech-windows-11-tiny-14279.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ankhtech-windows-11-tiny-14279.html
</guid><description>
Introducing Windows 11 Tiny 25H2 Modified ISO — a versatile, multi-purpose bootable media designed for low-end and legacy hardware. Completely bloatware-free, delivering maximum performance, speed, and stability.
Multi-boot (WinPE)
	A powerful boot environment equipped with professional tools.
	The taskbar appears when you move the mouse pointer to the bottom of the screen.
	Backup and restore, check hardware, manage drives, and process files before installing Windows.
Startup...
</description></item><item><title>Download AnkhTech Windows 10 Tiny 22H2 Build 19045.6456</title><pubDate> Fri, 07 Nov 2025 21:49:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ankhtech-windows-10-tiny-14278.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ankhtech-windows-10-tiny-14278.html
</guid><description>
Introducing Windows 10 Tiny 22H2 Modified ISO — a multi-boot, multi-purpose image designed for low-end and legacy hardware. Completely free of bloatware, delivering top performance, speed and stability.
Multi-Function Boot (WinPE)
	Powerful boot environment with professional tools.
	Taskbar appears when moving the mouse pointer to the bottom of the screen.
	Backup and restore, hardware diagnostics, disk management and file processing before installing Windows.
Programs Boot...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ant Download Manager Pro 2.16.2 Build 91828</title><pubDate> Fri, 07 Nov 2025 18:31:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ant-download-manager-pro-137.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ant-download-manager-pro-137.html
</guid><description>
Ant Download Manager Pro is software support download has the same features as IDM, even it has many prominent features, more user friendly more and have speed download data incredible. Ant Download Manager is a Internet content downloader quickly with support download at video! Function: fully Integrated with the web browsers most popular: Internet Explorer 8+, Mozilla Firefox 32 +, Google Chrome 31+ and the copies of them (Pale Moon, Opera, Vivaldi, Slimjet, ComodoDragon, etc.). you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Any Video Downloader Pro 9.7.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 07 Nov 2025 18:31:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-video-downloader-pro-3731.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-video-downloader-pro-3731.html
</guid><description>
Any Video Downloader Pro is software support you can download video HD 720p, 1080p, 2K, 4K and 8K from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion, Vimeo, Metacafe and thousands of video sharing sites, other. It is a tool to speed up multi-threading can speed up your download faster up to 5 times. This helpful program support download at the same time. Any Video Downloader Pro lets you download multiple videos at the same time. Moreover, it allows you to pause and resume downloads if you need more...
</description></item><item><title>Download Coolutils Total PDF Converter 6.5.0.153</title><pubDate> Fri, 07 Nov 2025 18:30:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-total-pdf-converter-830.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-total-pdf-converter-830.html
</guid><description>
Coolutils Total PDF Converter is software to convert PDF convert PDF files to HTML, DOC (Word), text, Excel, PostScript, CSV or image files. The advantage of Coolutils Total PDF Converter is the fast, easy-to-handle, accurate, does not require Adobe Acrobat, supports many target format and have the option of batch (can convert hundreds of PDF files as well as the single file). Added to this, registered users get command line support to manage the utility with maximum...
</description></item><item><title>Download Luminar Neo 1.25.0 (15875)</title><pubDate> Fri, 07 Nov 2025 18:30:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-luminar-neoo-7194.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-luminar-neoo-7194.html
</guid><description>
Luminar Neo is an innovative image editor powered by futuristic AI technologies that simplifies complex editing workflows and allows creators to turn their boldest ideas into reality. Luminar Neo calculates image depth and generates 3D maps, allowing you to naturally scatter light in 3D across a 2D image. This opens the door to unleash your creativity to bring your artistic vision to life.
MaskAI automates the masking process by identifying objects in the image and creating the correct...
</description></item><item><title>Download Musify 5.0.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 07 Nov 2025 18:29:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musify-4422.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musify-4422.html
</guid><description>
Musify is the convert YouTube Music best can download music from more than 1000 website share music to listen to offline without reducing sound quality. Such as: YouTube, Spotify, SoundCloud, Facebook, Instragram, and more. Easily convert music files mp3 to iPhone, iPad, iPod, Samsung and iOS devices and other Android. High speed and high quality. Musify is a YouTube converter is very efficient and fast, support format converting YouTube to MP3. You can batch convert mp3 files at the same...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ahnenblatt 4.37.0.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 07 Nov 2025 18:29:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ahnenblatt-3844.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ahnenblatt-3844.html
</guid><description>
Ahnenblatt is a genealogy software full-featured, easy to use suitable for beginners and even pedigree has the experience to organize genealogy research by you. Use plausibility checks to find out the inaccuracies in your family and create the chart impressive with just a few mouse clicks.
Ahnenblatt - Create family tree,
Recently, there has been strong increase of the general interest of the public for genealogical tree. Users who desire to track their heritage have many tools at...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cutting Optimization Pro 5.18.16.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 07 Nov 2025 18:28:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cutting-optimization-pro-6573.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cutting-optimization-pro-6573.html
</guid><description>
Cutting Optimization Pro is a cutting software used to obtain the optimal cut layout for one-dimensional (1D) and two-dimensional (2D) pieces. The software also allows you to define and process complex products, such as desks, tables, cabinets, cabinets, bookshelves... Cutting Optimization Pro can be used to cut rectangular panels made of glass, wood, metal, plastic or any other material used in industrial applications.
Features of Cutting Optimization Pro
	Optimize 1D and 2D in the...
</description></item></channel></rss>