<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 15:34:34 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 15:34:34 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download PortScan &amp;amp; Stuff 2.04</title><pubDate> Sat, 25 Oct 2025 18:33:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-portscan-stuff-2430.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-portscan-stuff-2430.html
</guid><description>
PortScan &amp;amp; Stuff is a small utility does not require installation, will help you to easily find all active devices on your network. After the scanning process gateway is started, the utility will display all the open ports for you. In addition, you can get a lot of other useful information. For example: host name, MAC address, FTP, SMTP and other services. PortScan can search the device is connected, can ping your personal computer.
PortScan &amp;amp; Stuff - Scan devices are using the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Photo Supreme 2025.3.3.8123</title><pubDate> Sat, 25 Oct 2025 18:33:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photo-supreme-430.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photo-supreme-430.html
</guid><description>
Photo Supreme is a software product management professional pictures of idimager. With Photo Supreme you can arrange, manage back stock photo archive of yourself and share them with you here and relatives easily via Email or Facebook. Photo Supreme provides users method to sort images effective, logical, as well as edit and share your photos with friends and relatives in the family. Especially the Photo Supreme allows to work with multiple image formats and support mounting support,...
</description></item><item><title>Download n-Track Studio Suite 10.2.2.10284</title><pubDate> Sat, 25 Oct 2025 18:33:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-n-track-studio-2991.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-n-track-studio-2991.html
</guid><description>
n-Track Studio is a recording software allows you record and create MIDI music and sounds top quality. The software allows you to add effects, VST3, DirectX, AU (Mac), VST and ReWire different on each track or channel. This program also allows you to automatically fade out, fade in and fade out or increase the volume of the music to indicate the voice of the singer.
n-Track Studio can record and playback the number of audio, MIDI and sound unlimited. In addition, you can handle the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Advanced CSV Converter 7.83</title><pubDate> Sat, 25 Oct 2025 18:32:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-csv-converter-4508.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-csv-converter-4508.html
</guid><description>
Advanced CSV Converter is a conversion tool CSV to DBF, Excel (XLS, XLSX), TXT, HTML, PRG, XML, SQL, RTF. To convert a file, the program provides an interface controlled by the wizard, guides you step by step conversion. Use the wizard, you select file input, select the format and destination folder. If necessary, you can set the filter switch according to the example and select columns you want to exclude from the process. When the conversion process is started, the program will extract...
</description></item><item><title>Download Let It Be Light 2.0.8</title><pubDate> Sat, 25 Oct 2025 18:32:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-let-it-be-light-13761.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-let-it-be-light-13761.html
</guid><description>
Let It Be Light – Illuminate the Invisible, Unleash Infinite Content! Tired of dark, underexposed footage that could be your next viral hit? Say hello to Let It Be Light – revolutionary AI image and video processing software that turns dull clips into beautiful, well-lit masterpieces!
Why Let It Be Light?
	Unlock Hidden Content – ​​Turn dark, grainy, or underexposed footage from film, old archives, or social media into crisp, bright, and useful content. No more discarding...
</description></item><item><title>Download ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro 15.25.1024</title><pubDate> Sat, 25 Oct 2025 18:31:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-videotube-downloader-pro-1276.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-videotube-downloader-pro-1276.html
</guid><description>
ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro is the professional version support download videos and playlists from YouTube, videos from Dailymotion, BBC iPlayer, ITV Player, ABC,  FOX,CBS.com Vimeo, Prosieben, Metacafe, Blip.tv CBC.ca many more video sites. After the video is downloaded, you can convert them to the formats compatible with iPad, iPhone, iPod, MPEG-4, H. 264, MP3, AC3.
ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro - Download videos on Youtube
This is one of the software download the most...
</description></item><item><title>Download Chaos Envision 1.3.0.582415</title><pubDate> Sat, 25 Oct 2025 18:31:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chaos-envision-14167.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chaos-envision-14167.html
</guid><description>
Chaos Envision is a standalone 3D visualization software designed for realistic real-time rendering combined with fast animation capabilities. The software is primarily aimed at architects, visualization professionals, and designers, providing a tool for creating professional, immersive presentations with animations, realistic crowds, and object manipulation.
Envision supports very large and complex scenes without compromising performance and integrates seamlessly with other Chaos tools...
</description></item><item><title>Download Atlantis Word Processor 5.0.0.7</title><pubDate> Sat, 25 Oct 2025 18:30:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-atlantis-word-processor-585.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-atlantis-word-processor-585.html
</guid><description>
Atlantis Word Processor is a word processor app with features format, standard text, autocorrect, and spell check.  Atlantis is a word processor in accordance with most of the tasks handled daily text. The interface is very easy to use and offers the toolbars, hotkeys and sound effects thanh can customize (can turn off). It includes a clip library for quick access to the text or images used regular preview, font format and many other features aimed at improving the process of your...
</description></item><item><title>Download R-Drive Image BootCD 7.3 Build 7312</title><pubDate> Sat, 25 Oct 2025 18:30:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-drive-image-bootcd-4878.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-drive-image-bootcd-4878.html
</guid><description>
R-Drive Image BootCD is a powerful utility provides create a file disk image for backup purposes, or copy. File disk image contains the exact copy each and every byte of hard drive, partition or logical disk and can be created with various levels compression without stopping Windows os and therefore without interrupting your work. The image file this drive can then be stored in many places, including various removable media as different as a CD-R (W) / DVD, Iomega Zip or Jazz,...
</description></item><item><title>Download ExifTool 13.40</title><pubDate> Sat, 25 Oct 2025 18:29:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-exiftool-1685.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-exiftool-1685.html
</guid><description>
ExifTool is a library of Perl platform-independent plus a command line application for reading, writing, and editing meta information in various file types. ExifTool supports many metadata formats including EXIF , GPS , IPTC , XMP , JFIF , GeoTIFF , ICC Profile , Photoshop IRB , FlashPix , AFCP and ID3 , as well as notes of the manufacturer of many digital cameras by Canon , Casio , DJI , FLIR , FujiFilm , GE , GoPro , HP , JVC / Victor , Kodak , Leaf , Minolta / Konica-Minolta , Motorola...
</description></item><item><title>Download Danil Pristupov Fork 2.13</title><pubDate> Sat, 25 Oct 2025 18:29:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fork-6879.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fork-6879.html
</guid><description>
Fork is a great Git client app that allows you to keep tabs on every file line so you can know who is the last person to make changes. The simple and intuitive design of this app helps the management of all of your warehouses much easier. The Fork interface is extremely friendly to users. There is a long list of repositories, branches, origins, tags and archives on the left side of the screen.
With Fork, you can also search and open any of the repositories quickly, from the top of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Vovsoft QR Code and Barcode Reader 1.4</title><pubDate> Sat, 25 Oct 2025 18:28:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-qr-code-and-barcode-reader-9714.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-qr-code-and-barcode-reader-9714.html
</guid><description>
Vovsoft QR Code and Barcode Reader is a user-friendly software designed specifically for the Windows operating system. This application allows users to easily scan and decode different types of barcodes and QR codes from a file or webcam.
The software's intelligent scanning technology automatically detects the type of code. Whether you need to decode product information or access website links, this tool is the software for Windows users looking for a reliable solution to scan and read...
</description></item><item><title>Download Synapse Audio DUNE 3 3.6.5</title><pubDate> Sat, 25 Oct 2025 18:27:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-synapse-audio-dune-1030.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-synapse-audio-dune-1030.html
</guid><description>
Synapse Audio DUNE is the new technology brought the concept of unison fame to new heights. Unison is a feature classic synthesizer developed at the same time many voice when playing a note, usually up to 8. The voice that can be separated and spread in the stereo field. The new thing about DUNE is the ability to do anything with the voice, not that most, or even the phrase the voice.
Synapse Audio DUNE 3
The filter is modified in Dune 3 now has filters multi-dual mode plus effects...
</description></item><item><title>Download Xreveal 2.8.6</title><pubDate> Sat, 25 Oct 2025 18:27:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xreveal-7252.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xreveal-7252.html
</guid><description>
Xreveal is an application similar to AnyDVD. This is an interactive research and purpose project. Xreveal does NOT contain any decryption key, it is based solely on the official public AACS specification. You need the decryption key or key database to make it work.
Features of Xreveal
	Remove Blu-ray AACS 1.0 protection
	Remove Blu-ray AACS 2.0 (UHD) protection
	Remove BD+ protection
	Remove BDAV Protection
	Remove DVD CSS protection
	Remove CPRM Protection
	Remove CPPM...
</description></item><item><title>Download Omidsoft System Information 18.35</title><pubDate> Sat, 25 Oct 2025 18:26:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-omidsoft-system-information-12255.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-omidsoft-system-information-12255.html
</guid><description>
System Information is a general Windows utility to display many useful information about Windows, Network and hardware - CPU information, PCI information, PCMCIA information, USB information, SMBus information, SPD information , ACPI method, machine information, hardware sensors, networked computer, operating system information, etc.
System Information is a simple yet highly effective tool designed for individuals who want to gain comprehensive insight into their computer systems. While...
</description></item><item><title>Download WPS Office - PDF, Word, Excel, PPT 18.21.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 25 Oct 2025 17:02:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wps-office-pdf-word-excel-ppt-8244.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wps-office-pdf-word-excel-ppt-8244.html
</guid><description>
WPS Office is a mobile office suite app that allows users to view, edit and create documents, spreadsheets, and presentations on their Android device. The app is available for download from the Google Play Store and is compatible with a wide range of file formats, including Microsoft Office documents.
WPS Office - Free Office suite for Word, PDF, Excel, is an all-in-one office suite that integrates Word, PDF, Excel, PowerPoint, Forms, Cloud Storage, Online Editing, Template library and...
</description></item><item><title>Download CCleaner – Phone Cleaner 25.21.0 build 800011284</title><pubDate> Sat, 25 Oct 2025 17:02:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ccleaner-pro-for-android-3428.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ccleaner-pro-for-android-3428.html
</guid><description>
CCleaner is a system cleaning and optimization tool for Android devices. CCleaner for Android allows users to delete unnecessary files, such as temporary files and caches, as well as identify and uninstall applications that are taking up too much space on the device. It also includes a task kill to close running applications and free up memory. This can help free up storage space and improve device performance. In addition, CCleaner for Android also has a security feature that allows you...
</description></item><item><title>Download ProShot 8.32 build 527</title><pubDate> Sat, 25 Oct 2025 17:01:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-proshot-8195.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-proshot-8195.html
</guid><description>
ProShot is a camera app for Android devices that offers advanced manual controls for photography enthusiasts. It allows users to manually adjust settings such as shutter speed, ISO, white balance, and focus. It also offers a level of integration, a powerful time-lapse mode, and many other features for advanced photography. It's designed for advanced users who want more control over their photos than the default camera app offers.
Camera features of ProShot
	Auto, Program, Manual and...
</description></item><item><title>Download PhotoDirector: AI Photo Editor 20.6.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 25 Oct 2025 17:01:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-photodirector-photo-editor-8144.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-photodirector-photo-editor-8144.html
</guid><description>
PhotoDirector is a photo editing app for Android devices that allows you to edit and enhance your photos with a variety of tools and effects. With PhotoDirector, you can adjust your photo's color and lighting, remove blemishes and other imperfections, and apply filters to give your photos a unique look. You can also use PhotoDirector to create photo collages and slideshows, add text and stickers to photos, and share your edited photos on social networks or through other sharing...
</description></item><item><title>Download All PDF Editor &amp;amp; Reader | Xodo 10.8.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 25 Oct 2025 17:01:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-xodo-pdf-reader-editor-8451.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-xodo-pdf-reader-editor-8451.html
</guid><description>
Xodo PDF Reader &amp;amp; Editor is a mobile application for reading and editing PDF documents on Android and iOS devices. The app allows users to view, annotate, and edit PDF files using a variety of tools, including highlighting, underlining, and adding notes. With Xodo, you can read, annotate, sign, and share PDFs and fill out PDF forms, all while syncing with Google Drive, Dropbox, and OneDrive.
Xodo PDF Reader &amp;amp; Editor Features
	PDF Viewer: Application that allows users to view...
</description></item><item><title>Download File Manager 3.6.4</title><pubDate> Sat, 25 Oct 2025 17:00:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-file-manager-8886.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-file-manager-8886.html
</guid><description>
File Manager+ is an easy and powerful file browser for Android devices. It's free, fast, and full-featured. Because of its simple user interface, it is extremely easy to use. With File Manager+, you can easily manage files and folders on your devices, NAS (Network Attached Storage), and cloud storage. What's more, you can quickly see how many files and apps you have on your device right after opening File Manager+.
It supports all file management actions (opening, searching, navigating...
</description></item><item><title>Download PowerDirector - Video Editor 15.8.0 build 2510201</title><pubDate> Sat, 25 Oct 2025 17:00:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-powerdirector-video-editor-8123.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-powerdirector-video-editor-8123.html
</guid><description>
PowerDirector APK - Video Editor (Unlocked Version) is video editing software developed by CyberLink. It is available for Windows and Android devices. If you are looking for the Android version of PowerDirector, you can download the APK (Android Package Kit) file from the Google Play Store or from taiwebs.com.
Features of PowerDirector APK - Unlocked Version:
	Easy-to-use interface: PowerDirector has a user-friendly interface that makes it easy to edit and create videos, even if...
</description></item><item><title>Download Silent Camera [High Quality] 8.16.4</title><pubDate> Sat, 25 Oct 2025 17:00:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-silent-camera-10536.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-silent-camera-10536.html
</guid><description>
Introducing the best silent camera! Without the shutter sound, photos can be taken in complete silence! It also ranks number 1 among many silent cameras thanks to its high image quality! Take high-quality photos with the silent camera! You won't disturb anyone around you because the shutter sound can't be heard. You can take high-quality photos of any situation, such as your baby's cute sleeping face, your pet's natural behaviors, and words written on a blackboard!
Silent Camera...
</description></item><item><title>Download OsmAnd+ — Maps &amp;amp; GPS Offline 5.2.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 25 Oct 2025 17:00:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-osmand-maps-gps-offline-8245.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-osmand-maps-gps-offline-8245.html
</guid><description>
OsmAnd+ (OSM Automatic Navigation Directions) is a mapping and navigation application with access to free, global, and high-quality OpenStreetMap (OSM) data. Enjoy voice and optical navigation, view POIs (points of interest), create and manage GPX routes, use contour visualization and elevation information, choose between driving modes, cyclists, pedestrians, OSM editing, etc.
This is a mobile navigation app that uses OpenStreetMap (OSM) data to provide users with detailed maps and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Rosetta Stone: Learn, Practice 8.34.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 25 Oct 2025 16:59:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-rosetta-stone-learn-practice-11241.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-rosetta-stone-learn-practice-11241.html
</guid><description>
Interactive and contextual lessons combined with Extended Learning features are truly at your fingertips–anytime, anywhere, on any device; online or offline and completely ad-free. Learn to speak Spanish, French, German, Italian, English, Japanese, Korean, Chinese, Arabic, Portuguese, Russian, Dutch, Filipino, Greek , Hebrew, Hindi, Irish, Persian, Polish, Swedish, Turkish, Vietnamese and more!
Rosetta Stone helps you speak confidently: With many lessons and features focused on...
</description></item></channel></rss>