<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 14:19:28 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 14:19:28 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Google Earth Pro 7.3.7.1094</title><pubDate> Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:49:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-earth-pro-1118.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-earth-pro-1118.html
</guid><description>
Google Earth Pro is the upgraded version of Google Earth helps track earth map and share the information with others. Google has released the new version of the software package called Google Earth. The application is designed to operate with the same service, which allows you to view satellite images of planet earth in 3D mode using OpenGL technology. There is a search function by address, by subject. The seventh version has a simple interface as well as the ability to display a number of...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDF-XChange Editor Plus 10.8.3.408</title><pubDate> Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:48:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-xchange-editor-plus-645.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-xchange-editor-plus-645.html
</guid><description>
PDF-XChange Editor Plus is the editor, PDF viewer, compact, fast with many features, add-ons, professional. When using the PDF-XChange Editor Plus, easy for users to create, view, edit, annotate, OCR and digital signing PDF files, plus much more.
PDF-XChange Editor is a PDF editing full-featured. With the help of it, you can edit, fix, add, or delete text easily. Graphics can also be moved, resized or removed.
Features PDF-XChange Editor Plus
Edit documents
	Use a variety of editing...
</description></item><item><title>Download EmEditor Pro 26.0.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:47:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-emeditor-pro-69.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-emeditor-pro-69.html
</guid><description>
EmEditor Pro - the professional version of editor text powerful for programmers, web developers and ordinary users with illumination of syntax and Unicode support. The features of the editor such as search and replace in files using regular expressions, automatic code detect, bookmark link and address email, block selection mode, configure the button bar, menu, font and elements color. With each language you can set separate configuration.
EmEditor Pro - text Editor professional
The...
</description></item><item><title>Download Scooter Beyond Compare 5.2.0.31950</title><pubDate> Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:46:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-scooter-beyond-compare-2649.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-scooter-beyond-compare-2649.html
</guid><description>
Scooter Beyond Compare is a powerful tool to compare quickly and easily the files and folders. This program provides you with a full report on work done so you can compare the complete data on the file, folder, folder with speed and file size, very fast and incredible, time changes on the file as well as the compared bytes Do byte this information. With the strong command of this program, you can merge the changes, synchronize files, create a report to record.
Scooter Beyond Compare -...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDF-XChange Pro 10.8.3.408</title><pubDate> Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:45:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-xchange-editor-pro-3422.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-xchange-editor-pro-3422.html
</guid><description>
PDF-XChange Editor Pro is an application to manipulate and create PDF versatile, offering a wide range of useful features and powerful will help you to easily work with PDF files. This application is very flexible and allows you to easily create and modify PDF files. PDF-XChange Editor Pro provides a powerful set of tools and flexibility to work with PDF files, such as editor PDF-XChange new, utilities series, OFFice2PDF and the Addin tool Bar allows you to easily convert multiple file...
</description></item><item><title>Download PIDKey Lite 1.64.4 b54</title><pubDate> Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:44:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pidkey-lite-2693.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pidkey-lite-2693.html
</guid><description>
PIDKey Lite is a program intended to show the renovation and preservation in the database of the product information to check "validity" of the key Microsoft from the famous program we or is Ratiborus and VAMT. Program PIDKey LiteIt is the successor of the PIDKey. and I got out of it the idea the best program (allows you To add new keyboard with two methods additional mode key).
The program has a number of configuration integration, but you can also create custom profiles by themselves....
</description></item><item><title>Download reaConverter Pro 8.0.200</title><pubDate> Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:43:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html
</guid><description>
reaConverter Pro is software image processing feature with batch conversion and image editing periodically becomes simple. eaConverter also provide command line utilities allow you to process images automatically, thus helping you shorten the time for other work.
reaConverter Pro integrated powerful tool of Uber with many great features. It provides advanced solutions to process and adjust images. Management of the conversion process the base image with the latest version of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Google Chrome 145.0.7632.117</title><pubDate> Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:43:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-chrome-1012.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-chrome-1012.html
</guid><description>
Google Chrome web browser is the most used today. Support surf the web, listen to music, watch movies, play web game effective no jerky lag with the internet connection stable. When you are surfing the web or performing an important task, whether it is operation big or small, work or entertainment, then Chrome has the smart features and the speed you need to make, create and explore on the net.
The latest version of Google Chrome is the third 114. But we are providing for users Google...
</description></item><item><title>Download DisplayFusion Pro 12.0.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:41:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-displayfusion-pro-1576.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-displayfusion-pro-1576.html
</guid><description>
DisplayFusion Pro is software that support open computer dual screen with good performance and smooth operation the most. With DisplayFusion Pro, you can add a taskbar to every monitor acts and looks just like the Windows taskbar. Or take advantage of background image support multi-screen, advanced Integrated Flickr to search for images and the hot key manager window can be fully customized. Here are just a few of the many things that DisplayFusion can do.
DisplayFusion Pro - open...
</description></item><item><title>Download DesktopPic 2.0.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:41:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktoppic-7444.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktoppic-7444.html
</guid><description>
DesktopPic allows you to display or watermark images on your Windows desktop wallpaper. Display one or more pictures in a resizable, movable window with no borders or captions, so all you see is the photo. This will give the illusion of the image being part of your wallpaper, but it's really just another window. Any icons on the desktop in the same area as the image will be masked. Bitmap image formats, such as PNG (recommended), JPG, BMP and animated GIF are supported.
Features of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Trellix Stinger (McAfee Stinger) 13.0.0.615</title><pubDate> Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:39:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mcafee-stinger-202.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mcafee-stinger-202.html
</guid><description>
McAfee Stinger is a free utility that functions to scan, check and remove the hazards and obstacles as virus or malware for Windows, whether they are hiding deep into the system.
In addition, due to the ability to search for the correct folder, or the data at risk contains viruses to scan instead you have to remove a long time waiting for antivirus software to scan all system on your computer. Thus speed of work of the McAfee Stinger faster and somewhat more accurate.
Themselves McAfee...
</description></item><item><title>Download dBpoweramp Image Converter Premier 2026-02-23</title><pubDate> Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:38:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbpoweramp-image-converter-7007.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbpoweramp-image-converter-7007.html
</guid><description>
dBpoweramp Image Converter is a simple visual transformation application that aims to make the transition as simple as possible. dBpoweramp Image Converter will switch between all popular formats, Bitmap, PNG, JPEG, TIFF and many other formats. It also has the ability to make mass transformation for multiple files and folders with only one click and filter on the png or other types of files.
dBpoweramp Image Converter is capable of switching high speed by using simultaneously all CPU...
</description></item><item><title>Download Boris FX Sapphire Plug-ins for OFX 2026.01</title><pubDate> Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:37:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-genarts-sapphire-839.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-genarts-sapphire-839.html
</guid><description>
GenArts Sapphire is the latest upgrade for the plugin VFX. The application includes LensFlare and Flare Designer been refurbished and completely revamped effects , digital art, new and is optimized for performance, CPU and GPU maximum. The current GenArts Sapphire is supported for Adobe, Avid, them Autodesk Flame and OFX as Resolve, Fusion, NUKE, Baselight (only version 4.3 and 4.4), VEGAS Pro and Harmony.
GenArts Sapphire - edit, add visual effects
The main features of GenArts...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinScript 2.0.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:36:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winscript-12800.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winscript-12800.html
</guid><description>
WinScript is an open source tool built to help you build custom scripts for Windows 10 and 11. It includes scripts for debugging, privacy, performance, and more, along with the ability to install all your favorite apps with just one click.
Features
	Debloat: Remove Windows bloatware, CoPilot, Edge, OneDrive, and other pre-installed features preset.
	Privacy: Disable Windows and 3rd party data collection, tracking, app access, and telemetry.
	Performance: Set background services to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sublime Merge 2 Build 2123</title><pubDate> Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:35:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sublime-merge-3957.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sublime-merge-3957.html
</guid><description>
Sublime Merge is the name of the application software and of course very useful for the programmer. In fact, the software in front of you is a text editor and the code light on the mass, and of course is strong. When using this software, you can view and edit multiple page text and his code at the same time and edit and complete them. User interface with great editing tools will give you experience coding very interesting.
Sublime Merge - source Editor and write the Code
Software...
</description></item><item><title>Download Kindle for PC 2.8.70987</title><pubDate> Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:34:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kindle-for-pc-6655.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kindle-for-pc-6655.html
</guid><description>
Kindle for PC is a handy and handy application that you can use to read a Kindle book with a computer without a Kindle device. To use it, you need to have an Amazon account registered, as the app will prompt you to log in as soon as the startup starts. Simple interface, which allows you to browse through your book library and manage your collections.
Features of Kindle for PC
	The navigation is so easy, because the entry can help you move to the desired chapter and you can use the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Boris FX Sapphire Plug-ins for Photoshop 2026.01</title><pubDate> Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:33:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-boris-fx-sapphire-plug-ins-for-photoshop-7185.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-boris-fx-sapphire-plug-ins-for-photoshop-7185.html
</guid><description>
Sapphire 2022 adds new host support for Adobe Photoshop. Featuring 270+ resolution independent and non-destructive effects built into a one-of-a-kind nodal based effects compositor. Photoshop artists will delight at 3000+ easily searchable presets organized by name, type, or intended use. Sapphire Photoshop has the same extensive parameter set as Sapphire plugins, giving artists complete control over every aspect of an effect.
Anything created with Sapphire Photoshop can be shared with...
</description></item><item><title>Download Find.Same.Images.OK 5.95</title><pubDate> Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:33:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-find-same-images-ok-113.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-find-same-images-ok-113.html
</guid><description>
Find.Same.Images.OK lets find the images identical or similar in the folder of you, even if they were to rotate, change size or change.
Just select one or more folders that you want the program to scan and it will return a list of all the duplicate images or very similar, as indicated by the percent the same and the preview is built.Then, you can select images from the list and then copy, move or delete them.
Find.Same.Images.OK
In addition, there are other options smart option allows...
</description></item><item><title>Download Atlantis Word Processor 5.0.1.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:32:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-atlantis-word-processor-585.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-atlantis-word-processor-585.html
</guid><description>
Atlantis Word Processor is a word processor app with features format, standard text, autocorrect, and spell check.  Atlantis is a word processor in accordance with most of the tasks handled daily text. The interface is very easy to use and offers the toolbars, hotkeys and sound effects thanh can customize (can turn off). It includes a clip library for quick access to the text or images used regular preview, font format and many other features aimed at improving the process of your...
</description></item><item><title>Download GOM Player Free 2.3.116 Build 5386</title><pubDate> Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:31:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gom-player-994.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gom-player-994.html
</guid><description>
GOM Player is a program to listen to music for free with the ability to play all format music and video now without the need to install additional codec. GOM Media Player brings all video codecs needed to play multiple video formats and various audio. Simple interface, light volume but powerful function is the factor which makes GOM Player famous in the music software.
GOM Media Player according to the reviews is considered the listen to music, watch video best. The user can control GOM...
</description></item><item><title>Download Zortam Mp3 Media Studio Pro 33.82</title><pubDate> Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:31:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zortam-mp3-media-studio-pro-135.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zortam-mp3-media-studio-pro-135.html
</guid><description>
Zortam Mp3 Media Studio Pro brings you rich processing tools music includes extract and convert music from CD to Mp3 format, edit, music cards, music download....You can also create discs CD high-quality music, with Zortam Mp3 Media Studio search music files duplicated to remove them from the system, rename music files, switch back and forth between formats.
Zortam Mp3 Media Studio Pro is rated as perfect software in the processing of the MP3 files on the computer. First of all, you can...
</description></item><item><title>Download StruSoft FEM-Design Suite 25.00.001</title><pubDate> Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:30:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-strusoft-fem-design-suite-7996.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-strusoft-fem-design-suite-7996.html
</guid><description>
FEM-Design Suite is a software for designing concrete, steel and timber structures according to EU standards. It features a unique user-friendly working environment based on familiar CAD tools that make structural modeling and editing simple and intuitive. The fast and easy nature of FEM-Design makes it ideal for all types of construction tasks from single element design to global stable analysis of large structures and making it become the best practical tool for structural...
</description></item><item><title>Download AD FastReporter Pro 26.2.20</title><pubDate> Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:29:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ad-fastreporter-pro-9439.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ad-fastreporter-pro-9439.html
</guid><description>
AD FastReporter Pro is a powerful tool for reporting and analyzing Active Directory (AD) data. It is designed to help administrators and IT professionals quickly and easily generate reports on AD users, computers, groups, and other objects.
With AD FastReporter Pro, you can generate many types of reports, including user account reports, team membership reports, computer inventory reports, security reports, and more. This tool allows you to customize your reports based on your specific...
</description></item><item><title>Download Boris FX Sapphire Plug-ins for After Effects 2026.01</title><pubDate> Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:28:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-boris-fx-sapphire-plug-ins-for-adobe-5314.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-boris-fx-sapphire-plug-ins-for-adobe-5314.html
</guid><description>
Boris FX, Sapphire Plug-ins for Adobe is a collection of very useful gadgets with additional powerful, as well as the effects to create the effect of the attractive images in the movies and video files. The film today is not complete without photo effects and include a number of photo effects to increase the beauty for their film. To add effect, clip to your movie, you can use a number of different applications and BorisFX Genarts Sapphire is one of them.
Boris FX, Sapphire Plug-ins for...
</description></item><item><title>Download Macro Expert Enterprise 4.9.8.9</title><pubDate> Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:28:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-macro-expert-enterprise-3558.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-macro-expert-enterprise-3558.html
</guid><description>
Macro Expert Enterprise is a powerful tool that will help you save time and money by empowering you to automate fully the work repetitive and regular. Macro Expert Enterprise can simplify a lot of work your computer, providing more than 260 action will meet most all your needs, automate your task. To keep they have the ability to access and organize high Macro Expert Enterprise split these actions into separate groups: Email, Excel document, database, Text, window, FTP, Internet, File,...
</description></item></channel></rss>