<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 17:40:18 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 17:40:18 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Background Video Recorder Pro 13.3.95</title><pubDate> Tue, 12 Aug 2025 20:05:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-background-video-recorder-pro-10919.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-background-video-recorder-pro-10919.html
</guid><description>
This application helps you record videos in the background even when the screen is closed. it has many other useful features, such as: remote camera control with Wear OS, motion detector with artificial intelligence algorithm, baby monitoring, calendar recording and continuous photo capture.
You can also control the camera with the volume button or 1 of 3 supported widgets
	"Big red button" - record video.
	"Big green button" - motion detection.
	"Big orange button" - takes photos...
</description></item><item><title>Download Folder Player Pro 5.35 build 351</title><pubDate> Tue, 12 Aug 2025 20:05:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-folder-player-pro-8330.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-folder-player-pro-8330.html
</guid><description>
Folder Player Pro is a mobile music player application available for Android devices. It allows users to play and organize their music files by folders, instead of just by artist or album. This app is perfect for users who have a lot of music files on their device and want to listen to them in a more organized way.
Features of Folder Player Pro APK
	Ability to play music files by folder, making it easy to find and listen to specific songs or albums
	Supports many audio file formats,...
</description></item><item><title>Download FP sDraw (Drawing app) 8.4</title><pubDate> Tue, 12 Aug 2025 20:04:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-fp-sdraw-drawing-app-11306.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-fp-sdraw-drawing-app-11306.html
</guid><description>
FP sDraw is a convenient drawing application. Suitable for sketches, as well as artistic drawings.
Program features
	Works very fast and smoothly.
	Small size: less than one megabyte.
	No advertising
	Access functions quickly with the volume button.
	Convenient menu.
	Full multi-touch support.
	Automatically saves to avoid losing drawings.
	Full support for brushes, especially Galaxy Note.
	Detect hovering fingers (if supported by device).
	Lots of settings.
	Unique road smoothing...
</description></item><item><title>Download ChatBox: AI Chat Bot Assistant 1.67.13</title><pubDate> Tue, 12 Aug 2025 20:04:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-chatbox-ai-chat-bot-assistant-12995.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-chatbox-ai-chat-bot-assistant-12995.html
</guid><description>
ChatBox is an advanced AI chat application and your virtual assistant built on the most advanced AI chat models. Designed to seamlessly integrate into your daily life, this AI chatbot uses advanced machine learning to improve productivity and provide instant solutions. Whether you're looking for help with a task or need answers to complex questions, your AI chatbot will leverage the latest advances in AI chat to help.
Some Highlights
	ChatBox leverages the latest AI technology to...
</description></item><item><title>Download WiFi Direct + 10.0.13</title><pubDate> Tue, 12 Aug 2025 20:04:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wifi-direct-10153.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wifi-direct-10153.html
</guid><description>
Wi-Fi Direct is a Wi-Fi standard for peer-to-peer wireless connections that allows two devices to establish a direct Wi-Fi connection without the need for an intermediate wireless access point, router, or Internet connection.
Features of WiFi Direct +
	Fast
	Completely free, no intrusive ads.
	Supports all file transfers.
	Supports multiple file transfers.
	Supports folder transfer.
	Supports file transfer to and from external sdcard.
	Tested on many devices.
	Advanced file chooser.
</description></item><item><title>Download Enhance it - AI Photo Editor 4.2.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 12 Aug 2025 20:03:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-enhance-it-fix-your-photos-11919.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-enhance-it-fix-your-photos-11919.html
</guid><description>
Enhance it is the best AI photo editing app to enhance your images, restore them and improve their quality and resolution. In addition to regular image editing tools, this application also uses artificial intelligence to automatically correct errors in photos, restore and improve their quality.
The perfect AI photo editing tool to help with any problem:
	AUTO ENHANCEMENT: This tool will restore low-quality images by removing noise, enhancing brightness and color, and better...
</description></item><item><title>Download Handy GPS 44.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 12 Aug 2025 20:03:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-handy-gps-8741.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-handy-gps-8741.html
</guid><description>
The perfect companion for your next outdoor adventure. Search, find, record and return home with handy GPS. This app is a powerful navigation tool designed for outdoor sports such as hiking, backpacking, mountain biking, kayaking, canoeing and horseback riding. It is also useful for surveying, mining, archeology and forestry applications.
This application is simple and works even in the most remote countries because it does not require a network connection. It allows you to work in UTM...
</description></item><item><title>Download PaperColor 2.9.15</title><pubDate> Tue, 12 Aug 2025 20:03:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-papercolor-10878.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-papercolor-10878.html
</guid><description>
PaperColor is a great drawing app that is imitating the paintbrush to draw and doodle, graffiti. Easy to draw, learn to paint!
	We have different paint styles and color libraries. Help you create perfect works of art.
	Whether you are on a journey, alone, at a party or just want to waste time in a plane，it is the best app that you can draw on your phone or tablet.
Exquisite drawing tools!
	Handwritten signature with pen after you finish the works
	There are many tools that...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sav PDF Viewer Pro - Read PDFs 1.16</title><pubDate> Tue, 12 Aug 2025 20:02:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sav-pdf-viewer-pro-read-pdfs-9082.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sav-pdf-viewer-pro-read-pdfs-9082.html
</guid><description>
SAV PDF Viewer Pro is a PDF reader application that allows users to easily read and manage PDF documents on their devices. It is a comprehensive PDF reader application that provides users with various features and tools to read and manage PDF documents. Whether you need to read PDFs for work or for fun, this app is a great choice for users who want a simple and efficient PDF reader.
Features of Sav PDF Viewer Pro for Android
	The app is safe, in fact, it doesn't require any...
</description></item><item><title>Download Lucid Launcher Pro 7.5</title><pubDate> Tue, 12 Aug 2025 19:54:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-lucid-launcher-pro-8381.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-lucid-launcher-pro-8381.html
</guid><description>
Lucid Launcher is a different kind of launcher than all the rest. It was built from the ground up, not based on any previous launcher. Lucid Launcher revolves around 3 categories (stability, features, and usability) that are constantly improved as the app grows. Don't let the size fool you, Lucid Launcher packs a punch while maintaining blazing fast performance. This launcher is packed with features that allow you to do what you really want to make it your own while maintaining a great...
</description></item><item><title>Download Typewise Offline Keyboard 4.4.24</title><pubDate> Tue, 12 Aug 2025 19:51:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-typewise-offline-keyboard-8578.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-typewise-offline-keyboard-8578.html
</guid><description>
Typewise Offline Keyboard for Android is the offline version of the popular and privacy-friendly "Typewise Keyboard" app. This offline version adds an extra layer of security. Note: online features will not be available in this app.
Features of Typewise Offline Keyboard
	Enter multiple languages without conversion
	Get personalized word suggestions
	16 more awesome themes
	Create your own alt text
	Turn on key vibration and set the perfect intensity
	Turn on tablet mode
	Change emoji...
</description></item><item><title>Download aCalendar+ Calendar &amp;amp; Tasks 2.9.3 build 2009300</title><pubDate> Tue, 12 Aug 2025 19:50:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-acalendar-calendar-tasks-9857.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-acalendar-calendar-tasks-9857.html
</guid><description>
aCalendar+ Calendar &amp;amp; Tasks is a popular calendar and task manager app for Android devices. It is developed by Tapir Apps GmbH and acts as an enhanced version of the free aCalendar app. aCalendar+ offers a variety of features and customization options to help users stay organized and manage their schedules and tasks effectively.
Features of aCalendar+ Calendar &amp;amp; Tasks Tasks
	intuitive navigation with smooth transitions
	day, week, month and year views
	full screen...
</description></item><item><title>Download Send files to TV 1.4.2b</title><pubDate> Tue, 12 Aug 2025 19:50:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-send-files-to-tv-11165.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-send-files-to-tv-11165.html
</guid><description>
SFTTV is a simple application to connect your Android smart TV, Android mobile device and personal computer. It allows you to quickly and easily share movies, TV shows or any files between these devices via your local network.
Features of Send Files to TV
	SFTTV is designed to be simple: The app automatically discovers other devices on your local network with SFTTV installed.
	Transfer large files in real time: SFTTV is faster than Bluetooth. SFTTV is the fastest and most private way...
</description></item><item><title>Download inCarDoc Pro | OBD2 7.8.7</title><pubDate> Tue, 12 Aug 2025 19:49:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-incardoc-pro-9775.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-incardoc-pro-9775.html
</guid><description>
inCarDoc Pro - the best doctor for your car: Tool to test, diagnose, scan, monitor and log engine codes: read stored and real-time diagnostic parameters from the car's ECU complying with the USB-II diagnostic system.
Requires ELM327 scanner or compatible diagnostic device. Support:OBD-II (Bluetooth, WiFi, Kiwi 3 (BLE), V-Gate iCar 3 (BLE), Veepeak (BLE), Carista, Vinli); GPS and Demo only mode. Read more at inCarDoc.com Limited functionality available without ELM327 only in GPS mode:...
</description></item><item><title>Download English Phrasal Verbs 2.1.6</title><pubDate> Tue, 12 Aug 2025 19:49:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-english-phrasal-verbs-12090.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-english-phrasal-verbs-12090.html
</guid><description>
Are you just starting to learn English or looking to improve your current English skills? This English learning app is for you! English is most widely used as a second language. You can use it in formal situations such as business, education, travel, shopping as well as in informal situations such as communicating with friends, etc.
The learning technique applied in the application allows you to learn English phrasal verbs (up to 900 per month), commonly used in common native English...
</description></item><item><title>Download Number to word convert offline 1.5</title><pubDate> Tue, 12 Aug 2025 19:45:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-number-to-word-convert-offline-11301.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-number-to-word-convert-offline-11301.html
</guid><description>
Simple Number to Word converter application helps convert the numbers you entered into words, you can copy, share converted words directly from the application.
Number to word converter app is 140 kb in size and does not require internet, the app does not ask for any permission because its simple stupid app just for converting numbers to words.&amp;lt; /p&amp;gt;
</description></item><item><title>Download Tape Measure: Measuring Ruler 6.5.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 12 Aug 2025 19:44:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ruler-app-camera-tape-measure-13657.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ruler-app-camera-tape-measure-13657.html
</guid><description>
ARCore Ruler App - A powerful measuring tool that takes advantage of Augmented Reality. The AR Ruler app uses augmented reality (AR) technology to measure the real world with your smartphone's camera. Aim at the detected plane and start using the AR tape measure tool:
	Line - allows to tape measure linear dimensions in cm, m, ft, yd, using a mm or inch ruler.
	Distance meter - allows to tape measure the distance from the device camera to a fixed point on the detected 3D plane.
	Angle -...
</description></item><item><title>Download Music for Meditation 9.5</title><pubDate> Tue, 12 Aug 2025 19:44:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-music-for-meditation-9803.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-music-for-meditation-9803.html
</guid><description>
With mindfulness meditation music, people are more focused, sleep better and are less stressed. Practicing meditation affects: stress, anxiety, sleepiness, concentration, depression, happiness, self-motivation, creativity, anger, pregnancy and more. Listening to music suitable for meditation will greatly facilitate the achievement of deep meditation, relaxation and concentration. Improve mental and physical health.
Science proves that people who meditate better fight stress, depression...
</description></item><item><title>Download Intel Wireless Bluetooth Driver (Windows 10/11) 23.160.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 12 Aug 2025 18:16:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intel-wireless-bluetooth-driver-5952.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intel-wireless-bluetooth-driver-5952.html
</guid><description>
Intel Wireless Bluetooth Driver is recommended for users, including family users and business customers with Intel Wireless Bluetooth technology.
Note: When you update the wireless application suite software package, it may not update the wireless controller controller if it includes the same driver as the previous release.
The internal products include:
	Intel ® Dual Band Wireless-AC 3165
	Intel ® Dual Band Wireless-AC 3168
	Intel ® Dual Band Wireless-AC 7265
	Intel ® Dual Band...
</description></item><item><title>Download HE - Hardware Read and Write Utility 1.25.08.11</title><pubDate> Tue, 12 Aug 2025 18:16:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-he-hardware-read-and-write-utility-4287.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-he-hardware-read-and-write-utility-4287.html
</guid><description>
HE - Hardware Read and Write Utility is a powerful utility intended for hardware engineer, engineer, BIOS developer, driver, engineer, QA engineers, performance test engineers, diagnostic, etc., this utility access almost all the computer hardware, including PCI (PCI Express), index / Data, PCI, memory, index memory / Data space I / O, Index I / O / Data, Super I / O, DIMM SPD, CPU The registers MSR, screen, SMART, physical area of the hard drive identification data, ATA, dump tables ACPI...
</description></item><item><title>Download EaseUS Fixo Technician 3.7.0 Build 20250808</title><pubDate> Tue, 12 Aug 2025 18:15:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-fixo-9814.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-fixo-9814.html
</guid><description>
Video is corrupted or inaccessible after power failure and sudden blackout, whole system crash, update failure, wrong file handling or some other reason? EaseUS Fixo allows you to repair many different video file formats including MOV, MP4, M2TS, MKV, MTS, 3GP, etc. easier no matter how broken it is.
It can intelligently and intelligently repair damaged and damaged photos from computers or other external storage devices such as USB flash drives, memory cards, SD cards, digital cameras...
</description></item><item><title>Download CorelDRAW Graphics Suite 2025 v26.2.0.29</title><pubDate> Tue, 12 Aug 2025 18:14:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coreldraw-graphics-suites-01en-1429.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coreldraw-graphics-suites-01en-1429.html
</guid><description>
CorelDRAW Graphics Suite is the software graphic designers with all the tools vector illustration, layout, photo editing and professional design. This is a comprehensive tool to help you work faster, smarter and in more places with software graphics design superiority this.
You will achieve superior productivity with new features are high-calibre program in graphic design this versatile. You will appreciate the process work smoother with support for PDF / X-4 standard and industrial...
</description></item><item><title>Download Lyric Video Studio 1.3.7</title><pubDate> Tue, 12 Aug 2025 18:14:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lyric-video-studio-13581.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lyric-video-studio-13581.html
</guid><description>
Lyric Video Studio is a powerful, feature-rich video editor specifically designed to create lyric videos, music videos, and visualizers with ease. It integrates simple and effective text tools along with generative AI capabilities to streamline the video creation process. Whether you're a musician launching a killer new track, a content creator, or just love playing with visuals, this app lets you sync your lyrics to your music in just a few clicks. Enter lyrics, drag to sync and you're...
</description></item><item><title>Download CorelDRAW Technical Suite 2025 v26.2.0.29</title><pubDate> Tue, 12 Aug 2025 18:13:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coreldraw-technical-suite-4733.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coreldraw-technical-suite-4733.html
</guid><description>
CorelDRAW Technical Suite 2020 allows you to create instructions for assembly details, instructions, use complex material, face and many more. Achieve superior productivity with the new features, caliber to increase the speed, efficiency and getting full support for the technical standards to publish, share or print with the software sketches and technical illustrations this extension.
CorelDRAW Technical Suite 2020 offers a wide range of design tools and illustrates exactly to create...
</description></item><item><title>Download Syncthing 2.0.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 12 Aug 2025 18:13:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncthing-2115.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncthing-2115.html
</guid><description>
Syncthing is synchronization service, cloud and open and non-focus allows you to share and sync files with other computers and gives you full control how to share your data and who can access it. Syncthing does not store your data in any other place, there is no server side Tuesday how to join. In addition, all the communication is secured by TLS and every button is determined by the certificate the strength of the encryption. Only computers that have explicitly allowed can connect with...
</description></item></channel></rss>