<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 13:47:16 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 13:47:16 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Soda PDF Desktop Pro 14.0.527.23106</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 16:34:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-soda-pdf-home-808.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-soda-pdf-home-808.html
</guid><description>
Soda PDF Pro  is intuitive PDF software that helps you to easily process and create PDF files from more than 300 different formats. Soda PDF is built to help you power through any PDF task. Convert to a wide range of file types. Edit the content of your document. Create custom forms. Annotate your files. Send and track contracts for electronic signatures.
Soda PDF Pro: Create PDF file
Features of Soda PDF Pro
	Read your PDFs and digital publications in 3D with unique page-turning...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Premiere Pro 2025 v25.6.1.002 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 16:33:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-premiere-pro-0021-1361.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-premiere-pro-0021-1361.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Premiere Pro is the leading video editing software for film, TV, and the web. Creative tools, integration with other Adobe apps and services, and the power of Adobe Sensei help you turn footage into finished movies and videos in a seamless workflow. It offers high-quality video editing at 4K x 4K resolution and beyond, with 32-bit color, in both RGB and YUV color spaces. Edit audio samples, support for VST audio plug-ins (plug-ins), and 5.1 surround sound tracks. The Premiere Pro...
</description></item><item><title>Download SepPDF 3.95</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 16:33:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-seppdf-924.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-seppdf-924.html
</guid><description>
SepPDF is a standalone tool simple allows you to split PDF document and create a PDF file for each page. SepPDF has a simple interface only provides access to a few configuration settings. The file can be added to the list by using the function drag and drop support of Wap or function built-in browser.
Advantages of SepPDF is the speed split pdf file was quite fast, with the capacity to compact software does not affect the operation performance of CPU as well as the performance of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Privacy Eraser Free 6.24.2 Build 5410</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 16:32:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-privacy-eraser-free-9160.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-privacy-eraser-free-9160.html
</guid><description>
Privacy Eraser is a software tool that helps protect user privacy by securely erasing or deleting unwanted data from their computer or device. This tool is designed to delete browsing history, cookies, cache, temporary files and other sensitive information that may be stored on the computer.
Privacy Eraser can be used to clear browsing history of popular web browsers such as Google Chrome, Mozilla Firefox and Microsoft Edge. It can also clear the history and cache of other applications,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Disk Drill Enterprise 6.1.1162.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 16:32:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-disk-drill-enterprise-6875.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-disk-drill-enterprise-6875.html
</guid><description>
Disk Drill Enterprise is software that allows you to recover files from hard drives and USB devices, external hard drives, memory cards, iPhone and iPad, drive formats like NTFS, FAT, exFAT, HFS + Mac drive, EXT2/3/4. The software provides fast scan and deep scan mode, depending on the user's needs, to save time and achieve the highest efficiency.
Features of Disk Drill Enterprise
	Users simply need one click to activate Disk Drill.
	Support to scan the entire drive and rejoin lost...
</description></item><item><title>Download Claris FileMaker Pro 22.0.4.406</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 16:31:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-filemaker-pro-advanced-487.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-filemaker-pro-advanced-487.html
</guid><description>
FileMaker Pro Advanced is software via internet easy manager database, contacts, projects and inventory data, and generate reports. FileMaker Pro will help users to build database customize and design them to fit with the activities and profile of their business. More than a million people around the world use platform FileMaker every day to complete the work faster and more efficient in work.
Features on FileMaker Pro Advanced
Anywhere access
	Use one unified platform to create the...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDF Architect Pro + OCR 9.1.83.23106</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 16:31:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-architect-pro-ocr-6381.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-architect-pro-ocr-6381.html
</guid><description>
PDF Architect  is professional software that provides PDF creation and editing features according to your needs. Our PDF editor keeps you up to date with forward-looking features. Take complete control of your PDF files with our PDF editor. Modify text, images, and pages, and convert PDF to Word and Excel and more.
It has many advanced options and features for customizing, securing, and collaborating PDF files. All necessary features are included in this for better user experience. This...
</description></item><item><title>Download RollBack Rx Server 4.9 Build 2711286639</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 16:30:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rollback-rx-server-5643.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rollback-rx-server-5643.html
</guid><description>
RollBack Rx Server is a powerful Windows Server backup and restore utility that allows IT professionals the ability to instantly backup, be able to quickly restore mission-critical systems back to real any number of restore points. It helps you to quickly and easily securely update sandbox and service patches with a fail-safe approach to system recovery. You can recover files and folders from any corrupted snapshots or system state.
RollBack Rx Server Features
	Fully supports active...
</description></item><item><title>Download Secure Delete Professional 2025 v214</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 16:30:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secure-delete-professional-4991.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secure-delete-professional-4991.html
</guid><description>
Secure Delete Professional is very simple tool but very effective to delete files and folders in a secure way. After using this tool, the files and folders selected will not be available for recovery. We have attached a number of security options so you can choose the security level that you need (this reflects the processing speed).
You can use this application in 3 ways. First, you can drag and drop the file or folder that you want to delete securely to the main window of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Serato Studio 2.4.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 16:29:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-serato-studio-2352.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-serato-studio-2352.html
</guid><description>
Serato Studio's beat making software intuitive for DJ and producer. Spend less time to block the barrier and more time in creative flow. Serato Studio is an audio workstation new digital (DAW), developed for those who have experience in the field of DJ. It reflects the essence of DJ software and make it become the ideal for any user in this field, it doesn't matter if you just decided to create music, or have experienced. This application has the working environment very friendly for...
</description></item><item><title>Download Photo Lab PRO Picture Editor 3.13.76</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 16:29:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-photo-lab-pro-picture-editor-8225.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-photo-lab-pro-picture-editor-8225.html
</guid><description>
Photo Lab PRO Picture Editor is a powerful photo editing application that allows users to enhance and transform their photos with a variety of filters, effects and frames. Enhance your photos with over 640 beautiful frames, effects, filters or montages! Photo Lab PRO is an easy, fast and fun photo editor. You don't have to be a Photoshop expert to make every photo funny and every portrait beautiful.
Features of Photo Lab PRO Picture Editor
	Photo effects: Photo Lab PRO offers a...
</description></item><item><title>Download AZIP Master: ZIP RAR Extractor 4.2.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 16:28:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-azip-master-zip-rar-extractor-9785.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-azip-master-zip-rar-extractor-9785.html
</guid><description>
AZIP Master is a file manager application, zip file reader, creates archives in ZIP or 7Z file format. Unzip multiple archive file formats: unZIP (unzip ZIP files) unRAR (unzip RAR files), etc. Being a stable application - AZIP Master is an attractive choice for mobile users globally.
AZIP Master Features: ZIP RAR Extractor
	Decompress multiple files at once
	️Create a packaged 7Z ZIP archive
	️Quick decompression: open compressed files with the ZIP RAR 7Z file decompression...
</description></item><item><title>Download Zero Cleaner: clear cache 25.11.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 16:28:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-zero-cleaner-clear-cache-10667.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-zero-cleaner-clear-cache-10667.html
</guid><description>
Zero Cleaner is a mobile application that specializes in removing cache files from your device. Cache files are temporary data stored by applications and websites to improve their performance and load times. Over time, cache files can accumulate and take up valuable storage space on your device.
Some key features of Zero Cleaner include:
	Cache Cleaner: The app will scan your device for cache files created by apps and web browsers, allowing you to clear them with just a tap. This...
</description></item><item><title>Download Custom Search Bar Widget CSBW 2.2.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 16:28:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-custom-search-bar-widget-csbw-10129.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-custom-search-bar-widget-csbw-10129.html
</guid><description>
Custom Search Bar Widget (CSBW) is a fully editable search bar widget with a customizable icon drawer. The widget can be changed in many ways to match the current theme of the device. This drawer includes editable icons that can switch search engines, provide quick links to apps, or apply functions like copy and paste.
Features of CSBW Custom Search Bar Widget
	Fully customize every aspect of the search bar widget and icon drawer.
	Save search bar themes and load them later.
	Keyword...
</description></item><item><title>Download Equalizer &amp;amp; Bass Booster Pro 2.0.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 16:27:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-equalizer-bass-booster-pro-10056.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-equalizer-bass-booster-pro-10056.html
</guid><description>
Improve the sound quality of your Android device with the first true Global Equalizer, Bass Boost and Surround Sound. Make your Android device sound like never before. Equalizer &amp;amp; Bass Booster includes volume slider, live music-guided stereo VU meter, Five-band Equalizer, Bass Boost and Virtualizer effects. Equalizer &amp;amp; Bass Booster lets you adjust the sound effect levels so you get the most out of your Music or Audio coming out of your phone.
Features of Equalizer &amp;amp; Bass...
</description></item><item><title>Download Librera PRO - Book reader 9.1.6 beta</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 16:26:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-librera-pro-all-my-books-9008.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-librera-pro-all-my-books-9008.html
</guid><description>
PRO Librera Reader is an easy-to-use and highly configurable reading application that supports most popular document formats, including: PDF, EPUB, EPUB3, MOBI, DjVu, FB2, FB2.zip, TXT, RTF, AZW, AZW3, CBR, CBZ, HTML, XPS, MHT and more. With a simple yet powerful interface, Librera Reader makes reading documents a real pleasure. Librera even has a unique hands-free, auto-scrolling music mode.
Some key features of Librera reader include:
Easily explore documents with optional and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Genius Scan Enterprise 7.33.2 build 7054</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 16:26:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-genius-scan-enterprise-8561.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-genius-scan-enterprise-8561.html
</guid><description>
Genius Scan Enterprise: Quickly scan your paper documents on the go and export them as multi-page PDF files. Place any document in front of your device's camera: our scanner app automatically recognizes the paper on the background, crops it and cleans the result. You get sharp, easy-to-read scans. Batch scanning allows you to scan dozens of pages in just a few seconds. Powerful tools help you organize, share or archive your documents.
Features of Genius Scan Enterprise for...
</description></item><item><title>Download BlackPlayer EX 20.65 build 414</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 16:25:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-blackplayer-ex-9732.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-blackplayer-ex-9732.html
</guid><description>
BlackPlayer Exclusive - The ultimate MP3 player. BlackPlayer EX removes Ads to focus on what matters most, the music. Includes a ton of additional premium features. Of course all the great features of the standard BlackPlayer are included in this player. Create your own look with customization available in the Settings menu.
Features of BlackPlayer EX
	Light themes!
	6 additional fonts, including the option to use System fonts.
	11 color accents.
	8 additional now playing...
</description></item><item><title>Download Audyssey MultEQ Editor app 1.13.3 build 44</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 16:25:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-audyssey-multeq-editor-app-10113.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-audyssey-multeq-editor-app-10113.html
</guid><description>
Denon Marantz's latest audio video products use Audyssey MultEQ for simple, precise setup tuning of your system to suit the space in which it's used. However, you can now go even further with the Audyssey MultEQ Editor app, going 'under the hood' to view and tweak settings for detailed adjustments – allowing you to more precisely customize your sound for your needs. your room's specific problems and adjust the sound to suit your personal preferences. With this comprehensive app, you...
</description></item><item><title>Download AI Notes &amp;amp; Memo 9.0.9</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 16:25:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ai-notes-memo-app-13165.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ai-notes-memo-app-13165.html
</guid><description>
Introducing NotesAI, the ultimate AI note-taking tool that revolutionizes the way you transcribe speech to text and take voice notes. Powered by advanced AI transcription technology, this powerful transcription tool makes speech to text and voice notes to text easy. With NotesAI, you can easily capture your ideas and turn your notes into clean, searchable records—an innovative alternative to Otter and Coconote.
Key Features:
	Live Recording &amp;amp; Voice Notes to Text: Enjoy reliable...
</description></item><item><title>Download Opera One 124.0.5705.42</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 16:24:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-972.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-972.html
</guid><description>
Opera is a fast, safe, configurable and compliant intranet web browser, which includes both the reader and the application. The Opera browser supports web browsing, listening to music, watching high speed movies, you can open many tabs on the Opera without affecting your browsing speed. Opera now supports almost all devices and operating systems such as windows, IOS, Android, linux, MacOS ...
Opera is a beautiful interface and many interesting features, operating on both PCs and mobile,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Process Explorer 17.08</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 16:21:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-process-explorer-370.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-process-explorer-370.html
</guid><description>
Process Explorer is a software to track and manage the active processes on your computer, at the same time, timely detection and debugging.  Process Explorer shows you information about the processing and the process DLL already open or download. Screen Process Explorer consists of two window. The top part always displays the list of processes that are currently active, including the name of the account owner of them
Process Explorer helps you get the look more depth, more details about...
</description></item><item><title>Download Telegram for Desktop 6.3.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 16:21:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-telegram-3376.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-telegram-3376.html
</guid><description>
Telegram is an instant messaging service and voice over IP services on the cloud platform. Client application Telegram is available for Android, iOS, Windows Phone, Windows NT, macOS, and Linux. Users can send messages and exchange photos, videos, stickers, audio and files of any kind.
Telegram - Messaging and free phone calls
Telegram seamless sync across all your devices and can be used on desktop, tablet and phone. You can send unlimited amount of messages, photos, videos and files...
</description></item><item><title>Download CoolUtils PDF Combine Pro 8.1.0.66</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 16:14:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-pdf-combine-pro-580.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-pdf-combine-pro-580.html
</guid><description>
CoolUtils PDF Combine Pro  is software that helps you combine  PDF, DOC, TXT, DOCX, HTML, XLS, images  h (TIFF, JPEG, PNG) and  email  as a  PDF  file. With PDF Combine Pro it is easier than ever to combine documents into one PDF file. Now you don't have to use some programs and converters to get a PDF. Everything for PDF Combine Pro to do for you.
Office, fax, email files - get combined PDF in seconds for personal use, commercial needs, electronic discovery, or manufacturing.  PDF...
</description></item><item><title>Download Daemon Tools Lite 12.3.0.2366</title><pubDate> Fri, 21 Nov 2025 16:13:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-daemon-tools-lite-3391.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-daemon-tools-lite-3391.html
</guid><description>
DAEMON Tools Lite is based on two key features, simulation of virtual disks and building the file disk image as iso. DAEMON Tools Lite can emulate up to 4 virtual drives, DVD, CD or Blu-ray on your computer. The virtual units will be present in your system the same as the unit. After you select the virtual drive you want, you will choose a disc image (nrg, iso, mdf, bin, cue, etc.) that you want to mount. Visit My Computer at the device have The mobile storage and you will find the disk...
</description></item></channel></rss>