<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 13:53:45 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 13:53:45 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download 3C All-in-One Toolbox 3.1.5b</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 16:45:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-3c-all-in-one-toolbox-8399.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-3c-all-in-one-toolbox-8399.html
</guid><description>
3C All-in-One Toolbox combines many features into one giant toolbox with a modern and easy-to-use interface. All the tools you need to monitor, control and fine-tune all your Android devices. This app uses the Accessibility service to help you stop the app on non-rooted devices but will never collect any information.
Features of 3C All-in-One Toolbox
	Device Manager offers very powerful configurations, task scheduling, and device watchdogs that you can find to optimize performance and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Rosetta Stone: Learn, Practice 8.34.4</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 16:45:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-rosetta-stone-learn-practice-11241.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-rosetta-stone-learn-practice-11241.html
</guid><description>
Interactive and contextual lessons combined with Extended Learning features are truly at your fingertips–anytime, anywhere, on any device; online or offline and completely ad-free. Learn to speak Spanish, French, German, Italian, English, Japanese, Korean, Chinese, Arabic, Portuguese, Russian, Dutch, Filipino, Greek , Hebrew, Hindi, Irish, Persian, Polish, Swedish, Turkish, Vietnamese and more!
Rosetta Stone helps you speak confidently: With many lessons and features focused on...
</description></item><item><title>Download Anti Spy Detector: Anti Hack 48.5.24.12.25</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 16:43:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-anti-spy-detector-firewall-10779.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-anti-spy-detector-firewall-10779.html
</guid><description>
With the powerful built-in firewall in this app, you can monitor every outgoing connection each app makes. If you don't trust the app, you can block it from accessing the internet with a firewall to prevent tracking and analysis. Every outgoing IP or domain will be saved and you can see them, the Firewall will show you the address, organization and information about that IP and if you feel suspicious you can block that domain so that application is no longer accessible. Additionally, you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Any.do - To do list &amp;amp; Calendar 5.18.15.5</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 16:43:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-anydo-to-do-list-calendar-8360.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-anydo-to-do-list-calendar-8360.html
</guid><description>
Any.do is a productivity app that combines the features of a to-do list and a calendar. It allows users to create and organize tasks as well as schedule them according to specific dates and times. The app also includes a feature called "My Day" that helps users focus on the most important tasks of the day.
Some of Any.do's other features include the ability to set reminders, create side and recurring tasks, and collaborate on tasks with others. Additionally, Any.do also has a calendar...
</description></item><item><title>Download Device Info: System &amp;amp; CPU Info 3.4.1.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 16:42:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-device-info-system-cpu-info-8723.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-device-info-system-cpu-info-8723.html
</guid><description>
Device Information: System &amp;amp; CPU Information is a mobile application that provides users with detailed information about the hardware and software specifications of their device. This app is designed to help users better understand their device's capabilities and performance as well as diagnose any potential issues or problems.
With Device Info: System and CPU Info, users can view information about the processor, memory, storage, battery, sensors, and more. of equipment. This app...
</description></item><item><title>Download Memento Database 5.8.4</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 16:42:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-memento-database-11185.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-memento-database-11185.html
</guid><description>
Memento Database is a powerful and user-friendly tool designed to work with any data, helping to store, organize, calculate and visualize information. It is more convenient than spreadsheets, more flexible than dedicated applications. If you are looking for a program to organize personal matters, hobbies or small or medium-sized businesses, Memento is the solution.
Personal use 
Memento can replace dozens of applications, helping you organize your life and increase your...
</description></item><item><title>Download ACR Phone 0.382</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 16:41:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-acr-phone-10805.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-acr-phone-10805.html
</guid><description>
ACR Phone &amp;amp; Dialer Spam call blocker is a phone app that can replace your default dialer. This is a completely new application and we are constantly improving it.
Features of ACR Phone
	Blacklist/Block spam
	Call person to notify
	Call notes
	Backup
	Outgoing call blocker
	Call log
	Supports dual SIM
	Contacts
	Video call and photo call screen
	SIP client (on supported devices)
	Call recording (on supported devices)
	Cloud Upload
	Auto Dialer
	Visual voicemail
</description></item><item><title>Download Multi Timer StopWatch 2.13.32</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 16:41:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-multi-timer-stopwatch-8914.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-multi-timer-stopwatch-8914.html
</guid><description>
Multi Timer is a beautifully designed time management app. Multiple timers can be set, started and run independently at the same time. Stopwatch results can be stored. Use Multi Timer for cooking, sports, machine washing, studying, working, gaming - whatever you like.
Features of Multi Timer StopWatch
	Multiple timers at once: Store the timers you often use for cooking, sports, studying, working, gaming, whatever you want. Start them with just one tap, anytime you need.
	Timer in...
</description></item><item><title>Download SnapTube for Android 7.52.1.75270901</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 16:41:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-snaptube-youtube-downloader-hd-video-8351.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-snaptube-youtube-downloader-hd-video-8351.html
</guid><description>
SnapTube is a mobile application that allows users to download videos from various platforms, such as YouTube, Vimeo, and Dailymotion. It provides video resolution in multiple formats 144p, 720p, 1080p HD, 2K HD, 4K HD and audio formats MP3 and M4A. With Snaptube, users can search for content across all their platforms without using multiple apps.
Features of SnapTube for Android
Download in multiple resolutions
	MP4 videos are available in resolutions: choose small 360 pixels or...
</description></item><item><title>Download Phone Dialer &amp;amp;amp; Contacts: drupe 3.20.7.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 16:40:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-phone-dialer-contacts-drupe-11477.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-phone-dialer-contacts-drupe-11477.html
</guid><description>
Want to see caller ID, spam indicator and block spammers, directly from your call screen? drupe is your application. Trusted by over 20 million users worldwide. drupe replaces your boring call screen with a fresh interface, built and configured precisely for you! Forget about traditional Phone Book applications!
Main features:
	Smart Dialer - Dialing across multiple apps is quick and easy
	Smart caller ID tracker and blocker to find unknown numbers - drupe ID identifier will help you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Map My Run GPS Running Tracker 25.13.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 16:40:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-map-my-run-by-under-armour-8145.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-map-my-run-by-under-armour-8145.html
</guid><description>
Map My Run by Under Armor is a mobile app that allows users to track their running, walking, and other outdoor activities using GPS. The app is available to download from the Google Play Store and Apple App Store. It was developed by Under Armour, a company specializing in sports apparel and equipment. In addition to tracking workouts, the app also provides users with tools to analyze performance and set goals.
Features of Map My Run by Under Armor APK
	GPS tracking: The app uses GPS...
</description></item><item><title>Download Passwords &amp;amp; Passkeys－Safe 26.8.9</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 16:40:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-password-manager-safeincloud-pro-10227.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-password-manager-safeincloud-pro-10227.html
</guid><description>
Protect your data with a unique and secure password! Forget the headache of remembering PINs and passwords! START USING PASSWORD MANAGER TODAY! SafeInCloud is a complete password management solution: Free desktop app + Mobile app for phones and tablets.
Features of Password Manager SafeInCloud Pro
	Material Design
	Dark theme
	Strong encryption (AES)
	Cloud synchronization (Google Drive, Dropbox, OneDrive)
	Finger Scan and Multi-Window (Samsung devices)
	Analyze password...
</description></item><item><title>Download Retrica 8.1.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 16:40:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-retrica-9784.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-retrica-9784.html
</guid><description>
Retrica is the catalyst for great photos with special effects and over 190 filters. Add vignette, grain or blur effects to bring that vintage atmosphere to your photos and videos. Take photos and videos with filters and effects in real time, or edit them from your phone's album.
Features of Retrica Pro for Android
Easy, simple and attractive
	Enhanced user interface provides an easy, simple, comfortable and enjoyable photography experience. Retrica also offers multiple aspect ratios,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Seven - 7 Minute Workout 9.24.6</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 16:39:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-seven-7-minute-workout-8424.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-seven-7-minute-workout-8424.html
</guid><description>
Working out has never been easier – or more fun. Seven's workouts are scientifically researched to deliver maximum benefits in the shortest possible time. With personalized training plans, Seven also ensures you get the most out of your workouts. Want to get fit, lose weight, or be healthier? Just set your goals and fitness level, and let Seven take care of the rest.
Seven - 7 Minute Workout Features
	Work out anytime, anywhere, no equipment needed
	Create a workout routine with our...
</description></item><item><title>Download FotMob - Soccer Live Scores 220.15405.20251222.rc</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 16:39:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-fotmob-soccer-live-scores-8241.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-fotmob-soccer-live-scores-8241.html
</guid><description>
FotMob gives you all the live scores, stats and storylines to help you keep up with the world of football. Personalized news and notifications make it easy to follow your favorite teams and players. And lightning-fast match updates ensure you never miss a goal, no matter where you are.
Features of FotMob - Live soccer scores
	Live match score
	Results, schedule, standings and lineup
	Detailed statistics, including expected goals (xG) and expected assists (xA)
	Capture map
	Player...
</description></item><item><title>Download Squid: Take Notes, Markup PDFs 4.5.1-GP</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 16:39:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-squid-take-notes-markup-pdfs-8747.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-squid-take-notes-markup-pdfs-8747.html
</guid><description>
Squid is a note-taking and PDF markup app for Android devices. It allows users to create handwritten notes, sketch drawings, and markup PDF documents with a variety of tools and options. With Squid you can write just like you would on paper using an active pen, passive stylus, or your finger. Easily markup PDFs to fill out forms, edit/grade papers, or sign documents. Import images, draw shapes, and add typed text to your notes. Quickly select, copy/paste, and move content between pages...
</description></item><item><title>Download CalendarTask (formerly DesktopCal) 3.26.262.8321</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 00:11:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopcal-1831.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopcal-1831.html
</guid><description>
CalendarTask (formerly DesktopCal) is a simple desktop calendar that blends into your desktop without blocking access to your desktop icons. You can double-click on a date to quickly add notes and also jump to specific dates in the past or future.
CalendarTask - Computer calendar
CalendarTask can use your current wallpaper or loop through images from your folder and update your desktop every few minutes. The program helps you make appointments, make plans... Not only that, the Screen...
</description></item><item><title>Download CapCut PC 7.7.0.3143 / 7.8.0.3245 Beta 6</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 00:10:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capcut-pc-9995.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capcut-pc-9995.html
</guid><description>
CapCut PC is a simple video editing tool that you can freely use anywhere. You can create videos on your browser, desktop and laptop, or on your phone. Versatile editing, magical AI tools, team collaboration, and built-in assets. Create videos in a whole new way.
You can edit videos based on editing the timeline, in the process you can add different elements and effects to the video to give the best effect to your work. It is a simple and intuitive set of editing tools and effects that...
</description></item><item><title>Download Better File Rename 6.29</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 00:08:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-better-file-rename-1433.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-better-file-rename-1433.html
</guid><description>
Better File Rename is software rename files, the most comprehensive with a lot of functions to handle, rename files, add, remove, insert and replace characters... Better File Rename is considered as a handy industrial strength fast, flexible, reliable and easy to use. That is why since 1999, thousands of hobbyists, professionals and businesses depend on to Change the name of the file to better organize and maintain their files.
Better File Rename - Change the name of the file
Better...
</description></item><item><title>Download IObit Driver Booster Pro Portable 13.1.0.171</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 00:07:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iobit-driver-booster-pro-portable-4169.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iobit-driver-booster-pro-portable-4169.html
</guid><description>
IObit Driver Booster Pro Portable is a portable version developed with IObit's most advanced driver update technology, which automatically identifies and scans for outdated, downloaded drivers and install the correct update for you with just one click, saving you a lot of time. In addition, IObit Driver Booster Pro Portable is specially developed to enhance drivers for better gaming performance and ensure better computer performance by improving update security with Restore, Uninstall...
</description></item><item><title>Download Garden Planner 3.8.81</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 00:06:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-garden-planner-186.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-garden-planner-186.html
</guid><description>
Garden Planner : If you want to create a garden plan, create a landscape by activity or simply be curious, then you can download Garden Planner .   Garden Planner is a program that helps the user to design a dream garden through the layout and arrangement of plants, plants, buildings and objects, creating living spaces. style is consistent with the user's criteria and standards.
Garden Planner application is very simple, just select bushes, other plants, trees, pond and drag them into...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare UniConverter Portable 17.1.1.457</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 00:06:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-uniconverter-portable-12162.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-uniconverter-portable-12162.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare UniConverter Portable - a portable version (unofficial), formerly known as Wondershare Video Converter Ultimate, is a comprehensive media conversion software developed by Wondershare. It offers a wide range of features to convert, edit and enhance multimedia files. Convert, download, compress, edit, record videos in 1000 formats and do more.
With this comprehensive program, you can customize your home movies through advanced editing features and get professional work in...
</description></item><item><title>Download ThisIsMyFile 4.48</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 00:05:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thisismyfile-2247.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thisismyfile-2247.html
</guid><description>
ThisIsMyFile is a program that is positive, will remove the open files affected from the appropriate program, and perform necessary action. If it is launch in mode administrator, you may need to know what you do. If not, it leads to instability to the operating system.
ThisIsMyFile - Delete protected files
Application does not need installation, after unpacking the archive file, we immediately start and can use it.We need a little, you just specify a folder or a specific file, then you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Password Depot 19.0.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 00:05:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-password-depot-1048.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-password-depot-1048.html
</guid><description>
Password Depot is a password manager powerful helps organize all your passwords, credit information or software licenses. Password Depot offers the ability to store your passwords in a secure way, ensuring you use the data safe and help you have secure passwords.
Password Depot does not only guarantee security: It also has the ability to convenient to use, customization ability, high flexibility, markedly when interacting with other devices and, last but not last long, flexibility is...
</description></item><item><title>Download XL-Connector 3.6.36.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 29 Dec 2025 00:04:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xl-connector-12415.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xl-connector-12415.html
</guid><description>
XL-Connector is a popular plugin that securely integrates Excel and Salesforce to export, import, refresh and transform data seamlessly with ultra-fast api connection. It provides Salesforce administrators with a comprehensive toolbox that easily performs data and metadata management activities in a familiar Excel environment.
Features
Export from Salesforce to Excel
	Get data from existing Salesforce reports or build your own SOQL queries directly into Excel.
Import data into...
</description></item></channel></rss>