<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 19:57:58 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 19:57:58 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download PDF-XChange Pro 10.7.0.398.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 22 Aug 2025 19:13:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-xchange-editor-pro-3422.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-xchange-editor-pro-3422.html
</guid><description>
PDF-XChange Editor Pro is an application to manipulate and create PDF versatile, offering a wide range of useful features and powerful will help you to easily work with PDF files. This application is very flexible and allows you to easily create and modify PDF files. PDF-XChange Editor Pro provides a powerful set of tools and flexibility to work with PDF files, such as editor PDF-XChange new, utilities series, OFFice2PDF and the Addin tool Bar allows you to easily convert multiple file...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDF-XChange Editor Plus 10.7.0.398.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 22 Aug 2025 19:12:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-xchange-editor-plus-645.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdf-xchange-editor-plus-645.html
</guid><description>
PDF-XChange Editor Plus is the editor, PDF viewer, compact, fast with many features, add-ons, professional. When using the PDF-XChange Editor Plus, easy for users to create, view, edit, annotate, OCR and digital signing PDF files, plus much more.
PDF-XChange Editor is a PDF editing full-featured. With the help of it, you can edit, fix, add, or delete text easily. Graphics can also be moved, resized or removed.
Features PDF-XChange Editor Plus
Edit documents
	Use a variety of editing...
</description></item><item><title>Download Office Timeline Plus 11.21.00.00 Expert / Pro / Pro+ Edition</title><pubDate> Fri, 22 Aug 2025 19:12:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-timeline-2106.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-timeline-2106.html
</guid><description>
Office Timeline is an add-on very useful and powerful software for Microsoft PowerPoint. With add-ons, you can create PowerPoint documents look more beautiful. With add-ons, you can add the time Line on the project by yourself. Application time for the composition and different segments of the document, your PowerPoint will not only increase the beauty for your work, but also for customers and your manager. The people who created this product is also believe that add-ons this is the only...
</description></item><item><title>Download 4K Video Downloader Plus 25.3.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 22 Aug 2025 19:11:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-video-downloader-617.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-video-downloader-617.html
</guid><description>
4K Video Downloader Plus is software support downloads video, audio and subtitles from YouTube with high quality up to 4K. Download process video is very simple: just copy the video link from your browser and click Paste Url. Done! If you want that video on your iPad, iPhone or other device, we have protected you.
The feature on 4K Video Downloader Plus
	Download entire playlists and channels from YouTube and save them in MP4, MKV, M4A, MP3, FLV, 3G, create a file .m3u for...
</description></item><item><title>Download KMPlayer (KMP) 2025.8.22.13 x64 / 4.2.3.24 x86</title><pubDate> Fri, 22 Aug 2025 19:10:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kmplayer-kmp-902.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kmplayer-kmp-902.html
</guid><description>
KMPlayer (KMP) is software watch movies listen to music multi-function for video enthusiasts. KMPlayer development is many types of the format different. KMPlayer has improved on sound quality, images when listening to music and watching movies, the playback speed of video is faster, more codec player is added to the software video decoder is optimized.
KMPlayer also supports a variety of audio formats and video and offers a the interface can be customized with the preview coverflow and...
</description></item><item><title>Download iTubeGo YouTube Downloader 10.7.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 22 Aug 2025 19:10:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-itubego-youtube-downloader-3681.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-itubego-youtube-downloader-3681.html
</guid><description>
iTubeGo YouTube Downloader  is the best way to download live video from 1000+ streaming sites. iTubeGo YouTube Downloader is a powerful download tool that allows you to save video and audio for free. The output format of high speed converter is high quality MP4, MP3. Fully compatible with iPhone, iPad, iTunes, iMovie, Android Phone and more.
iTubeGo YouTube Downloader - Solution for downloading high quality Youtube video 
Features of iTubeGo YouTube Downloader
	Download videos from...
</description></item><item><title>Download WiFi Password Decryptor 17.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 22 Aug 2025 19:09:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wifi-password-decryptor-3777.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wifi-password-decryptor-3777.html
</guid><description>
WiFi Password Decryptor is a useful software to recover now password wireless account stored on your system. WiFi Password Decryptor automatically recovers all type of Key / password wireless (WEP / WPA / WPA2 etc) stored by The configuration manager, wireless of Windows. WiFi Password Decryptor reveals WiFi passwords hidden under asterisks, which are stored in the table Manger Configuration wireless of Windows. It is very useful if you lose or forget the password prevents you from...
</description></item><item><title>Download MAC Address Scanner 7.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 22 Aug 2025 19:08:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mac-address-scanner-7490.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mac-address-scanner-7490.html
</guid><description>
MAC Address Scanner is a tool that remotely scans and finds the MAC Address of all systems in your local network. It allows you to scan a single server or multiple servers at the same time. During the scan, it shows the current status for each server. Once done, you can generate detailed scan reports in HTML/XML/TEXT/CSV format.
On certain secure WiFi configurations with MAC filtering enabled, this tool can help find active MAC addresses and then use them to connect to that wireless...
</description></item><item><title>Download Calibre 8.9.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 22 Aug 2025 19:07:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-calibre-1669.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-calibre-1669.html
</guid><description>
Calibre  is an eBook library management application that allows you to manage your eBook collection, convert eBooks between different formats, Sync with popular e-reading devices and read your e-books with included viewer. You can sort books by author, title, date and other details, download meta information and book covers, add personalized tags and comments, and view your images in the cover display.
Collection of essential tools for adding metadata editing books or managing your...
</description></item><item><title>Download 4K YouTube to MP3 25.3.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 22 Aug 2025 19:06:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-youtube-to-mp3-622.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-youtube-to-mp3-622.html
</guid><description>
4K YouTube to MP3 is a software to convert video youtube to mp3 quickly and easily by the manipulation drag-and-drop simple. With 4K YouTube to MP3 you just drag and drop the link to the favorite songs of you and get the MP3 files to your computer, as easy as that. Transfer songs directly to iPod, iPhone and iPad everywhere you go. No install annoying and complex to solve, just a clean interface, user friendly and functional.
When using 4K YouTube to MP3, users will get the playlists,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Activation Program 1.12 b07</title><pubDate> Fri, 22 Aug 2025 19:01:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-activation-program-12767.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-activation-program-12767.html
</guid><description>
Activation Program is a Windows and Office activator from Ratiborus for Windows 7 to 11. The program is created based on the MASSGRAVE code.
What advantages does this method have over other activation methods?
It offers the most advantages for activating older versions of Windows, such as Windows 7 to 8.1, as it can permanently activate any version of the versions This without modifying the Windows system boot process or executable files. This is the only public activator that provides...
</description></item><item><title>Download Stardock Start11 2.5.5.1 Beta</title><pubDate> Fri, 22 Aug 2025 19:01:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stardock-start11-7029.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stardock-start11-7029.html
</guid><description>
Start11 is an application capable of customizing the Start Menu and Taskbar on Windows 11 and Windows 10. This is an application that allows users to customize Windows 11 to suit their preferences. his personal. Start11 will help you bring the new Start Menu of Windows 11 to Windows 10. And vice versa, Start11 also helps you to bring the Start Menu of Windows 10 to Windows 11.
Start11 also helps users bring some functions of Windows 10 to Windows 11 through customizing the Taskbar such...
</description></item><item><title>Download RainbowTaskbar 3.2.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 22 Aug 2025 19:00:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rainbowtaskbar-6740.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rainbowtaskbar-6740.html
</guid><description>
RainbowTaskbar is an open source, customizable Windows taskbar that includes colors and transitions. Add some color to your taskbar by changing the color shift on the spectrum, you can like it visually. The program allows you to customize the colors; Instructions can be found on the author's website.
</description></item><item><title>Download Visual Studio Code 1.103.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 22 Aug 2025 18:59:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-visual-studio-code-3182.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-visual-studio-code-3182.html
</guid><description>
Visual Studio Code is the encryption tool of Microsoft has met most of the needs of the developer. Environment this encoding was introduced to compete with other products such as Sublime and Nodepad ++ . Microsoft, in its new product, has not been released in many years, has provided many features in a simple environment. In addition to the familiar with a dozen programming languages, the syntax and get to know coding language as soon as be encrypted and allows for syntax highlighting, it...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Saver Pro 10.7.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 22 Aug 2025 18:59:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-saver-6830.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-saver-6830.html
</guid><description>
YT Saver is a software that supports downloading Video, Audio, Playlist from 10,000+ websites, Convert Video to MP4, MOV, AAC, WAV and more. YT Saver is a powerful downloader that allows you to save video and audio for free. The output format of the high-speed converter is high-quality MP4, MP3. Fully compatible with iPhone, iPad, iTunes, iMovie, Android Phone and more.
Supported Input Formats:
	Video: MP4, M4V, 3GP, MPEG, DAT, AVI, ASF, WMV, VOB, MKV, FLV, 3GS, 3G2, F4V, WEBM, TS,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Easy System Utility Pro 1.1.49</title><pubDate> Fri, 22 Aug 2025 18:58:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easy-system-utility-pro-12380.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easy-system-utility-pro-12380.html
</guid><description>
Easy System Utility Pro is a powerful, all-in-one program designed for Windows 10 and 11 users. This versatile tool should be your primary choice to improve your computing experience ! This is the complete version with additional and enhanced features. It will help you easily determine your computer's hardware specifications with a system overview. You can view the operating system, CPU model, GPU, Memory, Motherboard, Network and even drivers.
It also supports launching programs,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Synchredible Professional 9.000</title><pubDate> Fri, 22 Aug 2025 18:53:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-synchredible-professional-1923.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-synchredible-professional-1923.html
</guid><description>
Synchredible Professional is the most advanced version help synchronize the folder and your drive quickly and easily. Whether it is a single file or an entire drive - Synchredible Professional will synchronize, copy and save them for you. The software guide will assist you to identify the work that is scheduled in advance or be done through the USB connection. This way, you can keep your files in sync - automatically.
In the past years, the advanced technology of the us in Synchredible...
</description></item><item><title>Download Rambox 2.5.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 22 Aug 2025 18:53:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rambox-1139.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rambox-1139.html
</guid><description>
Rambox is the app to email and messaging, open source, cross-platform and combine multiple web applications into a single interface. Rambox allows users to use a number of web services most commonly used to support the messaging feature and email editor, and displays the notification when the service has new messages through the main window simple and easy to use.
Instead of using several apps or have to use the web browser, you can access and manage all of the online services of from a...
</description></item><item><title>Download RegistryChangesView 1.31</title><pubDate> Fri, 22 Aug 2025 18:52:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-registrychangesview-1920.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-registrychangesview-1920.html
</guid><description>
RegistryChangesView lets you snap Windows Registry and then compare it with a snapshot of other Registry, with the Registry current or files, the Registry is saved in the shadow copy created by Windows. When you compare 2 snapshots of the registry, you can see the exact changes to be made in the register between 2 snapshots and arbitrary changes of the register into the file .reg standard of RegEdit.
RegistryChangesView - Compare Register Registry
RegistryChangesView doesn't require...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ultimate Power Assistant 1.1.22</title><pubDate> Fri, 22 Aug 2025 18:51:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ultimate-power-assistant-12372.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ultimate-power-assistant-12372.html
</guid><description>
Ultimate Power Assistant provides you with an efficient and easy way to manage your computer's power settings and tasks. With this tool, you can schedule and apply various power options in Windows.
Main features
	Shut down when download completes: Turn off your computer after your favorite game launcher or web browser completes the download. You no longer have to leave your PC running for hours wasting electricity!
	Change Power Plan when certain programs are detected: Launch a...
</description></item><item><title>Download HE - Hardware Read and Write Utility 1.25.08.21</title><pubDate> Fri, 22 Aug 2025 18:51:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-he-hardware-read-and-write-utility-4287.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-he-hardware-read-and-write-utility-4287.html
</guid><description>
HE - Hardware Read and Write Utility is a powerful utility intended for hardware engineer, engineer, BIOS developer, driver, engineer, QA engineers, performance test engineers, diagnostic, etc., this utility access almost all the computer hardware, including PCI (PCI Express), index / Data, PCI, memory, index memory / Data space I / O, Index I / O / Data, Super I / O, DIMM SPD, CPU The registers MSR, screen, SMART, physical area of the hard drive identification data, ATA, dump tables ACPI...
</description></item><item><title>Download UltraSearch Professional 4.8.2.1182</title><pubDate> Fri, 22 Aug 2025 18:50:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ultrasearch-professional-10252.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ultrasearch-professional-10252.html
</guid><description>
UltraSearch Professional is the professional version that helps you find your files and documents on all connected hard drives and network drives. Search by file type, document content, or file properties. Take back your valuable time and let UltraSearch do the searching for you.
UltraSearch Professional does not maintain an index stored on your hard disk. It achieves speed by working directly on the Master File Table (MFT) of NTFS partitions. So it even identifies NTFS hardlinks. That...
</description></item><item><title>Download MassTube 2026 v21.0.0.155 Ultra</title><pubDate> Fri, 22 Aug 2025 18:50:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-masstube-plus-461.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-masstube-plus-461.html
</guid><description>
MassTube Plus is a small utility used to download the favorite videos of you on youtube on your computer. This is a software compact, has a simple design with few options to download videos fastest. The you complete peace of mind because the software is easy to use, built exclusively for a single goal: to retrieve the video file from YouTube, so it doesn't pack the other useful features such as search engine integrated and a download audio file.
MassTube can work with multiple output...
</description></item><item><title>Download EF Mailbox Manager 25.10</title><pubDate> Fri, 22 Aug 2025 18:49:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ef-mailbox-manager-3212.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ef-mailbox-manager-3212.html
</guid><description>
EF Mailbox Manager can manage as many POP3 accounts as you want. To check periodically, polling time can be set separately for each account. You can check for new messages on the server and / or delete messages on the server or download the message at the local computer for further use.
Email downloaded will be saved in the text file ascii and is stored in a mailbox. If you use Outlook Express or any E-Mail program any other automatically open attachments, you should open the message...
</description></item><item><title>Download Synchredible 9.000</title><pubDate> Fri, 22 Aug 2025 18:49:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-synchredible-53.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-synchredible-53.html
</guid><description>
Synchredible is an easy to use tool to synchronize folders and files. It provides a wizard interface lets you set up the sync job, select files to exclude, schedule the job to execute automatically, and more.Additional features include support for network and external drives, check CRC32, and more.
Synchredible - synchronization of folders and files
Among other things, you can use the filter for the file type specific data synchronization according to the time or routine deletion of...
</description></item></channel></rss>