<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 03:37:39 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 03:37:39 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download SoundVolumeView 2.50</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 23:42:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-soundvolumeview-2695.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-soundvolumeview-2695.html
</guid><description>
SoundVolumeView is a simple tool for Windows Vista / 7/8/2008/10, displays general information and current volume levels for all components sound activity on your system and allows you to mute and unmute them instantly. SoundVolumeView also allows you to save audio configuration to a file, containing the current volume level status and mute / unmute of all audio components, as well as the audio devices to default, then upload the same file to restore exactly the same file volume levels and...
</description></item><item><title>Download CapCut PC 7.8.0.3263</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 23:42:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capcut-pc-9995.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capcut-pc-9995.html
</guid><description>
CapCut PC is a simple video editing tool that you can freely use anywhere. You can create videos on your browser, desktop and laptop, or on your phone. Versatile editing, magical AI tools, team collaboration, and built-in assets. Create videos in a whole new way.
You can edit videos based on editing the timeline, in the process you can add different elements and effects to the video to give the best effect to your work. It is a simple and intuitive set of editing tools and effects that...
</description></item><item><title>Download Drive SnapShot 1.50.0.1816</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 23:40:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-drive-snapshot-701.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-drive-snapshot-701.html
</guid><description>
Drive SnapShot is a backup software, Restore disk, including operating system, installed programs, your data and all security attributes - while windows is running and you continue to work. With Drive SnapShot you backup partition or hard drive and it can also create disk image of your system. If a disaster occurs (a virus, trojan or the fixed hard disk), the recover complete and accurate your system will be able to accomplish after only a few minutes. The image file can be mounted as...
</description></item><item><title>Download Reallusion Cartoon Animator 5.34.4905.1 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 23:39:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reallusion-crazytalk-animator-643.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reallusion-crazytalk-animator-643.html
</guid><description>
Reallusion Cartoon Animator (formerly known as CrazyTalk Animator) is a software to create animated simple, easy with transitions, visual effects, 2D animate. With CTA3, anyone can immediately bring back images, logo or property based by applying the effects of elastic motion. About the character, CTA3 is built with the template character 2D motion library has a value, the edit skeleton 2D powerful, puppet face and tool sync the audio to give the user control over great when creating...
</description></item><item><title>Download Atlantis Word Processor 5.0.0.17</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 23:38:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-atlantis-word-processor-585.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-atlantis-word-processor-585.html
</guid><description>
Atlantis Word Processor is a word processor app with features format, standard text, autocorrect, and spell check.  Atlantis is a word processor in accordance with most of the tasks handled daily text. The interface is very easy to use and offers the toolbars, hotkeys and sound effects thanh can customize (can turn off). It includes a clip library for quick access to the text or images used regular preview, font format and many other features aimed at improving the process of your...
</description></item><item><title>Download MiniTool Power Data Recovery Business Technician 12.8 Boot ISO</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 23:38:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minitool-power-data-recovery-business-technician-5660.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minitool-power-data-recovery-business-technician-5660.html
</guid><description>
MiniTool Power Data Recovery is a file recovery software and read-only data recovery software. Power data recovery software can help you recover all your data regardless of whether it was lost due to accidental deletion, formatting, repartition, system crash, or virus attack. Power Data Recovery can regionally scan your device by region to restore what's left on your device. Power Data Recovery provides a deep scan module that can scan and analyze raw data formats including Microsoft...
</description></item><item><title>Download iFoneTool EasyDown 2.4.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 23:37:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ifonetool-easydown-14405.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ifonetool-easydown-14405.html
</guid><description>
iFoneTool EasyDown is a download software for Windows that allows you to save videos and music from platforms like YouTube, TikTok, Spotify, and many others, with features such as batch downloading and support for high-quality formats. It's compatible with major platforms including YouTube, NicoNico, Apple Music, Spotify, TikTok, and Twitter. It supports batch downloading of playlists, channels, individual songs, albums, podcasts, and more. High quality, lossless downloads, fast saving of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Avanquest Photo Explosion Deluxe 5.10.31420</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 23:37:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avanquest-photo-explosion-premier-3259.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avanquest-photo-explosion-premier-3259.html
</guid><description>
Avanquest Photo Explosion Premier is a powerful application, the set of features powerful editing, special effects spectacular and the project professional quality photos all in a photo editing software, fast, and fun! Photo Exploding Premier help work with digital photography, your easier than ever with user interface is improved and the process working faster to repair, enhance &amp;amp; edit photos, and more.
Avanquest Photo Explosion Premier - edit, add photo effects
The features and...
</description></item><item><title>Download DA-HelpCreator 2.8.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 23:29:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-da-helpcreator-698.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-da-helpcreator-698.html
</guid><description>
DA-HelpCreator is a software editor help, help you create documents and online help quick, easy most. DA-HelpCreator help you create help file in the CHM format is Windows or frequently asked questions page for the internet and allows you to start quickly and focus on the essentials: content.
Input is done according to the syntax simple markup. Layout and content are separated. You can choose from the templates can be customized to output to HTML or help formats to be compiled (CHM)...
</description></item><item><title>Download Syncthing 2.0.13</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 23:28:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncthing-2115.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncthing-2115.html
</guid><description>
Syncthing is synchronization service, cloud and open and non-focus allows you to share and sync files with other computers and gives you full control how to share your data and who can access it. Syncthing does not store your data in any other place, there is no server side Tuesday how to join. In addition, all the communication is secured by TLS and every button is determined by the certificate the strength of the encryption. Only computers that have explicitly allowed can connect with...
</description></item><item><title>Download InvokeAI 6.10.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 23:28:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-invokeai-11059.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-invokeai-11059.html
</guid><description>
InvokeAI is a leading creation engine designed to leverage the capabilities of Steady Diffusion models. It enables professionals, artists, and enthusiasts to create and produce visual media using advanced AI-driven technologies. This platform offers a powerful and user-friendly Web Interface.
Incorporating the most advanced open source research, Invoke empowers creative professionals to enhance their work, streamline workflows, and get work done in seconds. Use styles, renderings,...
</description></item><item><title>Download TablePlus 6.8</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 23:26:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tableplus-2774.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tableplus-2774.html
</guid><description>
TablePlus is a software management database powerful and effective. In fact, the management and organization database with the software is extremely easy. Thanks to the powerful features and simple design, software, database management, data has become faster and more efficient. Benefits of using this program are many different options to keep them safe for database of you. These include authentication, multi-step, libssh original and TLS to encrypt your connection
TablePlus -...
</description></item><item><title>Download IBExpert Developer Studio 2025.12.19.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 23:25:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ibexpert-developer-studio-14247.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ibexpert-developer-studio-14247.html
</guid><description>
IBExpert Developer Studio is a comprehensive integrated development environment (IDE), designed primarily for the professional development and administration of Firebird and InterBase databases. It combines IBExpert and several modules to provide a complete toolkit for database professionals. The main components include an IBExpert IDE with visual editors for all database objects, a SQL editor and script executor, a debugger for stored procedures and triggers, a query builder, a powerful...
</description></item><item><title>Download LDPlayer 9.1.95.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 22:26:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ldplayer-2331.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ldplayer-2331.html
</guid><description>
LDPlayer is an Android emulator that allows users to play games and run applications on Windows computers. LDPlayer supports heavy gaming, running chat applications, editing photos, videos, and many other Android applications. LDPlayer is compatible with Android 5.1 and above, supporting multitasking for an experience that is not inferior to that of using on Mobile.
Installation is a simple and quick process that does not require any special attention from you, there are more. settings,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Image To PDF 4.2.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 22:26:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-image-to-pdf-10750.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-image-to-pdf-10750.html
</guid><description>
Image To PDF is free software that can convert any image into a PDF file. It supports the most commonly used image formats including: BMP, WBMP, JPEG, PNG, TIF, GIF, PSD, ICO, PCX, TGA, JP2, etc. Simple and intuitive interface. It is a simple application dedicated to any user who wants to quickly integrate image files into PDF documents. Without a doubt, there will not be any problems with the resulting product as long as you adjust the settings to suit your needs and/or...
</description></item><item><title>Download Inno Setup Compiler 6.7.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 22:25:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-inno-setup-compiler-2655.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-inno-setup-compiler-2655.html
</guid><description>
Inno Setup Compiler is a system installed based on free software created by Delphi by Jordan Russell. The first version was released in 1997. QuickStart of Inno Setup include main Inno Setup and also includes an option to install the script editor Inno Script Studio. The script editor is not official and is not mandatory for general use, but help Inno Setup easier to use.
Inno Setup Compiler - software create file setup.exe
The features of Inno Setup Compiler
	Support for every...
</description></item><item><title>Download TickTick Premium 8.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 20:35:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ticktick-premium-7770.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ticktick-premium-7770.html
</guid><description>
TickTick Premium is a task management application that helps users stay organized, it is very suitable for educators and students with many incentives. TickTick turns your Windows PC device into a flexible, easy-to-use and highly efficient office platform. Join millions of people to capture ideas, organize their lives, and do something creative every day.
Whether there are work related tasks or personal goals, TickTick is here to help you manage all your to-dos. With five different...
</description></item><item><title>Download Greywater Ultimate Mailer 4.9.9.5</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 20:32:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-greywater-ultimate-mailer-14441.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-greywater-ultimate-mailer-14441.html
</guid><description>
Ultimate Mailer is a powerful and flexible email application built for sending large-scale messages with high accuracy and control. It allows you to send customized messages to individual recipients or large numbers of recipients, while seamlessly handling SMTP servers and proxy connections in the background.
Designed for advanced campaigns, Ultimate Mailer makes it easy to customize each message for a recipient without being limited by scale. Its robust system is built to ensure high...
</description></item><item><title>Download MiniTool Power Data Recovery Personal / Business 12.8 All Editions</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 18:58:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minitool-power-data-recovery-1168.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minitool-power-data-recovery-1168.html
</guid><description>
MiniTool Power Data Recovery is software data recovery from hard drives, SD, Smartmedia, compact Flash, memory Cards and other media. Power Data Recovery recovers files and data lost due to random erase, format, attack virus, breakdown when creating the partition or download, turn off the computer, format the storage media, or use FDISK, damage the boot sector MBR,...
MiniTool Power Data Recovery - data recovery
Features of MiniTool Power Data Recovery
	Recover data after accidental...
</description></item><item><title>Download reaConverter Pro 8.0.176</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 18:58:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html
</guid><description>
reaConverter Pro is software image processing feature with batch conversion and image editing periodically becomes simple. eaConverter also provide command line utilities allow you to process images automatically, thus helping you shorten the time for other work.
reaConverter Pro integrated powerful tool of Uber with many great features. It provides advanced solutions to process and adjust images. Management of the conversion process the base image with the latest version of...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDQ Inventory 19.6.29.0 Enterprise</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 18:57:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdq-inventory-1468.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdq-inventory-1468.html
</guid><description>
PDQ Inventory is a software application to manage your system. This software will be able to manage your system by scanning the Windows operating system of you to provide information hardware, software, and configuration for the Windows operating system in your your tools. The tools available in this software helps you can scan the computer correctly.
In addition, the software PDQ Inventory can give you very detailed information. This software application is one of the management...
</description></item><item><title>Download iTop Data Recovery Pro 6.0.0.924</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 18:57:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-itop-data-recovery-pro-7139.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-itop-data-recovery-pro-7139.html
</guid><description>
iTop Data Recovery Pro is a powerful data recovery tool that speeds up scanning and data recovery processes due to iTop's unique recovery algorithm. In just a few minutes, you can get your deleted files back perfectly as expected. Besides, Scan options are diverse for different needs. You can quickly find your lost data by Location and File Type.
iTop Data Recovery allows you to easily perform file recovery without limitations. More than 1000 file formats are supported. Meanwhile, this...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDQ Deploy 19.6.29.0 Enterprise</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 18:56:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdq-deploy-1469.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdq-deploy-1469.html
</guid><description>
PDQ Deploy Enterprise is an application to keep the Windows PC and the programs installed on it. Software PDQ Deploy helps you to connect multiple patch or a windows app (.exe, .msi) with multiple operating systems. The deployment software can be install, delete, run script, reboot, copy the file, sliding mode, send messages, etc.
PDQ Deploy Enterprise
Features of PDQ Deploy Enterprise
	Send notifications (alerts) via email
	Run the script as popular as .vbs, .reg .bat and .ps1
	Run...
</description></item><item><title>Download Chaos Corona 14.1 for 3ds Max 2018 - 2026</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 18:55:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chaos-corona-2986.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chaos-corona-2986.html
</guid><description>
Corona Renderer is the name of the plug-in technique and dedicated powerful, but have high functionality for Autodesk software 3ds Max. Plug before you is a standalone application known to the CLI. In addition, users can use this tool to promote their business on software Maxon Cinema 4D is also used. The manufacturers of this product believe that working with this tool is very simple and in fact you only need to press the activities rendered. With this tool easier than ever can do the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Chaos Corona 14.1 for Cinema 4D R17 - 2026</title><pubDate> Tue, 06 Jan 2026 18:55:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-corona-renderer-for-cinema-4d-6499.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-corona-renderer-for-cinema-4d-6499.html
</guid><description>
Corona Renderer  is the name of a powerful, but highly functional engineering and dedicated plug-in for Autodesk 3ds Max software. Plug in before you are a known CLI standalone application. In addition, users can use this tool to advertise their business on Maxon Cinema 4D software which is also used. The manufacturers of this product firmly believe that working with this tool is very simple, and in fact you just need to hit render the rendering operations. With this tool it's easier...
</description></item></channel></rss>