<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 20:13:04 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 20:13:04 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Adobe Lightroom Classic 2026 v15.2.0 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Sat, 21 Feb 2026 21:14:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-photoshop-lightroom-classic-0004-734.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-photoshop-lightroom-classic-0004-734.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Photoshop Lightroom Classic is a desktop-optimized photo editing and organizing software. Lightroom Classic gives you powerful one-click tools and advanced controls to make your photos look great. Easily organize all your photos on your desktop and share them in a variety of ways.
In addition, Lightroom Classic has a powerful import process that allows users to preview images before importing. It supports many camera raw formats and includes a database system for efficient photo...
</description></item><item><title>Download 4K Video Downloader Plus 26.0.5</title><pubDate> Sat, 21 Feb 2026 21:13:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-video-downloader-617.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-video-downloader-617.html
</guid><description>
4K Video Downloader Plus is software support downloads video, audio and subtitles from YouTube with high quality up to 4K. Download process video is very simple: just copy the video link from your browser and click Paste Url. Done! If you want that video on your iPad, iPhone or other device, we have protected you.
The feature on 4K Video Downloader Plus
	Download entire playlists and channels from YouTube and save them in MP4, MKV, M4A, MP3, FLV, 3G, create a file .m3u for...
</description></item><item><title>Download pdfFactory Pro 9.23</title><pubDate> Sat, 21 Feb 2026 16:12:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdffactory-pro-277.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdffactory-pro-277.html
</guid><description>
pdfFactory Pro is software to create PDF files according to standards in a simple and secure documents secure. pdfFactory Pro on taiwebs.com that support encryption (40 or 128bit) and control access to the PDF file.
pdfFactory Pro has all the features of pdfFactory and adds bookmarks, job order, title a letter and the email function automatically. Only pdfFactory allows printing to paper or PDF without printing twice. Acrobat is not needed for the printing. Increases the convenience of...
</description></item><item><title>Download FinePrint 12.23</title><pubDate> Sat, 21 Feb 2026 16:11:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fineprint-276.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fineprint-276.html
</guid><description>
FinePrint is a software support you work in text saves paper and increases the lifespan of your printer. FinePrint is a software connected printer, you can print 4 or 8 pages file on the computer on a page of paper that still ensure the font is clear, easy to read.
With FinePrint works for you, the incidents of printing annoyances will disappear. Below are just some examples of incidents in which FinePrint can fix. Read more part of our Business for the benefit of the FinePrint in the...
</description></item><item><title>Download 4K YouTube to MP3 26.0.5</title><pubDate> Sat, 21 Feb 2026 16:10:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-youtube-to-mp3-622.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-youtube-to-mp3-622.html
</guid><description>
4K YouTube to MP3 is a software to convert video youtube to mp3 quickly and easily by the manipulation drag-and-drop simple. With 4K YouTube to MP3 you just drag and drop the link to the favorite songs of you and get the MP3 files to your computer, as easy as that. Transfer songs directly to iPod, iPhone and iPad everywhere you go. No install annoying and complex to solve, just a clean interface, user friendly and functional.
When using 4K YouTube to MP3, users will get the playlists,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Windows Server 2025 LTSC 24H2 Build 26100.32370 (x64) MSDN</title><pubDate> Sat, 21 Feb 2026 16:09:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-server-2025-12851.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-server-2025-12851.html
</guid><description>
Windows Server 2025 is a server operating system based on Windows 11, version 24H2 on the Long Term Servicing Channel (LTSC). It improves security, performance, and integration with Azure and cloud technologies. As an LTSC release, Windows Server 2025 includes Desktop Experience and Server Core installation options for the Datacenter and Standard editions. Security features that are part of the current Windows 11 release (24H2) are now available in Windows Server 2025.
Key...
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow WinIcon 3.2.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 21 Feb 2026 16:08:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winicon-maker-9761.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winicon-maker-9761.html
</guid><description>
WinIcon Maker is a simple application to create beautiful Windows icons (ico files) from JPG or PNG images. Just upload your own photo, resize and crop it, convert it to a shape you like, add borders and shadows, and save it as a PNG image or Windows icon.
The .ICO file format is defined and created by Microsoft corporation, .ico files are widely used in Windows operating systems including Windows 7, Windows 10, Windows 11, etc. On the Windows desktop, each application shortcut has an...
</description></item><item><title>Download AdwCleaner 8.7.1.626</title><pubDate> Sat, 21 Feb 2026 16:07:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-malwarebytes-adwcleaner-1132.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-malwarebytes-adwcleaner-1132.html
</guid><description>
Malwarebytes AdwCleaner is ad blocking software on the browser, which helps you completely remove the annoying stuff every time Internet access. The software is completely free for users, also AdwCleaner can remove unwanted software or virus on your computer.
When on the website is not secure, appearance various types of advertising PUP. Very can will appear on the website contain malicious code that when you click on the sensitive area, the virus infected computer very likely to happen....
</description></item><item><title>Download Windows 11 Pro Trimed 26H2 Build 28020.1546 (Super Lite)</title><pubDate> Sat, 21 Feb 2026 16:06:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-11-pro-trimed-9383.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-11-pro-trimed-9383.html
</guid><description>
Windows 11 Pro is the professional version of the Windows 11 operating system, which is the latest version of Microsoft's Windows operating system. It is designed to meet the needs of business and institutional users, providing enhanced features and capabilities beyond the standard consumer version.
Windows 11 Pro Trimed is a tweaked and deprecated version of Windows 11 to make it easier to work on more hardware, easier to operate and install. This one is for those who think MPB is too...
</description></item><item><title>Download Visual Studio Code 1.109.5</title><pubDate> Sat, 21 Feb 2026 16:05:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-visual-studio-code-3182.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-visual-studio-code-3182.html
</guid><description>
Visual Studio Code is the encryption tool of Microsoft has met most of the needs of the developer. Environment this encoding was introduced to compete with other products such as Sublime and Nodepad ++ . Microsoft, in its new product, has not been released in many years, has provided many features in a simple environment. In addition to the familiar with a dozen programming languages, the syntax and get to know coding language as soon as be encrypted and allows for syntax highlighting, it...
</description></item><item><title>Download Smadav Pro 2026 v15.7</title><pubDate> Sat, 21 Feb 2026 16:05:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-smadav-pro-2443.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-smadav-pro-2443.html
</guid><description>
Smadav is an antivirus powerful virus for Windows operating system. Like any program anti-virus any other, this program will provide insurance on your system in order to prevent attacks and security threats. In addition to detecting viruses and malware like worms, Trojans, advertising, spammers, ransomware, etc., this program has good ability to protect and detect all type of virus Autorun. These viruses are often found in flash memory and storage media, mobile. You attach and copy the...
</description></item><item><title>Download NetSpeedTray 1.2.5 + Portable</title><pubDate> Sat, 21 Feb 2026 15:57:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-netspeedtray-14068.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-netspeedtray-14068.html
</guid><description>
NetSpeedTray is a lightweight, open source network monitor for Windows that displays upload/download speeds directly on the Taskbar with a native look and feel.
Designed to blend seamlessly with Windows 10/11 user interface. Includes intelligent detection of light and dark themes on the taskbar to ensure text is always visible. Sits quietly in the system tray without hogging resources. Features "Dynamic Update Rate" that automatically reduces update frequency when the network is idle to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mountain Duck 5.2.0.28648</title><pubDate> Sat, 21 Feb 2026 15:55:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mountain-duck-4115.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mountain-duck-4115.html
</guid><description>
Mountain Duck allows you to mount servers and cloud storage as the disk on the computer to your desk. Open the file remotely with any application and act as on a local disk without the need to synchronize the file. Based on the platform open source solid of Cyberduck, all of the main protocols are supported to connect to any server you want, including FTP, SFTP, WebDAV, Azure Cloud Storage, Amazon S3, Google Cloud Storage, Google Drive, Dropbox, Backblaze B2 &amp;amp; OpenStack Swift. Transfer...
</description></item><item><title>Download K-Lite Codec Pack Update 19.5.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 21 Feb 2026 15:55:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-update-5145.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-update-5145.html
</guid><description>
K-Lite Codec Pack Update is the update of the set of codecs and related tools. Codec stands for Compressor-decompressor. Codec is necessary to encode and decode (play) audio and video. K-Lite Codec Pack Update is designed as a user-friendly solution with users to play all movie files your. With Codec Pack K-Lite, you can play 99% of all the movies found on your computer. A number of packages codec is not friendly with computers, as they tend to slow down Windows, break down multimedia...
</description></item><item><title>Download SysTools EML Viewer Pro Plus 5.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 21 Feb 2026 15:54:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-systools-eml-viewer-pro-plus-9676.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-systools-eml-viewer-pro-plus-9676.html
</guid><description>
SysTools EML Viewer Pro Plus is a software tool developed by SysTools that allows users to view and manage EML (Email Messages) files. EML files are commonly used to store individual emails and can be created by various email clients such as Microsoft Outlook, Mozilla Thunderbird, and Windows Live Mail.
Features of SysTools EML Viewer Pro Plus
	Allows analysis of damaged or corrupted EML files without risk
	Just install and access the software in multiple languages
	Application that...
</description></item><item><title>Download Chess Assistant Pro 26 v12.00 Build 1</title><pubDate> Sat, 21 Feb 2026 15:53:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chess-assistant-pro-1506.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chess-assistant-pro-1506.html
</guid><description>
Chess Assistant Pro is a unique tool to manage the game and database, chess, playing chess through the Internet, analyzing games or playing chess against the computer. Chess Assistant 19 includes the program, the martial play, the flag mode, the opening Encyclopedia, a system powerful search mode, Tree unique database of about 7.077.000 games in total.
Chess Assistant Pro - help play chess
Houdini 6 PRO, chess program strongest in the world, continue to surge the impression created by...
</description></item><item><title>Download Windows Server 2022 LTSC 21H2 Build 20348.4773 (x64) MSDN</title><pubDate> Sat, 21 Feb 2026 15:52:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-server-2022-12850.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-server-2022-12850.html
</guid><description>
Windows Server 2022 delivers advanced multi-layered protection, hybrid Azure-based capabilities, and a flexible application platform for the first time. This release also includes secure kernel features that help protect Windows Server hardware, firmware, and functionality from sophisticated security threats.
The new release also supports secure connections with several new features, including faster HTTPS connections with more secure encryption, industry-standard AES 256 encryption for...
</description></item><item><title>Download Macro Commander Pro+ 2.8.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 21 Feb 2026 15:51:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-macro-commander-pro-12815.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-macro-commander-pro-12815.html
</guid><description>
Macro Commander is an all-in-one data entry and desktop automation software. It is designed to empower users to easily create, manage, and trigger macros and scripts to automate manual, repetitive tasks quickly and error-free. Its clean user interface allows for quick and easy creation and organization of macros either manually or using the built-in macro recorder.
While Macro Commander offers powerful data entry features to quickly and easily fill in data in other applications, it also...
</description></item><item><title>Download PentaLogix CAMMaster 11.24.76</title><pubDate> Sat, 21 Feb 2026 15:39:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pentalogix-cammaster-5559.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pentalogix-cammaster-5559.html
</guid><description>
CAMMaster Designer is CAM software of choice by the Designer for the most demanding jobs. Experience the industry's best CAD companion to get your work done. The disinfection process is fast with all the features available in this package. Exploiting Netlist and DRC sets industry standards. Basically, CamMaster provides many functions depending on the relevant needs of the user. It also provides nearly five free technical support. Furthermore, net list comparison and class comparison make...
</description></item><item><title>Download Shortcuts Search And Replace 2.7.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 21 Feb 2026 15:37:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-shortcuts-search-and-replace-12360.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-shortcuts-search-and-replace-12360.html
</guid><description>
Shortcuts Search And Replace allows you to search for a shortcut's target path, working directory, arguments, and icon location content. You can override shortcut target paths, working folders, arguments, and icon location content - this will be useful when moving portable applications to another drive or another folder. It can also search for dead links, to resolve or remove them (resolve multiple times/remove with one click). You also have the option to copy selected or all files to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ocenaudio 3.17.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 21 Feb 2026 15:36:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ocenaudio-837.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ocenaudio-837.html
</guid><description>
Ocenaudio: software for windows, this is the sound editing easy, fast and powerful. ocenaudio is a program for audio editing multi-platform, easy to use, fast and functional. This is the ideal software for those who need to edit and analyze audio files.
Ocenaudio - editor powerful audio for windows
This software is based on Ocen Framework , a powerful library developed to simplify and standardize the development of application analysis and sound processing on many platforms.
Features...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinScript 1.4.9</title><pubDate> Sat, 21 Feb 2026 15:36:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winscript-12800.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winscript-12800.html
</guid><description>
WinScript is an open source tool built to help you build custom scripts for Windows 10 and 11. It includes scripts for debugging, privacy, performance, and more, along with the ability to install all your favorite apps with just one click.
Features
	Debloat: Remove Windows bloatware, CoPilot, Edge, OneDrive, and other pre-installed features preset.
	Privacy: Disable Windows and 3rd party data collection, tracking, app access, and telemetry.
	Performance: Set background services to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Playnite 10.51</title><pubDate> Sat, 21 Feb 2026 15:35:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-playnite-6972.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-playnite-6972.html
</guid><description>
Playnite is an open-source video game library manager and manager with support for third-party libraries such as Steam, GOG, Origin, Battle.net and Uplay. Includes supporting the game, providing a unified interface for your game. With Playnite, you can comfortably enter the game from Steam, Battle.net, Origin, GOG and Uplay services, including uninstalled games.
You have three options to view when using Playnite. You also have the custom game option or add any game or program with...
</description></item><item><title>Download AI Offline OCR Scanner Pro 1.0.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 21 Feb 2026 13:01:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ai-offline-ocr-scanner-pro-14574.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ai-offline-ocr-scanner-pro-14574.html
</guid><description>
Stop manually retyping documents. AI Offline OCR Scanner Pro uses advanced Artificial Intelligence to recognize text in images and documents with high accuracy. Designed for security and high performance, this application works completely offline on your computer—ensuring your sensitive data never leaves your device.
Key Features:
100% Offline Security: Unlike cloud-based converters, your images are processed locally. No data is uploaded to the internet, ensuring the safety of...
</description></item><item><title>Download AIM Toolkit 20251223</title><pubDate> Sat, 21 Feb 2026 12:48:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aim-toolkit-14573.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aim-toolkit-14573.html
</guid><description>
AIM Toolkit is a Windows utility used to create ultra-fast RAM drives and mount disk image files (ISO, IMG, BIN, VHD, HDD, etc.) as virtual drives.
Explanation of RAM drives: It is part of working memory (RAM) and is integrated as a particularly fast data storage medium. Such RAM drives offer significantly higher read/write speeds, even compared to SSDs.
AIM Toolkit (Arsenal Image Mounter Toolkit) is the successor to "ImDisk Toolkit".
Features of AIM Toolkit:
Create RAM drives
	Use...
</description></item></channel></rss>