<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 17:35:38 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 17:35:38 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download MSI Afterburner 4.6.6.16757</title><pubDate> Wed, 01 Oct 2025 19:00:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-msi-afterburner-1075.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-msi-afterburner-1075.html
</guid><description>
MSI Afterburner is overclocking software to speed up computer graphics card to increase gaming performance, support for spin off video card downloads. MSI Afterburner is a utility graphics card that supports users to track the status of the GPU and use the GPU with the maximum performance. Core application MSI Afterburner is based on RivaTuner - software overclocking graphics card top. The program is designed to enhance the performance of the GPU and support multiple graphics cards MSI...
</description></item><item><title>Download Windows 11 Installation Assistant 1.4.19041.6448</title><pubDate> Wed, 01 Oct 2025 18:38:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-11-installation-assistant-6839.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-11-installation-assistant-6839.html
</guid><description>
Windows 11 Installation Assistant (or Windows 11 Update Assistant) is a free tool from Microsoft designed to prepare your computer for an upgrade or update. update Windows 10 by checking for compatibility issues and downloading all necessary files to start beginning of settings.
Although Windows 11 Installation Assistant has built-in tools to check your computer's compatibility with Windows 11, but you can still use the tool PC Health Check to see if your computer has any problems....
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft Support and Recovery Assistant 17.01.3658.000</title><pubDate> Wed, 01 Oct 2025 18:37:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-support-and-recovery-assistant-4821.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-support-and-recovery-assistant-4821.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft Support and Recovery Assistant is a client to enable customers of Microsoft troubleshooting and diagnosis of incidents, their relation to the application OS &amp;amp; Windows. It can help you troubleshoot, install, uninstall, activate and more. Open the app and click on the Microsoft products you need to help.
Current it can fix the problem Office, Office 365, Outlook and Windows. If it can't troubleshoot for you, it will propose the next steps and help you to contact the support...
</description></item><item><title>Download Activation Program 1.13</title><pubDate> Wed, 01 Oct 2025 18:37:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-activation-program-12767.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-activation-program-12767.html
</guid><description>
Activation Program is a Windows and Office activator from Ratiborus for Windows 7 to 11. The program is created based on the MASSGRAVE code.
What advantages does this method have over other activation methods?
It offers the most advantages for activating older versions of Windows, such as Windows 7 to 8.1, as it can permanently activate any version of the versions This without modifying the Windows system boot process or executable files. This is the only public activator that provides...
</description></item><item><title>Download MuseScore 4.6.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 01 Oct 2025 18:31:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musescore-2857.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musescore-2857.html
</guid><description>
MuseScore is the tool score for Windows, macOS and Linux, can compare with Finale and Sibelius, support multiple file formats and input methods. It is released as free software and open source under The GNU general public License.
MuseScore - The application composer
Features of MuseScore
	Design WYSIWYG, notes are entered on a "virtual notice"
	TrueType fonts for printing and display allows split ratio high quality for all sizes
	Enter notes easily and quickly
	Many editing...
</description></item><item><title>Download Franzis SHARPEN #6 professional 6.25.04285</title><pubDate> Wed, 01 Oct 2025 18:28:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-franzis-sharpen-projects-6680.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-franzis-sharpen-projects-6680.html
</guid><description>
Franzis SHARPEN Projects is a professional software for the sharpness of the image, it helps you to rescue images affected by fuzzy motion or targeting specific areas to enhance the intensity, fix the sensor, all of this with just a few clicks.
With automatic sharpness and 45 pre-installed settings, you will have almost perfect results without losing a lot of time. A suitable automatic installation is provided for every situation and every texture. However, there are also some manual...
</description></item><item><title>Download Nitro Pro Enterprise 14.41.1.3</title><pubDate> Wed, 01 Oct 2025 18:27:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nitro-pdf-pro-34.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nitro-pdf-pro-34.html
</guid><description>
Nitro Pro Enterprise create, edit and convert PDF files easily with the help of the visual program this also allows users to accurately extract text from PDF files thanks to OCR function of it. Nitro Pro is one of the software solutions, create and edit PDF most advanced, providing basically all the tools you need to help you in this area. Although it is called 'Professional', this app has been developed to target beginners and advanced users, so you won't feel too hard to use.
Direct...
</description></item><item><title>Download Nitro Pro 14.41.1.3 (x64) Retail</title><pubDate> Wed, 01 Oct 2025 18:27:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nitro-pro-379.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nitro-pro-379.html
</guid><description>
Nitro Pro is software that provides features to create, edit and convert PDF files or share PDF files standard.  This is a simple software, easy to understand and intuitive to use so you can work more efficiently. Nitro Pro you can share your files with others, regardless of whether they are using the platform or device, and Nitro Pro helps convert easily.
Nitro Pro convert one or multiple files into PDF with just one or two clicks. Re-use and re-use content based on the PDF with higher...
</description></item><item><title>Download ExpanDrive 2025.09.29</title><pubDate> Wed, 01 Oct 2025 18:26:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-expandrive-609.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-expandrive-609.html
</guid><description>
ExpanDrive is software sync cloud storage strong support BackBlaze B2, Google Team Drive, SMB / CIFS and new interface and easy user search file version, share links and much more.  ExpanDrive mapped network drives for macOS and Micosoft Windows connect with all the provide major cloud storage such as Dropbox, Google Drive, Google Team Drive, Amazon Drive, Box, OneDrive, OneDrive for Business, Sharepoint, Openstack Swift , BackBlaze B2, Amazon S3 or SFTP servers, FTP or WebDAV on your own...
</description></item><item><title>Download ChrisPC YTD Downloader MP3 Converter Pro 6.25.0929</title><pubDate> Wed, 01 Oct 2025 18:25:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-ytd-downloader-mp3-converter-pro-2767.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-ytd-downloader-mp3-converter-pro-2767.html
</guid><description>
ChrisPC YTD Downloader MP3 Converter Pro is a Windows software dedicated to download and convert YouTube videos to audio file MP3 high quality. ChrisPC YTD Downloader MP3 Converter is one of the few program convert YouTube to MP3 (if not unique) available in the market to help you have quality best sound in the YouTube video you want to download and convert to MP3.
A in what format is most commonly used for recording in this decade is the MP3 format and thus we store on our utility...
</description></item><item><title>Download NVIDIA App 11.0.5.266</title><pubDate> Wed, 01 Oct 2025 18:25:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nvidia-app-12646.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nvidia-app-12646.html
</guid><description>
NVIDIA App is an indispensable companion for PC gamers and creators. Make sure your PC is always updated with the latest NVIDIA drivers and technology. Optimize your games and apps with the new unified GPU control center, capture your favorite moments with powerful recording tools through in-game overlays, and explore new tools and features. Latest NVIDIA software.
The program consists of two main parts
	Game Ready Drivers: GeForce Game Ready Drivers are fine-tuned in collaboration...
</description></item><item><title>Download MiniTool Video Converter 4.5.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 01 Oct 2025 18:24:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minitool-video-converter-5358.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minitool-video-converter-5358.html
</guid><description>
MiniTool Video Converter is the most direct solution for converting audio and video files to a wide variety of formats. This free video converter is available to convert audio to video and convert video to audio. This free video converter supports over 1000 conversion formats including 4K / FHD / HD files MP4, MOV, MKV, AVI, WMV, M4V and audio formats like MP3, WAV, M4A, WMA High Quality, AAC, AC3.
MiniTool Video Converter allows you to convert batches of files at the same time. Just...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ahnenblatt 4.34.0.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 01 Oct 2025 18:24:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ahnenblatt-3844.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ahnenblatt-3844.html
</guid><description>
Ahnenblatt is a genealogy software full-featured, easy to use suitable for beginners and even pedigree has the experience to organize genealogy research by you. Use plausibility checks to find out the inaccuracies in your family and create the chart impressive with just a few mouse clicks.
Ahnenblatt - Create family tree,
Recently, there has been strong increase of the general interest of the public for genealogical tree. Users who desire to track their heritage have many tools at...
</description></item><item><title>Download DriversCloud 12.0.28.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 01 Oct 2025 18:23:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-driverscloud-6228.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-driverscloud-6228.html
</guid><description>
DriversCloud is a complex tool that helps you retrieve full data on your system configuration, both hardware and software, while simultaneously implementing additional maintenance tasks such as installing and updating drivers, tracking hard real-time or BSOD analysis. The incident. This tool does not only accurately detect your complete system configuration but also allows you to export this important data to PDF documents to allow you to easily share them online.
Not only did the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Fast File Encryptor 13.9.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 01 Oct 2025 18:23:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fast-file-encryptor-2606.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fast-file-encryptor-2606.html
</guid><description>
Fast File Encryptor is the encoder files fast designed for fast processing of the file very big. It can encrypt or decrypt files, contents of folders and contains a lot of additional tools. In addition, there is a tool responsible to completely remove files from the hard drive, you need it if you don't want to leave traces 100 percent in the system. You need to specify the password or key, then select the encryption method, remember remember everything, otherwise it will not work, then...
</description></item><item><title>Download FileLocator Pro 2022 Build 3535</title><pubDate> Wed, 01 Oct 2025 18:22:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-filelocator-pro-1056.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-filelocator-pro-1056.html
</guid><description>
FileLocator Pro is software manage files and search function the file quickly the software and data. FileLocator Pro helps you find things quickly. The unique feature of it allows the extraction of information in all file formats the most obscure.
FileLocator Pro - file Manager
The features of FileLocator Pro
	Search algorithm based on the C ++ multi-threading for ultra-fast
	Search for network drive by mapped drive or UNC paths
	Support regular expressions for file name and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Stardock Start11 2.5.5.4 Beta</title><pubDate> Wed, 01 Oct 2025 18:21:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stardock-start11-7029.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stardock-start11-7029.html
</guid><description>
Start11 is an application capable of customizing the Start Menu and Taskbar on Windows 11 and Windows 10. This is an application that allows users to customize Windows 11 to suit their preferences. his personal. Start11 will help you bring the new Start Menu of Windows 11 to Windows 10. And vice versa, Start11 also helps you to bring the Start Menu of Windows 10 to Windows 11.
Start11 also helps users bring some functions of Windows 10 to Windows 11 through customizing the Taskbar such...
</description></item><item><title>Download Abelssoft Easy PDF 2026 v7.01.66068</title><pubDate> Wed, 01 Oct 2025 18:21:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-abelssoft-easy-pdf-5981.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-abelssoft-easy-pdf-5981.html
</guid><description>
Abelssoft Easy PDF is software that helps you easily combine multiple PDF files, delete individual pages from PDF or separate pages from PDF. Anyone who can use a mouse can do these things a completely intuitive way with just a few clicks! The program has been designed to be easy to use, so users do not need to click through the complex menus to get results.
The features of Abelssoft Easy PDF
	With a drag and drop feature, you can add PDF files and merge them easily.
	Delete the...
</description></item><item><title>Download ExtraDisks Home 25.9.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 01 Oct 2025 18:21:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-extradisks-home-7758.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-extradisks-home-7758.html
</guid><description>
ExtraDisks is a set of tools for creating virtual disks on your computer physical drives that do not change and are not divided into additional partitions. The program contains tools for creating encrypted disks, file-based virtual disks and directory-based virtual disks. The current version includes the following tools: Encrypted Disks, Virtual Disks, Folder Disks, Startup Manager, System Tweaker.
Features of ExtraDisks
ExtraDisks: Encrypted Disk
This tool is used to create encrypted...
</description></item><item><title>Download PanFone Manager 1.3.3</title><pubDate> Wed, 01 Oct 2025 18:20:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-panfone-manager-6104.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-panfone-manager-6104.html
</guid><description>
PanFone Manager is an Android/iOS data management tool! Free management, transfer, backup, recovery and deletion of mobile image data on Windows PCs. A click to transmit music, videos, movies, television shows and other media files freely between iOS/Android devices and PCs without reducing the quality.
Features of PanFone Manager
	Music, photos, videos, contacts, etc. between PC and mobile phones.
	Music management, editing songs and removing duplicate tracks on iOS/Android...
</description></item><item><title>Download SweetScape 010 Editor 16.0.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 01 Oct 2025 18:19:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sweetscape-010-editor-1492.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sweetscape-010-editor-1492.html
</guid><description>
SweetScape 010 Editor is a text editor and hex editor professional is designed to quickly and easily edit any file or drive on your computer. Combine the easy to use interface with a complete set of editing tools, 010 Editor is a valuable tool for anyone working with text files or binary files. One of the most powerful features of 010 Editor is the ability to analyze virtually any file binary how to change binary form.
Instead of browsing through a bunch of bytes hex as the hex editor...
</description></item><item><title>Download Audio Modeling SWAM Solo Brass 3.10.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 01 Oct 2025 18:19:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-audio-modeling-swam-solo-brass-bundle-10441.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-audio-modeling-swam-solo-brass-bundle-10441.html
</guid><description>
Audio Modeling SWAM Solo Brass Bundle is a collection of acoustic instruments based on Physical Modeling technology and does not use any samples. It includes 15 instruments, grouped by product line: SWAM Trumpet, SWAM Trombone and SWAM Horns and Tubas. It enables composers, musicians and performers to play - both in the recording studio and in live performances - the most realistic and expressive virtual trumpet solo ever conceived, through musical instruments can be controlled in real...
</description></item><item><title>Download JWIZARD Cleaner 1.9.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 01 Oct 2025 18:17:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jwizard-cleaner-12853.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jwizard-cleaner-12853.html
</guid><description>
Effective Windows cleaning software to remove unnecessary files from your PC. JWIZARD Cleaner for Windows quickly frees up disk space and keeps your system in an optimal state, ensuring your PC runs stably and efficiently. This application is designed to provide you with a comprehensive tool to analyze and optimize your PC by performing a comprehensive cleanup or a more detailed cleanup, targeting specific areas such as system, browser, mail, etc.
Features of JWIZARD Cleaner
	Clean...
</description></item><item><title>Download Syncios Mobile Manager 7.2.3</title><pubDate> Wed, 01 Oct 2025 18:17:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncios-mobile-manager-5943.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncios-mobile-manager-5943.html
</guid><description>
Syncios Mobile Manager is the best iTunes alternative, which can help you manage your vehicle collection in the way you want. Simple to move the song between Android/iPhone/iPad/iPod Touch and the computer.
The features of Syncios Mobile Manager
	Exposition music, bell music, talk books, music videos, podcasts, iTunes U, TV shows, etc.
	Enter a file or a song folder or video from the computer
	Manage the playlist on your mobile phone.
	The duplicate/delete the song on your Android/iOS...
</description></item><item><title>Download Extra Subst Home 10.9</title><pubDate> Wed, 01 Oct 2025 18:17:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-extra-subst-2605.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-extra-subst-2605.html
</guid><description>
Extra Subst is program designed to help access to the folder is regular use of your computer easier. It is also used to create, edit and remove virtual drives of your computer. Extra Subst creates virtual drives on the basis of the selected folder. Physical drives remain unchanged and are not divided into additional partitions.
Create a new virtual disk is very simple, because you only need to specify the folder which will be connected to, then select the letters and go to it. New virtual...
</description></item></channel></rss>