<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 13:49:51 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 13:49:51 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Syncovery Premium 11.11.5.135</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Dec 2025 16:49:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncovery-pro-enterprise-232.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncovery-pro-enterprise-232.html
</guid><description>
Syncovery Pro Enterprise is a great application used to back up data and to synchronize personal computers, servers, laptops, notepads and storage online. The software comes with support for FTP and secure FTP servers, SSH, WebDAV, Amazon S3, http, update the part file, ZIP compression, data encryption, and schedule automatic backups.
Syncovery Pro Enterprise have the ability to freely select files and folders across the whole folder hierarchy in tree view and supports email...
</description></item><item><title>Download All Dlls Dependencies 2.2.1.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Dec 2025 16:48:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-all-dlls-dependencies-7796.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-all-dlls-dependencies-7796.html
</guid><description>
All Dlls Dependencies is a free utility designed to allow static analysis of DLL dependencies. It is capable of analyzing modules to find missing imported DLLs or functions. All Dlls Dependencies aims to assist you if you receive an annoying warning that specific DLLs are missing and cannot run your intended application. Sometimes, but not often, restarting the application will help, but more than likely, you will need to install the missing DLL on your machine. This is where this...
</description></item><item><title>Download Shortcuts Search And Replace 2.7.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Dec 2025 16:48:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-shortcuts-search-and-replace-12360.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-shortcuts-search-and-replace-12360.html
</guid><description>
Shortcuts Search And Replace allows you to search for a shortcut's target path, working directory, arguments, and icon location content. You can override shortcut target paths, working folders, arguments, and icon location content - this will be useful when moving portable applications to another drive or another folder. It can also search for dead links, to resolve or remove them (resolve multiple times/remove with one click). You also have the option to copy selected or all files to...
</description></item><item><title>Download SysTools Email Decryptor 3.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 09 Dec 2025 13:46:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-systools-email-decryptor-14322.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-systools-email-decryptor-14322.html
</guid><description>
SysTools Email Decryptor is a powerful email decryption tool. It is designed to decrypt SMIME and OpenPGP encrypted emails from PST, OST and EDB files. This versatile tool allows users to export decrypted emails to multiple formats including PST, PDF, MSG, EML and HTML with secure and efficient access to user data.
Features of SysTools Email Decryptor
	Remove SMIME and OpenPGP encryption from emails easily
	Email decryption is easy with advanced algorithms
	This email decryption...
</description></item><item><title>Download Serato DJ Pro Suite 4.0.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 08 Dec 2025 23:04:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-serato-dj-pro-suite-1961.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-serato-dj-pro-suite-1961.html
</guid><description>
Serato DJ Pro Suite is collection of tools Mix DJ music most popular in the world with hundreds of other sound effects to Mix the music perfect. Serato DJ Pro Suite supports the sound effects such as Delay, Reverb, Flanger, Echo, PingPong Delay, Phaser, Distortion, High and Low Pass Filter, as well as combinations of them.
Serato DJ Pro Suite - Set of tools Mix DJ music the most perfect
Tool-kit Serato Pro DJ Suite includes:
	Serato DJ Pro
	Serato Play
	Serato DVS
	Serato...
</description></item><item><title>Download Certificate Manager 18.44</title><pubDate> Mon, 08 Dec 2025 23:03:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-certificate-manager-13958.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-certificate-manager-13958.html
</guid><description>
Certificate Manager provides an in-depth overview of your current certificates, allowing you to easily access detailed information. It also provides functions for both exporting existing certificates and importing new certificates, enhancing your certificate management capabilities.
Application certificates are often overlooked by most users until problems arise during application installation. For the average end user, there is little reason to focus on application certificates....
</description></item><item><title>Download Glary Utilities Pro 6.35.0.39</title><pubDate> Mon, 08 Dec 2025 22:58:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-utilities-pro-76.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-utilities-pro-76.html
</guid><description>
Glary Utilities Pro is a collection of tools and system utilities to fix, speed up, maintain and protect your computer. Glary Utilities Pro allows you to clean junk files, system downloads, as well as the subscriptions are not valid and Internet traces (that support the plug-in more for the 45+ program outside). You can also manage and delete add-ons of the browser, analyze the use of disk and find the file duplicate.
Glary Utilities Pro - optimized system
Key features Glary Utilities...
</description></item><item><title>Download Soda PDF Desktop Pro 14.0.529.23111</title><pubDate> Mon, 08 Dec 2025 22:57:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-soda-pdf-home-808.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-soda-pdf-home-808.html
</guid><description>
Soda PDF Pro  is intuitive PDF software that helps you to easily process and create PDF files from more than 300 different formats. Soda PDF is built to help you power through any PDF task. Convert to a wide range of file types. Edit the content of your document. Create custom forms. Annotate your files. Send and track contracts for electronic signatures.
Soda PDF Pro: Create PDF file
Features of Soda PDF Pro
	Read your PDFs and digital publications in 3D with unique page-turning...
</description></item><item><title>Download ProfiCAD 13.3.7</title><pubDate> Mon, 08 Dec 2025 22:57:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-proficad-1546.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-proficad-1546.html
</guid><description>
ProfiCAD is a software Program to draw diagram and circuit diagram of the electrical circuit and electronics with many features to support users. ProfiCAD will search the control circuit is different then help, you can design a variety of diagram techniques, such as diagrams, pneumatic and hydraulic. One of the obvious features of this product is the simplicity of it. Simple in the tool bar and the icons represent the parts. Simply arrange the menu, just put the items on the screen and...
</description></item><item><title>Download CalendarTask (formerly DesktopCal) 3.26.260.8238</title><pubDate> Mon, 08 Dec 2025 22:56:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopcal-1831.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopcal-1831.html
</guid><description>
CalendarTask (formerly DesktopCal) is a simple desktop calendar that blends into your desktop without blocking access to your desktop icons. You can double-click on a date to quickly add notes and also jump to specific dates in the past or future.
CalendarTask - Computer calendar
CalendarTask can use your current wallpaper or loop through images from your folder and update your desktop every few minutes. The program helps you make appointments, make plans... Not only that, the Screen...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ashampoo Backup Pro 27.5.26</title><pubDate> Mon, 08 Dec 2025 22:55:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-backup-pro-716.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-backup-pro-716.html
</guid><description>
Ashampoo Backup Pro is software to backup and restore data professional to save the file, the important data for your computer. Ashampoo Backup Pro will remove the fear of viruses, ransomware, or hardware errors. Ashampoo® Backup Pro offers you various options to backup individual files or entire disk partitions on any storage media or on the cloud. User friendly, intuitive, fast. Even in case an error occurs the entire system, application integrated emergency can bring your...
</description></item><item><title>Download Hard Disk Sentinel Pro 6.30.6 Beta</title><pubDate> Mon, 08 Dec 2025 22:55:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hard-disk-sentinel-pro-562.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hard-disk-sentinel-pro-562.html
</guid><description>
Hard Disk Sentinel Pro is a tool for monitoring and optimal performance for hard drive HDD and help diagnose the HDD as well as SSD. Version of Hard Disk Sentinel Pro is a professional version, the most advanced of Hard Disk with many advanced features that meet basic needs, check the hard drive for the user.
The goal of it is to find, test, diagnose and repair the malfunction, hard drive, report and display the health status of the SSD and hard drive failure, decreased performance and...
</description></item><item><title>Download ExtraMAME 25.12</title><pubDate> Mon, 08 Dec 2025 22:54:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-extramame-2608.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-extramame-2608.html
</guid><description>
ExtraMAME is a simple tool that allows simulation of the arcade game from the most popular platform but is long forgotten, thanks to which the game industry has reached the current level. After launch, you will get 11 games pre-installed, among which are: Super Mario Bros, Pac-Man Plus, Space Invaders II and other games.
The simulation of multiple machine arcade is authored by Nicola Salmoria and team MAME. MAME lets you play thousands of arcade game old school on your computer. ExtraMAME...
</description></item><item><title>Download Directory Opus Pro 13.20.1 Beta</title><pubDate> Mon, 08 Dec 2025 22:54:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-opus-pro-779.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-opus-pro-779.html
</guid><description>
Directory Opus Pro is a software replacement for Explorer with traditional strength and function more than any manager other files. Directory Opus Pro full support for high DPI screen (for example 4K and 5K) with the rename dialog is redesigned, with new features. Besides being a recording macro only allows you to perform mass renaming complex that don't need regular expressions. In addition, Directory Opus Pro also enhances the ability to script.Better handling of renaming recursive and...
</description></item><item><title>Download BackupAssist 15.0.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 08 Dec 2025 22:53:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-backupassist-4533.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-backupassist-4533.html
</guid><description>
BackupAssist is a software application that allows you to create backup for all file types, as well as recover and restore the item, follow the process is running and creating reports. BackupAssist is built for small and medium business is developing your. Select backup software Windows help to keep safe your data. Software backup storage to your server from the ruin. Never lose data again. Use BackupAssist to perform backups onsite and offsite to protect your server.
BackupAssist -...
</description></item><item><title>Download Glary Malware Hunter PRO 1.209.0.840</title><pubDate> Mon, 08 Dec 2025 22:53:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-malware-hunter-pro-77.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-malware-hunter-pro-77.html
</guid><description>
Glary Malware Hunter PRO - detection of file malware on your computer and delete dangerous content, allowing you to run on-demand scan of the area, important system or specific files. As suggested by its name, Malware Hunter is designed to find and remove the files and components potential danger on your computer, keep it out of the virus and the type of threat other.
Glary Malware Hunter PRO - perfect protection of your equipment
Features Glary Malware Hunter PRO
- Scan ultrasound...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ventoy 1.1.08 + LiveCD</title><pubDate> Mon, 08 Dec 2025 22:53:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ventoy-4578.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ventoy-4578.html
</guid><description>
Ventoy is an open source tool for creating bootable USB drives for ISO files. With ventoy, you don't need to format the disk multiple times, you just need to copy the iso file to the USB drive and boot it. You can copy multiple iso files at once and ventoy will give you a boot menu to select them.
Features of Ventoy
100% Open Source
Simple to Use
Fast (limited only by iso file copy speed)
Boot directly from iso file, no extraction required
Legacy + UEFI supported in the same...
</description></item><item><title>Download MEmu Android Emulator 9.3.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 08 Dec 2025 22:52:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-memu-2975.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-memu-2975.html
</guid><description>
MEmu or also known as Android Emulator is the Android emulator light and free, allowing Windows users to enjoy Android experience the original on the computer and device Microsoft their. This app provides outstanding performance, allowing you to play on PC a series of games designed to run on Android devices. This app allows you to play the game favorite Android on larger screens, to bring you a better gaming experience.
MEmu - Android emulator, lightweight and free
Software MEmu also...
</description></item><item><title>Download RAM Saver Professional 25.12.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 08 Dec 2025 22:52:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ram-saver-pro-565.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ram-saver-pro-565.html
</guid><description>
RAM Saver Pro is a professional software optimize RAM is for system stable operation with high performance. RAM Saver Pro aims to provide all the tools necessary to increase the amount of free memory, at any time, also monitor and check the RAM.
When using RAM Saver Pro, you will be allowed to access its main menu by right-clicking on the tray icon. Also, if you want to display the main panel of the program you just double-click the icon. In addition, from the main interface of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Glarysoft Malware Hunter Pro 1.209.0.840</title><pubDate> Mon, 08 Dec 2025 22:51:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glarysoft-malware-hunter-pro-235.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glarysoft-malware-hunter-pro-235.html
</guid><description>
Glarysoft Malware Hunter capabilities, comprehensive protection against threats, data protection and privacy, ensure the computer is no longer virus. It allows you against many types of viruses, trojans with the ability to super fast scanning to detect and remove the malware quickly. Glarysoft Malware Hunter has a simple design of the interface, but the pace of new work is the most important problem of this software.
Features Glarysoft Malware Hunter Pro
	Automatically search, detect,...
</description></item><item><title>Download BigTextFileSplitter 4.2.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 08 Dec 2025 22:50:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bigtextfilesplitter-7325.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bigtextfilesplitter-7325.html
</guid><description>
BigTextFileSplitter is software that helps you to split large text files into smaller text files. It can work with CSV files, TSV files, JSON Lines files, log files and others.
Features of BigTextFileSplitter
	Easy, intuitive, one-click configuration.
	Support session save/load, repeat execution.
	Execute on command line.
	Execute automatically at specific time.
	Support Windows, Linux, MacOS
</description></item><item><title>Download QontrolPanel (QuickSoundSwitcher) 1.10.3</title><pubDate> Mon, 08 Dec 2025 22:50:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quicksoundswitcher-14033.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quicksoundswitcher-14033.html
</guid><description>
QuickSoundSwitcher is a lightweight, open-source Windows utility designed to quickly and easily manage audio input and output devices. It allows users to switch between multiple audio devices (e.g. speakers, headphones, microphones) and control the volume directly from the system tray without navigating to complex Windows settings.
The program also provides an application volume mixer, allowing for volume adjustment and muting for individual programs. This tool is especially useful for...
</description></item><item><title>Download Glary Disk Cleaner 6.0.1.38</title><pubDate> Mon, 08 Dec 2025 22:49:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-disk-cleaner-1341.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-disk-cleaner-1341.html
</guid><description>
Glary Disk Cleaner is the software helps to erase the file system temporarily, cleanup your browser cache, or release the folder. Glary Disk Cleaner show scan results in detail, help you pick exactly each file to delete. The list file is much more wide open, with temporary files, user-generated, or the file system, cache, bug report, log files, data in recycle bin, the shortcut expires.
Glary Disk Cleaner - garbage system
Glary Disk Cleaner is designed to be simple as possible in use....
</description></item><item><title>Download Code VBA 11.0.0.26</title><pubDate> Mon, 08 Dec 2025 22:49:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-code-vba-7207.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-code-vba-7207.html
</guid><description>
Code VBA allows professional software developers and MS Office users to write VBA code faster and take less time to search for online solutions. Find and insert VBA for Excel, Access and Word according to the application object model. The tool annotation explains what classes and procedures perform and grant direct access (F1) to the relevant documentation on Office MSDN online. In addition, the VBA code creator supports the writing of larger code blocks.
Features of Code VBA:
	The...
</description></item><item><title>Download PVSOL premium 2026 R1 v2026.1.32412</title><pubDate> Mon, 08 Dec 2025 22:48:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pvsol-premium-11142.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pvsol-premium-11142.html
</guid><description>
PVSOL Premium is a software tool used to design and simulate photovoltaic (PV) solar energy systems. It was developed by Valentin Software, a company specializing in software solutions for the renewable energy sector. PVSOL Premium is designed to help engineers, solar installers and solar industry professionals plan and optimize solar projects.
Features of PVSOL premium
	Solar photovoltaic system design: PVSOL Premium allows users to design solar photovoltaic systems by specifying the...
</description></item></channel></rss>