<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 13:53:38 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 13:53:38 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Any DWG DXF Converter Pro 2027.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jan 2026 16:52:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-dwg-dxf-converter-pro-7581.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-dwg-dxf-converter-pro-7581.html
</guid><description>
Any DWG DXF Converter Pro  is batch DWG and DXF bidirectional converter and file version converter, it allows you to convert DWG to DXF, DXF to DWG without AutoCAD.
Features of Any DWG DXF Converter Pro
	Utility standalone, does NOT require AutoCAD.
	Convert DWG to DXF and DXF to DWG in batch.
	Outputs DWG, ASCII DXF and Binary DXF.
	It is also a DWG / DXF file version converter, it outputs AutoCAD R2.5 files - AutoCAD 2023 DWG / DXF.
	All versions of DWG / DXF file are...
</description></item><item><title>Download Screencapt Professional 3.000</title><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jan 2026 16:51:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-screencapt-professional-12260.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-screencapt-professional-12260.html
</guid><description>
Screencapt Professional is powerful Windows software for screen recording that allows you to accurately and easily record any on-screen activity. Whether you want to create tutorials, record webinars, or simply record your favorite games, Screencapt gives you all the tools you need.
With Screencapt, you can record the entire screen, a selected area, or a specific window. This flexibility makes Screencapt the perfect screen recorder for any type of application. Thanks to the built-in...
</description></item><item><title>Download Any DWG to Image Converter Pro 2027.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jan 2026 16:50:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-dwg-to-image-converter-pro-7587.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-dwg-to-image-converter-pro-7587.html
</guid><description>
Any DWG to Image Converter Pro  is a batch converter that allows you to convert DWG, DXF and DWF files to TIF (TIFF), JPG (JPEG), BMP, GIF, PNG, TGA, PCX, WMF and EMF without AutoCAD.
Features of Any DWG to Image Converter Pro
	Utility standalone, does NOT require AutoCAD.
	Convert DWG, DXF and DWF to Batch Image.
	Supports paper space and model space.
	Supports all versions of DWG / DXF files (Supports format R2.5 / 2.6 to AutoCAD 2023)
	Very easy to use.
	Command line support.
</description></item><item><title>Download Waterfox 6.6.8 / 2022.11</title><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jan 2026 16:49:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-waterfox-114.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-waterfox-114.html
</guid><description>
Waterfox is a 64-bit version of the foundation Firefox was built and the compiler Intel is optimized for speed and performance on Windows systems.Waterfox does not add any additional features or bling, in fact, it will automatically import all the gadgets and install is have of you, so you will feel like at home when you run it the first time.All the add-on your Firefox will work with Waterfox, however, only support the plug-in more 64-bit, is includes Adobe Flash, Oracle Java and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Obsidian 1.11.4</title><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jan 2026 16:49:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-obsidian-10386.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-obsidian-10386.html
</guid><description>
Obsidian is a powerful knowledge base that operates on a local folder containing plain text Markdown files. It allows users to create internal links for notes and then display the connections as a graph. Additionally users can also organize and structure their thoughts and knowledge in a flexible, non-linear way.
Features of Obsidian
Personal notes:
	Links: Create connections between your notes.
	Graph: Visualize the relationships between your notes.
	Plugins: Build your ideal...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mountain Duck 5.1.1.28444</title><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jan 2026 16:49:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mountain-duck-4115.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mountain-duck-4115.html
</guid><description>
Mountain Duck allows you to mount servers and cloud storage as the disk on the computer to your desk. Open the file remotely with any application and act as on a local disk without the need to synchronize the file. Based on the platform open source solid of Cyberduck, all of the main protocols are supported to connect to any server you want, including FTP, SFTP, WebDAV, Azure Cloud Storage, Amazon S3, Google Cloud Storage, Google Drive, Dropbox, Backblaze B2 &amp;amp; OpenStack Swift. Transfer...
</description></item><item><title>Download AnyDWG Software DGN to DWG Converter 2027.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jan 2026 16:44:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-dgn-to-dwg-converter-7582.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-dgn-to-dwg-converter-7582.html
</guid><description>
Any DGN to DWG Converter  is a software to batch convert DGN files to DWG / DXF without AutoCAD and MicroStation.
Features of Any DGN to DWG Converter
	Convert DGN to DWG and DGN to DXF quickly.
	Standalone program, AutoCAD and MicroStation are not required.
	Batch Conversion, allowing you to convert unlimited number of DGN files at a time.
	Export AutoCAD R2.5 to an AutoCAD 2023 DWG / DXF file.
	Supports MicroStation DGN V7 and V8.
	Command line feature support (You can find a...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wing IDE Pro 11.0.7</title><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jan 2026 16:44:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wing-ide-pro-2080.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wing-ide-pro-2080.html
</guid><description>
Wing IDE Pro is a integrated development environment to create applications using the Python language. Wing IDE Pro provides a code editor professional, in which you can use the keyboard shortcuts vi and emacs, auto-complete code re-structure, follow up calls, reminders, contextual. A code debugger graphics to debug locally and remotely, an interface to version control system, a test unit, a search tool flexibility available.
Wing IDE Pro - programming language Python
Features of Wing...
</description></item><item><title>Download AnyDWG Software DWF to DWG Converter 2027.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jan 2026 16:43:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-dwf-to-dwg-converter-7586.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-dwf-to-dwg-converter-7586.html
</guid><description>
Any DWF to DWG Converter  is software that allows you to convert DWF files to AutoCAD DWG and DXF file formats, so you can restore DWF entities to DWG entities corresponding easily.
Features of Any DWF to DWG Converter
	Convert DWF to DWG and DXF.
	Supports all types of DWF entities exported by AutoCAD, including arcs, elliptical arcs, ellipses, real style fonts, and more
	Supports DWF multipage specification.
	Restore layers in DWF, rendering the entire DWF pages.
	Extract Embedded...
</description></item><item><title>Download Karaosoft Karma 2026.1.12</title><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jan 2026 16:38:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-karma-2379.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-karma-2379.html
</guid><description>
Karma is an enhancement program that helps you tune, karaoke can view the text of the files sound different. At first glance, after launch, the layout may seem complicated, unclear where to start. You can customize the display prompts to understand the function of each parameter is highlighted integrated.
Management program your karaoke a easy way. Search no need to click, drag and drop feature and many other unique features designed to bring you the easiest management for the program...
</description></item><item><title>Download AnyDWG Software DWG to DWF Converter 2027.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jan 2026 16:38:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-dwg-to-dwf-converter-7585.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-dwg-to-dwf-converter-7585.html
</guid><description>
Any DWG to DWF Converter  is a full featured DWG to DWF converter that allows you to convert DWG and DXF files to DWF without AutoCAD.
Features of Any DWG to DWF Converter
	Batch convert DWG to DWF and DXF to DWF.
	Utility standalone, does NOT require AutoCAD.
	Flexible and customizable output. Allows you to choose the Quality, Format, Version and Background Color of your DWF file.
	Supports SHX, Xref and Line Width.
	Supports DWF 6 and 3D DWF. The new DWF 6 format supports...
</description></item><item><title>Download Fan Control v254</title><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jan 2026 16:36:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fancontrol-5749.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fancontrol-5749.html
</guid><description>
FanControl is a highly customizable fan control software for Windows. Stay in control of every aspect of your PC's GPU and CPU fan with the help of this highly customizable fan control app.
Features of FanControl
	Save, edit and load multiple configurations
	Multiple temperature sources (CPU, GPU, motherboard, hard drive, ".sensor" files)
	Custom fan curve
	Fine tune fan control response with steps,% start,% stop, response time and delay
	Mix different curves and sensors...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sync Breeze Ultimate 17.6.28 + Enterprise + Pro</title><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jan 2026 16:29:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sync-breeze-ultimate-enterprise-1462.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sync-breeze-ultimate-enterprise-1462.html
</guid><description>
Sync Breeze Ultimate / Enterprise is software sync files fast, powerful and reliable for the local disk, shared network storage devices, NAS and storage systems business. Users are provided with multiple modes sync files one-way and two-way sync files periodically, sync file real time sync file-level bits, sync files multi-threading, synchronization, files, wallpaper and more.
Sync Breeze Ultimate / Enterprise - synchronize files
App GUI main Sync Breeze Ultimate allows a person to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Operant Peak Spectroscopy 4.00.539</title><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jan 2026 16:28:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-operant-peak-spectroscopy-7976.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-operant-peak-spectroscopy-7976.html
</guid><description>
Operant Peak Spectroscopy for Spectroscopy reads and converts over 60 spectral file formats. It includes library search, spectrum manipulation and many other functions. Mid IR, Near IR, FTIR, Raman, Fluorescence, LIBS, XRF, UV-VIS, Raman and EELS.
Features of Operant Peak Spectroscopy
	Peak can read data from more than 70 spectral file types.
	Convert files in bulk from closed proprietary formats.
	Peak is used worldwide in industry, education, government and military
	Peak has a...
</description></item><item><title>Download PentaLogix ViewMate Pro 11.24.74</title><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jan 2026 16:28:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pentalogix-viewmate-pro-1008.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pentalogix-viewmate-pro-1008.html
</guid><description>
PentaLogix ViewMate Pro is software to view, edit and convert files from DXF to other formats such as Gerber. When using ViewMate Pro, with the DFM smart, you can check the data view there are mass violations or not. And not just a class once! Many violations, laminated with results quickly and accurately. The system provides an error report in ASCII, and in addition, create a file Gerber to help edit the file plot quickly.
PentaLogix ViewMate Pro - View and convert DXF
ViewMate Pro,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Data Sync for MySQL 24.3.0.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jan 2026 13:47:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-data-sync-for-mysql-14479.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-data-sync-for-mysql-14479.html
</guid><description>
Data Sync for MySQL by SQLMaestroGroup is a Windows tool used to compare and synchronize data between two MySQL databases (or schemas), then automatically apply the differences or through generated SQL scripts.
Available Features
	Compare data between different database management systems
	Native support for most common data sources
	Compare and synchronize internal data
	Automatically generate error-free synchronization scripts
	Display easy-to-read differences
	Save all options to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Code Factory for MySQL 17.4.0.12</title><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jan 2026 13:42:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-code-factory-for-mysql-14478.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-code-factory-for-mysql-14478.html
</guid><description>
Code Factory for MySQL is part of the SQLMaestro Group's MySQL toolset for database management, control, and development. It provides an integrated environment for writing, executing, and managing SQL queries and scripts against MySQL databases.
Features
	Visual query builder
	Handy SQL editor with code minification and syntax highlighting
	Concurrent execution of multiple queries with multi-threading
	Data management: editing, grouping, sorting, and filtering
	Export data to maximum...
</description></item><item><title>Download Database Converter for MySQL 23.3.0.7</title><pubDate> Tue, 13 Jan 2026 13:33:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-database-converter-for-mysql-14477.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-database-converter-for-mysql-14477.html
</guid><description>
Database Converter for MySQL is a Windows tool used to migrate schemas and data from various databases to MySQL, including ADO/ODBC compatible sources such as SQL Server, Oracle, PostgreSQL, Firebird, SQLite, and MS Access.
Key features include:
	Copy tables, indexes, and keys external
	Native support for most popular database servers
	Supports all other data sources accessible via ODBC/OLE DB
	Batch data loading
	Flexible and customizable data type mapping
	Intelligent database...
</description></item><item><title>Download XnViewMP 1.9.9</title><pubDate> Mon, 12 Jan 2026 23:13:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xnview-mp-1074.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xnview-mp-1074.html
</guid><description>
XnViewMP "XnView MP" is the enhanced version of XnView Classic. This is the view and convert images multi-platform powerful, compatible with more than 500 image formats, different today. XnView MP easily export images to about 70 file format is different. Similar to XnConvert, XnView MP also features integrated switch at the same time batch file to help you process photos faster. XnView is another version of the photo viewer but with the ability to support formats more limited.
XnView...
</description></item><item><title>Download LAV Filters 0.81</title><pubDate> Mon, 12 Jan 2026 23:12:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lav-filters-7279.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lav-filters-7279.html
</guid><description>
LAV Filters offers you a comprehensive package that includes a multi-format splitter, audio codec and video decoder. Visually named LAV Splitter, LAV Audio, and LAV Video, the components work together to enable playback of any file format in a DirectShow compatible player.
Based on the FFmpeg multimedia package and its built-in libraries, LAV Splitter aims to provide you with a dedicated tool for splitting various types of media files into their underlying streams and allowing Blu-Ray...
</description></item><item><title>Download ReShade 6.7.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 12 Jan 2026 23:11:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-450-3227.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-450-3227.html
</guid><description>
ReShade is an open Source tool help improve the look of the old games on modern video cards as well as allow additional display technology / new video over on the old game doesn't support the technology that.
ReShade, technically, is a tool processing general for the games and video software. Imagine you see your favorite game yourself with the obscure-around, effects market the true depth or color correction. Function ReShade by showing in an automatic way and general access to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Zoom Player Max 22.0.1.2201</title><pubDate> Mon, 12 Jan 2026 23:11:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zoom-player-max-104.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zoom-player-max-104.html
</guid><description>
Zoom Player MAX help you to see the film on DVD, Blu-ray, Flash movies and HD format with high quality and the ability to display subtitles in English very well. The advantage of software is that takes up very little system resources to play the movie with quick speed, change the wallpaper options while viewing movies.
Zoom Player MAX is the movies, browse high-quality photos on the computer with the advantages such as compact size, quick start, built-in codec. The application supports...
</description></item><item><title>Download reaConverter Pro 8.0.179</title><pubDate> Mon, 12 Jan 2026 23:10:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html
</guid><description>
reaConverter Pro is software image processing feature with batch conversion and image editing periodically becomes simple. eaConverter also provide command line utilities allow you to process images automatically, thus helping you shorten the time for other work.
reaConverter Pro integrated powerful tool of Uber with many great features. It provides advanced solutions to process and adjust images. Management of the conversion process the base image with the latest version of...
</description></item><item><title>Download FotoJet Collage Maker 1.4.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 12 Jan 2026 23:10:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fotojet-collage-maker-8003.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fotojet-collage-maker-8003.html
</guid><description>
FotoJet Collage Maker is a FotoJet collage maker that has 800+ stunning collage layouts and templates, including birthday collages, wedding collages, baby collages, family collages, love collages, and more, all designed to help you create online collages quickly and easily.
Thanks to FotoJet Collage Maker, everyone can become a professional designer delivering impressive results with this powerful graphic design tool! Whenever you feel inspired, you can always create amazing designs...
</description></item><item><title>Download MeinPlatz 8.55</title><pubDate> Mon, 12 Jan 2026 23:10:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-meinplatz-1860.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-meinplatz-1860.html
</guid><description>
MeinPlatz is a free software provides an easy and fast way to scan the hard disk to find the disk space lost. After the search is complete, results can be exported to XLS, HTM, CSV and TXT. MeinPlatz "My-Place" also has a print function with preview feature integrated print and frame rate change, and is also a magnifying glass the small screen.
MeinPlatz - Scan disk
The new features of MeinPlatz
	General optimization and general improvements as well as update the file language in...
</description></item></channel></rss>