<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 11:49:01 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 11:49:01 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Office Tool Plus 10.29.50.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Dec 2025 01:17:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-tool-plus-3664.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-office-tool-plus-3664.html
</guid><description>
Office Tool Plus based on the Office deployment tool from Microsoft. You can customize configuration files installation and install Office of to install Office without Internet. Configure install Office, as well as customize the product C2R have installed, such as add and remove components, language packs, etc.
Office Tool Plus - Download and install Office
The characteristics of Office Tool Plus
	1. Configure install Office, as well as customize the product C2R have installed, such...
</description></item><item><title>Download Krita Studio 4.4.3 (x32) / 5.2.14 (x64)</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Dec 2025 01:15:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-krita-studio-4058.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-krita-studio-4058.html
</guid><description>
Krita Studio is a drawing tool digital open-source and FREE are designed for the designer, illustrator, painter, texture painter and matte, as well as for the field of VFX (visual Effects). Krita has been in development for over ten years and has recently undergone a growth explosion. It provides many common features and creative to help both amateur and professional. Krita Studio provides support CMYK, grid perspective drawing, HDR, filters, assistant, drawing, painting, docker and many...
</description></item><item><title>Download EndNote 2025.2 Build 19737</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Dec 2025 01:06:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-endnote-4237.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-endnote-4237.html
</guid><description>
EndNote X9 as a researcher, you constantly carry the different roles, addressing the competing demands on your time and coordinate not only the activities of the own in study published that all your collaborators on the whole and on the whole world. EndNote X9 is software management reference not only frees you from the tedious work in collecting and managing research material and format folder manually but also help you easy and more controlled in coordination with colleagues.
EndNote...
</description></item><item><title>Download Capture One Pro 16.7.2.3273 + Enterprise</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Dec 2025 01:06:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capture-one-pro-624.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capture-one-pro-624.html
</guid><description>
Capture One Pro is the software solution complete photo editing. With powerful tools to organize, color grading, editing grades, and more, you have full control over the images and process his work. Capture One has been developed with quality images and easy to use. Every tool is designed to give you full control over all aspects of the process editing - preserve, restore and optimize all information from the file RAW of you. Full the tool provides the ability to expand to always achieve...
</description></item><item><title>Download FastCopy Pro 5.11.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Dec 2025 01:05:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fastcopy-pro-9404.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fastcopy-pro-9404.html
</guid><description>
FastCopy Pro is file copying and synchronization software designed to provide faster and more efficient file transfer operations than native file copying tools in operating system. It provides various features and optimizations to enhance the speed and reliability of file copying.
It can copy/delete unicode and more than MAX_PATH(260byte) pathname files. Automatically, after copy source and copy destination are HDD under the same physical HDD or evaluated, it will work as follows. Diff...
</description></item><item><title>Download FastCopy 5.11.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Dec 2025 01:04:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fastcopy-2525.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fastcopy-2525.html
</guid><description>
FastCopy - application copy data super fast, is a tool perfect replacement for copy default of windows. FastCopy is a tool that gives you the great utility with the ability to increase speed copy data files up to 4MB/sec. In particular, FastCopy perform copy data without interruption by ignoring the file error.
After launch, you will see a small window with the necessary parameters, if you go to settings, then there is a list of options impressive.To start the copy, you just need to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Alfa eBooks Manager Pro / Web 9.4.10.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Dec 2025 01:04:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-alfa-ebooks-manager-web-981.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-alfa-ebooks-manager-web-981.html
</guid><description>
Alfa eBooks Manager Web is a program that enables to arrange the electronic books and paper of you in a single electronic library. eBooks Manager Website will host the electronic books and print in an electronic library. Group, filter and sort books by multiple parameters. Find any book in just a second by title, author or ISBN.
Alfa eBooks Manager Web - ebook library
Alfa eBooks Manager Web provides comprehensive set of fields, including the author, category, publisher, series, ISBN,...
</description></item><item><title>Download ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro 15.25.1210</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Dec 2025 01:03:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-videotube-downloader-pro-1276.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-videotube-downloader-pro-1276.html
</guid><description>
ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro is the professional version support download videos and playlists from YouTube, videos from Dailymotion, BBC iPlayer, ITV Player, ABC,  FOX,CBS.com Vimeo, Prosieben, Metacafe, Blip.tv CBC.ca many more video sites. After the video is downloaded, you can convert them to the formats compatible with iPad, iPhone, iPod, MPEG-4, H. 264, MP3, AC3.
ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro - Download videos on Youtube
This is one of the software download the most...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Acrobat Pro DC 2025.001.20997 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Dec 2025 01:02:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-001en-adobe-acrobat-pro-458.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-001en-adobe-acrobat-pro-458.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Acrobat Pro DC is a comprehensive software that helps you create and edit the PDF&amp;nbsp;document, or create form, sign, protect PDF, connect, split PDF, export PDF to various formats. The Acrobat Pro DC is the latest version of Adobe with improvements in the interface with the polished ribbon bar and the ability to create and handle pdf files as well as its male versions.
The highlight of the Acrobat Pro DC is probably the ability to connect, store documents on the cloud, you can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Fast File Encryptor 25.12</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Dec 2025 01:01:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fast-file-encryptor-2606.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fast-file-encryptor-2606.html
</guid><description>
Fast File Encryptor is the encoder files fast designed for fast processing of the file very big. It can encrypt or decrypt files, contents of folders and contains a lot of additional tools. In addition, there is a tool responsible to completely remove files from the hard drive, you need it if you don't want to leave traces 100 percent in the system. You need to specify the password or key, then select the encryption method, remember remember everything, otherwise it will not work, then...
</description></item><item><title>Download RealVNC VNC Server Enterprise 7.16.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Dec 2025 01:00:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vnc-connect-enterprise-2057.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vnc-connect-enterprise-2057.html
</guid><description>
VNC Connect Enterprise is the management software but update keeps you connected with remote access to another computer for control in real time anywhere in the world. VNC Connect Enterprise technology use VNC to connect, this is the latest version (6+) of software, remote access, multi-platform our for personal purposes and commercial.
VNC Connect, Enterprise - connect remote access
The features of VNC Connect Enterprise
A product for all needs remote access to your
	VNC Connect...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Substance 3D Painter 11.1.1.5024 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Dec 2025 00:59:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-substance-painter-1279.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-substance-painter-1279.html
</guid><description>
Substance Painter is a drawing application 3D completely new with the possibility of unprecedented and workflow is optimized, help in creating graphics easier than ever. To create sprites or 3D characters, no need to have knowledge about a painters professional animation, now it has become easy and accessible for the average user . The program is recognized in the world is creative tool and the most convenient to draw 3D create character models.
Substance Painter - App 3D drawing
The...
</description></item><item><title>Download VanDyke SecureCRT and SecureFX 9.7.0.3761</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Dec 2025 00:58:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vandyke-securecrt-and-securefx-815.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vandyke-securecrt-and-securefx-815.html
</guid><description>
VanDyke SecureCRT and SecureFX is a file transfer app safety, flexibility with an intuitive interface provides remote access, secure file transfer. VanDyke provides simulation terminal firmly to the expert computing, enhance productivity with management enhanced and a variety of ways to save time and streamline the task repeated. SecureCRT has the security firm of SSH, session management extension and advanced commands, SecureCRT will help enhance your productivity.
VanDyke SecureCRT...
</description></item><item><title>Download Remote Desktop Manager Enterprise 2025.3.26</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Dec 2025 00:57:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-remote-desktop-manager-enterprise-242.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-remote-desktop-manager-enterprise-242.html
</guid><description>
Remote Desktop Manager Enterprise software is the complete management of remote connections and virtual machines from a single location, at the same time access support data online and cloud storage. Remote Desktop Manager supports multiple types of connections, not only connections for the protocol connect remote computer Remote Desktop Protocol (RDP).
Remote Desktop Manager easily add, edit, delete, share, organize and find your remote connection of you quickly. Compatible with...
</description></item><item><title>Download QuickBooks Enterprise Solutions 2024 v24.0 R18</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Dec 2025 00:56:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quickbooks-enterprise-solutions-6151.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quickbooks-enterprise-solutions-6151.html
</guid><description>
QuickBooks Enterprise Solutions takes advantage of all the features that make QuickBooks a small business accounting software ranked No. 1, but it is designed specifically for more complex management businesses. It is the most powerful version of QuickBooks and includes additional features and additional flexibility that small businesses need in accounting software.
Enterprise management software:
	More than six times the capacity of other QuickBooks products.
	The ability to add up...
</description></item><item><title>Download Able2Extract Professional 21.0.3.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Dec 2025 00:56:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-able2extract-professional-3133.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-able2extract-professional-3133.html
</guid><description>
Able2Extract Professional is a PDF conversion only on the market to help increase efficiency, productivity PDF of you on Windows. Convert PDF format to Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Publisher, AutoCAD and CSV. Get photo create perfect PDF with the optional enhanced security and quickly modify text and page PDF. Fill in, edit and create the PDF form can be filled right in the Able2Extract or insert the order number on long PDF documents. All the tasks are performed in a user interface smooth...
</description></item><item><title>Download Kaspersky Lab Products Remover 1.0.5569.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Dec 2025 00:55:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kaspersky-lab-products-remover-2207.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kaspersky-lab-products-remover-2207.html
</guid><description>
Kaspersky Lab Products Remover is a mobile gadget from a famous developer will allow you to completely remove all products of Kaspersky Lab. Working with the program as simple as possible, we started, enter code from image, then you can choose the product with the pen or selecting them about what the program found.
Kaspersky Lab Products Remover - Uninstall the software of Kaspersky Lab
I think won't mean anything when writing any program is support, look carefully at the screenshot...
</description></item><item><title>Download Donemax Data Eraser Business 4.0</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Dec 2025 00:55:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-donemax-data-eraser-7665.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-donemax-data-eraser-7665.html
</guid><description>
Donemax Data Eraser is designed to permanently delete your data to prevent data recovery. The software deleting safety, robust and easy to use helps you to permanently delete data from the SSD, HDD, USB flash drive, memory card, digital camera, etc. Donemax Data Eraser can help you delete sensitive data safely and permanently before you sell, donate, exchange, or lend you your external hard drive/device. The deleted data will disappear permanently, unable to recover from any data...
</description></item><item><title>Download FabulaTech USB for Remote Desktop 6.3.6.1</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Dec 2025 00:54:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fabulatech-usb-for-remote-desktop-6425.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fabulatech-usb-for-remote-desktop-6425.html
</guid><description>
When you work in a remote computer environment, access to your local USB devices can be quite difficult. In some cases, you can still use some sort of solution, such as plugging the USB device directly into the remote machine but in most cases, it is not a solution.
USB for Remote Desktop is a software that allows the switching of USB devices to be plugged locally to your remote computer session. It appears that the USB device is plugged directly into remote control.
The program...
</description></item><item><title>Download Freemake Video Converter Gold 5.0.0.24</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Dec 2025 00:54:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-freemake-video-converter-gold-167.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-freemake-video-converter-gold-167.html
</guid><description>
Freemake Video Converter Gold is a software to help convert tail high quality videos with many different formats on many devices. Freemake Video Converter - convert video to AVI, MP4, WMV, MKV, 3GP, DVD, MP3, iPad, iPhone, PSP, Android phone. Video to MP3 just with one click! Rip and burn DVD. Convert YouTube to MP4, AVI, etc. with Freemake! Results guaranteed. Freemake Video Converter has fast conversion speed, guarantee the output quality,support create HTML5 videos have the embed code...
</description></item><item><title>Download Muziza YouTube Downloader Converter 9.0.5</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Dec 2025 00:53:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-muziza-youtube-downloader-converter-3972.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-muziza-youtube-downloader-converter-3972.html
</guid><description>
Muziza YouTube Downloader Converter is a tool to create conditions for an attractive interface and many features to help you to download video clips from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion, Instagram and other sites. Muziza YouTube Downloader Converter can also download the video UHD 8K, 5K, 4K, QHD 2K, HD 1080p and 720p from YouTube. The app allows you download only audio stream from YouTube and save as MP3. You don't need to download the entire video file.
Muziza YouTube Downloader...
</description></item><item><title>Download 3Dsurvey 4.0.2</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Dec 2025 00:52:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-3dsurvey-3831.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-3dsurvey-3831.html
</guid><description>
3Dsurvey is a software solution to handle soil survey data. Take a photo with any digital camera standard how to import photos into 3Dsurvey and create a map orthophoto of own models, digital surface and calculates volume faster and easier. The data is processed automatically based on the matching algorithm. Use the smart tool of the us to be even more effective. Software 3Dsurvey this is designed to operate with any digital camera, DSLR, or GoPro. Use any UAV to take pictures of terrain...
</description></item><item><title>Download FRITZ 20.7</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Dec 2025 00:52:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fritz-14060.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fritz-14060.html
</guid><description>
FRITZ 20 is more than just a chess engine – it’s a training revolution for aspiring players and professionals. Whether you’re taking your first steps into the world of professional chess training, or are already playing at tournament level, FRITZ 20 will help you train more efficiently, intelligently and personally than ever before.
Simulate playing styles at the highest level
FRITZ 20 analyzes your next opponent – and plays just like them!
Use the style analysis feature in...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Video Downloader 12.0.10</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Dec 2025 00:50:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-video-downloader-9636.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-video-downloader-9636.html
</guid><description>
YT Video Downloader is software used to easily and quickly download any video or audio content from any website in HD quality using video downloader online. Save videos from almost any website supported by a video downloader on your local hard drive. Media search is a convenient way to do this.
Features of YT Video Downloader
	Download videos from hundreds of video sites.
	Really increase your download speed by up to 500% or even more!
	Download 8K, 5K, 4K Ultra HD, 2K Quad HD, 1080p...
</description></item><item><title>Download Coolutils Total Excel Converter 7.1.0.106</title><pubDate> Thu, 11 Dec 2025 00:50:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-total-excel-converter-849.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-total-excel-converter-849.html
</guid><description>
Coolutils Total Excel Converter is software that converts Excel documents to other formats like ODS, XML, SQL, WK2, WKS WAB, DBF, TEX and DIF for you to use. In addition, the software also supports converting Excel files into file DOC, DOCX, PDF, HTML, Access, TXT, ODT, ODS, XML, SQL, CSV, Lotus, DBF, TEX, DIFF, SYLK and LaTeX.
Coolutils Total Excel Converter - batch convert Excel
Total Excel Converter has a perfect layout and tight. When the conversion is finished you will get an...
</description></item></channel></rss>