<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 01:48:21 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 01:48:21 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download CalendarTask (formerly DesktopCal) 3.26.261.8277</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Dec 2025 22:17:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopcal-1831.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopcal-1831.html
</guid><description>
CalendarTask (formerly DesktopCal) is a simple desktop calendar that blends into your desktop without blocking access to your desktop icons. You can double-click on a date to quickly add notes and also jump to specific dates in the past or future.
CalendarTask - Computer calendar
CalendarTask can use your current wallpaper or loop through images from your folder and update your desktop every few minutes. The program helps you make appointments, make plans... Not only that, the Screen...
</description></item><item><title>Download AnyDesk 9.6.7</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Dec 2025 22:17:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anydesk-1321.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anydesk-1321.html
</guid><description>
AnyDesk is software computer control remote, easy connection with remote computer management and manipulation on the computer. After installing the AnyDesk up 2 the computer then you can easily use the software to provide technical support for a friend or family member or you have access to your computer while you away from home or office.
AnyDesk - control your computer remotely
The process of using very simple software, want to allow access to his computer, only need to provide for...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe InDesign 2026 v21.1.0.056 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Dec 2025 22:15:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-001en-adobe-indesign-334.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-001en-adobe-indesign-334.html
</guid><description>
Adobe InDesign is the industry-leading page design and layout software for print and digital media. Create beautiful graphic designs with typography from the world's leading foundries and images from Adobe Stock. Quickly share content and feedback as PDFs. Easily manage production with Adobe Experience Manager. InDesign has everything you need to create and publish books, digital magazines, eBooks, posters, interactive PDFs, and more.
Adobe InDesign was developed by Adobe Systems, first...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe InCopy 2026 v21.1.0.056 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Dec 2025 22:14:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-incopy-3894.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-incopy-3894.html
</guid><description>
Adobe InCopy 2023 is a solution to write and edit professional, tightly integrated with the software Adobe InDesign. Adobe InCopy allows a process to work in parallel between design staff and editorial copy, accurate copy to layout and efficiently meet editorial deadline. Adobe software this is designed to expand according to the needs of the content publishers, small, medium and large. You will be able to deliver content that will support both print and digital, thereby simplifying the...
</description></item><item><title>Download MusConv 4.10.442 Lifetime</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Dec 2025 22:13:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html
</guid><description>
MusConv transfers playlists, albums, followed artists and liked songs across a variety of services – Spotify, Apple Music, Amazon Music, YouTube, YouTube Music, iTunes, Deezer, Tidal, SoundCloud, Pandora and more 125 music services!
Features of MusConv Ultimate
	Transfer playlists, albums, followed artists and liked tracks between over 125 music servicesManage playlists (Delete, Merge, Split, Copy...)
	More than 125 music services supported
	Access DAILY updated music charts on...
</description></item><item><title>Download MSI Dragon Center 2.0.151.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Dec 2025 22:12:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-msi-dragon-center-7095.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-msi-dragon-center-7095.html
</guid><description>
MSI Dragon Center is an official control panel for MSI computers that enables you to get the most out of your MSI experience by enhancing per-key RGB lighting, tones, and tones. bar, get information about the cooling system, or change the display. With MSI Dragon Center, you can closely monitor CPU, GPU and RAM performance to optimize your PC's performance while gaming.
Features of MSI Dragon Center:
	Optimize gaming performance with just 1 click.
	Free up memory, prioritize system...
</description></item><item><title>Download Directory List and Print Pro 4.38</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Dec 2025 22:12:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-list-and-print-pro-481.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-list-and-print-pro-481.html
</guid><description>
Directory List and Print Pro is software that provides function lists and support printing content, quick, simple. In addition, the file list can be formatted, filtered, saved to several file formats and also further processed (delete / copy / move files). By copying to the clipboard the list can be exported into other programs or opened directly in Word and Excel.
The features Directory List and Print basic
	Choose the folders listed in a tree structure.
	Select the folder by...
</description></item><item><title>Download Unicodia 3.0.6</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Dec 2025 22:11:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-unicodia-8521.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-unicodia-8521.html
</guid><description>
Unicodia is free, open source software that can be used as an alternative character map for your Windows machine. The interface contains everything you need, allowing you to easily cycle through all the available ASCII symbols and copy them to the clipboard. Uncicodia is a great alternative to your standard Unicode characters and is filled with symbols/characters that make it useful for a number of different uses.
Features of Unicodia
	In Windows 10/11 — all characters of Unicode 15...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tenorshare 4DDiG File Repair 4.3.5.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Dec 2025 22:11:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tenorshare-4ddig-file-repair-5630.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tenorshare-4ddig-file-repair-5630.html
</guid><description>
Tenorshare 4DDiG File Repair is AI-powered software to repair damaged or damaged videos, photos, files and audios, improve their quality and add color to black media white. 4DDiG photo editing solves all photo problems like blurry photos, overexposed photos, etc. Powered by AI, it can dramatically improve image resolution and colorize black and white photos in seconds, not hours.
Features of Tenorshare 4DDiG File Repair
	Easily repair any blurry, overexposed and damaged videos, photos...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sleipnir 6.5.14</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Dec 2025 22:10:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sleipnir-1133.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sleipnir-1133.html
</guid><description>
Sleipnir is a popular web browser of Japanese made tools Blink, also used in Google Chrome. Sleipnir is designed to become a browser is highly customizable, users can configure to suit your own needs themselves. With Sleipnir, you can create a browser as noted by changing the design, skin, and the effects show.
Browser Sleipnir has the ability to customize and provide unique interface with the tab thumbnails, support for mouse gestures, favorites management of you. Especially Sleipnir 3...
</description></item><item><title>Download TrayStatus Pro 5.1.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Dec 2025 22:09:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-traystatus-pro-1597.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-traystatus-pro-1597.html
</guid><description>
TrayStatus Pro is professional software to help display the status of the keys Caps Lock, Num Lock, Scroll Lock, Kana, Alt, Ctrl, Shift in the system tray. In addition, the software TrayStatus this Pro also displays CPU, memory or operation of the hard drive or use performance counters to track things like the queue length, disk, network activity, requires IIS and more.
TrayStatus Pro - Show keyboard status and parameters of the computer
The features and functions TrayStatus...
</description></item><item><title>Download Psiphon 186.20251222</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Dec 2025 22:09:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-psiphon-7347.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-psiphon-7347.html
</guid><description>
Psiphon is a firewall bypass tool by Psiphon Inc. Uses VPN, SSH and HTTP Proxy technology to give you uncensored access to Internet content. Your Psiphon app automatically learns about new hotspots to maximize your chances of bypassing censorship.
The way the software works is that Psiphon constantly changes the proxy, so the user's IP address is also constantly changing, the server will not detect the user's real address, so you can feel free. roof. access to websites and software...
</description></item><item><title>Download Macrorit Data Wiper 8.3.0 All Editions</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Dec 2025 19:10:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-macrorit-data-wiper-911.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-macrorit-data-wiper-911.html
</guid><description>
Macrorit Data Wiper software delete data, partitions and disks safe. Macrorit Data Wiper completely delete the system / boot partition. This is a very good tool for those who want to delete data permanently from the system to prevent others from using.
Macrorit Data Wiper - Delete all data and partitions safe
The main features of Macrorit Data Wiper
	Completely delete the system / boot partition.
	Completely erase USB flash drives, memory cards, micro SD or TF card
	Wipe data...
</description></item><item><title>Download DirPrintOK 7.49</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:42:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dirprintok-2073.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dirprintok-2073.html
</guid><description>
DirPrintOK allows you to print and save the contents of the folder and / or entire folder structures. You can browse the directory with Explorer-like interface and arbitrary filter folder contents by file extensions or matching the wildcard. You can also right-click to exclude files or folders selected from the printed version.
&amp;nbsp;
Folder contents can be grouped by path, date, size or file extension and you can customize the data columns to be included in the printed book. Very easy...
</description></item><item><title>Download ON1 Photo RAW 2026.2 v20.2.1.17865</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:40:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-on1-photo-raw-1791.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-on1-photo-raw-1791.html
</guid><description>
ON1 Photo RAW 2023  includes the essential tools and features every photographer needs in their workflow. Our state-of-the-art, super-fast, non-destructive processing engine gives you an extremely smooth and efficient editing experience.
ON1 Photo RAW focuses on letting you get the most out of every photo. Photographers now have a quick photo management engine, hundreds of customizable photo effects, fast and beautiful HDR, masking and selection tools, layers and more in one app. Quickly...
</description></item><item><title>Download ON1 Resize AI 2026.2 v20.2.1.17865</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:39:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-on1-resize-2055.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-on1-resize-2055.html
</guid><description>
ON1 Resize 2019 is the edited final image when you need to zoom in the highest quality - with technology genuine Fractals® - to resize your photo to print. You can quickly change the image size without losing sharpness or detail. ON1 Resize also includes one of the fastest ways to view, remove and edit photos.
ON1 Resize - Zoom, change photo size
The features of ON1 Resize
	ON1 Resize using interpolation algorithm based on fractal - helps quickly change the image size without losing...
</description></item><item><title>Download ON1 Photo RAW MAX 2026.2 v20.2.1.17865</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:39:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-on1-photo-raw-max-10717.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-on1-photo-raw-max-10717.html
</guid><description>
ON1 Photo RAW MAX 2024 is powerful photo editing software that provides photographers with many tools and features to enhance and edit their images. With a user-friendly interface, it offers advanced editing capabilities, including non-destructive editing, AI-powered adjustments, and precise control over color and tone. It also supports raw files from over 800 cameras and works with JPEG, TIF, PSD, PSB, PNG and DNG files. Additionally, it also includes photo organization tools to manage...
</description></item><item><title>Download Light Image Resizer 7.5.0.142</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:38:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-light-image-resizer-945.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-light-image-resizer-945.html
</guid><description>
Light Image Resizer or also known as VSO Image Resizer. This is a software support thumbnail resolution images or move images in your hard drive. Light Image Resizer helps people store photos and digital images on their PC and who want to resize, compress, convert, create copies, import or organize photos. Light Image Resizer is integrated into Windows Explorer, right-click on your pictures and start working on your photos.
Light Image Resizer - miniature high-resolution photos and sort...
</description></item><item><title>Download ExamDiff Pro Master Edition 16.0.1.18</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:32:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-examdiff-pro-master-312.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-examdiff-pro-master-312.html
</guid><description>
ExamDiff Pro Master is a tool to compare files and folders intuitive and easy to use, intuitive and easy to use for Windows. ExamDiff Pro Master has unique features distinguishes ExamDiff Pro with the program compare other. ExamDiff Pro Master to help perform reviews of code and share other reports with your colleagues and compare local website with FTP server by plug-ins more integrated.
ExamDiff Pro Master can create a snapshot folder for comparison and storage in the future, compare...
</description></item><item><title>Download HopToDesk 1.45.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:31:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hoptodesk-11056.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hoptodesk-11056.html
</guid><description>
HopToDesk is a remote desktop application that allows users to access their remote computer or server from anywhere using a mobile device or browser their website. It provides a secure and convenient way to control and manage computers remotely, making it easier for individuals and teams to work remotely or access their files and applications on the go.
With HopToDesk, users can establish a secure connection to a remote computer or server and perform tasks as if they were sitting in...
</description></item><item><title>Download Picture Window Pro 8.0.541</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:31:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-picture-window-pro-7452.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-picture-window-pro-7452.html
</guid><description>
Picture Window Pro is a powerful image editing tool designed for serious photographers with strict creative and quality standards. Its comprehensive set of photo editing and editing tools let you control and shape every aspect of your images.
Picture Window Pro 8 is a complete rewrite of Picture Window Pro 7. It features non-destructive image editing through a novel interface based on an image tree. It also fully supports large, high-resolution displays and can be used in dual monitor...
</description></item><item><title>Download EaseUS Fixo Technician 4.2.0 Build 20251219</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:30:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-fixo-9814.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-fixo-9814.html
</guid><description>
Video is corrupted or inaccessible after power failure and sudden blackout, whole system crash, update failure, wrong file handling or some other reason? EaseUS Fixo allows you to repair many different video file formats including MOV, MP4, M2TS, MKV, MTS, 3GP, etc. easier no matter how broken it is.
It can intelligently and intelligently repair damaged and damaged photos from computers or other external storage devices such as USB flash drives, memory cards, SD cards, digital cameras...
</description></item><item><title>Download GiliSoft USB Stick Encryption 12.6</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:25:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-usb-stick-encryption-886.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-usb-stick-encryption-886.html
</guid><description>
GiliSoft USB Stick Encryption is software designed specifically to create a USB memory stick be protected by a password. GiliSoft USB Stick Encryption will create the protected area on the disk need to enter password to see contents. Data on the protected areas are encrypted by 256 bit AES on the move. Protected USB stick is fully autonomous and does not require any special software be installed on the computer.
GiliSoft USB Stick Encryption - encryption, protect USB card
Features of...
</description></item><item><title>Download O&amp;amp;O SafeErase Pro 20.1.578</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:25:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-safeerase-pro-294.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-safeerase-pro-294.html
</guid><description>
O&amp;amp;O SafeErase Pro is software that helps you to delete sensitive data securely with safeguards against misuse of data. With O&amp;amp;O SafeErase Pro you can be sure that no data is put into the wrong hands. O&amp;amp;O SafeErase provides reliable solution to securely delete files sensitive security and provide you with data protection optimization. With O&amp;amp;O SafeErase even hackers and spyware data can't restore the deleted files of your safety.
&amp;nbsp;O&amp;amp;O SafeErase is the solution...
</description></item><item><title>Download Agisoft Metashape Professional 2.3.0 Build 21805</title><pubDate> Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:18:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-agisoft-metashape-professional-1731.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-agisoft-metashape-professional-1731.html
</guid><description>
Agisoft Metashape (formerly PhotoScan) is a software product independently perform image processing and digital data creation, 3D space used in GIS applications, material cultural heritage and the production visual effects as well as the indirect measurement of the different subjects scale. Technical digital photography is deployed wisely is applied with the method of computer vision led to the system processor, smart auto, on the one hand, can be managed by a new person in the field of...
</description></item></channel></rss>