<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 13:43:44 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 13:43:44 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Pale Moon 33.9.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Sep 2025 16:43:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pale-moon-1883.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pale-moon-1883.html
</guid><description>
Pale Moon is a copy of Firefox has been optimized for the Windows operating System with the processor performance, high current. It looks identical to Firefox browser standard, and supports the extensions, themes and identities of Firefox. All extensions, bookmarks and settings of your existing be entered during the installation process, so except for the logo, you won't notice any difference on function.
Pale Moon - secure web browser
However, what you may notice is the difference in...
</description></item><item><title>Download Flyby11 1.22.432</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Sep 2025 16:43:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-flyby11-12467.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-flyby11-12467.html
</guid><description>
Flyby11 is a simple patcher that removes annoying restrictions that prevent you from installing Windows 11 (24H2) on unsupported hardware. Do you have an old PC? No TPM, Secure Boot or your processor is not supported? Flyby11 allows you to install Windows 11 24H2. There are no complicated steps. Just run the tool and you'll be running Windows 11 on your outdated machine in no time.
Technical overview
Flyby11 takes advantage of a feature of the Windows 11 setup process that uses the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Flyoobe 1.22.432</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Sep 2025 16:42:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oobelux-13956.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oobelux-13956.html
</guid><description>
Flyoobe was born out of the frustration many users felt with the Windows 11 setup experience. Whether it was the mandatory online account, the endless "Next, next, next..." screens, or the incomplete configuration options when you finally reached the desktop, the current setup lacked focus on what users really wanted.
Why choose Flyoobe?
	Simplifies the Windows 11 setup process right out of the box.
	Allows easy local account creation without need to hunt for hidden options.
	Includes...
</description></item><item><title>Download APU Dynamics Optimizer 4.3.6</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Sep 2025 16:42:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-apu-dynamics-optimizer-11954.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-apu-dynamics-optimizer-11954.html
</guid><description>
APU Dynamics Optimizer is a dynamics optimization tool designed to support modern volume types (LUFS, True Peak). The Optimizer uses the same compression engine as the APU Volume Compressor, but benefits from full audio waveforms instead of real-time measurements. This allows the gain envelope to be meticulously optimized across the entire waveform.
The design of this tool allows you to very precisely target a specific average LUFS and dynamic range. Once the gain envelope has been...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cash Register Pro 4.0.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Sep 2025 16:41:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cash-register-pro-3853.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cash-register-pro-3853.html
</guid><description>
Cash Register Pro a software cash register full of features and creative for a Windows computer, it will help you to better handle all the activities of the computer money. The application comes with the user interface logical and user friendly allows you to work quickly and do not commit the common error. The program can be used on a number of computers and offers a wide range of authorization secure and reliable. Cash Register Pro will help you track products and goods remain...
</description></item><item><title>Download Argente Registry Cleaner 4.0.3.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Sep 2025 16:41:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-argente-registry-cleaner-13814.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-argente-registry-cleaner-13814.html
</guid><description>
Argente Registry Cleaner is a free Windows utility designed to scan, clean and repair invalid or obsolete entries in the Windows Registry, helping to improve system stability and performance. This utility quickly analyzes the entire Registry for errors such as invalid entries left by uninstalled programs, missing keys, broken references, and other junk that can cause system crashes.
Key Features:
	Fast and Thorough Scan: Provides multiple scan modes including Safe (fastest), Normal...
</description></item><item><title>Download Social Media Downloader 7.8.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Sep 2025 16:40:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-socialmediaapps-facebook-video-downloader-3742.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-socialmediaapps-facebook-video-downloader-3742.html
</guid><description>
SocialVideo Downloader (formerly SocialMediaApps Facebook Video Downloader) is a Windows application to download and convert your favorite videos from Facebook and hundreds of other video sharing sites. It increases your loading speed by up to 500%, or even more! The application has a simple and intuitive user interface, its main functions and features are quite obvious to anyone. , regardless of prior experience with similar purpose tools.
&amp;nbsp;
SocialVideo Downloader
The main...
</description></item><item><title>Download APU Software APU Loudness Limiter 4.3.6</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Sep 2025 16:40:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-apu-software-loudness-limiter-12413.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-apu-software-loudness-limiter-12413.html
</guid><description>
APU Software Loudness Limiter is a real-time limiter designed to support multiple loudness types simultaneously. The limiter can be configured to use LUFS, True Peak, RMS and/or Peak volume types. This allows you to target multiple requests simultaneously, such as a specific LUFS target and a specific True Peak target. Internally, the limiter's ballistics are adjusted to accommodate different volume type limiter settings.
One of the main features of this limiter is support for various...
</description></item><item><title>Download APU Loudness Compressor 4.3.6</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Sep 2025 16:39:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-apu-loudness-compressor-9446.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-apu-loudness-compressor-9446.html
</guid><description>
APU Loudness Compressor is a compressor/extender designed to support modern volume types (LUFS, True Peak). Typical compressors operate using only RMS and/or Peak units of measurement. But technology has come a long way since then and we are long overdue to upgrade..
This compressor uses modern industry-standard LUFS units of measurement to provide much clearer feedback, connected to how people actually experience loudness. This is not just a superficial difference, the entire signal...
</description></item><item><title>Download Argente Malware Cleaner 3.0.2.8</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Sep 2025 16:39:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-argente-malware-cleaner-13494.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-argente-malware-cleaner-13494.html
</guid><description>
Argente Malware Cleaner is a lightweight utility designed to detect and remove a wide range of malware, including spyware, adware, Trojans and other threats that can compromise your privacy and data. It works as a complementary tool alongside your main antivirus software, helping to detect malware that may slip through the cracks.
Key features of Argente Malware Cleaner include:
	Easy-to-use, clean, and user-friendly interface that suits both casual and advanced users.
	Deep scanning...
</description></item><item><title>Download Kalmuri 4.1.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Sep 2025 16:38:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kalmuri-12521.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kalmuri-12521.html
</guid><description>
Kalmuri provides one of the simplest means of recording screen activity, working as both a snapshot utility and a screen recorder. It requires no installation and is ready to go at any time, waiting for your action quietly in the tray area, thus not disturbing your work.
Features of Kalmuri
	Supports video recording (specify entire screen and area)
	Entire screen, active program, window control, application area
	Supports PNG, JPG, BMP, GIF, MP4 file formats
	Supports saving documents...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDF Scanner app - TapScanner 3.0.84</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Sep 2025 16:38:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pdf-scanner-app-tapscanner-12104.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pdf-scanner-app-tapscanner-12104.html
</guid><description>
TapScanner is a mobile application that allows you to scan documents with your smartphone camera and convert them into PDF files or image formats. It essentially turns your device into a portable scanner, making capturing and digitizing physical documents convenient on the go.
TapScanner Features
	Scan documents, receipts, QRs and business cards
	Document Scanner App - Automatic Border Detection
	Tweak your images with multiple filters to achieve perfection
	Easily manage your...
</description></item><item><title>Download Calculator Plus with History 8.1.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Sep 2025 16:37:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-calculator-plus-with-history-10531.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-calculator-plus-with-history-10531.html
</guid><description>
Plus Calculator with History is the perfect calculator for Android. It remembers everything you calculate and allows you to review it at any time, which is perfect for me when shopping, doing homework, balancing my checkbook, or even helping with taxes. And if you need to quit your job and go do something else, I'll have it all ready for you when you get back. You'll never need to re-enter the same calculation twice.
Features of Calculator Plus with History
	Show your calculations in...
</description></item><item><title>Download Carly - OBD2 car scanner 49.62</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Sep 2025 16:37:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-carly-obd2-car-scanner-8278.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-carly-obd2-car-scanner-8278.html
</guid><description>
Carly is a mobile OBD2 (On-Board Diagnostics) car scanner application that allows users to diagnose, monitor and repair their vehicles. The application works by connecting to the vehicle's OBD2 port, usually located under the dashboard, and collecting data from the vehicle's computer system. The adapter and app work with Audi, BMW, Lexus, Mercedes, Mini, Porsche, Renault, Seat, Skoda, Toyota, VW and most car brands in the world with OBD2 port.
Carly - OBD2 car scanner Features
Check...
</description></item><item><title>Download AIDA64 for Android 2.12</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Sep 2025 16:37:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-aida64-for-android-9749.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-aida64-for-android-9749.html
</guid><description>
Hardware and software information utility for devices running Android. Building on the extensive hardware knowledge of the AIDA64 for Windows app, AIDA64 for Android is capable of displaying a variety of diagnostic information for phones, tablets, smartwatches and TVs.&amp;lt; /p&amp;gt;
Features of AIDA64 for Android
	Detect CPU, measure core clock in real time
	Screen size, pixel density and camera information
	Monitor battery level and temperature
	Information about WiFi and mobile...
</description></item><item><title>Download IELTS Practice Test 5.20</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Sep 2025 16:37:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ielts-practice-test-13333.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ielts-practice-test-13333.html
</guid><description>
Are you aiming for a high IELTS score? IELTS Practice Test is the complete solution for comprehensive exam preparation. Whether you are aiming for a band 7 or higher, our app provides the tools and resources you need to succeed. It covers all four sections of the IELTS exam, ensuring you are fully prepared for either the Academic or General Training test.
Key Features
	Realistic Practice Tests: Simulate the real IELTS exam with full practice tests in Listening, Reading, Writing and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Guru Maps Pro &amp;amp; GPS Tracker 5.9.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Sep 2025 16:36:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-guru-maps-pro-gps-tracker-9530.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-guru-maps-pro-gps-tracker-9530.html
</guid><description>
Guru Maps helps you find the best route and spend some time enjoying the great outdoors like traveling, hiking, cycling or off-roading. With detailed maps covering the entire world, offline navigation and real-time GPS tracking, you'll have everything you need to plan and organize your adventure.
Features of Guru Maps Pro &amp;amp; GPS Tracker
Offline map
	High resolution and based on OpenStreetMap (OSM) data.
	Updated monthly with the latest fixes and additions.
	Label font size is...
</description></item><item><title>Download Podcast Addict: Podcast player 2025.7.2 build 21528</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Sep 2025 16:36:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-podcast-addict-podcast-player-8373.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-podcast-addict-podcast-player-8373.html
</guid><description>
Podcast Addict is a popular podcast streaming application for Android devices. It allows users to listen to and manage their favorite podcasts, audiobooks, live streams, and YouTube channels. The app provides an easy way to discover and subscribe to new podcasts, while also allowing users to create playlists and customize the listening experience. Podcast Addict allows you to manage your Podcast, Radio, Audiobook, Live streaming, YouTube, SoundCloud channels and RSS News feeds from a...
</description></item><item><title>Download Money Manager Expense &amp;amp; Budget 4.10.3 GF build 1115</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Sep 2025 16:36:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-money-manager-expense-budget-13837.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-money-manager-expense-budget-13837.html
</guid><description>
Money Manager - the #1 financial planning, budgeting, expense tracking and personal wealth management app for Android! Money Manager makes managing your personal finances as easy as pie! Now you can easily record personal and business financial transactions, generate spending reports, review daily, weekly and monthly financial data and manage your assets with Money Manager's spending tracker and budget planner.
Key Features
- Adopt double-entry bookkeeping system
Money Manager...
</description></item><item><title>Download Enpass Password Manager 6.11.14.1176</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Sep 2025 16:35:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-enpass-password-manager-8212.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-enpass-password-manager-8212.html
</guid><description>
Enpass helps you avoid having to remember too many passwords and other important authentication information. It protects them in one place with your master password and makes them accessible anywhere and everywhere - on your smartphone, tablet or desktop. This application also helps you create strong and unique passwords for each login without having to remember any passwords.
Features of Enpass Password Manager APK
	Free full-featured desktop version for Mac, Windows and Linux
	No...
</description></item><item><title>Download Magnifier Plus with Flashlight 4.8.13</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Sep 2025 16:35:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-magnifier-plus-with-flashlight-8494.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-magnifier-plus-with-flashlight-8494.html
</guid><description>
Are you tired of trying to read labels with small fonts? Now you can use your Android device as the perfect digital magnifier! No need to use a magnifying glass to read small labels - this app lets you see text large and clearly. The magnifier has on-screen zoom and illumination controls for easy operation. You can also use the flash as a light to get a brighter image, and the negative mode inverts the colors so you can see this differently when they're hard to see.
Features of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Kettlebell Home Workout 3.10</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Sep 2025 16:34:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-kettlebell-home-workout-8683.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-kettlebell-home-workout-8683.html
</guid><description>
A kettlebell workout at home is an exercise that uses a kettlebell, a ball-shaped dumbbell made of cast iron or steel with handles, as the main piece of equipment. Kettlebell workouts are a type of resistance training that can help build strength, improve cardiovascular fitness, and burn calories.
A kettlebell workout at home typically involves a variety of movements that target multiple muscle groups and can be customized to suit an individual's fitness level and goals. Some popular...
</description></item><item><title>Download TickTick:To Do List &amp;amp; Calendar 7.6.9.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Sep 2025 16:34:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ticktick-to-do-list-tasks-8702.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ticktick-to-do-list-tasks-8702.html
</guid><description>
TickTick is a simple and effective task management and to-do list application that helps you schedule, manage time, remind about deadlines and organize your life at work, at home. home and everywhere else. TickTick is here to help you make the most of your day and get things done (gtd). Whether there's an idea you want to capture, a personal goal to achieve, a job to complete, or collaborating with other colleagues, even create a shopping list (with the help of a list creator). book)....
</description></item><item><title>Download Podcast Republic - Podcast app 25.9.16R</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Sep 2025 16:34:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-podcast-republic-podcast-app-8131.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-podcast-republic-podcast-app-8131.html
</guid><description>
Podcast Republic is a podcast app that allows users to discover, download and listen to podcasts on their mobile devices. Podcast Republic is a top quality Podcast App on Android with 4+ million downloads, 76k+ authentic reviews, 600k+ podcasts, and 40+ million episodes worldwide. It offers features like automatic downloading, variable playback speed, and the ability to create and manage playlists. Podcast Republic also supports Android Auto and Chromecast, so you can listen to podcasts...
</description></item><item><title>Download Signal Strength 29.0.4</title><pubDate> Wed, 24 Sep 2025 16:34:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-signal-strength-8179.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-signal-strength-8179.html
</guid><description>
Signal Strength APK App is a type of app that allows users to view the mobile and/or Wi-Fi signal strength on their devices. These types of applications typically display signal strength as a numerical value (e.g., in dBm) or as a visual representation (e.g., using a series of bars, similar to those shown above). mobile phone).
In addition, some apps can also provide you with advanced information such as network type and service provider, IP address, etc. These apps can be used to...
</description></item></channel></rss>