<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 15:43:36 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 15:43:36 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Currency Converter Plus 3.1.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 17:09:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-currency-converter-plus-8174.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-currency-converter-plus-8174.html
</guid><description>
Advanced currency converter - With multiple currency fields, historical rate charts, and a built-in calculator for convenience, compare prices wherever you travel abroad to ensure Make sure you get the best deal at today's price. All conversions use live exchange rates from AccuRate™, providing the most accurate rates available in the world. Plus, it still works offline for moves when exchange rate data isn't available. This app even supports Bitcoin!
Features of Currency Converter...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sygic GPS Navigation &amp;amp; Maps 25.3.3-2453</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 17:09:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sygic-gps-navigation-maps-8606.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sygic-gps-navigation-maps-8606.html
</guid><description>
Sygic GPS Navigation &amp;amp; Maps is the most downloaded GPS navigation app in the world, trusted by more than 200 million drivers. Offline 3D maps stored on your phone for GPS navigation without an internet connection. We update our maps for free multiple times each year so you can always rely on Sygic GPS Navigation.
Navigate anywhere, even without an Internet connection
	Offline maps of all the countries in the world, from TomTom and other providers
	Free map updates several times...
</description></item><item><title>Download 3C All-in-One Toolbox 3.1.0f</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 17:09:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-3c-all-in-one-toolbox-8399.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-3c-all-in-one-toolbox-8399.html
</guid><description>
3C All-in-One Toolbox combines many features into one giant toolbox with a modern and easy-to-use interface. All the tools you need to monitor, control and fine-tune all your Android devices. This app uses the Accessibility service to help you stop the app on non-rooted devices but will never collect any information.
Features of 3C All-in-One Toolbox
	Device Manager offers very powerful configurations, task scheduling, and device watchdogs that you can find to optimize performance and...
</description></item><item><title>Download All PDF Editor &amp;amp; Reader | Xodo 10.5.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 17:09:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-xodo-pdf-reader-editor-8451.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-xodo-pdf-reader-editor-8451.html
</guid><description>
Xodo PDF Reader &amp;amp; Editor is a mobile application for reading and editing PDF documents on Android and iOS devices. The app allows users to view, annotate, and edit PDF files using a variety of tools, including highlighting, underlining, and adding notes. With Xodo, you can read, annotate, sign, and share PDFs and fill out PDF forms, all while syncing with Google Drive, Dropbox, and OneDrive.
Xodo PDF Reader &amp;amp; Editor Features
	PDF Viewer: Application that allows users to view...
</description></item><item><title>Download AI Speech to text: Transcribe 1.30</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 17:08:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ai-speech-to-text-transcribe-13800.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ai-speech-to-text-transcribe-13800.html
</guid><description>
Welcome to AI Speech to Text: Audio to Text, an innovative and sophisticated solution designed to enhance your transcription experience. Our AI Speech to Text app sets new standards in speech to text conversion by combining cutting-edge technology with user-friendly features. Whether you are a professional who wants to transcribe real-time conversations, an academic who needs to convert audio files, or a business professional managing important meeting notes, our AI audio to text...
</description></item><item><title>Download µTorrent® Pro - Torrent App 8.2.51</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 17:08:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-utorrent-pro-torrent-app-9897.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-utorrent-pro-torrent-app-9897.html
</guid><description>
µTorrent® Pro - Torrent App downloads files quickly using the BitTorrent P2P file sharing protocol. Multi-threading when seeding helps speed up downloads of music, movies, and videos. The application will help users split files with too heavy data into smaller files. From there, downloading movies will be smoother than ever. Owning this unique application, users will no longer need to worry too much about downloading anything that is too heavy.
Other features of µTorrent® Pro -...
</description></item><item><title>Download Dev Tools Pro (Developer Tools) 9.0.0-gp</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 17:07:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-dev-tools-pro-developer-tools-12197.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-dev-tools-pro-developer-tools-12197.html
</guid><description>
Android Dev Tools Pro is an essential, efficient, powerful, automation Android Development Assistant, It can improve your development productivity. It can be used to decompile another app, view other app's layout details, view screen colors (color sampler or eyedropper), view latest open source projects, view activity history, view manifest of any app, view recently used or installed apps, extract apk or more, debug apps, view hardware and firmware related information phone software,...
</description></item><item><title>Download BitTorrent®- Torrent Downloads 8.2.51</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 17:07:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-bittorrent-pro-torrent-app-9913.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-bittorrent-pro-torrent-app-9913.html
</guid><description>
Find torrents and download them directly to your phone or tablet, WITHOUT ADS, with the official BitTorrent® Pro app for Android -- now with battery saver and auto-shutdown features.
Features of BitTorrent Pro - Torrent App
	Neat, light and beautiful design
	Wi-Fi only mode to save mobile data
	No speed limit and no size limit
	Easy access to your media with integrated music and video libraries
	Select files to download in torrents to minimize your storage space
	Better music and...
</description></item><item><title>Download SnapTube for Android 7.46.1.74603801</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 17:06:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-snaptube-youtube-downloader-hd-video-8351.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-snaptube-youtube-downloader-hd-video-8351.html
</guid><description>
SnapTube is a mobile application that allows users to download videos from various platforms, such as YouTube, Vimeo, and Dailymotion. It provides video resolution in multiple formats 144p, 720p, 1080p HD, 2K HD, 4K HD and audio formats MP3 and M4A. With Snaptube, users can search for content across all their platforms without using multiple apps.
Features of SnapTube for Android
Download in multiple resolutions
	MP4 videos are available in resolutions: choose small 360 pixels or...
</description></item><item><title>Download CALCU Stylish Basic Calculator 4.7.8</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 17:06:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-stylish-calculator-calcu-8716.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-stylish-calculator-calcu-8716.html
</guid><description>
Express your style with a computer made just for you. Choose a stylish, colorful theme to brighten your day while you calculate with ease. CALCU™ is easy to use for everyday calculations, with all the scientific capabilities you need for work and school at a swipe. And for your most demanding needs, CALCU™ lets you add or remove the functions and constants you need to create the perfect calculator you designed for you.
Features of Fashion Calculator - CALCU
	Try our new Material...
</description></item><item><title>Download Podcast Republic - Podcast app 25.8.20R</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 17:06:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-podcast-republic-podcast-app-8131.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-podcast-republic-podcast-app-8131.html
</guid><description>
Podcast Republic is a podcast app that allows users to discover, download and listen to podcasts on their mobile devices. Podcast Republic is a top quality Podcast App on Android with 4+ million downloads, 76k+ authentic reviews, 600k+ podcasts, and 40+ million episodes worldwide. It offers features like automatic downloading, variable playback speed, and the ability to create and manage playlists. Podcast Republic also supports Android Auto and Chromecast, so you can listen to podcasts...
</description></item><item><title>Download SeriesGuide 2025.2.8</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 17:05:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-seriesguide-show-manager-8240.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-seriesguide-show-manager-8240.html
</guid><description>
With SeriesGuide, you can find shows and movies to watch, keep track of your watched episodes and movies, get notifications about upcoming episodes, and back up and sync across your devices. suffered.
Explore. Find shows with new, popular, or similar episodes to the ones you're watching. Discover movies currently in theaters, released digitally or on disc.
Backup and synchronization. Sign in to SeriesGuide Cloud to back up and sync your shows, lists, and movies.
Integration with...
</description></item><item><title>Download Conversations (Jabber / XMPP) 2.19.3 build 4215404</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 17:05:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-conversations-jabber-xmpp-11493.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-conversations-jabber-xmpp-11493.html
</guid><description>
Free and open source Jabber/XMPP client for Android. Easy to use, reliable, battery friendly. With built-in support for images, group chats and e2e encryption.
Main features
	End-to-end encryption with OMEMO or OpenPGP
	Encrypted audio and video calls (DLTS-SRTP)
	Send and receive images
	Intuitive user interface follows Android Design guidelines
	Image / Avatar for your Contacts
	Sync with desktop client
	Conference (with bookmark support)
	Address book integration
	Multiple accounts...
</description></item><item><title>Download Muviz Edge: AOD &amp;amp; Edge Lights 2.0.6.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 17:05:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-always-on-edge-music-lighting-8536.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-always-on-edge-music-lighting-8536.html
</guid><description>
Muviz Edge is the first app to display a live Music Visualizer around the edges of the screen while you are listening to music from your favorite music apps. It is the perfect music companion to add musical lighting to your new-age devices with its edge-to-edge display. No root required.
Features of Always On: Edge Music Lighting
Supports major music applications
	Enjoy the audio visualizer with music from various music apps whether they are offline or streaming.
Customizable...
</description></item><item><title>Download ASICS Runkeeper - Run Tracker 16.11</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 17:05:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-asics-runkeeper-run-tracker-8334.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-asics-runkeeper-run-tracker-8334.html
</guid><description>
Join a community that helps people escape difficulties and stick with running forever! Track your workouts, set goals, sweat, and see your progress. Whether you're trying to track a 5K goal or train for a marathon, use the GPS app trusted by 50 million users and counting.
ASICS Runkeeper - Run Tracker is a mobile application that allows users to track running and fitness activities on their Android devices. The app uses GPS to track the user's distance, pace, and running time as well as...
</description></item><item><title>Download Your Calendar Widget 1.67.4</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 17:04:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-your-calendar-widget-8141.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-your-calendar-widget-8141.html
</guid><description>
Your Calendar Widget is an app that provides a customizable calendar widget for Android devices. The app allows users to view their upcoming events and appointments directly from their device's home screen. It shows your upcoming events. You can easily configure and adjust the widget according to your needs. Each widget has its own configuration. This allows you to have several widgets with different display and calendar settings.
Features of Your Calendar Widget
	Widgets can be used...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mstudio: Audio &amp;amp; Music Editor 5.0.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 17:04:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-mstudio-audio-music-editor-11872.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-mstudio-audio-music-editor-11872.html
</guid><description>
Mstudio is the most advanced and amazing Music Editor! This gives you advanced control and professional audio editing features with Mp3 cutter, Mp3 Player, Mp3 Merger, Mp3 Mixer, Mp3 Extractor, Change Tempo, Change pitch converter, Mp3 Converter, Mp3 Mutter, Mp3 Omitter, Mp3 Splitter. It's a music hub that has all the features you could want in a single app.
Some features of Mstudio
	Mp3 Player: Easily browse and play songs by song, album, artist and folder. Music &amp;amp; Mp3 Player...
</description></item><item><title>Download Water Garden Live Wallpaper 2.02</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 17:04:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-water-garden-live-wallpaper-10075.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-water-garden-live-wallpaper-10075.html
</guid><description>
Amazing 3D live wallpaper that will instantly reshape your mobile screen into an incredibly beautiful, ultra-realistic pond filled with spiritual koi fish! Use finger gestures to create stunning, incredibly realistic, velvety water ripples and waves! Watch adorable koi fish happily explore your pond! Feed or tease these naughty koi fish with your fingers to make them happier! Choose from a rich set of amazing natural scenes, almost every pixel is intentionally polished just for your...
</description></item><item><title>Download OH Web Browser - Safe &amp;amp; Simple 10.0.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 17:03:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-oh-web-browser-safe-simple-13834.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-oh-web-browser-safe-simple-13834.html
</guid><description>
Browsers are great on mobile devices. OH takes it to the next level. OH reinvents the mobile browsing experience. From the UI to the PDF converter, everything is redesigned for intuitive browsing.
Design:
OH isn't just another design. It's a design revolution. The next-generation user interface. Make browsing stylish, fun and awesome!
	All controls at the bottom
	One-handed use
	Simple and minimalistic
	Intuitive gestures
Privacy:
OH doesn't need any unnecessary dangerous...
</description></item><item><title>Download myTuner Radio App: FM stations 9.6.7</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 17:03:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-mytuner-radio-app-fm-stations-11072.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-mytuner-radio-app-fm-stations-11072.html
</guid><description>
Now available for Samsung TVs, LG TVs AND Roku! With the myTuner Radio app, you can listen to live radio from around the world on your Android phone or tablet. With a modern, beautiful and easy-to-use interface, myTuner gives you the best experience when listening to online radio, internet radio, AM and FM radio.
myTuner Radio App Features: FM Radio
	listen to more than 50,000 radio stations from more than 200 countries and territories;
	follow your favorite shows and over 1 million...
</description></item><item><title>Download Network Scanner 2.7.6</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 17:03:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-network-scanner-9363.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-network-scanner-9363.html
</guid><description>
The application will find all servers in your home network or in the selected IP range. It is not only used to see who is using your WiFi and learn more about every device but also for professional tasks: dynamic port scanning and the ability to filter servers by opened ports allows to find servers the required service is available in the selected network. IP scanner supports 4 scanning modes - arp read, icmp ping, udp ping, dns request. Additionally, you can manually select the used DNS...
</description></item><item><title>Download Money Lover - Spending Manager 8.44.1.16</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 17:02:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-money-lover-spending-manager-8349.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-money-lover-spending-manager-8349.html
</guid><description>
Receive personal finance awards &amp;amp; Money management app to manage money now! Track your spending, monitor your transactions, create a monthly budget, motivate yourself to save money, and more. You can also link your Money Lover wallet to your bank account to automatically track your transaction history. Money Lover is a must-have app for personal finance management. Financial management becomes super easy and fast!
Managing personal finances can be difficult for many people. You need...
</description></item><item><title>Download OH Private Web Browser 3.0.5</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 17:02:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-oh-private-web-browser-privacy-by-design-10753.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-oh-private-web-browser-privacy-by-design-10753.html
</guid><description>
Auto cleanup &amp;amp; always clean! Automatically delete everything (history, cookies, cache, form data, web storage, etc.) on exit! No complicated settings required! OH doesn't need any unnecessary dangerous permissions. So you can surf the internet with absolute peace of mind.
OH Private Web Browser Features
OH comes with the essential features. No plug-ins needed! Some of the features are...
	Multiple search engine support
	Ad blocker
	PDF converter
	Web archive converter
	Download...
</description></item><item><title>Download Drivvo - car management 8.6.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 17:01:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-drivvo-car-management-8614.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-drivvo-car-management-8614.html
</guid><description>
Drivvo is a car management app that helps users track and manage expenses related to their vehicles. It provides a platform to record and analyze fuel consumption, maintenance costs and other expenses, making it easier to budget and manage car-related expenses.
Save Money: Manage fuel consumption and economic costs, car maintenance costs and service costs of your car, motorcycle, bus or truck.
Control Finances: Track average KM/liter, monthly costs, average per day, fuel,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sun Surveyor (Sun &amp;amp; Moon) 2.7</title><pubDate> Mon, 25 Aug 2025 17:01:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sun-surveyor-sun-moon-13217.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-sun-surveyor-sun-moon-13217.html
</guid><description>
Sun Surveyor helps you uncover the mysteries of sunrise, sunset and moon phases, allowing photographers and filmmakers to find the best locations, plan efficiently and get the perfect shot.
Live camera views, interactive maps (with street view), 3D compass and detailed ephemeris provide a wealth of information about the largest natural light source in the galaxy, as well as the moon and the Milky Way. Ha:
	View augmented reality projections of the sun and moon paths, pinpointing...
</description></item></channel></rss>