<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 14:00:28 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 14:00:28 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download NokoPrint - Mobile Printing 5.26.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 16:18:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-nokoprint-mobile-printing-8528.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-nokoprint-mobile-printing-8528.html
</guid><description>
Print photos and share them with family and friends. Print documents, PDFs, invoices, receipts, boarding passes, and more. at home, at work or on the go! You can print images, photos, web pages, PDF and Microsoft Office documents without downloading any additional apps or printing tools anytime, anywhere on almost any WiFi, Bluetooth or USB printer .
Features of NokoPrint for Android
	Print directly from your Android phone or tablet to almost any inkjet, laser or thermal...
</description></item><item><title>Download AR Ruler App: Tape Measure Cam 3.2.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 16:18:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ar-ruler-app-tape-measure-cam-8721.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ar-ruler-app-tape-measure-cam-8721.html
</guid><description>
AR Ruler app is a mobile app that uses augmented reality (AR) technology to measure distances, angles, and sizes of objects in real-world environments. This app works by using the device's camera and sensors to create a virtual 3D representation of a real-life environment.
The AR Ruler app uses augmented reality (AR) technology to measure the real world using your smartphone's camera. Target the detected plane and start using the AR
tape measure tool
Features of AR Ruler...
</description></item><item><title>Download Fraction Calculator Plus 6.1.5</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 16:17:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-fraction-calculator-plus-8354.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-fraction-calculator-plus-8354.html
</guid><description>
Fraction Calculator Plus is a mobile application that provides a user interface to perform basic mathematical operations such as addition, subtraction, multiplication and division. Many calculator apps also have advanced features such as scientific calculations, unit conversions, and graphing.
Features of Fraction Calculator Plus
	It displays your calculations in sharp, clear, elegant text that you can quickly read from a distance.
	My innovative three-keyboard display lets you type...
</description></item><item><title>Download Audiomack: Music Downloader 7.11.2 build 31487</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 16:17:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-audiomack-music-downloader-11192.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-audiomack-music-downloader-11192.html
</guid><description>
Stream and download the best new trending music (full tracks offline data-free) and listen to your local MP3s!&amp;nbsp;Browse music from the best artists in top categories like Hip-Hop, Rap, R&amp;amp;B, EDM, Afropop, and Reggae on the Audiomack music app. Download songs and listen offline, without using your data, or listen to your personal MP3 collection! Audiomack provides download access and unlimited streaming to the newest and hottest tracks, right at your fingertips. Our music download...
</description></item><item><title>Download Accumulator PDF creator 2.41</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 16:17:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-accumulator-pdf-creator-11512.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-accumulator-pdf-creator-11512.html
</guid><description>
The application's simple operation allows you to select images, videos or PDF files and perform the desired functions with a simple press of a button. With countless functions, your creativity is your main asset and this application is your ultimate tool.
Features of Accumulator PDF creator
	Convert images and GIFs to PDF.
	Convert PDF to image.
	Write or paste text into PDF.
	Create professional PDF pages and presentations from scratch, implementing your own design on each...
</description></item><item><title>Download Speed test 4G 5G WiFi &amp;amp; maps 2.15.26 build 21526001</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 16:17:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-speed-test-4g-5g-wifi-maps-9642.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-speed-test-4g-5g-wifi-maps-9642.html
</guid><description>
More than just a simple speed test, nPerf offers you the best and most complete mobile connection quality measurement tool with speeds up to 1 Gbps! All your results are saved in history with all test locations on the map. Easily share your results on social networks with the nPerf share image that presents a useful summary of your test. Customize your app by switching the background theme using Settings.
Features of Speed ​​test 4G 5G WiFi &amp;amp; maps
	Full QoS test: In seconds,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Peak – Brain Games &amp;amp; Training 4.30.5</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 16:16:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-peak-brain-games-training-8236.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-peak-brain-games-training-8236.html
</guid><description>
Peak is a brain training application aimed at improving cognitive abilities and brain activity. It has many games and exercises designed to target different areas of the brain such as memory, attention, problem solving and more. It only takes 10 minutes a day to complete a brain training exercise. And, with 45 brain games for adults and new brain training exercises every day, there's always a fun challenge waiting for you.
Some features of the application include:
	Daily brain...
</description></item><item><title>Download TickTick:To Do List &amp;amp; Calendar 8.0.1.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 16:16:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ticktick-to-do-list-tasks-8702.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ticktick-to-do-list-tasks-8702.html
</guid><description>
TickTick is a simple and effective task management and to-do list application that helps you schedule, manage time, remind about deadlines and organize your life at work, at home. home and everywhere else. TickTick is here to help you make the most of your day and get things done (gtd). Whether there's an idea you want to capture, a personal goal to achieve, a job to complete, or collaborating with other colleagues, even create a shopping list (with the help of a list creator). book)....
</description></item><item><title>Download Clipboard CopyPaster Pro v58</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 16:15:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-clipboard-copypaster-pro-11369.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-clipboard-copypaster-pro-11369.html
</guid><description>
Clipboard CopyPaster Pro is a manager that simplifies work with standard clipboards; you can use it to copy and paste various texts and images as well as manage clipboard history.
CopyPaster Pro is a clipboard manager and has many additional and very useful functions:
	Save all copied data (text, links, images).
	Copy the saved data and paste it to the desired location.
	Edit data.
	Create your own notes.
	Share saved data.
	Voice listens to saved notes
	Search in saved data.
	Create...
</description></item><item><title>Download Weather &amp;amp; Widget - Weawow 7.0.9</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 16:15:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-weather-widget-weawow-8870.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-weather-widget-weawow-8870.html
</guid><description>
Weawow is a beautiful and highly accurate weather forecast application. You can also sell your photos at the Weawow marketplace. Weawow is a comprehensive and user-friendly weather app and widget that provides users with accurate and reliable weather information and forecasts as well as a host of other features and functions. This is a useful tool for those who want to stay up to date with the latest forecasts and weather conditions, whether for personal or professional purposes.
Weawow...
</description></item><item><title>Download NFC Tools - Pro Edition 9.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 16:15:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-nfc-tools-pro-edition-10792.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-nfc-tools-pro-edition-10792.html
</guid><description>
NFC Tools is an app which allows you to read, write and program tasks on your NFC tags and other RFID compatible chips. NFC Tools Pro Edition includes additional features such as profiles management and many others. Save your tags or task profiles to reuse them later. Export and import easily. NFC Tools Pro Edition allows you to import your records or tasks directly from an existing NFC tag. You can edit your tag very quickly. Also you can run directly your tasks profile without NFC...
</description></item><item><title>Download Learn Coding/Programming: Mimo 8.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 16:15:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-learn-codingprogramming-mimo-11634.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-learn-codingprogramming-mimo-11634.html
</guid><description>
Code in Python, JavaScript, HTML, CSS or SQL and start your career in Technology in 5 minutes a day! Whether you're an aspiring developer or just starting your journey Code in HTML, JavaScript, or other programming languages, the Mimo programming and coding app is designed to make learning to code accessible, engaging, and effective. Learn to code in these languages popular programming languages ​​like Python, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, SQL, etc. With Mimo coding app, you can learn...
</description></item><item><title>Download Lark Player:Music Player &amp;amp; MP3 2026.1.9</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 16:14:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-music-player-mp3lark-player-11711.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-music-player-mp3lark-player-11711.html
</guid><description>
Lark Player is a stylish and free offline music and video player for Android, it supports playing all major formats of offline music and videos. This free music player has powerful equalizer lyrics and best user interface. It also supports file management on the device such as deleting files and creating playlists. Currently, more than 100 million users worldwide use Lark Player to play music offline.
Other free features:
	Powerful equalizer gives you the best sound effect with sound...
</description></item><item><title>Download Librera PRO - Book reader 9.3.58</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 16:14:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-librera-pro-all-my-books-9008.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-librera-pro-all-my-books-9008.html
</guid><description>
PRO Librera Reader is an easy-to-use and highly configurable reading application that supports most popular document formats, including: PDF, EPUB, EPUB3, MOBI, DjVu, FB2, FB2.zip, TXT, RTF, AZW, AZW3, CBR, CBZ, HTML, XPS, MHT and more. With a simple yet powerful interface, Librera Reader makes reading documents a real pleasure. Librera even has a unique hands-free, auto-scrolling music mode.
Some key features of Librera reader include:
Easily explore documents with optional and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Lucky Patcher 12.0.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 16:14:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-lucky-patcher-11914.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-lucky-patcher-11914.html
</guid><description>
Lucky Patcher is a free Android app that can modify many apps and games, Block ads, remove unwanted system apps, backup apps before and after modification, Move apps apps to SD card, remove license verification from paid apps and games, etc.
Lucky Patcher features and details:
	Remove or block ads on Android apps and games. You can easily block ads with Lucky Patcher.
	Block in-app purchase verification with the app. You can use premium apps and games for free by removing in-app...
</description></item><item><title>Download Lockscreen Widgets and Drawer 3.2.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 16:13:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-lockscreen-widgets-and-drawer-8656.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-lockscreen-widgets-and-drawer-8656.html
</guid><description>
Widgets and drawers on the lock screen: A long time ago, Android introduced a feature that allowed you to display certain widgets on the lock screen. For some reason, this useful feature was removed with the release of Android 5.0 Lollipop, limiting widgets to the home screen only. While some manufacturers, such as Samsung, have brought back limited versions of lock screen widgets, you're usually limited to the widgets the manufacturer has created for you. Well, not anymore! Lock screen...
</description></item><item><title>Download Simple Radio: Live AM FM Radio 6.1.2 build 830</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 16:13:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-simple-radio-live-am-fm-radio-10456.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-simple-radio-live-am-fm-radio-10456.html
</guid><description>
Simple Radio: Live AM FM Radio is the easiest way to tune in to FM radio, AM radio and amp; Radio online. You can access music, news &amp;amp; Live sports radio in seconds with our free radio station app. With over 50,000 stations, you can follow the ones you already love or sit back and discover exciting new things from around the world.
Listen to FM radio &amp;amp; AM stations include: NPR Radio, BBC Radio, MRN, 77 WABC, La Mega 97.9, KNBR &amp;amp; WNYC. Keep up with the news, listen to music or...
</description></item><item><title>Download TuneIn Radio Pro - Live Radio 40.8</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 16:13:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-tunein-radio-pro-live-radio-8217.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-tunein-radio-pro-live-radio-8217.html
</guid><description>
TuneIn Radio Pro allows users to listen to many radio stations and podcasts from around the world. The Pro version offers additional features like the ability to record live stations, remove ads, and access more premium content. It is available for download on Google Play Store as an apk file.
All your sounds in one app:
	News: Listen and update live news 24/7 from local, national and global news sources, including CNBC, CNN, MSNBC and FOX News Radio.
	Sports: Listen live to NFL, NHL...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cinexplore - Movie &amp;amp; TV Tracker 4.0.19</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 16:11:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-cinexplore-movie-tv-tracker-8189.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-cinexplore-movie-tv-tracker-8189.html
</guid><description>
Cinexplore－Movie &amp;amp; TV Tracker is a simple and user-friendly tool that helps you discover and track movies, TV shows and actors that suit your interests. Cinexplore is the tracking app you need to help organize all the movies and TV shows you like.
Discover movies, TV shows and actors:
	Discover movies and TV shows that suit your interests among thousands of categories
	Search for movies and TV shows based on a variety of criteria (name, genre, rating, streaming network, release...
</description></item><item><title>Download Privacy Eraser Pro 6.26.0.5480</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 01:51:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-privacy-eraser-1141.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-privacy-eraser-1141.html
</guid><description>
Privacy Eraser is the cleanup for computer help to clear the tracks, junk files and traces of recent activity of the computer. Privacy Eraser support the popular web browsers like Internet Explorer, Mozilla Firefox, Google Chrome, Safari and Opera. The program can quickly erase the browser cache, cookies, browsing history, website history, website URL entered, form data, auto complete, file index.dat, file swapping, temporary directory and the position in other common.
Privacy Eraser -...
</description></item><item><title>Download Nero AI Video Upscaler Pro 1.3.13.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 01:50:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nero-ai-video-upscaler-pro-14415.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nero-ai-video-upscaler-pro-14415.html
</guid><description>
Nero AI Video Upscaler Pro is software for Windows that uses artificial intelligence to improve video quality by upscaling resolution to 4K and increasing frame rates for smoother playback. It also includes features such as noise reduction, clip-level resolution upscaling, face enhancement, and AI-based frame interpolation, enabling smoother motion and sharper detail in both real footage and AI-generated content.
Users can choose from multiple AI models (Fast, Animated, Realistic) to...
</description></item><item><title>Download CyberLink PowerDirector Ultimate 2026 v24.1.1328.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 01:50:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-powerdirector-ultimate-425.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-powerdirector-ultimate-425.html
</guid><description>
CyberLink PowerDirector Ultimate is software editor, edit video and make movies on the computer from a variety of templates are made available, complete with effects, transitions, animations, and music. CyberLink PowerDirector 17 is a combination of video editing software with advanced video editing features powerful. Cblowing need to add your clips into the time line and click on 'Production'!
The tool design video in CyberLink PowerDirector have the ability to customize helps you...
</description></item><item><title>Download VideoProc Converter AI 8.8</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 01:49:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-videoproc-2473.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-videoproc-2473.html
</guid><description>
VideoProc (an improved version of WinX HD Video Converter Deluxe) - processing software the most powerful video designed to edit, cut, crop, merge, adjust, convert and compress (4K) video with full Hardware Acceleration. Is the heir to be improved a lot, VideoProc integrated conversion / compression video UHD, the download at videos (YouTube) with the video editor, gives you the power to control optimal for every video file much music, SD, HD and 4K on your PC. With technology hardware...
</description></item><item><title>Download CyberLink PhotoDirector Ultra 2026 v17.1.1327.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 01:49:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-photodirector-ultra-129.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-photodirector-ultra-129.html
</guid><description>
Cyberlink PhotoDirector Ultra is known to be photo editing tools and videos with the effect is extremely rich, help you to change the style for the individual images or the videos of his favorite. This software integrated the 3D engine helps to speed up Video processing, which allows accessing the repository effect online and extract the Videos into the movies 3D Bru-ray, 3D AVCHD.
Cyberlink PhotoDirector Ultra to offer users a more professional tool to handle their images, remove...
</description></item><item><title>Download Hasleo Disk Clone Professional 5.6.2.0 / Enterprise / Technician</title><pubDate> Sat, 31 Jan 2026 01:48:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hasleo-disk-clone-professional-14012.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hasleo-disk-clone-professional-14012.html
</guid><description>
Hasleo Disk Clone Professional is a comprehensive disk and partition cloning software for Windows, which allows users to clone entire disks, specific partitions, and migrate Windows operating system from one disk to another without reinstalling the application. It is a professional Windows cloning software, providing multiple disk alignment modes, sector-by-sector copy of disks and partitions, flexible partition adjustment (location/size on target disk), and MBR/GPT disk conversion during...
</description></item></channel></rss>