<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 10:32:54 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 10:32:54 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Microsoft PC Manager 3.18.11.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Dec 2025 00:20:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-pc-manager-7924.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-pc-manager-7924.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft PC Manager is a program that offers super-fast antivirus, one-click speed boost, and system-wide security testing. It is designed to keep your PC running smoothly through a number of maintenance and security features.
Features of Microsoft PC Manager
	Boost cleans up your temporary files and improves your memory usage.
	Health Check lets you clear system logs and recent files, and you can also disable unwanted startup applications to save resources.
	Store manager has four...
</description></item><item><title>Download VideoProc Converter AI 8.7</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 23:48:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-videoproc-2473.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-videoproc-2473.html
</guid><description>
VideoProc (an improved version of WinX HD Video Converter Deluxe) - processing software the most powerful video designed to edit, cut, crop, merge, adjust, convert and compress (4K) video with full Hardware Acceleration. Is the heir to be improved a lot, VideoProc integrated conversion / compression video UHD, the download at videos (YouTube) with the video editor, gives you the power to control optimal for every video file much music, SD, HD and 4K on your PC. With technology hardware...
</description></item><item><title>Download KMSAuto Lite 1.9.9.9 b08</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 23:47:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kmsauto-lite-188.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kmsauto-lite-188.html
</guid><description>
KMSAuto Lite - software activate Windows and Office license Windows XP, Windows Vista, 7, Windows 8, 8.1, 10, server 2008, 2008 R2, 2012, 2012 R2, Office 2010/2013/2016. In addition, you can activate Office 2010 VL on Windows XP. The switches provide access to the key GVLK installed and configured the scheduled task.
KMSAuto Lite
Features KMSAuto Lite:
The program does NOT require any version of .NET Framework.
is product activate windows and office license the most reliable...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinNc 11.4</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 23:46:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winnc-1212.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winnc-1212.html
</guid><description>
WinNc is a powerful file manager powerful can be the great alternative for Windows Explorer standard. WinNc uses the keyboard function and mouse like the DOS version of a file manager, Norton Commander. The program allows you convenient access to the FTP server and locally different, local disk, etc., thanks to the interface is divided into two windows.
WinNc
Program WinNc capable of operation with archive formats, files most common, and has an FTP client integrated. As an additional...
</description></item><item><title>Download Activation Program 1.16</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 23:46:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-activation-program-12767.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-activation-program-12767.html
</guid><description>
Activation Program is a Windows and Office activator from Ratiborus for Windows 7 to 11. The program is created based on the MASSGRAVE code.
What advantages does this method have over other activation methods?
It offers the most advantages for activating older versions of Windows, such as Windows 7 to 8.1, as it can permanently activate any version of the versions This without modifying the Windows system boot process or executable files. This is the only public activator that provides...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Lightroom Classic 2026 v15.1 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 23:45:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-photoshop-lightroom-classic-0004-734.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-photoshop-lightroom-classic-0004-734.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Photoshop Lightroom Classic is a desktop-optimized photo editing and organizing software. Lightroom Classic gives you powerful one-click tools and advanced controls to make your photos look great. Easily organize all your photos on your desktop and share them in a variety of ways.
In addition, Lightroom Classic has a powerful import process that allows users to preview images before importing. It supports many camera raw formats and includes a database system for efficient photo...
</description></item><item><title>Download Freemake Video Converter Gold 5.0.0.26</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 23:44:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-freemake-video-converter-gold-167.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-freemake-video-converter-gold-167.html
</guid><description>
Freemake Video Converter Gold is a software to help convert tail high quality videos with many different formats on many devices. Freemake Video Converter - convert video to AVI, MP4, WMV, MKV, 3GP, DVD, MP3, iPad, iPhone, PSP, Android phone. Video to MP3 just with one click! Rip and burn DVD. Convert YouTube to MP4, AVI, etc. with Freemake! Results guaranteed. Freemake Video Converter has fast conversion speed, guarantee the output quality,support create HTML5 videos have the embed code...
</description></item><item><title>Download AAct Network 1.4.3</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 23:44:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aact-network-538.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aact-network-538.html
</guid><description>
AAct Network Portable: Activate Windows XP, Windows Vista, 7, Windows 8, 8.1, 10, Server 2008, 2008 R2, 2012, 2012 R2, 2016, Office 2010/2013/2016 VL editions. Program does NOT require any version .NET Framework.
AAct - KMS-activator for operating systems Windows VL editions:
Vista, 7, 8, 8.1, 10, Server 2008, 2008 R2, 2012, 2012 R2, 2016 and Office 2010, 2013, 2016. Also, you can activate Office 2010 VL on Windows XP.
Additional startup parameters (keys):
Activate windows: Run...
</description></item><item><title>Download TeamViewer 15.73.5 + Portable</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 23:43:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-teamviewer-528.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-teamviewer-528.html
</guid><description>
TeamViewer is software that functions to connect and control the remote computer, the ability to connect with any system anywhere from all over the place. This is a support tool users is very convenient. TeamViewer to help users control remote computer becomes much more simple, help you interact and collaborate with others in the exchange and share of information, instruction manual, application software or fix the computer.
TeamViewer as a revolution of computer science. when you have...
</description></item><item><title>Download ASUS GPU Tweak III 2.0.7.3</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 23:42:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-asus-gpu-tweak-3252.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-asus-gpu-tweak-3252.html
</guid><description>
ASUS GPU Tweak is a tools overclocking powerful and full-featured allows you to significantly enhance the performance of the graphics processor ASUS. Utility that allows you to get the best results just by few mouse clicks. ASUS GPU Tweak has a number mode allows you to adjust the parameters of graphics according to the specific needs of his. Mode OC allows you to benefit from maximum performance supplied by your graphics card. Game play mode allows you to play the game using the default...
</description></item><item><title>Download Abelssoft YouTube Song Downloader Plus 2026 v26.03</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 23:42:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-abelssoft-youtube-song-downloader-plus-111.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-abelssoft-youtube-song-downloader-plus-111.html
</guid><description>
Abelssoft YouTube Song Downloader Plus 2018.18.17 Program YouTube Song Downloader Plus will help you search the music and video files from YouTube, after you can download them at. To search for music you just need to enter song name in the required field and you will get results, then you can download all videos and audio files. The program can search the entire album, this function will help to find individual songs from separate albums, because of this we specify the name of the artist...
</description></item><item><title>Download ViewCompanion Premium 16.24.0.1118</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 23:41:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-viewcompanion-premium-1868.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-viewcompanion-premium-1868.html
</guid><description>
ViewCompanion Premium version is the most powerful in all versions of ViewCompmate. ViewCompanion Premium can view, print and convert the file plot PLT, Adobe PDF, Autodesk DWF, Postcript, CGM, TIFF, CALS and other formats. ViewCompanion premium files, support PLT plotter using HPGL, HPGL / 2, HP-RTL, and formats Calcomp.
ViewCompanion Premium
With ViewCompanion Premium, you can add bookmarks to files has download. The markup elements are supported, including rectangles, lines,...
</description></item><item><title>Download FabulaTech USB for Remote Desktop 6.3.10.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 23:41:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fabulatech-usb-for-remote-desktop-6425.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fabulatech-usb-for-remote-desktop-6425.html
</guid><description>
When you work in a remote computer environment, access to your local USB devices can be quite difficult. In some cases, you can still use some sort of solution, such as plugging the USB device directly into the remote machine but in most cases, it is not a solution.
USB for Remote Desktop is a software that allows the switching of USB devices to be plugged locally to your remote computer session. It appears that the USB device is plugged directly into remote control.
The program...
</description></item><item><title>Download Waterfox 6.6.7 / 2022.11</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 23:40:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-waterfox-114.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-waterfox-114.html
</guid><description>
Waterfox is a 64-bit version of the foundation Firefox was built and the compiler Intel is optimized for speed and performance on Windows systems.Waterfox does not add any additional features or bling, in fact, it will automatically import all the gadgets and install is have of you, so you will feel like at home when you run it the first time.All the add-on your Firefox will work with Waterfox, however, only support the plug-in more 64-bit, is includes Adobe Flash, Oracle Java and...
</description></item><item><title>Download 3DCoat 2025.16</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 23:40:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-3d-coat-1269.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-3d-coat-1269.html
</guid><description>
3D Coat is a computer program that trade for modeling objects of different organic and 3D models low-poly. The app provides a variety of tools allow users to create sculptures, adding topology, create UV maps, texture surface interactions of the model, showing the static and animated round of the pattern.
3D Coat - 3D modeling
The content in the software 3D Coat:
Texture simple and PBR:
	Support drawing drawings top en model, draw the pixel and Ptex
	Rendered physics-based (PBR)...
</description></item><item><title>Download Artweaver Plus 8.1.1.3587</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 23:39:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-artweaver-plus-1324.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-artweaver-plus-1324.html
</guid><description>
Artweaver Plus is a software graphics editor with many functions fundamental to advanced and supports many different formats. Artweaver Plus works with image files in formats BMP, GIF, JPEG, JPG, JPE, PCX, PNG, TGA, VDA, ICB, VST, TIF, TIFF and AWD. Out of the possibilities of it, you can do outstanding work with layers, import and export graphic in different formats.
Artweaver Plus - editing software graphics
Artweaver Plus owner interface very similar to Photoshop , so users very...
</description></item><item><title>Download AutoPowerOptionsOK 6.31</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 23:39:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-autopoweroptionsok-1820.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-autopoweroptionsok-1820.html
</guid><description>
AutoPowerOptionsOK is a small program that can automatically turn off your screen, put your computer in sleep mode or switch between the power options. Each action can be triggered based on the absence of events keyboard and / or mouse for a specified time interval. For example, you can automatically turn off the screen if the mouse or keyboard has not been used in 10 minutes.
AutoPowerOptionsOK - power Management automatically
AutoPowerOptionsOK is a compact tool designed to help you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Omidsoft System Information 19.00</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 23:38:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-omidsoft-system-information-12255.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-omidsoft-system-information-12255.html
</guid><description>
System Information is a general Windows utility to display many useful information about Windows, Network and hardware - CPU information, PCI information, PCMCIA information, USB information, SMBus information, SPD information , ACPI method, machine information, hardware sensors, networked computer, operating system information, etc.
System Information is a simple yet highly effective tool designed for individuals who want to gain comprehensive insight into their computer systems. While...
</description></item><item><title>Download Icecream Video Converter Pro 1.48</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 23:38:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-icecream-video-converter-9618.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-icecream-video-converter-9618.html
</guid><description>
Icecream Video Converter is a nicely made video converter that makes the process as simple as possible while still producing quality results. You can also apply output settings to all files if needed. All popular formats are supported, like MP4, AVI, MKV, 3GP, WMV, MOV, M4V, MPG, M2TS, MTS, etc. It also has device presets for those times when you are unsure about the format and resolution of the output document. Built-in presets include iPad, iPhone, Android, and PS5, among...
</description></item><item><title>Download Daemon Tools Lite 12.4.0.2387</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 23:38:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-daemon-tools-lite-3391.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-daemon-tools-lite-3391.html
</guid><description>
DAEMON Tools Lite is based on two key features, simulation of virtual disks and building the file disk image as iso. DAEMON Tools Lite can emulate up to 4 virtual drives, DVD, CD or Blu-ray on your computer. The virtual units will be present in your system the same as the unit. After you select the virtual drive you want, you will choose a disc image (nrg, iso, mdf, bin, cue, etc.) that you want to mount. Visit My Computer at the device have The mobile storage and you will find the disk...
</description></item><item><title>Download Vovsoft Auto Change Wallpapers 1.4</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 23:37:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-auto-change-wallpapers-2783.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-auto-change-wallpapers-2783.html
</guid><description>
Vovsoft Auto Change Wallpapers software changes your wallpaper automatically. If you often use the computer and feel bored with the wallpaper on your computer then this will be good tool to refresh old wallpaper up your. Instead of having to manually change the desktop wallpaper of his daily, users can instead rely on a software implementation of the job automatically. Auto Change Wallpapers is a program designed to allow users to automatically change the wallpaper of their...
</description></item><item><title>Download Diffchecker 6.7.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 23:37:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-diffchecker-5025.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-diffchecker-5025.html
</guid><description>
Diffchecker is a application compare text, images and powerful file to desktop of your. Available for Windows, macOS. Compare text files, documents, PDF. Compare photos, graphics. Because Diffchecker Desktop running entirely on your computer, so it does not have to communicate with our servers to create your difference. This means that there is no other way in addition you can view your sensitive data, you.
Diffchecker Desktop run offline, that means you can use it anytime, anywhere and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Syncovery Premium 11.11.11.141</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 23:36:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncovery-pro-enterprise-232.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncovery-pro-enterprise-232.html
</guid><description>
Syncovery Pro Enterprise is a great application used to back up data and to synchronize personal computers, servers, laptops, notepads and storage online. The software comes with support for FTP and secure FTP servers, SSH, WebDAV, Amazon S3, http, update the part file, ZIP compression, data encryption, and schedule automatic backups.
Syncovery Pro Enterprise have the ability to freely select files and folders across the whole folder hierarchy in tree view and supports email...
</description></item><item><title>Download Foxit PDF Reader 2025.3.0.35737</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 23:36:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-foxit-reader-1898.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-foxit-reader-1898.html
</guid><description>
Foxit Reader is the software support people, office, create, edit and read PDF files, create notes, create a signature, set password protection and print PDF files quickly and easily. Foxit Reader is already supported on many different platforms on PC. Mac or Mobile, particularly on iPhone, Android with called Foxit MobilePDF, allowing reading material in many languages, this software creates a processing environment PDF convenient, moreover also is integrated with service cloud storage to...
</description></item><item><title>Download ProtonVPN 4.3.11</title><pubDate> Fri, 19 Dec 2025 23:33:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-protonvpn-10433.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-protonvpn-10433.html
</guid><description>
ProtonVPN app for Windows is the best way to stay safe and private while surfing the internet. It is open source, easy to use, and packed with useful security features. ProtonVPN will secure your connection by routing your traffic through multiple servers to protect you against advanced network-based attacks.
It helps keep your IP address safe if something goes wrong with your VPN connection. If your VPN connection fails, the kill switch feature will prevent your device from connecting...
</description></item></channel></rss>