<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 21:42:35 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 21:42:35 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download AIDA64 for Android 2.16</title><pubDate> Wed, 10 Dec 2025 23:20:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-aida64-for-android-9749.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-aida64-for-android-9749.html
</guid><description>
Hardware and software information utility for devices running Android. Building on the extensive hardware knowledge of the AIDA64 for Windows app, AIDA64 for Android is capable of displaying a variety of diagnostic information for phones, tablets, smartwatches and TVs.&amp;lt; /p&amp;gt;
Features of AIDA64 for Android
	Detect CPU, measure core clock in real time
	Screen size, pixel density and camera information
	Monitor battery level and temperature
	Information about WiFi and mobile...
</description></item><item><title>Download PowerDirector - Video Editor 15.9.1 build 2512081</title><pubDate> Wed, 10 Dec 2025 23:19:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-powerdirector-video-editor-8123.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-powerdirector-video-editor-8123.html
</guid><description>
PowerDirector APK - Video Editor (Unlocked Version) is video editing software developed by CyberLink. It is available for Windows and Android devices. If you are looking for the Android version of PowerDirector, you can download the APK (Android Package Kit) file from the Google Play Store or from taiwebs.com.
Features of PowerDirector APK - Unlocked Version:
	Easy-to-use interface: PowerDirector has a user-friendly interface that makes it easy to edit and create videos, even if...
</description></item><item><title>Download VSCO: Photo &amp;amp; Video Editor v453</title><pubDate> Wed, 10 Dec 2025 23:19:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-vsco-photo-video-editor-8163.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-vsco-photo-video-editor-8163.html
</guid><description>
VSCO is the leading photo and video editor, nurturing the creative journey with our library of over 200 high-quality tools and presets. We also offer an easy-to-use video editor and a curated collection of photos across every genre, style and aesthetic from our global community of talented creators.
This application offers many tools and features that can be used to adjust color, exposure, and other aspects of the image. It also includes many filters that can be applied to give photos a...
</description></item><item><title>Download All PDF Editor &amp;amp; Reader | Xodo 10.10.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 10 Dec 2025 23:19:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-xodo-pdf-reader-editor-8451.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-xodo-pdf-reader-editor-8451.html
</guid><description>
Xodo PDF Reader &amp;amp; Editor is a mobile application for reading and editing PDF documents on Android and iOS devices. The app allows users to view, annotate, and edit PDF files using a variety of tools, including highlighting, underlining, and adding notes. With Xodo, you can read, annotate, sign, and share PDFs and fill out PDF forms, all while syncing with Google Drive, Dropbox, and OneDrive.
Xodo PDF Reader &amp;amp; Editor Features
	PDF Viewer: Application that allows users to view...
</description></item><item><title>Download PhotoDirector: AI Photo Editor 20.8.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 10 Dec 2025 23:18:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-photodirector-photo-editor-8144.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-photodirector-photo-editor-8144.html
</guid><description>
PhotoDirector is a photo editing app for Android devices that allows you to edit and enhance your photos with a variety of tools and effects. With PhotoDirector, you can adjust your photo's color and lighting, remove blemishes and other imperfections, and apply filters to give your photos a unique look. You can also use PhotoDirector to create photo collages and slideshows, add text and stickers to photos, and share your edited photos on social networks or through other sharing...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Photoshop Express Photo Editor 17.8.14 build 1992</title><pubDate> Wed, 10 Dec 2025 23:18:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-photoshop-express-photo-editor-02en-8249.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-photoshop-express-photo-editor-02en-8249.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Photoshop Express is a mobile photo editing app that allows users to edit photos quickly and easily on their Android devices. Join millions of creators who trust and use Adobe Photoshop Express, one of the best photo editors and collage makers on Android for fast, easy, and powerful editing on mobile devices.
Premium version / No Adobe ID account required
Features of Adobe Photoshop Express APK
	Basic photo editing: Users can crop, rotate, adjust brightness, contrast and...
</description></item><item><title>Download SnapTube for Android 7.51.1.75171701</title><pubDate> Wed, 10 Dec 2025 23:18:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-snaptube-youtube-downloader-hd-video-8351.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-snaptube-youtube-downloader-hd-video-8351.html
</guid><description>
SnapTube is a mobile application that allows users to download videos from various platforms, such as YouTube, Vimeo, and Dailymotion. It provides video resolution in multiple formats 144p, 720p, 1080p HD, 2K HD, 4K HD and audio formats MP3 and M4A. With Snaptube, users can search for content across all their platforms without using multiple apps.
Features of SnapTube for Android
Download in multiple resolutions
	MP4 videos are available in resolutions: choose small 360 pixels or...
</description></item><item><title>Download KMPlayer Plus (Divx Codec) 35.12.081</title><pubDate> Wed, 10 Dec 2025 23:17:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-kmplayer-plus-divx-codec-8720.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-kmplayer-plus-divx-codec-8720.html
</guid><description>
KMPlayer Plus with DivX codec is also available for Android devices, providing a powerful media player that supports many video and audio formats. These features include ad-free playback, cloud storage support, and high-resolution video playback support.
With support for DivX, KMPlayer Plus for Android allows users to watch high-quality DivX encoded videos on their mobile devices without the need for additional codecs or software. This is a convenient feature for users who want to watch...
</description></item><item><title>Download OsmAnd+ — Maps &amp;amp; GPS Offline 5.2.13</title><pubDate> Wed, 10 Dec 2025 23:17:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-osmand-maps-gps-offline-8245.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-osmand-maps-gps-offline-8245.html
</guid><description>
OsmAnd+ (OSM Automatic Navigation Directions) is a mapping and navigation application with access to free, global, and high-quality OpenStreetMap (OSM) data. Enjoy voice and optical navigation, view POIs (points of interest), create and manage GPX routes, use contour visualization and elevation information, choose between driving modes, cyclists, pedestrians, OSM editing, etc.
This is a mobile navigation app that uses OpenStreetMap (OSM) data to provide users with detailed maps and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Solid Explorer File Manager 3.2.7</title><pubDate> Wed, 10 Dec 2025 23:17:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-solid-explorer-file-manager-8924.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-solid-explorer-file-manager-8924.html
</guid><description>
Solid Explorer is a file management application inspired by old file management applications. Solid Explorer is a popular file management app for Android devices that allows users to manage and organize their files and folders in an intuitive and user-friendly interface. It offers many features that make it stand out from other file management apps.
Solid Explorer allows you to navigate to files stored on your device and automatically organize them into collections. You can view,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Reminder Pro 4.1.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 10 Dec 2025 23:16:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-reminder-pro-8695.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-reminder-pro-8695.html
</guid><description>
Are you looking for a simple pop-up reminder app? Do you want to create reminders for one-time and recurring tasks? Get reminders and increase your productivity. Never forget an important task again! Finally, a simple and easy way to set reminders or deadline notifications. This hourly reminder app gets straight to the point. Set notifications to remind you of all your tasks, chores, and to-do list items, then sit back and clear your head.
No unnecessary or complicated features....
</description></item><item><title>Download Passport Photo: ID Photo Print 1.2.13</title><pubDate> Wed, 10 Dec 2025 23:16:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-passport-photo-id-photo-print-11981.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-passport-photo-id-photo-print-11981.html
</guid><description>
Passport Photo: ID Photo Print is a powerful passport photo editor that will adjust your passport size photos properly. It's the easiest way for you to create passport photos and visa photos at home. With passport size photo maker, you can quickly access high quality passport photos, visa photos that meet all government requirements.
Passport Photo: ID Photo Print has all the premium features that make it the ideal passport size photo solution for conveniently editing visa or passport...
</description></item><item><title>Download YoWindow Weather - Unlimited 2.54.2</title><pubDate> Wed, 10 Dec 2025 23:16:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-yowindow-weather-unlimited-8421.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-yowindow-weather-unlimited-8421.html
</guid><description>
YoWindow is a unique new weather app. The magic of YoWindow is a living landscape that reflects your real-life weather. For example, if it rains - it will rain in YoWindow. Sunset and sunrise in YoWindow take place at the same time as in real life. But the cool thing is you can roll time forward. Just swipe the screen and you'll see how the weather changes throughout the day.
YoWindow Weather Features - Unlimited
	All the weather at your fingertips. You see the current weather,...
</description></item><item><title>Download WiFi Mouse Pro 5.6.5</title><pubDate> Wed, 10 Dec 2025 23:15:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wifi-mouse-pro-8925.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wifi-mouse-pro-8925.html
</guid><description>
Convert your phone into a wireless mouse, keyboard and trackpad for your computer, it allows you to control your PC/Mac/Linux easily via local network connection. Media Controller, Presentation Controller and Remote File Explorer are all included in this controller app.
Now you can relax on the sofa and control movies or games in the comfort of your own home, replacing your broken mouse and keyboard with this app.
Features of WiFi Mouse Pro
	Fully simulated mouse
	Built-in support...
</description></item><item><title>Download AdGuard Ad Blocker 4.14.25 Nightly</title><pubDate> Wed, 10 Dec 2025 23:15:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-adguard-block-ads-without-root-8215.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-adguard-block-ads-without-root-8215.html
</guid><description>
AdGuard for Android is the only root-free ad blocker for Android that removes ads in apps and browsers, protects your privacy, and helps you manage your apps. Adguard is designed to block unwanted ads, pop-ups and banners while you browse the web on your device. It uses a combination of local VPN technology and a custom DNS server to block ads, meaning it can block ads in apps as well as in web browsers.
In addition, Adguard also blocks tracking scripts from collecting information about...
</description></item><item><title>Download Duolingo: language lessons 6.58.7</title><pubDate> Wed, 10 Dec 2025 23:15:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-duolingo-language-lessons-8265.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-duolingo-language-lessons-8265.html
</guid><description>
Duolingo is a popular language learning app that offers interactive lessons to help users learn new languages. This application offers many languages for you to choose from, including Spanish, French, German, Italian, Portuguese, Chinese, Japanese and many more.
This app offers an gamified learning experience with interactive lessons, exercises, and quizzes designed to help users learn new words, phrases, and grammar rules. This app is designed to be easy to use and suitable for people...
</description></item><item><title>Download Footej Camera - PRO HD Camera 1.2.14</title><pubDate> Wed, 10 Dec 2025 23:14:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-footej-camera-pro-hd-camera-10592.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-footej-camera-pro-hd-camera-10592.html
</guid><description>
Footej Camera - Pro HD Camera is a new, attractive, user-friendly and powerful professional camera app that is here, ready to capture, organize and give a new life to your best moments! Improve the quality of your photos with the best camera app! Footej is a unique photo and video camera app that uses Android's Camera 2 API! Professional-grade Camera app that's easy to use, take photos and create a masterpiece.
Experience a whole new level of mobile photography! FUL DSLR Camera, Manual...
</description></item><item><title>Download Bluelight Filter for Eye Care 6.5.10</title><pubDate> Wed, 10 Dec 2025 23:14:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-bluelight-filter-for-eye-care-8192.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-bluelight-filter-for-eye-care-8192.html
</guid><description>
Blue light from smartphones or tablets causes eye strain and makes it difficult to sleep at night. This app adjusts your screen color to reduce blue light and relax your eyes, helping you sleep better.
Features of Blue Light Filter for Eye Care
	Free screen filter app to protect your eyes
	Screen filter with natural colors
	Easy operation
	Turn on or off quickly and easily
	Automatic start
	Eye care on your smartphone or tablet
	This app works on most smartphones like Samsung Galaxy,...
</description></item><item><title>Download QuickEdit Text Editor Pro 1.12.4 build 258</title><pubDate> Wed, 10 Dec 2025 23:14:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-quickedit-text-editor-pro-9059.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-quickedit-text-editor-pro-9059.html
</guid><description>
QuickEdit is a fast, stable and full-featured text editor for Android devices. It has been optimized for both phones and tablets. This app is designed to provide a variety of features and tools that make editing and formatting text on mobile devices as easy and efficient as possible.
QuickEdit Text Editor Pro Features
	Advanced notepad application with many improvements.
	Code editor and syntax highlighting for over 40 languages ​​(C++, C#, Java, XML, Javascript, Markdown, PHP,...
</description></item><item><title>Download BubbleUPnP for DLNA/Chromecast 4.6.2.1</title><pubDate> Wed, 10 Dec 2025 23:13:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-bubbleupnp-for-dlnachromecast-8657.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-bubbleupnp-for-dlnachromecast-8657.html
</guid><description>
BubbleUPnP is a mobile app for Android and iOS devices that allows you to stream media from a UPnP/DLNA media server or Chromecast device to your mobile device or to a compatible renderer. like other UPnP/DLNA on your local network.
UPnP (Universal Plug and Play) is a set of network protocols that allows different devices on a network to communicate with each other and share data. DLNA (Digital Living Network Alliance) is a technology standard that allows devices to share multimedia...
</description></item><item><title>Download Elevate - Brain Training Games 5.218.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 10 Dec 2025 23:13:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-elevate-brain-training-games-8564.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-elevate-brain-training-games-8564.html
</guid><description>
Elevate is a brain training program designed to improve speech, processing speed, memory skills, mental math, and more. Each person is provided with their own personalized learning program, which is adjusted over time to maximize results.
The more you practice with Elevate, the more you'll improve key cognitive skills proven to increase productivity, earning potential, and confidence. More than 90% said their vocabulary, memory, math skills and overall acuity improved when they...
</description></item><item><title>Download FotMob - Soccer Live Scores 219.15193.20251205.rc</title><pubDate> Wed, 10 Dec 2025 23:13:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-fotmob-soccer-live-scores-8241.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-fotmob-soccer-live-scores-8241.html
</guid><description>
FotMob gives you all the live scores, stats and storylines to help you keep up with the world of football. Personalized news and notifications make it easy to follow your favorite teams and players. And lightning-fast match updates ensure you never miss a goal, no matter where you are.
Features of FotMob - Live soccer scores
	Live match score
	Results, schedule, standings and lineup
	Detailed statistics, including expected goals (xG) and expected assists (xA)
	Capture map
	Player...
</description></item><item><title>Download AccuWeather: Weather Radar 21.1.5-1-rc</title><pubDate> Wed, 10 Dec 2025 23:12:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-accuweather-weather-radar-8893.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-accuweather-weather-radar-8893.html
</guid><description>
Weather warnings from AccuWeather are exceptionally accurate. Whether it's windy, sunny or rainy, you can stay one step ahead with AccuWeather weather radar. Be prepared for daily forecasts or sudden changes in weather with live alerts and accurate weather forecasts. Daily weather snapshots provide storm warnings, weather updates and RealFeel Temperature®, helping to predict today's weather.
With AccuWeather's superior accuracy™ for local forecasts, you'll never miss a memorable...
</description></item><item><title>Download SeriesGuide 2025.3.4</title><pubDate> Wed, 10 Dec 2025 23:12:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-seriesguide-show-manager-8240.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-seriesguide-show-manager-8240.html
</guid><description>
With SeriesGuide, you can find shows and movies to watch, keep track of your watched episodes and movies, get notifications about upcoming episodes, and back up and sync across your devices. suffered.
Explore. Find shows with new, popular, or similar episodes to the ones you're watching. Discover movies currently in theaters, released digitally or on disc.
Backup and synchronization. Sign in to SeriesGuide Cloud to back up and sync your shows, lists, and movies.
Integration with...
</description></item><item><title>Download The Guardian - Live World News 6.201.22275</title><pubDate> Wed, 10 Dec 2025 23:12:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-the-guardian-news-sport-8572.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-the-guardian-news-sport-8572.html
</guid><description>
Read the best news stories, hot news &amp;amp; comments along the way. The Guardian app gives you access to the latest politics, business and sports news through award-winning journalism.
World news, live updates &amp;amp; opinion - take your news feed with you wherever you go. Explore US stories, headlines, content and media on a variety of topics; from business to music, politics, sports, culture &amp;amp; more.
5 reasons to download The Guardian App
	Breaking news alerts, sent straight to...
</description></item></channel></rss>