<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 05:30:06 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 05:30:06 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download VirtualBox 7.2.4.170995</title><pubDate> Tue, 21 Oct 2025 23:32:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-virtualbox-285.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-virtualbox-285.html
</guid><description>
VirtualBox is a virtualization software open source allows you to run one or more operating system in a virtual machine while running Windows. It is used for purposes such as experience app or try to play the game new in a safe environment, do not affect the main operating system of you. With this software, users will better control multiple virtual machines at the same time.
VirtualBox - Create virtual drive allows running multiple operating systems at the same time
The program comes...
</description></item><item><title>Download OCCT 15.0.3.99</title><pubDate> Tue, 21 Oct 2025 23:32:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-occt-perestroika-1680.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-occt-perestroika-1680.html
</guid><description>
OCCT is a free application designed to benchmark and overclock system components. Test tool OverClock includes 4 different tests to assess the stability of your computer. CPU and CPU: Linpack to test the processor, GPU: 3D to check stability of the graphics processor and power supply combination of CPU: Linpack and GPU: 3D to download power of you up to the maximum.
OCCT - Measuring system components
The features of OCCT
	Support is enabled for a maximum of 16 cores.
	All the tests...
</description></item><item><title>Download JSoft PDF Reducer 8.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 21 Oct 2025 23:28:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jsoft-pdf-reducer-8994.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jsoft-pdf-reducer-8994.html
</guid><description>
JSoft PDF Reducer is a software application designed to compress and reduce the size of PDF files. The program provides many features and tools to optimize PDF files, such as removing unused objects, compressing images, and removing bookmarks and annotations. You are also allowed to rearrange, delete pages, add or remove text, and secure your PDF files with Watermarks, passwords and digital signatures. It's set up in a wizard format, so you'll be guided through the steps.
Features of...
</description></item><item><title>Download IObit Smart Defrag Pro 11.1.0.466</title><pubDate> Tue, 21 Oct 2025 23:25:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iobit-smart-defrag-pro-319.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iobit-smart-defrag-pro-319.html
</guid><description>
IObit Smart Defrag Pro is software that defragment the disk to help speed up the whole system to prevent the technical errors not desired. Based on the technology of disk defragmentation latest of IObit, and technology “boot Time disk defrag” Smart Defrag 5 is created with the ability to defragment in the world. It not only provides defragmentation, but also smart sorting your files based on using frequency, thus increasing the disk speed and the whole system for highest...
</description></item><item><title>Download Remote Desktop Manager Enterprise 2025.3.17</title><pubDate> Tue, 21 Oct 2025 23:25:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-remote-desktop-manager-enterprise-242.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-remote-desktop-manager-enterprise-242.html
</guid><description>
Remote Desktop Manager Enterprise software is the complete management of remote connections and virtual machines from a single location, at the same time access support data online and cloud storage. Remote Desktop Manager supports multiple types of connections, not only connections for the protocol connect remote computer Remote Desktop Protocol (RDP).
Remote Desktop Manager easily add, edit, delete, share, organize and find your remote connection of you quickly. Compatible with...
</description></item><item><title>Download MAGIX Photostory Deluxe 2026 v25.0.1.313</title><pubDate> Tue, 21 Oct 2025 23:24:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-magix-photostory-deluxe-717.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-magix-photostory-deluxe-717.html
</guid><description>
MAGIX Photostory Deluxe version 2019 provides the movement of camera, zoom and music in a slideshow of photos incredible. Our templates help you to create the slideshow entertainment absolutely does take time. Includes: new photos and 1,500 effects and music. Add to that, get more effects, more in Store Photostory!
MAGIX Photostory Deluxe - professional photo editing and add effects on the photos
Unlimited slideshows. Explore the design possibilities endless: With the stunning effects...
</description></item><item><title>Download Navicat Premium 17.3.5 Enterprise</title><pubDate> Tue, 21 Oct 2025 23:24:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-navicat-premium-87.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-navicat-premium-87.html
</guid><description>
Navicat Premium is a developer tool database allows you to connect simultaneously with the MySQL database, MariaDB, SQL Server, Oracle, PostgreSQL and SQLite from a single application. Navicat Premium is compatible with the database cloud such as Amazon RDS, Amazon Aurora, Amazon Redshift, SQL Azure, Oracle Cloud and Google Cloud. You can quickly and easily build, manage and maintain database of your.
Features, characteristics, Navicat Premium:
Move data seamlessly
Data transfer, data...
</description></item><item><title>Download Advanced Renamer Commercial 4.18.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 21 Oct 2025 23:23:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-renamer-2647.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-renamer-2647.html
</guid><description>
Advanced Renamer is a program to rename multiple files and folders at the same time. By configuring the method name change, the name can be manipulated in many different ways. It's easy to set up a batch job using multiple methods on a large number of files. 14 different modes allow you to change the name, attributes and timestamp of the file in once. The file can also be copied or moved to new location based on information in the file.
The program can rename files in many different ways,...
</description></item><item><title>Download AmoyShare BeeConverter Pro 3.1.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 21 Oct 2025 23:23:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-amoyshare-beeconverter-pro-7285.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-amoyshare-beeconverter-pro-7285.html
</guid><description>
BeeConverter Pro is a great application for video converter capable of converting multiple files simultaneously, converting videos for specific devices, handling multiple audio formats and video and most importantly, do all of this with 60x faster conversions. With its help, you can convert video or audio in any popular formats, such as MP4, MKV, AVI, FLV, WEBM and MP3, WMA, WAV, M4A, etc., as well as 4K video.
Features of BeeConverter Pro
	All popular video/audio formats are...
</description></item><item><title>Download A4ScanDoc 2.0.9.23</title><pubDate> Tue, 21 Oct 2025 23:22:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-a4scandoc-4421.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-a4scandoc-4421.html
</guid><description>
A4ScanDoc is a software solution useful provide you with a set of features reasonable and support the document feeder and two-sided printing, at the same time provides a fast scanning engine handy based on the profile of users to create. It is very easy to use, and it has a minimalist interface, while somewhat outdated, has intuitive layout. However, the application does not provide materials to help first-time users.
A4ScanDoc - Scan and print documents
When one or more documents have...
</description></item><item><title>Download Fast File Encryptor 13.10</title><pubDate> Tue, 21 Oct 2025 23:22:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fast-file-encryptor-2606.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fast-file-encryptor-2606.html
</guid><description>
Fast File Encryptor is the encoder files fast designed for fast processing of the file very big. It can encrypt or decrypt files, contents of folders and contains a lot of additional tools. In addition, there is a tool responsible to completely remove files from the hard drive, you need it if you don't want to leave traces 100 percent in the system. You need to specify the password or key, then select the encryption method, remember remember everything, otherwise it will not work, then...
</description></item><item><title>Download doPDF 11.9.511</title><pubDate> Tue, 21 Oct 2025 23:21:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dopdf-923.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dopdf-923.html
</guid><description>
doPDF is software that converts any printable document how to PDF format. doPDF acts as a virtual printer for PDF documents. The program installs as a printer driver virtual and can be accessed from any application which supports printing.
doPDF which allows users to create PDF documents by choosing "Print" from any application and with only a single operation, you can convert your document such as Microsoft Excel, Word, PowerPoint or the email and the address of your favorite websites to...
</description></item><item><title>Download reaConverter Pro 8.0.147</title><pubDate> Tue, 21 Oct 2025 23:21:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html
</guid><description>
reaConverter Pro is software image processing feature with batch conversion and image editing periodically becomes simple. eaConverter also provide command line utilities allow you to process images automatically, thus helping you shorten the time for other work.
reaConverter Pro integrated powerful tool of Uber with many great features. It provides advanced solutions to process and adjust images. Management of the conversion process the base image with the latest version of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Avanquest Architect 3D Ultimate Plus 20.0.0.1036</title><pubDate> Tue, 21 Oct 2025 23:20:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avanquest-architect-3d-ultimate-plus-8064.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avanquest-architect-3d-ultimate-plus-8064.html
</guid><description>
Avanquest Architect 3D Ultimate Plus is 3D architectural software for designing or renovating your home. It is the combination of advanced tools with LightWorks technology that gives you realistic image rendering. It is the ideal tool for both your interior decoration, renovation or landscaping projects. The new material editor, 3D cutting view, or improved Sketchup 3D object import make it one of the most powerful and intuitive software available.
Features of Avanquest Architect 3D...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tenorshare 4DDiG 10.6.1.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 21 Oct 2025 23:20:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tenorshare-4ddig-professional-5629.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tenorshare-4ddig-professional-5629.html
</guid><description>
Tenorshare 4DDiG is software to recover data from laptop / PC, external drive or USB flash disk. Recover Windows partitions, such as raw partitions, formatted partitions, damaged partitions, etc. Recover lost or deleted photos, videos, audio, videos, documents, etc.
With 4DDiG, you can recover many different types of data from this powerful Windows Data Recovery Tool feature. No matter what you have lost, 4DDiG is capable of recovering deleted files Windows 10 / 8.1 / 8/7 /...
</description></item><item><title>Download Avanquest Architect 3D Interior Design 20.0.0.1036</title><pubDate> Tue, 21 Oct 2025 23:19:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avanquest-architect-3d-interior-design-8069.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avanquest-architect-3d-interior-design-8069.html
</guid><description>
Avanquest Architect 3D Interior Design is the perfect tool for viewing and planning your interior design and decoration projects. Organize your room or apartment, try different furniture layouts and color schemes, or plan a complete renovation of your kitchen or bathroom.
It already includes a QuickStart wizard to define the layout of your rooms with just drag and drop. Decorate and personalize your home by choosing from thousands of drag-and-drop items: furniture, floor and wall...
</description></item><item><title>Download Imposition Wizard 3.6.8</title><pubDate> Tue, 21 Oct 2025 23:19:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-imposition-wizard-3645.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-imposition-wizard-3645.html
</guid><description>
Imposition Wizard is software apply PDF with integrated Adobe Acrobat, user interface simple, real-time preview and supports command line. Imposition Wizard created with simplicity in mind and features a user interface dead simple allows you to focus on your main task. Imposition Wizard comes with support for all the imposed standards, namely step and repeat,cut stack and diagram booklet, utilities the software will provide a variety of options when rearrange with shuffle feature page of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Pale Moon 33.9.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 21 Oct 2025 23:18:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pale-moon-1883.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pale-moon-1883.html
</guid><description>
Pale Moon is a copy of Firefox has been optimized for the Windows operating System with the processor performance, high current. It looks identical to Firefox browser standard, and supports the extensions, themes and identities of Firefox. All extensions, bookmarks and settings of your existing be entered during the installation process, so except for the logo, you won't notice any difference on function.
Pale Moon - secure web browser
However, what you may notice is the difference in...
</description></item><item><title>Download ExtraDisks Home 25.10.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 21 Oct 2025 23:18:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-extradisks-home-7758.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-extradisks-home-7758.html
</guid><description>
ExtraDisks is a set of tools for creating virtual disks on your computer physical drives that do not change and are not divided into additional partitions. The program contains tools for creating encrypted disks, file-based virtual disks and directory-based virtual disks. The current version includes the following tools: Encrypted Disks, Virtual Disks, Folder Disks, Startup Manager, System Tweaker.
Features of ExtraDisks
ExtraDisks: Encrypted Disk
This tool is used to create encrypted...
</description></item><item><title>Download SecretDNS 3.7.9</title><pubDate> Tue, 21 Oct 2025 23:17:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secretdns-12481.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secretdns-12481.html
</guid><description>
SecretDNS provides a quick means to deploy DNS over HTPS, meaning it allows DNS (short for Domain Name Server) resolution to be performed remotely using the HTTPS protocol to encrypts data between the client and the DNS resolver. Its purpose, obviously, is related to data security and user privacy, to prevent unauthorized interception and manipulation of DNS data.
Default DNS settings in SecretDNS use CloudFlare to ensure security. You can change DNS configuration in the dedicated tab...
</description></item><item><title>Download Argente Registry Cleaner 4.0.3.6</title><pubDate> Tue, 21 Oct 2025 23:17:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-argente-registry-cleaner-13814.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-argente-registry-cleaner-13814.html
</guid><description>
Argente Registry Cleaner is a free Windows utility designed to scan, clean and repair invalid or obsolete entries in the Windows Registry, helping to improve system stability and performance. This utility quickly analyzes the entire Registry for errors such as invalid entries left by uninstalled programs, missing keys, broken references, and other junk that can cause system crashes.
Key Features:
	Fast and Thorough Scan: Provides multiple scan modes including Safe (fastest), Normal...
</description></item><item><title>Download Coolutils Total PDF Converter 6.5.0.152</title><pubDate> Tue, 21 Oct 2025 23:16:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-total-pdf-converter-830.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-total-pdf-converter-830.html
</guid><description>
Coolutils Total PDF Converter is software to convert PDF convert PDF files to HTML, DOC (Word), text, Excel, PostScript, CSV or image files. The advantage of Coolutils Total PDF Converter is the fast, easy-to-handle, accurate, does not require Adobe Acrobat, supports many target format and have the option of batch (can convert hundreds of PDF files as well as the single file). Added to this, registered users get command line support to manage the utility with maximum...
</description></item><item><title>Download Draftable Desktop 25.10.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 21 Oct 2025 23:16:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-draftable-desktop-3749.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-draftable-desktop-3749.html
</guid><description>
Draftable Desktop is comparison tool documents the fastest. Compare over 300 pages in a few seconds. Draftable Desktop 2.0 is now available - faster and stronger than ever! See all the changes in your documents, locally and online. Take your work to the next level. Compare secret and private do not use the internet and your documents never leave your computer. Specifically, Draftable Desktop compatible with .xls, .xlsx, .xlsxm. With Office 2013, 2016 or 365, you can compare text in...
</description></item><item><title>Download Avanquest Architect 3D Landscape Design 20.0.0.1036</title><pubDate> Tue, 21 Oct 2025 23:15:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avanquest-architect-3d-landscape-design-8070.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avanquest-architect-3d-landscape-design-8070.html
</guid><description>
Avanquest Architect 3D Landscape Design is a professional design software that provides a complete set of tools for planning, designing and viewing your landscape and outdoor living space. The possibilities are endless: place different plants in your flowerbed, create the ideal outdoor kitchen, add a terrace or relaxation area!
Easily build your landscape with drag-and-drop gardens, or create a custom landscape thanks to an extensive plant library. Decorate your exterior with thousands...
</description></item><item><title>Download App Builder 2025.36</title><pubDate> Tue, 21 Oct 2025 23:15:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-app-builder-241.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-app-builder-241.html
</guid><description>
App Builder is a software application developer to help create and design apps, HTML5, web app, web app PWA on both platforms mobile and desktop. App Builder is professional software supports users to create the program HTML5 without writing code. It is very easy to use, suitable with all users who lack of professional knowledge in the field of programming and application design.
App Builder brings to 22 different themes that users can use to design for your app. You can choose 1 or a...
</description></item></channel></rss>