<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 01:42:26 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 01:42:26 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Tails 7.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 14 Oct 2025 20:36:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tails-3241.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tails-3241.html
</guid><description>
Tails is a live operating system that you can boot on almost any computer from a USB memory stick or DVD. Tails does this by using the distribution classic Gnome of Linux. The top navigation bar allows you quick access to "Applications" and "Places" so you can easily access what you need quickly and easily and not lost.
Tails - independent operating System for security
Menu "apps" provide shortcuts for bundled software, including graphics, audio and video, office, system tools, and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Revo Uninstaller Pro 5.4.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 14 Oct 2025 20:35:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-revo-uninstaller-pro-35.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-revo-uninstaller-pro-35.html
</guid><description>
Revo Uninstaller Pro is software that helps you to uninstall unnecessary software and easily remove unwanted programs installed on your personal computer. Revo Uninstaller Pro gives you the convenience to optimize your device, as well as get rid of all the program files you don't need and slow down your computer.
Traces such as registry entries or program files and folders may remain. Now with Revo Uninstaller Pro, you can be sure that you can clean your system of all these residues,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Advanced SystemCare Pro 19.0.1.158</title><pubDate> Tue, 14 Oct 2025 20:35:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-systemcare-pro-368.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-systemcare-pro-368.html
</guid><description>
Advanced SystemCare Pro is software that provides features to optimize a PC system professional cleanup, repair, speed up and protect PC.  Advanced SystemCare Pro tab Protect new is added, is designed to provide quick access to protect browsing from being tracked by automatically delete traces of privacy when browser closed and detect and resist the attack of the plugin / malicious toolbar by Browser Anti -Backing and Plugin / toolbar cleaner.
Program speed up pc top
Advanced SystemCare...
</description></item><item><title>Download Revo Uninstaller Pro Portable 5.4.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 14 Oct 2025 20:34:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-revo-uninstaller-pro-portable-4370.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-revo-uninstaller-pro-portable-4370.html
</guid><description>
Revo Uninstaller Pro Portable helps you to uninstall the program and delete the unwanted program is installed on your PC the easy way! Even if you have problems uninstalling and cannot uninstall them from control panel, Programs and features of Windows. Revo Uninstaller is an alternative agile and stronger for optional Programs and features of Windows. It has the very powerful feature to uninstall and remove programs.
Revo Uninstaller Pro Portable - Uninstall software
With complex...
</description></item><item><title>Download MAGIX VEGAS Pro 23.0.0.302</title><pubDate> Tue, 14 Oct 2025 20:33:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-magix-vegas-pro-81.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-magix-vegas-pro-81.html
</guid><description>
MAGIX VEGAS Pro provides an interface fully customizable brings maximum flexibility. Full of new features, both inside and outside, MAGIX VEGAS Pro create the power for your creativity. Whether you work in HD or 4K, VEGAS Pro willing to become a partner of your creativity. Video / Audio production, and DVD / Blu-ray authoring all in one powerful software package.
FEATURES, CHARACTERISTICS MAGIX VEGAS Pro
VEGAS Pro provides all the tools you need to edit your video quickly. Coding...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ashampoo Privacy Inspector 3.00.00</title><pubDate> Tue, 14 Oct 2025 20:33:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-privacy-inspector-8733.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-privacy-inspector-8733.html
</guid><description>
Windows keeps extensive records of what you do and when you do it on your PC (offline and online). So what is logged and more importantly, what can you do about it? Ashampoo Privacy Inspector lifts the veil of secrecy and shows you exactly what activities are logged along with the ability to erase your data and regain your privacy.
Features of Ashampoo Privacy Inspector
	See used objects neatly organized
	Delete confidential usage data securely
	Analysis of browsing behavior for all...
</description></item><item><title>Download DriversCloud 12.0.31</title><pubDate> Tue, 14 Oct 2025 20:33:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-driverscloud-6228.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-driverscloud-6228.html
</guid><description>
DriversCloud is a complex tool that helps you retrieve full data on your system configuration, both hardware and software, while simultaneously implementing additional maintenance tasks such as installing and updating drivers, tracking hard real-time or BSOD analysis. The incident. This tool does not only accurately detect your complete system configuration but also allows you to export this important data to PDF documents to allow you to easily share them online.
Not only did the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Directory Opus Pro 13.18.7 Beta</title><pubDate> Tue, 14 Oct 2025 20:32:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-opus-pro-779.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-opus-pro-779.html
</guid><description>
Directory Opus Pro is a software replacement for Explorer with traditional strength and function more than any manager other files. Directory Opus Pro full support for high DPI screen (for example 4K and 5K) with the rename dialog is redesigned, with new features. Besides being a recording macro only allows you to perform mass renaming complex that don't need regular expressions. In addition, Directory Opus Pro also enhances the ability to script.Better handling of renaming recursive and...
</description></item><item><title>Download CoolUtils Total Doc Converter 5.1.0.368/140</title><pubDate> Tue, 14 Oct 2025 20:32:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-total-doc-converter-84.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-total-doc-converter-84.html
</guid><description>
CoolUtils Total Doc Converter Program that will allow you to document conversion DOC to others, the list can be viewed on the official website or you can watch carefully the screenshot, I think the question would no longer can download CoolUtils Total Doc Converter below. There is batch processing,in general, everything is convenient, I hope you like it.
Total Doc Converter is conversion tools text comprehensive and multi-featured, very necessary when storing or printing the text. It also...
</description></item><item><title>Download KILHO AutoClick 1.4.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 14 Oct 2025 20:31:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kilho-autoclick-12515.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kilho-autoclick-12515.html
</guid><description>
AutoClick is a software or script designed to automate mouse clicking tasks, especially useful for repetitive actions in a variety of applications, including gaming and data entry. It allows users to define specific click points and automatically click at those locations. This tool is user-friendly and supports recording click sequences for repeated use.
AutoClick allows users to set precise time intervals and geographic coordinates for various click patterns. Additionally, AutoClick...
</description></item><item><title>Download Free Music and Video Downloader 3.09</title><pubDate> Tue, 14 Oct 2025 20:31:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-music-and-video-downloader-123.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-music-and-video-downloader-123.html
</guid><description>
Free Music &amp;amp; Video Downloader (formerly the Free Music Downloader) allows you to download his favorite music at the form of MP3 files from many different online sources, including Last.FM, Grooveshark, Sogou, VKontakte, SoundCloud, and many other things.Just enter name of artist or song you are looking for and click the Search button to see a list of results and download the songs you want.You can customize the services that applications will use to search, put the download folder...
</description></item><item><title>Download Photo Mechanic All-in-One 2025.10 build 8835</title><pubDate> Tue, 14 Oct 2025 20:31:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photo-mechanic-all-in-one-12282.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photo-mechanic-all-in-one-12282.html
</guid><description>
Photo Mechanic All-in-One is an image management software, photo collection and categorization of all photos on your computer, it allows you to Import, Edit and Export quickly, helping you reduce your work. work in the workflow. Powerful batch processing, full support for image variables, IPTC and Exif metadata, make it the perfect tool for any digital photographer.
Photo Mechanic All-in-One Features
	Photo Mechanic takes this step further by automating other tasks at the same time,...
</description></item><item><title>Download JWIZARD Cleaner 1.9.4</title><pubDate> Tue, 14 Oct 2025 20:30:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jwizard-cleaner-12853.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jwizard-cleaner-12853.html
</guid><description>
Effective Windows cleaning software to remove unnecessary files from your PC. JWIZARD Cleaner for Windows quickly frees up disk space and keeps your system in an optimal state, ensuring your PC runs stably and efficiently. This application is designed to provide you with a comprehensive tool to analyze and optimize your PC by performing a comprehensive cleanup or a more detailed cleanup, targeting specific areas such as system, browser, mail, etc.
Features of JWIZARD Cleaner
	Clean...
</description></item><item><title>Download Private Windows Script (PrivWindoze) 5.7.9</title><pubDate> Tue, 14 Oct 2025 20:29:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-private-windows-script-12878.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-private-windows-script-12878.html
</guid><description>
Are you concerned about your personal information sent to others? Or do you feel that your Windows settings have many programs that you never use? Private Windows Script (or Privwindoze) provides a comprehensive anti -remote monitoring set designed to enhance your privacy when using Windows operating system.
The main features
	End the positive process. All unnecessary processes are turned off while the scanning program. A small white list is maintained.
	Clean up the positive runonce....
</description></item><item><title>Download IsMyTouchScreenOK 3.03</title><pubDate> Tue, 14 Oct 2025 20:29:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ismytouchscreenok-11229.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ismytouchscreenok-11229.html
</guid><description>
With IsMyTouchScreenOK you can simply but very quickly check if there are any bad contacts on your touch screen. It can be used to test the functionality of a new touch screen before purchasing or to test a purchased touch screen during the warranty period. You may receive a replacement product after the manufacturer reports a contact failure.
By touching and testing all areas of the touchscreen with one or more fingers, you can ensure that the touchscreen is...
</description></item><item><title>Download OP Auto Clicker 4.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 14 Oct 2025 16:19:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-op-auto-clicker-4289.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-op-auto-clicker-4289.html
</guid><description>
OP Auto Clicker software auto mouse click advanced mode click at the mouse cursor, dynamic, or at a location to be determined in advance. The shortcut works on the system background should be very convenient to use. OP Auto Clicker is especially useful when you play games or work with the utility requires to click the mouse many times, quickly and repeated. It helps you get rid of the missions repetitive, boring by the creation of a list queue the click position on the screen.
OP Auto...
</description></item><item><title>Download CPU-Z 2.17</title><pubDate> Tue, 14 Oct 2025 16:17:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cpu-z-2240.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cpu-z-2240.html
</guid><description>
A wonderful development has been updated, in a simple way, can display technical information about the computer, your personal nature it will operate in Windows operating systems from version 98 to latest version 7. After starting, you can see the specifications of different sets of processing center, you can find out full data on the video card and motherboard, I forgot to add about RAM, download CPU-Z from our project in full news.
CPU-Z - Check CPU hardware
After installing, launch...
</description></item><item><title>Download EverNote 10.158.1.45283</title><pubDate> Tue, 14 Oct 2025 16:16:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-evernote-3261.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-evernote-3261.html
</guid><description>
EverNote is the all in one tool allows you to track notes, todo items, memos, outlines, excerpts, websites, ideas and other things and automatically synchronize them between multiple computers and mobile devices (iPhone, Android, etc.). You can choose to sort their notes into categories, password protect them, export them to XML and more. EverNote supports a number of pattern notes allow you to add to-do list, spreadsheet like Excel to calculate costs (automatic sum), notes, phone, contact...
</description></item><item><title>Download Turbo Studio 25.10.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 14 Oct 2025 16:15:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-turbo-studio-1797.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-turbo-studio-1797.html
</guid><description>
Turbo Studio (formerly known as Spoon Studio) - with this application you can combine the files needed to make the application run into a ready-to-use package without deployment. This application allows you to create a container program and run it virtually in a virtual environment without installing and making changes in the registry and system. Since driver and system updates are constantly being developed to reduce the likelihood of errors, applications may need to be rooted to your...
</description></item><item><title>Download MyLanViewer Enterprise 6.6.1 / Business</title><pubDate> Tue, 14 Oct 2025 16:14:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mylanviewer-enterprise-1274.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mylanviewer-enterprise-1274.html
</guid><description>
MyLanViewer is a program for scanning IP address, Netbios and LAN / Network powerful for Windows tool whois and traceroute, remote shutdown and process management Wake On LAN (WOL), scan and monitor wireless networks. This app will help you find all IP addresses, MAC addresses and shared folders of computers on the network wired or wireless (Wi-Fi).
MyLanViewer Enterprise - Scan IP address LAN/Network
The program scans network and displays the computer network in your window, friends...
</description></item><item><title>Download Photo Supreme 2025.3.3.8115</title><pubDate> Tue, 14 Oct 2025 16:13:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photo-supreme-430.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photo-supreme-430.html
</guid><description>
Photo Supreme is a software product management professional pictures of idimager. With Photo Supreme you can arrange, manage back stock photo archive of yourself and share them with you here and relatives easily via Email or Facebook. Photo Supreme provides users method to sort images effective, logical, as well as edit and share your photos with friends and relatives in the family. Especially the Photo Supreme allows to work with multiple image formats and support mounting support,...
</description></item><item><title>Download DU Meter 9.01</title><pubDate> Tue, 14 Oct 2025 16:13:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-du-meter-91.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-du-meter-91.html
</guid><description>
DU Meter provides users the ability to check the internet connection at any time. The software allows users to check download and upload speeds practice at different times. DU Meter also provides features press the clock to measure the exact download time of the communication line and report back. DU Meter really useful and necessary for parents to control their children use the internet or the manager supervision of his employees during office hours
DU Meter - Check the internet...
</description></item><item><title>Download Coolutils Total PDF Converter 6.5.0.356/149</title><pubDate> Tue, 14 Oct 2025 16:12:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-total-pdf-converter-830.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolutils-total-pdf-converter-830.html
</guid><description>
Coolutils Total PDF Converter is software to convert PDF convert PDF files to HTML, DOC (Word), text, Excel, PostScript, CSV or image files. The advantage of Coolutils Total PDF Converter is the fast, easy-to-handle, accurate, does not require Adobe Acrobat, supports many target format and have the option of batch (can convert hundreds of PDF files as well as the single file). Added to this, registered users get command line support to manage the utility with maximum...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ableton Live Suite 12.2.6</title><pubDate> Tue, 14 Oct 2025 16:12:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ableton-live-suite-663.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ableton-live-suite-663.html
</guid><description>
Ableton Live Suite is professional software to create, edit, music with effects, instruments, audio and all creative. Ableton Live Suite is the software fast, flexible and flexibility to create and perform music. Move freely between the musical elements and play with ideas, that don't stop the music and do not break the flow of your sound.
Features, Ableton Live Suite
	Meet Wavetable, Echo, Drum Buss and Pedal: the new equipment means new sounds, colorful can with the instruments and...
</description></item><item><title>Download MusConv 4.10.426 Lifetime</title><pubDate> Tue, 14 Oct 2025 16:10:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html
</guid><description>
MusConv transfers playlists, albums, followed artists and liked songs across a variety of services – Spotify, Apple Music, Amazon Music, YouTube, YouTube Music, iTunes, Deezer, Tidal, SoundCloud, Pandora and more 125 music services!
Features of MusConv Ultimate
	Transfer playlists, albums, followed artists and liked tracks between over 125 music servicesManage playlists (Delete, Merge, Split, Copy...)
	More than 125 music services supported
	Access DAILY updated music charts on...
</description></item></channel></rss>