<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 01:35:27 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 01:35:27 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download SmartSystemMenu 2.32.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 21 Sep 2025 02:54:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-smartsystemmenu-6018.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-smartsystemmenu-6018.html
</guid><description>
SmartSystemMenu will help to work with more windows becoming a more efficient process with many useful functions to arrange your work. It can be attached to the title bar menu for easy access. The fact that it can be portable is just another bonus because you can quickly upload it to the flash drive to use on any machine you might be using.
SmartSystemMenu will be a significant upgrade to the default Windows installation with the ability to be added to help with window management...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare PDFelement Pro 12.0.6.3738</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Sep 2025 17:24:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-pdfelement-pro-105.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-pdfelement-pro-105.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare PDFelement Pro support users to convert PDF to office documents for easier use, modify in every situation. Is one of the software conversion material is rated best today, integrated with many features. We recommend that you should use experience software many useful features this.
Wondershare PDFelement Pro - conversion Fie PDF more features, multi-language
Wondershare PDFelement Pro what?
Convert PDF into Word, Excel, PowerPoint...
• Convert PDF and protected PDF into...
</description></item><item><title>Download Master PDF Editor 5.9.95</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Sep 2025 17:24:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-master-pdf-editor-612.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-master-pdf-editor-612.html
</guid><description>
Master PDF Editor is a powerful software that helps users to view, create and modify PDF documents or combine multiple files into one, split a source document into several documents, and also review, sign, and encrypt PDF files. With Master PDF Editor you can add text with any format to documents in PDF or edit existing text. You can also insert images into your document, select and move the object, change the size of the object save image to a file and copy them to the...
</description></item><item><title>Download JRiver Media Center 34.0.70</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Sep 2025 17:22:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jriver-media-center-110.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jriver-media-center-110.html
</guid><description>
JRiver Media Center can help you strictly manage all your files media and enjoy them in a completely new way. Launching the application for the first time, users will be immediately impressed with the intuitive and eye-catching interface with many interesting features to explore. Most people who have used JRiver Media Center evaluate that the software interface design is youthful and modern.
The software for arranging cover art of music files is also extremely neat, especially Insert...
</description></item><item><title>Download SkinFiner 5.7.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Sep 2025 17:22:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-skinfiner-6346.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-skinfiner-6346.html
</guid><description>
SkinFiner  is photo editing software designed to free you from tedious manual work in skin retouching. It helps to smooth and strengthen the skin easily and quickly.
Features of SkinFiner
	Smartly smooths skin and removes blemishes while preserving skin texture to give portraits a natural and professional look
	Skin tone adjustment helps you to improve skin tone, change skin color, refine skin light with shadows and highlights, adjust skin brightness and contrast, make skin look...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mozilla Firefox 143.0.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Sep 2025 17:21:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-firefox-quantum-501.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-firefox-quantum-501.html
</guid><description>
Firefox Quantum is a web browser independently provide the tabbed browsing combined with numerous handy features like pop-up blocker, Bookmarks, direct (integrated RSS), password manager, and more. Functionality can be extended with dozens of plugins available for free (extensions).
Firefox Quantum are interface completely new, beautiful, neat, minimalistic and delicate, eats less RAM to 30% compared with the old version and solve the condition consuming capacity
Firefox can import all...
</description></item><item><title>Download MEmu Android Emulator 9.2.8</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Sep 2025 17:20:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-memu-2975.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-memu-2975.html
</guid><description>
MEmu or also known as Android Emulator is the Android emulator light and free, allowing Windows users to enjoy Android experience the original on the computer and device Microsoft their. This app provides outstanding performance, allowing you to play on PC a series of games designed to run on Android devices. This app allows you to play the game favorite Android on larger screens, to bring you a better gaming experience.
MEmu - Android emulator, lightweight and free
Software MEmu also...
</description></item><item><title>Download Any Video Downloader Pro 9.6.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Sep 2025 17:20:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-video-downloader-pro-3731.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-video-downloader-pro-3731.html
</guid><description>
Any Video Downloader Pro is software support you can download video HD 720p, 1080p, 2K, 4K and 8K from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion, Vimeo, Metacafe and thousands of video sharing sites, other. It is a tool to speed up multi-threading can speed up your download faster up to 5 times. This helpful program support download at the same time. Any Video Downloader Pro lets you download multiple videos at the same time. Moreover, it allows you to pause and resume downloads if you need more...
</description></item><item><title>Download R-Drive Image 7.3 Build 7310</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Sep 2025 17:19:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-drive-image-1971.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-drive-image-1971.html
</guid><description>
R-Drive Image is a powerful utility provides create a file disk image for backup purposes, or copy. File disk image contains the exact copy each and every byte of hard drive, partition or logical disk and can be created with various levels compression without stopping Windows os and therefore without interrupting your work. The image file this drive can then be stored in many places, including various removable media as different as a CD-R (W) / DVD, Iomega Zip or Jazz, etc.
R-Drive...
</description></item><item><title>Download WYSIWYG Web Builder 20.3.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Sep 2025 17:18:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wysiwyg-web-builder-177.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wysiwyg-web-builder-177.html
</guid><description>
WYSIWYG Web Builder : The construction of the website from scratch using HTML code isn't a pleasant process, even when you know what you are doing. The website can be built using WYSIWYG Web Builder with using the element similar to the package published on the desktop: text and images placed in frames and tables on the page, so very little surprised when most of the efforts to make the web become a experience user-friendly than. the controls do you use to build your pages.
WYSIWYG Web...
</description></item><item><title>Download R-Drive Image BootCD 7.3 Build 7310</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Sep 2025 17:18:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-drive-image-bootcd-4878.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-drive-image-bootcd-4878.html
</guid><description>
R-Drive Image BootCD is a powerful utility provides create a file disk image for backup purposes, or copy. File disk image contains the exact copy each and every byte of hard drive, partition or logical disk and can be created with various levels compression without stopping Windows os and therefore without interrupting your work. The image file this drive can then be stored in many places, including various removable media as different as a CD-R (W) / DVD, Iomega Zip or Jazz,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Automatic Email Processor 3.8.14</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Sep 2025 17:17:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-automatic-email-processor-702.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-automatic-email-processor-702.html
</guid><description>
Automatic Email Processor is a software for managing Email in Outlook efficiency by automatically working with predefined settings. The user interface is divided into two main parts, which is the area allows you to view a list of profiles that you have created and their status and the filters located in the lower part of the interface.
Automatic Email Processor is a comprehensive solution in the archive and print emails and attachments on Outlook fully-automatic. Therefore, you can create...
</description></item><item><title>Download Stardock Start11 2.5.5.3 Beta</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Sep 2025 17:16:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stardock-start11-7029.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stardock-start11-7029.html
</guid><description>
Start11 is an application capable of customizing the Start Menu and Taskbar on Windows 11 and Windows 10. This is an application that allows users to customize Windows 11 to suit their preferences. his personal. Start11 will help you bring the new Start Menu of Windows 11 to Windows 10. And vice versa, Start11 also helps you to bring the Start Menu of Windows 10 to Windows 11.
Start11 also helps users bring some functions of Windows 10 to Windows 11 through customizing the Taskbar such...
</description></item><item><title>Download DumboFab Blu-ray Ripper 7.3.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Sep 2025 17:16:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dumbofab-blu-ray-ripper-12024.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dumbofab-blu-ray-ripper-12024.html
</guid><description>
DumboFab Blu-ray Ripper is a widely used Blu-ray/DVD to MP4 conversion software in just a few minutes, to highly compressed HEVC, MKV (multi-track) and many other formats for playback again on iPhone, iPad, Android, HDTV, Mac, PSP, Xbox, VLC, etc.; Copy Blu-ray/DVD in 1:1 ratio with original quality.
Equipped with leading Blu-ray/DVD decoding algorithms, DumboFab Blu-ray Ripper supports copying almost all Blu-ray and DVD movies regardless of region restrictions. It also allows you to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cascadeur 2025.2.4</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Sep 2025 17:15:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cascadeur-9720.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cascadeur-9720.html
</guid><description>
Cascadeur is a standalone software for 3D keyframe animation of human figures or other characters. Never before has it been so easy and fun to create an animation from scratch or re-edit. Thanks to AI-powered tools, you can perform key poses very quickly, see the physical results immediately, and adjust the secondary movement. All while retaining full control at any point.
Cascadeur uses advanced simulation techniques and algorithms to accurately simulate the movements and interactions...
</description></item><item><title>Download Rowbyte Plexus 3.2.10</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Sep 2025 17:15:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rowbyte-plexus-524.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rowbyte-plexus-524.html
</guid><description>
Claire morris, bill maher Plexus is a plugins of Adobe After Effects allows you to create, manipulate and visualise data. Workflow Plexus allows you to create the configuration and parameter actually infinite. Plexus 3 comes with Table objects help you to organize many objects Plexus in the class. It significantly improves the workflow and myself, the control panel can be mounted anywhere with the After Effects.
Object Effector, objects rendered and the Group by allows you to choose...
</description></item><item><title>Download SepPDF 3.94</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Sep 2025 17:11:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-seppdf-924.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-seppdf-924.html
</guid><description>
SepPDF is a standalone tool simple allows you to split PDF document and create a PDF file for each page. SepPDF has a simple interface only provides access to a few configuration settings. The file can be added to the list by using the function drag and drop support of Wap or function built-in browser.
Advantages of SepPDF is the speed split pdf file was quite fast, with the capacity to compact software does not affect the operation performance of CPU as well as the performance of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download HE - Hardware Read and Write Utility 1.25.09.19</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Sep 2025 17:11:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-he-hardware-read-and-write-utility-4287.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-he-hardware-read-and-write-utility-4287.html
</guid><description>
HE - Hardware Read and Write Utility is a powerful utility intended for hardware engineer, engineer, BIOS developer, driver, engineer, QA engineers, performance test engineers, diagnostic, etc., this utility access almost all the computer hardware, including PCI (PCI Express), index / Data, PCI, memory, index memory / Data space I / O, Index I / O / Data, Super I / O, DIMM SPD, CPU The registers MSR, screen, SMART, physical area of the hard drive identification data, ATA, dump tables ACPI...
</description></item><item><title>Download XL-Connector 3.6.13.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Sep 2025 17:11:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xl-connector-12415.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xl-connector-12415.html
</guid><description>
XL-Connector is a popular plugin that securely integrates Excel and Salesforce to export, import, refresh and transform data seamlessly with ultra-fast api connection. It provides Salesforce administrators with a comprehensive toolbox that easily performs data and metadata management activities in a familiar Excel environment.
Features
Export from Salesforce to Excel
	Get data from existing Salesforce reports or build your own SOQL queries directly into Excel.
Import data into...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wing FTP Server Corporate 8.0.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Sep 2025 17:10:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wing-ftp-server-corporate-2752.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wing-ftp-server-corporate-2752.html
</guid><description>
Wing FTP Server Corporate is a highly functional, easy and safe can be used in the operating system Windows, Linux, Mac and Solaris are used. The software supports a number of file transfer protocol such as FTP, HTTP, FTPS, HTTPS and SFTP. Wing FTP Server provides web-based interface to manage the server at any time. You can also get performance server and the online and even send email notifications about various events happening on the server.
Management server multi-function
Wing FTP...
</description></item><item><title>Download CherryTree 1.6.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Sep 2025 17:10:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cherrytree-1041.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cherrytree-1041.html
</guid><description>
CherryTree is a software to create the hierarchical notes, save and sort notes, which in simple structure, easy to navigate. CherryTree carry to many tools and useful features than just insert and save text often. Each note in CherryTree are customized according to size, big in many different ways. Besides the ability to choose the font and font size, CherryTree also allows users to highlighting the section, paragraph, particular, settings changes, alignment changes, superscript and...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT-DL 11.6</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Sep 2025 17:09:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-dl-5876.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-dl-5876.html
</guid><description>
YT-DL is a small program to download videos from YouTube and other video sites. Our goal is to make the program as simple as its name.
The features of YT-DL
	Download the video from YouTube and other video sites
	Increase download speed up to 400%
	Download multiple videos at the same time
	Pause and continue to download at any time
	Preview video content while downloading
</description></item><item><title>Download MusConv 4.10.420 Lifetime</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Sep 2025 17:09:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html
</guid><description>
MusConv transfers playlists, albums, followed artists and liked songs across a variety of services – Spotify, Apple Music, Amazon Music, YouTube, YouTube Music, iTunes, Deezer, Tidal, SoundCloud, Pandora and more 125 music services!
Features of MusConv Ultimate
	Transfer playlists, albums, followed artists and liked tracks between over 125 music servicesManage playlists (Delete, Merge, Split, Copy...)
	More than 125 music services supported
	Access DAILY updated music charts on...
</description></item><item><title>Download JWIZARD Cleaner 1.9.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Sep 2025 17:09:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jwizard-cleaner-12853.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-jwizard-cleaner-12853.html
</guid><description>
Effective Windows cleaning software to remove unnecessary files from your PC. JWIZARD Cleaner for Windows quickly frees up disk space and keeps your system in an optimal state, ensuring your PC runs stably and efficiently. This application is designed to provide you with a comprehensive tool to analyze and optimize your PC by performing a comprehensive cleanup or a more detailed cleanup, targeting specific areas such as system, browser, mail, etc.
Features of JWIZARD Cleaner
	Clean...
</description></item><item><title>Download Robin YouTube Video Downloader Pro 6.17</title><pubDate> Sat, 20 Sep 2025 17:08:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-video-downloader-pro-2828.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-youtube-video-downloader-pro-2828.html
</guid><description>
YouTube Video Downloader Pro is a Windows application professional to download and convert videos from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion and thousands of video sharing sites, other. It accelerates your download up to 5 times. YouTube Video Downloader Pro allows you to download multiple videos at the same time. It also allows you to pause, resume and cancel a download at any time.
YouTube Video Downloader Pro - Download online videos on social networks
Features of YouTube Video Downloader...
</description></item></channel></rss>