<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 05:36:38 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 05:36:38 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Shotcut 25.07</title><pubDate> Mon, 28 Jul 2025 04:09:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-shotcut-2756.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-shotcut-2756.html
</guid><description>
Shotcut is a video editing application multi-platform free and open source for FreeBSD, Linux, macOS and Windows. Was started in 2011 by Dan Dennedy, Shotcut is developed on the multimedia MLT, which was developed from 2004. With age grow quite long years, Shotcut offers users many tools to perform the manipulation, Video editing based on adjusting each frame to enhance image quality. You can add an introduction, edit rate, bitrate, resolution or file encryption, and optionally use the...
</description></item><item><title>Download XMedia Recode 3.6.1.5</title><pubDate> Mon, 28 Jul 2025 04:08:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xmedia-recode-919.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xmedia-recode-919.html
</guid><description>
XMedia Recode is software to change the quality for video files on windows operating system, it has the ability to change quality, video format. XMedia Recode supports the format conversion such as 3GP, 3GPP, 3GPP2, AAC, AC3, AIFF, AMR, ASF, AU, AVI, DIVX, DTS, DVR-MS, FLV, H. 261, H. 263, H. 264, M4A, M1V, M2V, M4V, MKV.
Parameters advanced
The user can step into the more advanced and modify bitrate, frame interval the frame rate, modes, speed control and many other settings regarding...
</description></item><item><title>Download Internet Download Manager (IDM) 6.42 Build 42</title><pubDate> Sun, 27 Jul 2025 19:12:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-inetnet-download-manager-161.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-inetnet-download-manager-161.html
</guid><description>
Internet Download Manager is the download acceleration software, the best download support now, it can help you speed up the download up to five times, continue and schedule downloads. The latest version of IDM adds the compatibility of Windows 10 and Windows 11, it has supported all current popular browsers such as Internet Explorer, Mozilla Firefox, Opera, Google Chrome, ..
Download IDM with the latest version on taiwebs.com making it easy to download and manage your downloaded files...
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 6.7.8</title><pubDate> Sun, 27 Jul 2025 19:11:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-11-7760.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-11-7760.html
</guid><description>
TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 is a program that allows users to discover hidden settings in Windows 11. This application is specially designed for Windows 11, groups many registry settings and distribute them from the easy and secure user interface. With TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 you can move the Windows taskbar to the top and resize the taskbar by editing the registry value. With any application that modifies the registry, we recommend that you have a backup copy...
</description></item><item><title>Download Bulk Rename Utility 4.0.1.0 Commercial</title><pubDate> Sun, 27 Jul 2025 19:11:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bulk-rename-utility-2119.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bulk-rename-utility-2119.html
</guid><description>
Bulk Rename Utility is a utility batch rename allows you to easily rename multiple files and folders, based on the criteria flexible. Bulk Rename Utility lets you easily Add time / date stamp, replace numbers, insert text, convert case, add auto number, processing folder and sub-folder,..
Bulk Rename Utility - Change the name of the file series
Rename many files and / or directories has never been easier! It has a small memory footprint so it can be left running all the time without...
</description></item><item><title>Download IDM Retail 6.42 Build 42</title><pubDate> Sun, 27 Jul 2025 19:11:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-internet-download-manager-retail-3609.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-internet-download-manager-retail-3609.html
</guid><description>
IDM - Internet Download Manager Retail is a reliable utility and high efficiency will help you to increase your download speed and manage download at better. The program allows you to easily schedule, pause and resume downloads with a single click. Moreover, the application provides error resilience robust and can restart the download at the interrupted or broken. You can restore the download is interrupted due to network problems, lost connections, unexpected power outages, computer...
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 6.7.8</title><pubDate> Sun, 27 Jul 2025 19:10:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-10-7759.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-10-7759.html
</guid><description>
TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 is a utility that allows users to discover hidden settings in Windows 10. This application is specially designed for Windows 10, groups many registry settings and provide them from an easy and secure user interface. With TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 10 you can move the Windows taskbar to the top and resize the taskbar by editing the registry value. With any application that modifies the registry, we recommend that you have a backup copy to...
</description></item><item><title>Download AI Speech to text: Transcribe 1.28</title><pubDate> Sun, 27 Jul 2025 19:04:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ai-speech-to-text-transcribe-13800.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ai-speech-to-text-transcribe-13800.html
</guid><description>
Welcome to AI Speech to Text: Audio to Text, an innovative and sophisticated solution designed to enhance your transcription experience. Our AI Speech to Text app sets new standards in speech to text conversion by combining cutting-edge technology with user-friendly features. Whether you are a professional who wants to transcribe real-time conversations, an academic who needs to convert audio files, or a business professional managing important meeting notes, our AI audio to text...
</description></item><item><title>Download StbEmu (Pro) 2.0.16</title><pubDate> Sun, 27 Jul 2025 19:04:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-stbemu-pro-9840.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-stbemu-pro-9840.html
</guid><description>
StbEmu is an application for Android 5.0+, allowing downloading IPTV web portals, designed to run on IPTV STB (Set-Top-Box), on devices running Android, such as phones, tablets tablets and TV boxes. Currently, the application supports simulation of many STBs created by the Ukrainian company Infomir, such as MAG 250, MAG 270 or MAG 322.
StbEmu (Pro) for IPTV: Remember that this application is configured for a demo IPTV portal for testing purposes. If you want to use the app, you must...
</description></item><item><title>Download Photo Lab Picture Editor &amp;amp; Art 3.13.68</title><pubDate> Sun, 27 Jul 2025 19:04:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-photo-lab-picture-editor-art-13190.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-photo-lab-picture-editor-art-13190.html
</guid><description>
Join AI Photo Lab photo editor that lets you edit photos with face filters for photos, fashion photo effects and many photo art ideas. Amazing face collage maker, photo frames, photo effects and filters are here for you to enjoy. A smart and fast new way to turn any photo into a work of art — choose from over 50 preset styles and experience enhanced photo editing with the introduction of AI photo styles.
Key Features
	Photo Frames: Whether you want to highlight a memorable moment or...
</description></item><item><title>Download Shazam: Find Music &amp;amp; Concerts 16.2.0-250717</title><pubDate> Sun, 27 Jul 2025 19:04:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-shazam-music-discovery-10763.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-shazam-music-discovery-10763.html
</guid><description>
Shazam will identify any song in seconds. Discover, artists, lyrics, videos &amp;amp; playlists, all for free. Over 1 billion installs and counting. Use Pop-up Shazam to identify music in any app - Instagram, YouTube, TikTok... No connection? No problem! Shazam while offline.
Features of Shazam: Music Discovery
	Find the name of any song in seconds.
	Listen and add to Apple Music playlists.
	Follow along with time-synced lyrics.
	Watch music videos from Apple Music or YouTube.
	Enable...
</description></item><item><title>Download 3C All-in-One Toolbox 3.0.8c</title><pubDate> Sun, 27 Jul 2025 19:03:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-3c-all-in-one-toolbox-8399.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-3c-all-in-one-toolbox-8399.html
</guid><description>
3C All-in-One Toolbox combines many features into one giant toolbox with a modern and easy-to-use interface. All the tools you need to monitor, control and fine-tune all your Android devices. This app uses the Accessibility service to help you stop the app on non-rooted devices but will never collect any information.
Features of 3C All-in-One Toolbox
	Device Manager offers very powerful configurations, task scheduling, and device watchdogs that you can find to optimize performance and...
</description></item><item><title>Download PowerDirector - Video Editor 15.5.1 build 2507231</title><pubDate> Sun, 27 Jul 2025 19:03:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-powerdirector-video-editor-8123.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-powerdirector-video-editor-8123.html
</guid><description>
PowerDirector APK - Video Editor (Unlocked Version) is video editing software developed by CyberLink. It is available for Windows and Android devices. If you are looking for the Android version of PowerDirector, you can download the APK (Android Package Kit) file from the Google Play Store or from taiwebs.com.
Features of PowerDirector APK - Unlocked Version:
	Easy-to-use interface: PowerDirector has a user-friendly interface that makes it easy to edit and create videos, even if...
</description></item><item><title>Download Block Apps &amp;amp; Sites | Wellbeing 9.3.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 27 Jul 2025 19:02:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-block-apps-sites-wellbeing-8629.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-block-apps-sites-wellbeing-8629.html
</guid><description>
Block Apps &amp;amp; Sites&amp;nbsp;is an easy-to-use Android app that improves your self-control by blocking or limiting app usage and giving you insights into how you use it time on the phone. Whether you need to focus on your studies, don't want to be distracted at work, can't sleep at night, or want to socialize more, this app can help you out.
Select a group of apps and create a custom time schedule where these apps will be automatically blocked. The schedule is fully customizable,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Swiftly switch Pro 4.3.5</title><pubDate> Sun, 27 Jul 2025 19:02:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-swiftly-switch-pro-10045.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-swiftly-switch-pro-10045.html
</guid><description>
Swiftly Switch is an edge app that improves your Android experience by allowing you to use your phone with one hand and multitask faster! Swiftly Switch runs in the background and can be easily accessed from any screen with just a swipe from the edge screen. It's fast, battery-friendly, highly customizable, and ad-free.
Features of Swiftly switch for Android
	Recent apps switcher: Organize your recent apps in a floating circular sidebar. Switch between them with a swipe from the area...
</description></item><item><title>Download The Daily Telegraph 9.10.3</title><pubDate> Sun, 27 Jul 2025 19:02:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-the-daily-telegraph-11527.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-the-daily-telegraph-11527.html
</guid><description>
The Daily Telegraph app delivers the latest news and biggest stories as they happen, from our team of award-winning journalists in New South Wales, Australia and globally. Read today with our rich content, award-winning journalism and trusted local perspectives. We're proud to tell incredible stories every hour of every day with The Daily Telegraph app.
Main features:
Personalize your news feed
	Set your local news area, follow journalists and topics, along with your favorite codes...
</description></item><item><title>Download Duolingo: language lessons 6.40.3</title><pubDate> Sun, 27 Jul 2025 19:02:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-duolingo-language-lessons-8265.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-duolingo-language-lessons-8265.html
</guid><description>
Duolingo is a popular language learning app that offers interactive lessons to help users learn new languages. This application offers many languages for you to choose from, including Spanish, French, German, Italian, Portuguese, Chinese, Japanese and many more.
This app offers an gamified learning experience with interactive lessons, exercises, and quizzes designed to help users learn new words, phrases, and grammar rules. This app is designed to be easy to use and suitable for people...
</description></item><item><title>Download Multi Timer StopWatch 2.13.17 build 482</title><pubDate> Sun, 27 Jul 2025 19:01:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-multi-timer-stopwatch-8914.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-multi-timer-stopwatch-8914.html
</guid><description>
Multi Timer is a beautifully designed time management app. Multiple timers can be set, started and run independently at the same time. Stopwatch results can be stored. Use Multi Timer for cooking, sports, machine washing, studying, working, gaming - whatever you like.
Features of Multi Timer StopWatch
	Multiple timers at once: Store the timers you often use for cooking, sports, studying, working, gaming, whatever you want. Start them with just one tap, anytime you need.
	Timer in...
</description></item><item><title>Download Memento Database 5.6.3</title><pubDate> Sun, 27 Jul 2025 19:01:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-memento-database-11185.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-memento-database-11185.html
</guid><description>
Memento Database is a powerful and user-friendly tool designed to work with any data, helping to store, organize, calculate and visualize information. It is more convenient than spreadsheets, more flexible than dedicated applications. If you are looking for a program to organize personal matters, hobbies or small or medium-sized businesses, Memento is the solution.
Personal use 
Memento can replace dozens of applications, helping you organize your life and increase your...
</description></item><item><title>Download Power Shortcuts 1.4.6</title><pubDate> Sun, 27 Jul 2025 19:01:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-power-shortcuts-10040.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-power-shortcuts-10040.html
</guid><description>
This app uses the Accessibility Service to perform some of its features. Some of the features of this app are implemented by the Android framework's unofficial (non-open) API. This means they are not guaranteed to work properly on all Android devices.
Features of Power Shortcuts
	Apps: Set some predefined settings when launching an app.
	Activities: Find out some hidden activities on your device.
	Intents: Try out many predefined intents or create your own.
	Content: Quickly open one...
</description></item><item><title>Download ACR Phone 0.372</title><pubDate> Sun, 27 Jul 2025 19:00:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-acr-phone-10805.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-acr-phone-10805.html
</guid><description>
ACR Phone &amp;amp; Dialer Spam call blocker is a phone app that can replace your default dialer. This is a completely new application and we are constantly improving it.
Features of ACR Phone
	Blacklist/Block spam
	Call person to notify
	Call notes
	Backup
	Outgoing call blocker
	Call log
	Supports dual SIM
	Contacts
	Video call and photo call screen
	SIP client (on supported devices)
	Call recording (on supported devices)
	Cloud Upload
	Auto Dialer
	Visual voicemail
</description></item><item><title>Download Colorimeter 2.25.18</title><pubDate> Sun, 27 Jul 2025 19:00:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-colorimeter-13047.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-colorimeter-13047.html
</guid><description>
Discover the ultimate app for professional color capture and analysis, widely used by designers, scientists, architects, artists, personal color consultants, developers, and color enthusiasts.
Key Features
	Smart Capture: Instantly recognize colors through your camera or photo library with scientific-grade accuracy.
	Professional Analysis: Complete convert in RGB, HEX, CMYK, HSV, HSL, XYZ, CIE Lab, LCh, RYB, Luminance, Binary, Wavelength, and more.
	Paint palettes: Extract color...
</description></item><item><title>Download Busuu: Learn &amp;amp; Speak Languages 32.17.2(1393986)</title><pubDate> Sun, 27 Jul 2025 19:00:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-busuu-learn-languages-8400.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-busuu-learn-languages-8400.html
</guid><description>
Busuu: Learn Languages is a mobile application that allows users to learn and practice various languages ​​on their Android devices. It includes various features such as interactive lessons, flashcards, quizzes, and exercises designed to help users learn and practice vocabulary, grammar, and conversation skills. The app also includes many customizable settings, such as the ability to choose between different languages ​​and set learning goals.
Busuu Features: Learn...
</description></item><item><title>Download Image Size - Photo Resizer 9.9</title><pubDate> Sun, 27 Jul 2025 18:59:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-image-size-photo-resizer-12071.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-image-size-photo-resizer-12071.html
</guid><description>
This app allows you to resize images to any size you like (with limitations), quickly and easily. It is actually a resizing application. You can specify the output format using one of the following four measurement units: pixels, millimeters, centimeters, inches. To maintain aspect ratio, simply tap the chain icon between the width and height input fields. Image Dimensions gives you the option to save, email, print, or share the final image.
Main features:
	Resize photos or images...
</description></item><item><title>Download Easy Notes - Note Taking Apps 1.3.18.0716</title><pubDate> Sun, 27 Jul 2025 18:59:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-easy-notes-notebook-notepad-8388.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-easy-notes-notebook-notepad-8388.html
</guid><description>
Easy Notes - Great note taking app, Notepad, Notebook, Free Notes is a free easy to use note taking app for notes app. With this easy notebook and notepad app, take quick notes with colorful backgrounds and checklists to organize notes and tasks easily. Use this aesthetic note taker and note taker to add photos or audio to your notes. Easy Notes is a useful notebook and note-taking app for taking notes and organizing work.
Features of Easy Notes - Notebook, Notepad
	Free Notepad and...
</description></item></channel></rss>