<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 20:37:36 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 20:37:36 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Ashampoo Burning Studio 2026 2026 v1.27.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:26:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-burning-studio-free-7691.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-burning-studio-free-7691.html
</guid><description>
Ashampoo Burning Studio Free is a reliable and feature-rich recording software with everything you need to burn and backup data, rip music discs, create audio discs or burn existing videos, such as MP4 files, photos to Blu-ray and more! With an intuitive interface, the program is also ideal for beginners who will achieve great results quickly.
Features of Ashampoo Burning Studio Free
	100% free to use.
	Easily burn data in a variety of formats, including CD, DVD and Blu-ray...
</description></item><item><title>Download PIDKey Lite 1.64.4 b53</title><pubDate> Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:25:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pidkey-lite-2693.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pidkey-lite-2693.html
</guid><description>
PIDKey Lite is a program intended to show the renovation and preservation in the database of the product information to check "validity" of the key Microsoft from the famous program we or is Ratiborus and VAMT. Program PIDKey LiteIt is the successor of the PIDKey. and I got out of it the idea the best program (allows you To add new keyboard with two methods additional mode key).
The program has a number of configuration integration, but you can also create custom profiles by themselves....
</description></item><item><title>Download PassFab 4EasyPartition 3.10.0.16</title><pubDate> Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:24:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-passfab-4easypartition-7983.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-passfab-4easypartition-7983.html
</guid><description>
After using your PC for many years, there are bound to be many files you want to transfer to your new PC. PassFab 4EasyPartition can perform a one-click migration saving you hours of reinstalling operating systems and applications. It has an intuitive interface and step-by-step wizard that makes migrating the system in just a few steps. PassFab 4EasyPartition will effectively solve the problem of low disk space, speed up your computer and make it run faster.
Features of PassFab...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Acrobat Reader DC 2025.001.21151</title><pubDate> Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:23:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-acrobat-reader-3707.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-acrobat-reader-3707.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Acrobat Reader DC is a system of application software and Web services developed by Adobe Systems to view, create, manipulate, print and manage PDF files. With Adobe Acrobat Reader DC, you can create, export, edit, and track PDF files from anywhere - and maintain connection with the recent set of files on all your devices.
Adobe Acrobat Reader current DC is connected with Adobe Document Cloud - help working on the computers and mobile devices becomes easier than ever before. This is...
</description></item><item><title>Download TeamViewer QuickSupport 15.74.4</title><pubDate> Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:23:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-teamviewer-quicksupport-1933.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-teamviewer-quicksupport-1933.html
</guid><description>
A different version of TeamViewer is TeamViewer QuickSupport is a solution easy to use allows you to share your desktop with a users TeamViewer other to receive technical support or other support. All what you need to do is run the TeamViewer QuickSupport and provides for the remote user ID and your password to grant access to the computer to your desk. Only people you trust can connect to your computer and access password will automatically change after each session.
The software also...
</description></item><item><title>Download App Builder 2026.4</title><pubDate> Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:22:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-app-builder-241.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-app-builder-241.html
</guid><description>
App Builder is a software application developer to help create and design apps, HTML5, web app, web app PWA on both platforms mobile and desktop. App Builder is professional software supports users to create the program HTML5 without writing code. It is very easy to use, suitable with all users who lack of professional knowledge in the field of programming and application design.
App Builder brings to 22 different themes that users can use to design for your app. You can choose 1 or a...
</description></item><item><title>Download MaxCut Business Edition 2.9.6.4</title><pubDate> Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:22:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-maxcut-business-edition-3912.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-maxcut-business-edition-3912.html
</guid><description>
MaxCut Business Edition is a software to create cutting diagrams, accurate, and cost estimate for the wood industry, cabinets and metal,.. You enter the size and material, MaxCut will do the rest! Produce optimized cutting diagrams, create estimates, orders, and labels - it's just a click. Run the application MaxCut Business Edition brings a pretty clean interface and slick quickly get you up and running. Most space represents the editing area, with the main function are stored cleverly in...
</description></item><item><title>Download Opera One 127.0.5778.14</title><pubDate> Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:22:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-972.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-972.html
</guid><description>
Opera is a fast, safe, configurable and compliant intranet web browser, which includes both the reader and the application. The Opera browser supports web browsing, listening to music, watching high speed movies, you can open many tabs on the Opera without affecting your browsing speed. Opera now supports almost all devices and operating systems such as windows, IOS, Android, linux, MacOS ...
Opera is a beautiful interface and many interesting features, operating on both PCs and mobile,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Zoom Player Max 22.2 Beta 2</title><pubDate> Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:21:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zoom-player-max-104.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zoom-player-max-104.html
</guid><description>
Zoom Player MAX help you to see the film on DVD, Blu-ray, Flash movies and HD format with high quality and the ability to display subtitles in English very well. The advantage of software is that takes up very little system resources to play the movie with quick speed, change the wallpaper options while viewing movies.
Zoom Player MAX is the movies, browse high-quality photos on the computer with the advantages such as compact size, quick start, built-in codec. The application supports...
</description></item><item><title>Download 4DDiG Partition Manager 3.10.0.16</title><pubDate> Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:21:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4ddig-partition-manager-2024-9781.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4ddig-partition-manager-2024-9781.html
</guid><description>
4DDiG Partition Manager is a powerful Windows disk partition software expert in system migration, disk cloning and disk partition management. It can effectively clone your entire disk or partition, providing a reliable solution for data backup.
This is Windows 10 fast system and data transfer solution &amp;amp; 11. 4DDiG Partition Manager can move the system and large files or folders from one disk partition to a larger one with just one click. Or you can use it to move the system and large...
</description></item><item><title>Download Lightmap HDR Light Studio 9.3.1.2025.1225</title><pubDate> Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:20:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lightmap-hdr-light-studio-xenon-5459.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lightmap-hdr-light-studio-xenon-5459.html
</guid><description>
HDR Light Studio software gives 3D artists a new way to illuminate 3D images. Adorn your photos with lights. Lighting process is now easy, fast, accurate, creative and fun. HDR Light Studio builds the lighting used by your existing 3D rendering software and renderers. By adding HDR Light Studio, 3D artists become more productive and image quality improves.
When combining photography and CG images, combining light between the image content and CG elements is the key to a successful and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Markdown Monster 4.1.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:19:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-markdown-monster-2640.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-markdown-monster-2640.html
</guid><description>
Markdown Monster is the edit and view Markdown allows you to edit Markdown by syntax highlighting and fast text input. Live preview can collapse, synchronized allows you to see the output of when you enter. You can easily embed images, links, emoticons and code in text form or by using the support UI lightness of we to simplify many operations. You can also paste and drag images directly into the editor.
Markdown Monster is a solution comprehensive software designed to solve almost any...
</description></item><item><title>Download EMDB 5.41</title><pubDate> Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:19:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-emdb-64.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-emdb-64.html
</guid><description>
EMDB (Eric's Movie Database) allows you to sort and catalog collection DVD of you.All you have to do is enter the title (or part of it) and the program will enter the detail information and movie cover image from a selection database online.You can then add personal ratings, customize the details, replace cover photo and also set the path local file (if you have a digital copy on your disk).
EMDB - sort and catalog collection DVD of you
Other features include an option to track movies...
</description></item><item><title>Download CalendarTask (formerly DesktopCal) 3.26.266.8492</title><pubDate> Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:18:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopcal-1831.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopcal-1831.html
</guid><description>
CalendarTask (formerly DesktopCal) is a simple desktop calendar that blends into your desktop without blocking access to your desktop icons. You can double-click on a date to quickly add notes and also jump to specific dates in the past or future.
CalendarTask - Computer calendar
CalendarTask can use your current wallpaper or loop through images from your folder and update your desktop every few minutes. The program helps you make appointments, make plans... Not only that, the Screen...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cygwin 3.6.6</title><pubDate> Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:18:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cygwin-3236.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cygwin-3236.html
</guid><description>
Cygwin is designed to provide functionality similar to Linux distribution on Windows with many application options to be compiled first. Cygwin is a *nix environments in Windows by creating a compatibility Layer. Through which Windows users can run the app which is still popular on Linux, Unix after program that is transferred through Cygwin. Current Cygwin running on the official version of Windows since Windows Vista.
Cygwin comes with the installer to ensure you have the latest...
</description></item><item><title>Download X-Ability Winmostar 11.14.4</title><pubDate> Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:17:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-x-ability-winmostar-11156.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-x-ability-winmostar-11156.html
</guid><description>
Winmostar is an integrated GUI software designed for simulation programs such as GAMESS, MOPAC, LAMMPS, Gromacs and Quantum ESPRESSO. Winmostar serves as an integrated software solution, using programs (solvers) for MO, DFT and MD calculations as its backend. It provides pre- and post-processing capabilities, as well as file and process management functions. Software supported solvers include GAMESS, MOPAC, LAMMPS, Gromacs and Quantum ESPRESSO. Winmostar is designed to be installed and...
</description></item><item><title>Download RapidGrade 1.5.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:16:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rapidgrade-14512.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rapidgrade-14512.html
</guid><description>
RapidGrade is a color grading plugin designed for DaVinci Resolve, offering cinematic effects with just one click, film simulation, and color grading tools aimed at speeding up the professional color grading process. It is positioned as part of a larger training and plugin ecosystem (QazVerse) rather than a completely standalone product.
Key features include:
Core color grading tool
	One-touch settings, applying all available color corrections in a single button, giving you an...
</description></item><item><title>Download SoftPerfect RAM Disk 26.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:15:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-softperfect-ram-disk-4359.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-softperfect-ram-disk-4359.html
</guid><description>
SoftPerfect RAM Disk is a program disk, RAM performance is designed to help you have a disk on the computer is stored completely in memory. Because memory is much faster than physical hard disk, should store temporary data on disk in fast memory to achieve higher performance. Whether your job is what, keep reading to find out if a RAM disk can offer you what. The program creates a virtual disk located in the computer RAM accessible in Windows Explorer and other applications, allowing you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tower 11.0.543</title><pubDate> Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:14:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tower-6598.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tower-6598.html
</guid><description>
Tower is software that helps you build better software, over 100,000 developers and designers are more productive with Tower, the most powerful Git client for Mac and Windows.
Tower Features
	Beautiful new features like interactive facility or Quick Actions and tons of improvements
	Undo everything
	Unique Conflict Wizard
	File history
	Rich documents
	Great customer support...
	Tower helps you master version control with Git.
	One-click cloning
	Automatically store and fetch
	Quickly...
</description></item><item><title>Download BitRecover PST to PDF Wizard Pro 26.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:13:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bitrecover-pst-to-pdf-wizard-9707.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bitrecover-pst-to-pdf-wizard-9707.html
</guid><description>
BitRecover PST to PDF Wizard is a software tool designed to convert Microsoft Outlook PST files into PDF format. PST files are personal archive files used by Microsoft Outlook to store email, contacts, calendar entries, and other data. On the other hand, PDF (Portable Document Format) is a widely used file format for sharing and preserving documents.
BitRecover PST to PDF Wizard provides a simple and user-friendly interface to convert PST files to PDF. It allows you to select individual...
</description></item><item><title>Download MemoryCleaner 1.9.4</title><pubDate> Mon, 02 Feb 2026 17:11:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-memorycleaner-12469.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-memorycleaner-12469.html
</guid><description>
MemoryCleaner is a tool to free up memory on your computer. This is a free app with a simple user interface that makes it easy for users of all skill levels to use. MemoryCleaner uses many functions built into Windows to free up memory without affecting your system. You can also access Memory Cleaner's functions right from the system tray without having to open the program. The cleaning processes are silent and the only time you see a warning is to briefly display the amount of RAM...
</description></item><item><title>Download Executor 2.2.3.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 02 Feb 2026 17:10:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-executor-271.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-executor-271.html
</guid><description>
Executor for windows is a software alternative premium customization features for the Windows "Run" and "Search Programs". When you press WIN + Z and provides the search results instant, as-you-type for any keywords you enter. By default, Executor will index all the Desktop and Start Menu and you can easily expand the search range by adding the folder location additional.
Executor for windows
The program comes with a list of commands built in which you can use to quickly access many...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDFgear 2.1.15</title><pubDate> Mon, 02 Feb 2026 17:09:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdfgear-9049.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdfgear-9049.html
</guid><description>
PDFgear is a PDF reader and editor that combines PDF editing functionality with an AI (artificial intelligence) assistant powered by ChatGPT. The user-friendly product PDFgear offers options that you cannot find in Adobe Acrobat. It's great that you can change the color of your comments with simple clicks.
PDFgear is a full-featured PDF editor that basically helps me do everything I need: edit, convert, form, signature, etc. The interface is intuitive and familiar, and all the features...
</description></item><item><title>Download XYplorer 28.20.0100</title><pubDate> Mon, 02 Feb 2026 17:07:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-533.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-533.html
</guid><description>
XYplorer - File Manager for Windows is software that supports users to manage files on the Window quickly and to arrange the folder tidy. XYplorer features tabbed browsing, search, files, powerful, preview, flexible, highly customizable interface, dual frame options and a variety of unique ways to automate effective tasks often repeat. It's fast, lightweight, and portable.
Features XYplorer
	XYplorer is a file manager mobile. It does not require any settings, store all configuration...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ratiborus KMS Tools Lite 01.02.2026</title><pubDate> Mon, 02 Feb 2026 17:06:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ratiborus-kms-tools-lite-11160.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ratiborus-kms-tools-lite-11160.html
</guid><description>
Ratiborus KMS Tools Lite is a collection of activators from Ratiborus for Windows XP, Vista, 7, 8, 8.1, 10, 11, Windows Server, Office 2010/2013/2016/2019 /2021/2024. It includes several utilities, each with its own set of features, mainly aimed at activating Microsoft Windows and Office products. The program is used to activate Microsoft products such as Windows and Office using Key Management Service (KMS). With a simple, easy-to-use interface that allows users to activate the product...
</description></item></channel></rss>