<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 23:37:49 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 23:37:49 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download MakeMKV 1.18.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 27 Sep 2025 01:06:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-makemkv-3126.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-makemkv-3126.html
</guid><description>
MakeMKV is the solution a click of your mouse to convert video that you own into free format and the patent can be found everywhere. MakeMKV is a format converter, otherwise called "transcoder". It converts the video clips from disc proprietary (and usually encrypted) into a set of files MKV, keeping most information but not changing it in any way. MKV format can store more music / video with all the meta information and retention programs. There are many the player can playback files MKV...
</description></item><item><title>Download Advanced Renamer Commercial 4.17</title><pubDate> Sat, 27 Sep 2025 01:05:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-renamer-2647.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-renamer-2647.html
</guid><description>
Advanced Renamer is a program to rename multiple files and folders at the same time. By configuring the method name change, the name can be manipulated in many different ways. It's easy to set up a batch job using multiple methods on a large number of files. 14 different modes allow you to change the name, attributes and timestamp of the file in once. The file can also be copied or moved to new location based on information in the file.
The program can rename files in many different ways,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Irix HDR Pro 2.3.51</title><pubDate> Sat, 27 Sep 2025 01:05:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-irix-hdr-pro-10653.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-irix-hdr-pro-10653.html
</guid><description>
Irix HDR Pro is an AI-powered photo editing application for Windows, it is available on Microsoft Store. This program has tons of professional HDR photo editing features including Sky Replacement, Face Sculpting &amp;amp; body, over 200 presets &amp;amp; AI powered tool' and is a Photo Editor in the category of photo &amp;amp; Graphics. It delivers true-to-life HDR photo editing, providing one-click edits for a full-scale professional editing toolkit.
Features of Irix HDR Pro
	Sky Replacement...
</description></item><item><title>Download BluffTitler Ultimate 16.7.7.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 27 Sep 2025 01:05:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bluffTitler-ultimate-39.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bluffTitler-ultimate-39.html
</guid><description>
Create 3D titles brilliant for your video with BluffTitler Ultimate. You want to impress your friends and clients with 3D titles interesting? But don't want to spend a fortune on 3D animation, as well as professional software video titling?
BluffTitler is the easiest way to add animated text, 3D spectacular for photos and videos of you! Other 3D programs always seemed too hard to learn and too expensive to justify. But thanks to BluffTitler, I can finally create all the wonderful...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Acrobat Pro DC 2025.001.20744 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Sat, 27 Sep 2025 01:04:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-001en-adobe-acrobat-pro-458.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-001en-adobe-acrobat-pro-458.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Acrobat Pro DC is a comprehensive software that helps you create and edit the PDF&amp;nbsp;document, or create form, sign, protect PDF, connect, split PDF, export PDF to various formats. The Acrobat Pro DC is the latest version of Adobe with improvements in the interface with the polished ribbon bar and the ability to create and handle pdf files as well as its male versions.
The highlight of the Acrobat Pro DC is probably the ability to connect, store documents on the cloud, you can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Leawo Prof. Media 13.0.0.7</title><pubDate> Sat, 27 Sep 2025 01:03:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-leawo-prof-media-1349.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-leawo-prof-media-1349.html
</guid><description>
Leawo Prof. Media is the conversion tool that include rich media offers many solutions between the video up to 1080P, DVD, Blu-ray, online video, audio and images, with bonus features, incredible. Leawo Prof. Media is software integrated many tools in a single program.
Leawo Prof. Media includes the HD video converter Program audio converter free, DVD Ripper, Blu-ray Creator, DVD Copy, DVD Creator, Photo slideshow Maker, Photo slideshow burner and YouTube Downloader free, adapter means...
</description></item><item><title>Download Irix HDR Classic Pro 2.3.51</title><pubDate> Sat, 27 Sep 2025 01:02:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-irix-hdr-classic-pro-10652.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-irix-hdr-classic-pro-10652.html
</guid><description>
Irix HDR Classic Pro is an AI-powered photo editor that delivers true-to-life HDR photo editing, providing one-click edits to the editing toolkit professional at full scale with a highly cognitive user interface (UI).
Main features:
	Sky replacement (SkyXpress): replaces the sky and imports weather. Import custom skies and merge, blend, and integrate with your images for a natural look with AI Edge Detect.
	Presets &amp;amp; Filters: 200+ social media optimized presets with just one tap...
</description></item><item><title>Download Synchredible Professional 9.002</title><pubDate> Sat, 27 Sep 2025 01:02:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-synchredible-professional-1923.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-synchredible-professional-1923.html
</guid><description>
Synchredible Professional is the most advanced version help synchronize the folder and your drive quickly and easily. Whether it is a single file or an entire drive - Synchredible Professional will synchronize, copy and save them for you. The software guide will assist you to identify the work that is scheduled in advance or be done through the USB connection. This way, you can keep your files in sync - automatically.
In the past years, the advanced technology of the us in Synchredible...
</description></item><item><title>Download Atlantis Word Processor 5.0.0.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 27 Sep 2025 01:01:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-atlantis-word-processor-585.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-atlantis-word-processor-585.html
</guid><description>
Atlantis Word Processor is a word processor app with features format, standard text, autocorrect, and spell check.  Atlantis is a word processor in accordance with most of the tasks handled daily text. The interface is very easy to use and offers the toolbars, hotkeys and sound effects thanh can customize (can turn off). It includes a clip library for quick access to the text or images used regular preview, font format and many other features aimed at improving the process of your...
</description></item><item><title>Download ExpanDrive 2025.09.22</title><pubDate> Sat, 27 Sep 2025 01:01:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-expandrive-609.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-expandrive-609.html
</guid><description>
ExpanDrive is software sync cloud storage strong support BackBlaze B2, Google Team Drive, SMB / CIFS and new interface and easy user search file version, share links and much more.  ExpanDrive mapped network drives for macOS and Micosoft Windows connect with all the provide major cloud storage such as Dropbox, Google Drive, Google Team Drive, Amazon Drive, Box, OneDrive, OneDrive for Business, Sharepoint, Openstack Swift , BackBlaze B2, Amazon S3 or SFTP servers, FTP or WebDAV on your own...
</description></item><item><title>Download Macrium Reflect X Server (WinPE) 10.0.8665</title><pubDate> Sat, 27 Sep 2025 01:01:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-macrium-reflect-winpe-7237.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-macrium-reflect-winpe-7237.html
</guid><description>
Macrium Reflect's image-based backup and disaster recovery solutions have taken another big leap forward in speed, simplicity, and power. The whole focus of Macrium Reflect is on helping organizations protect their business-critical data and systems without causing hassles and breaking budget costs.
Features of Macrium Reflect WINPE
	New Backup Engine: Up to 60x Faster Incremental and Differential Images
	Quick virtual startup of backup images: instantly create, start, and manage...
</description></item><item><title>Download Pazu StreamGet All-In-One Video Downloader 2.8.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 27 Sep 2025 01:00:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pazu-streamget-all-in-one-video-downloader-12037.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pazu-streamget-all-in-one-video-downloader-12037.html
</guid><description>
StreamGet All-In-One Video Downloader is the ultimate downloading solution for you. It supports downloading any movies and shows from the most popular streaming sites including Netflix, Prime Video, Disney Plus, Max, Hulu, and Apple TV Plus. The downloader is continuously updated to support more platforms in the future.
Download movies and shows from various streaming platforms to MP4/MKV on your Windows device and enjoy them anywhere you want.
Features of Pazu StreamGet All-In-One...
</description></item><item><title>Download Synchredible 9.002</title><pubDate> Sat, 27 Sep 2025 01:00:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-synchredible-53.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-synchredible-53.html
</guid><description>
Synchredible is an easy to use tool to synchronize folders and files. It provides a wizard interface lets you set up the sync job, select files to exclude, schedule the job to execute automatically, and more.Additional features include support for network and external drives, check CRC32, and more.
Synchredible - synchronization of folders and files
Among other things, you can use the filter for the file type specific data synchronization according to the time or routine deletion of...
</description></item><item><title>Download iZotope Trash 3 1.3.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 27 Sep 2025 00:59:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-izotope-trash-2843.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-izotope-trash-2843.html
</guid><description>
iZotope Trash is plugins audio iconic will allow you to distort audio signals, add effects, carry a set of instruments in full on the train, is a favorite of many musicians, including: Garbage, KoЯn, Sigur R, etc. If you want to add "dirt" and achieve a unique sound for its music, then it is better not to find a plugin. Because this version is Monday, it is worth noting that this tool has undergone many changes after the release of the first version was released back in 2008. You will get...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Downloader 9.17.6</title><pubDate> Sat, 27 Sep 2025 00:59:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html
</guid><description>
YTD Youtube Downloader is an application that reliable and intuitive, allowing you to quickly download YouTube videos and save them to your computer. You can also convert the media files to the format desired video or extract audio streams and save separately. YTD Youtube Downloader lets you save your favorite clips of yourself from Youtube, Facebook, Vimeo and Dailymotion to your desktop. The software supports URLS from many web site hosting, multimedia and allows you to download desired...
</description></item><item><title>Download PanFone Manager 1.3.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 27 Sep 2025 00:58:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-panfone-manager-6104.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-panfone-manager-6104.html
</guid><description>
PanFone Manager is an Android/iOS data management tool! Free management, transfer, backup, recovery and deletion of mobile image data on Windows PCs. A click to transmit music, videos, movies, television shows and other media files freely between iOS/Android devices and PCs without reducing the quality.
Features of PanFone Manager
	Music, photos, videos, contacts, etc. between PC and mobile phones.
	Music management, editing songs and removing duplicate tracks on iOS/Android...
</description></item><item><title>Download PanFone iOS Eraser Pro 1.3.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 27 Sep 2025 00:58:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-panfone-ios-eraser-pro-5579.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-panfone-ios-eraser-pro-5579.html
</guid><description>
PanFone iOS Eraser Pro is a software that allows you to permanently delete 29 types of all existing data and deleted files, including SMS, contacts, call history, photos and videos, notes, bookmarks, calendar, reminders, etc. from iPhone / iPad / iPod without any chance of recovery. There are a lot of temporary files, junk files, trash and caches created on your iOS device with daily usage, which will make your phone run slowly. 1 click to free up massive space and speed up your iPhone,...
</description></item><item><title>Download BricsCad Ultimate 25.2.09.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 23:29:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bricscad-ultimate-3256.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bricscad-ultimate-3256.html
</guid><description>
BricsCad Ultimate is a software solution, CAD powerful and comprehensive, providing both tools advanced 2D and model 3D live smart on Linux and windows platform. Utility that allows you to sort the file DWG in hierarchical structures and allows you to easily assemble their products with the help of a set of tools and ingredients powerful 3D.
BricsCad Ultimate allows you to rotate and move any part of your model to solve all problems kinematics in real time. The program also allows you to...
</description></item><item><title>Download FrontFace Lockdown Tool 5.5.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 23:28:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-frontface-lockdown-tool-6281.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-frontface-lockdown-tool-6281.html
</guid><description>
FrontFace Lockdown Tool is software that allows you to protect and lock any Windows PC to use as a public kiosk terminal, digital signage application or other non-monitoring use. The program allows you to disable multiple features and functionality of Windows to prevent users from making changes to the operating system. This includes options to hide the system tray, turn off the Machine and Log out, disable the Windows key and Task Manager, prevent changes in the password, turn off the...
</description></item><item><title>Download RocketCake Professional 6.4</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 23:26:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rocketcake-professional-2632.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rocketcake-professional-2632.html
</guid><description>
RocketCake Professional is a WYSIWYG HTML editor that allows you to create a website based on the responsive template without coding. Simply choose your template and customize it or create a new design from scratch.In addition to text content you can add images, galleries, slideshows, YouTube videos, Flash, buttons, audio / video HTML5, table and many page elements enhance the other.
RocketCake Professional - design application Website
Allows you to create a website as quickly as...
</description></item><item><title>Download HE - Hardware Read and Write Utility 1.25.09.26</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 23:25:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-he-hardware-read-and-write-utility-4287.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-he-hardware-read-and-write-utility-4287.html
</guid><description>
HE - Hardware Read and Write Utility is a powerful utility intended for hardware engineer, engineer, BIOS developer, driver, engineer, QA engineers, performance test engineers, diagnostic, etc., this utility access almost all the computer hardware, including PCI (PCI Express), index / Data, PCI, memory, index memory / Data space I / O, Index I / O / Data, Super I / O, DIMM SPD, CPU The registers MSR, screen, SMART, physical area of the hard drive identification data, ATA, dump tables ACPI...
</description></item><item><title>Download tinyMediaManager 5.2.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 23:25:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tinymediamanager-1819.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tinymediamanager-1819.html
</guid><description>
tinyMediaManager is a media manager full-featured to arrange and cleanup your media library your. Just choose (s) the folder containing your movies and the program can automatically get all meta data required for movies and program your TV from TheMovieDB.org, Imdb.com, OFDb.de and other online sources. tinyMediaManager download at artwork, film, cast, plot and details of other communication. Each film or program is presented with a unique art background, category, and appropriate...
</description></item><item><title>Download Syncios iOS Eraser Pro 1.3.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 23:24:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncios-ios-eraser-pro-5721.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncios-ios-eraser-pro-5721.html
</guid><description>
Syncios iOS Eraser Pro is this application which helps you to delete data and files from your iPhone, iPad and iPod with 100% irreversible results without effort. Once a successful connection has been established, you need to scan your device so that the Syncios iOS Eraser Pro can analyze in depth. After you complete this action, you will receive information about free space, temporary files, or large amounts of space on your device. Gallery and photo galleries were also checked, along...
</description></item><item><title>Download Syncios Mobile Manager 7.2.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 23:23:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncios-mobile-manager-5943.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-syncios-mobile-manager-5943.html
</guid><description>
Syncios Mobile Manager is the best iTunes alternative, which can help you manage your vehicle collection in the way you want. Simple to move the song between Android/iPhone/iPad/iPod Touch and the computer.
The features of Syncios Mobile Manager
	Exposition music, bell music, talk books, music videos, podcasts, iTunes U, TV shows, etc.
	Enter a file or a song folder or video from the computer
	Manage the playlist on your mobile phone.
	The duplicate/delete the song on your Android/iOS...
</description></item><item><title>Download MobiKin Transfer for Mobile 5.1.12</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 23:23:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mobikin-transfer-for-mobile-4879.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mobikin-transfer-for-mobile-4879.html
</guid><description>
MobiKin Transfer for Mobile is software that helps you easily copy data from a device (iDevice / Android) to other mobile phones without any restrictions. All the transmission can be done only with 1 click simply and without risk. Switch to a new phone and want to transfer data from old phone to new phone? Or simply want to share something between two different devices? MobiKin Transfer for Mobile can help you complete the data transmission with ease.
MobiKin Transfer for Mobile could...
</description></item></channel></rss>