<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 01:50:36 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 01:50:36 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download PCSX2 2.6.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:32:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pcsx2-4470.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pcsx2-4470.html
</guid><description>
PCSX2 is a software application copy your Playstation 2, allowing you to play the game on your computer. As a gaming machine, virtual PCSX2 can overcome the hardware limitations to bring you these important advantages such as the ability to use the memory card is not limited to save games, screen resolution, custom, game cheats, save game is loading at any time during your game - play, the ability to tom to use any controller compatible Windows operating system and HD recordings of your...
</description></item><item><title>Download Hasleo BitLocker Data Recovery 6.8 All Editions</title><pubDate> Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:30:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hasleo-bitlocker-data-recovery-5918.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hasleo-bitlocker-data-recovery-5918.html
</guid><description>
Hasleo BitLocker Data Recovery is software that can help you recover deleted/missing data from the BitLocker encrypted drive, which restore the missing data from the formated BitLocker drive, failed to access, failed, corrupted, or restored the missing data from the deleted/missing BitLocker encryption partition. And Hasleo BitLocker Data Recovery supports restoring data from the FAT file system, NTFS and exFAT located on hard disk, external hard drive, USB flash drive, SD card,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Album TD 4.9.1.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:30:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-album-td-3968.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-album-td-3968.html
</guid><description>
Album TD has the full name is "Album Turbo Design" can help you design a wedding album album family photo album, with friends, etc.; any theme album with the great entertainment in just a few seconds. Album TD is equipped with fishing features from Album DS design software album for Photoshop, a new tool has been developed: Album Turbo Design. All the power to pull and drop-at services, album design, tools design new of, we will immediately create layouts for both page count and paging...
</description></item><item><title>Download UPDF 2.1.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:29:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-updf-14160.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-updf-14160.html
</guid><description>
UPDF for Windows is easy-to-use PDF software for Windows! Enjoy powerful editing tools for text, images, links, and more in your PDFs. Customize backgrounds, watermarks, and page sizes as easily as in Word. AI-powered PDF editor and manager that offers a wide range of features including editing, annotating, converting, OCR (Optical Character Recognition), organizing, protecting, sharing, printing, summarizing, translating, and interpreting PDF files.
Features of UPDF
Analyze PDFs with...
</description></item><item><title>Download CapCut PC 7.9.0.3294</title><pubDate> Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:29:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capcut-pc-9995.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capcut-pc-9995.html
</guid><description>
CapCut PC is a simple video editing tool that you can freely use anywhere. You can create videos on your browser, desktop and laptop, or on your phone. Versatile editing, magical AI tools, team collaboration, and built-in assets. Create videos in a whole new way.
You can edit videos based on editing the timeline, in the process you can add different elements and effects to the video to give the best effect to your work. It is a simple and intuitive set of editing tools and effects that...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft Edge 143.0.3650.139</title><pubDate> Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:28:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-edge-3940.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-edge-3940.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft Edge is web browser developed specifically for Windows operating system 10 alternatives to Internet Explorer is the default browser on Windows. Browser Microsoft Edge built-in assistant Cortana brings content and website based on the user's preferences, there are also system utilities quite extensive help you to customize according to individual. Microsoft Edge has the similarity with Google Chrome quite large, except the target is marked more of the interface and the rounded...
</description></item><item><title>Download Browser Password Decryptor 19.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:27:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-browser-password-decryptor-10253.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-browser-password-decryptor-10253.html
</guid><description>
Browser Password Decryptor is a useful software created to instantly recover website login passwords stored by popular web browsers. It works on most Windows platforms starting from Windows XP to Windows 11. Supported web browsers:
	Chrome
	Firefox
	Internet Explorer
	Microsoft Edge (old &amp;amp; new)
	Opera Browser
	Apple Safari
	AVG Secure Browser
	Avast Secure Browser
	Brave Browser
	CCleaner Browser
	Chromium Browser
	Citrio Browser
	Comodo Dragon Browser
	Comodo IceDragon
	Maxthon...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cutting Optimization Pro 5.18.18.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:27:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cutting-optimization-pro-6573.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cutting-optimization-pro-6573.html
</guid><description>
Cutting Optimization Pro is a cutting software used to obtain the optimal cut layout for one-dimensional (1D) and two-dimensional (2D) pieces. The software also allows you to define and process complex products, such as desks, tables, cabinets, cabinets, bookshelves... Cutting Optimization Pro can be used to cut rectangular panels made of glass, wood, metal, plastic or any other material used in industrial applications.
Features of Cutting Optimization Pro
	Optimize 1D and 2D in the...
</description></item><item><title>Download GiliSoft Audio Converter Ripper 9.7</title><pubDate> Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:27:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-audio-converter-ripper-7403.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-audio-converter-ripper-7403.html
</guid><description>
GiliSoft Audio Converter Ripper is a program that combines a powerful audio converter and a handy CD ripper in one useful program. Free audio converter between formats. More than 40 audio formats supported! Convert WMA to MP3, MP3 to M4A, WAV to MP3, MP3 to WMA, FLAC to MP3, AAC to MP3, M4A to MP3, OGG to MP3, APE to MP3.
It can convert (rip) audio from CD to several audio files or convert music files from one type to another and extract audio from video files to different audio formats...
</description></item><item><title>Download QontrolPanel (QuickSoundSwitcher) 1.11.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:26:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quicksoundswitcher-14033.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quicksoundswitcher-14033.html
</guid><description>
QuickSoundSwitcher is a lightweight, open-source Windows utility designed to quickly and easily manage audio input and output devices. It allows users to switch between multiple audio devices (e.g. speakers, headphones, microphones) and control the volume directly from the system tray without navigating to complex Windows settings.
The program also provides an application volume mixer, allowing for volume adjustment and muting for individual programs. This tool is especially useful for...
</description></item><item><title>Download HopToDesk 1.45.5</title><pubDate> Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:26:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hoptodesk-11056.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hoptodesk-11056.html
</guid><description>
HopToDesk is a remote desktop application that allows users to access their remote computer or server from anywhere using a mobile device or browser their website. It provides a secure and convenient way to control and manage computers remotely, making it easier for individuals and teams to work remotely or access their files and applications on the go.
With HopToDesk, users can establish a secure connection to a remote computer or server and perform tasks as if they were sitting in...
</description></item><item><title>Download SysNucleus WebHarvy 7.9.0.246</title><pubDate> Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:25:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sysnucleus-webharvy-881.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sysnucleus-webharvy-881.html
</guid><description>
SysNucleus WebHarvy is software to extract data website such as Text, image, URL &amp;amp; email from the website and save the content... WebHarvy is a tool which scans website intuitive. Absolutely no need to write any scripts or code to scrape data. You will use the browser built-in of WebHarvy to navigate the website.
WebHarvy automatically identifies patterns of data occurring in web pages. So if you need a list of items (name, address, email, price etc) from a website, you do not need to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Filter Forge 15.001</title><pubDate> Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:25:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-filter-forge-studio-edition-9171.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-filter-forge-studio-edition-9171.html
</guid><description>
Filter Forge is a powerful software for creating and editing digital filters and effects. It comes in two versions: Filter Forge Standard and Filter Forge Studio. The Studio version is the more advanced version of the two and it offers many features for professional filter creation and image manipulation.
Filter Forge Studio Edition allows users to create their own custom filters and effects from scratch using an intuitive button-based interface. This interface allows users to connect...
</description></item><item><title>Download GiliSoft MP3 CD Maker 9.6</title><pubDate> Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:24:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-mp3-cd-maker-7400.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-mp3-cd-maker-7400.html
</guid><description>
GiliSoft MP3 CD Maker is software to create normal audio CDs from your favorite music. It supports you to create MP3 CD/DVD from popular music formats, burn WMA CD/DVD disc from popular audio and video format files. Enjoy sound in your portable CD player or car CD player. Support high speed recording. Easy to use with intuitive user interface.
GiliSoft MP3 CD Maker supports burning music CDs (Audio CDs) from all popular audio and video formats files including MP3, WMA, WAV, AAC, FLAC,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Clementine Music Player 1.4.1-60</title><pubDate> Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:24:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-clementine-4762.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-clementine-4762.html
</guid><description>
Clementine is a tools multi-platform software which allows you to listen to music from hard drive, library, audio CDS or the Internet, as well as manage it, edit the card and see the lyrics. Clementine is inspired by Amarok 1.4, focusing on a easy to use interface for searching and playing your music.
Clementine also allows you can view track information such as length, bit rate, sample rate, size, file type, number of times played and your ranking, as well as complete the card...
</description></item><item><title>Download Diffchecker 6.7.5</title><pubDate> Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:23:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-diffchecker-5025.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-diffchecker-5025.html
</guid><description>
Diffchecker is a application compare text, images and powerful file to desktop of your. Available for Windows, macOS. Compare text files, documents, PDF. Compare photos, graphics. Because Diffchecker Desktop running entirely on your computer, so it does not have to communicate with our servers to create your difference. This means that there is no other way in addition you can view your sensitive data, you.
Diffchecker Desktop run offline, that means you can use it anytime, anywhere and...
</description></item><item><title>Download DesktopPic 2.0.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:23:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktoppic-7444.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktoppic-7444.html
</guid><description>
DesktopPic allows you to display or watermark images on your Windows desktop wallpaper. Display one or more pictures in a resizable, movable window with no borders or captions, so all you see is the photo. This will give the illusion of the image being part of your wallpaper, but it's really just another window. Any icons on the desktop in the same area as the image will be masked. Bitmap image formats, such as PNG (recommended), JPG, BMP and animated GIF are supported.
Features of...
</description></item><item><title>Download SoftPerfect NetWorx 26.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:22:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-softperfect-networx-1592.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-softperfect-networx-1592.html
</guid><description>
SoftPerfect NetWorx is a software simple and effective way to manage traffic and bandwidth consumption in Windows. If we ignore traffic not regular, and occasionally of the operating system to update itself, as well as updates for the different drivers, one of the important factors in the job vacancy Internet soon is the use of the Internet is hidden by the software is installed on your system. . If you are the user settings clock software and you don't pay attention to it, the existence...
</description></item><item><title>Download Coolmuster iPhone SMS + Contacts Recovery 5.0.9</title><pubDate> Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:22:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-iphone-sms-contacts-recovery-8524.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-iphone-sms-contacts-recovery-8524.html
</guid><description>
Coolmuster iPhone SMS + Contacts Recovery is professional software that helps to recover all contacts and SMS from iPhone. It recovers not only phone numbers and text messages, but also contact names, addresses, companies, emails, SMS attachments, and more. The 100% read-only and safe recovery process provided by the iPhone data recovery program allows you to back up your recovered iPhone text messages and contacts on your computer without any quality loss.
Features of Coolmuster iPhone...
</description></item><item><title>Download Coolmuster iPhone Data Recovery 6.0.53</title><pubDate> Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:22:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-iphone-data-recovery-6599.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-iphone-data-recovery-6599.html
</guid><description>
Coolmuster iPhone Data Recovery is a useful tool designed to help users retrieve all lost data in the iPhone, iPad, or iPod quickly and efficiently. This professional software provides users with a safe way to find lost or deleted data on the Windows system. It can be used in any situation, both online and offline.
Features of Coolmuster iPhone Data Recovery
	Quickly restore the missing or deleted files from the iOS device and the iTunes backup.
	The processing of your iPhone data in...
</description></item><item><title>Download SeaTools for Windows 5.2.5</title><pubDate> Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:15:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-seatools-for-windows-7464.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-seatools-for-windows-7464.html
</guid><description>
SeaTools for Windows is an easy-to-use, comprehensive diagnostic tool that helps you quickly determine the health of a drive in an external hard drive, desktop or laptop computer. hand. It includes several tests that will check the physical media on a Seagate, Maxtor or Samsung drive and any non-Seagate drive. SeaTools for Windows will run on both internal and external hard drives.
Before you ship a drive, it's in your best interest to determine if a replacement drive is really needed....
</description></item><item><title>Download Just Color Picker 6.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:14:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-just-color-picker-2332.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-just-color-picker-2332.html
</guid><description>
Just Color Picker is a super program simple and compact help take the color code quickly suitable with Photoshop,Corel or WHO is. Just Color Picker help for the get the color code becomes much simpler through the move the mouse pointer to anywhere on the screen and you will be informed about the color of that point. For those who are proficient in the image processing program Photoshop professional, then this is quite simple, but with those who are not used to get the color code photo...
</description></item><item><title>Download MobiKin Doctor for iOS 4.3.44</title><pubDate> Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:14:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mobikin-doctor-for-ios-6580.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mobikin-doctor-for-ios-6580.html
</guid><description>
MobiKin Doctor for iOS is a flexible iOS data recovery tool to recover lost data from iPhone, iPad, iPod touch and iTunes backup files, turning it into The most comprehensive iPhone data recovery solution you can find.
When you start scanning files on your iDevice with this iPhone recovery software, it will automatically erase all existing data on your iPhone, iPad or iPod touch. You can then select and export them to your computer. So this iPhone data recovery software can also be...
</description></item><item><title>Download SoftPerfect RAM Disk 26.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:29:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-softperfect-ram-disk-4359.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-softperfect-ram-disk-4359.html
</guid><description>
SoftPerfect RAM Disk is a program disk, RAM performance is designed to help you have a disk on the computer is stored completely in memory. Because memory is much faster than physical hard disk, should store temporary data on disk in fast memory to achieve higher performance. Whether your job is what, keep reading to find out if a RAM disk can offer you what. The program creates a virtual disk located in the computer RAM accessible in Windows Explorer and other applications, allowing you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ekoche Studios Whispering Thoughts 1.0.0.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:20:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ekoche-studios-whispering-thoughts-14455.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ekoche-studios-whispering-thoughts-14455.html
</guid><description>
Whispering Thoughts is a private journaling application for Windows. No account. No cloud computing. No subscription. Just you and your thoughts—protected with military-grade encryption that even we can't read.
Every journal entry is encrypted using the AES-256-GCM standard before saving. Your password is protected by the Argon2id algorithm—the industry-recommended standard for security. We cannot read, nor can we recover passwords. Your privacy is guaranteed by mathematics.
Key...
</description></item></channel></rss>