<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 13:40:26 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 13:40:26 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download All Document Reader and Viewer 3.0.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 16:37:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-all-document-reader-and-viewer-8877.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-all-document-reader-and-viewer-8877.html
</guid><description>
All Document Reader: PDF, excel, word, Documents is a smart office application that helps you read all documents downloaded from the internet, supports reading PDF files, PDF Reader, doc, docx xls, ppt, txt, excel, xlxs files... fast, easy and convenient.. All Document Reader: PDF, excel, word, Documents are providing multiple Document reading features including PDF Reader, Docs Reader &amp;amp; Docx, ppt reader, xls reader, txt, excel &amp;amp; documents different from readers.
All Document...
</description></item><item><title>Download PowerDirector - Video Editor 15.8.1 build 2510282</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 16:37:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-powerdirector-video-editor-8123.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-powerdirector-video-editor-8123.html
</guid><description>
PowerDirector APK - Video Editor (Unlocked Version) is video editing software developed by CyberLink. It is available for Windows and Android devices. If you are looking for the Android version of PowerDirector, you can download the APK (Android Package Kit) file from the Google Play Store or from taiwebs.com.
Features of PowerDirector APK - Unlocked Version:
	Easy-to-use interface: PowerDirector has a user-friendly interface that makes it easy to edit and create videos, even if...
</description></item><item><title>Download OsmAnd+ — Maps &amp;amp; GPS Offline 5.2.6</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 16:37:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-osmand-maps-gps-offline-8245.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-osmand-maps-gps-offline-8245.html
</guid><description>
OsmAnd+ (OSM Automatic Navigation Directions) is a mapping and navigation application with access to free, global, and high-quality OpenStreetMap (OSM) data. Enjoy voice and optical navigation, view POIs (points of interest), create and manage GPX routes, use contour visualization and elevation information, choose between driving modes, cyclists, pedestrians, OSM editing, etc.
This is a mobile navigation app that uses OpenStreetMap (OSM) data to provide users with detailed maps and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Duolingo: language lessons 6.54.5</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 16:36:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-duolingo-language-lessons-8265.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-duolingo-language-lessons-8265.html
</guid><description>
Duolingo is a popular language learning app that offers interactive lessons to help users learn new languages. This application offers many languages for you to choose from, including Spanish, French, German, Italian, Portuguese, Chinese, Japanese and many more.
This app offers an gamified learning experience with interactive lessons, exercises, and quizzes designed to help users learn new words, phrases, and grammar rules. This app is designed to be easy to use and suitable for people...
</description></item><item><title>Download Smart Tools 2 v1.2.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 16:36:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-smart-tools-8136.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-smart-tools-8136.html
</guid><description>
Smart Tools is a complete package of 6 individual applications. It has 6 sets below with a total of 15 tools.
	Offline support (Wi-Fi tablets only): Open this section multiple times using internet, you can open it without internet.
	Magnetic sensor required. So this app cannot support some Android devices (e.g. HTC One V).
	This is one of the essential applications of Google Play for Education.
6 application sets include:
	Set 1. Smart Ruler Pro: length, angle, slope, level,...
</description></item><item><title>Download MDScan + OCR 3.9.90</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 16:36:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-mobile-doc-scanner-mdscan-ocr-8307.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-mobile-doc-scanner-mdscan-ocr-8307.html
</guid><description>
Mobile Doc Scanner (MDS) is an application that allows users to scan, edit and save documents using the Android device's camera. It's designed to work as a portable scanner so you can easily digitize documents, receipts, business cards, and more.
All image processing is done on your device only! No material will be posted online without your wishes! Take photos with your camera, edit them with many advanced features, save to your favorite format and share on social networks, email,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Shazam: Find Music &amp;amp; Concerts 16.16.0-251024</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 16:35:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-shazam-music-discovery-10763.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-shazam-music-discovery-10763.html
</guid><description>
Shazam will identify any song in seconds. Discover, artists, lyrics, videos &amp;amp; playlists, all for free. Over 1 billion installs and counting. Use Pop-up Shazam to identify music in any app - Instagram, YouTube, TikTok... No connection? No problem! Shazam while offline.
Features of Shazam: Music Discovery
	Find the name of any song in seconds.
	Listen and add to Apple Music playlists.
	Follow along with time-synced lyrics.
	Watch music videos from Apple Music or YouTube.
	Enable...
</description></item><item><title>Download Weather data &amp;amp; microclimate: Weather Underground 6.19.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 16:35:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-weather-data-microclimate-weather-underground-8592.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-weather-data-microclimate-weather-underground-8592.html
</guid><description>
Weather Underground is a weather information website and app that provides local and global weather data, including current conditions, hourly and 10-day forecasts, and historical weather data. It also provides information on microclimate, which refers to small-scale local variations in weather conditions.
Weather Underground collects data from a network of more than 270,000 individual weather stations and other sources to provide highly accurate, localized weather information to users....
</description></item><item><title>Download Camera FV-5 5.4.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 16:34:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-camera-fv-5-10516.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-camera-fv-5-10516.html
</guid><description>
Camera FV-5 is a professional camera app for mobile devices that puts DSLR-like manual controls at your fingertips. Designed specifically for professional and enthusiast photographers, with this camera app, you can capture the best raw photos so you can post-process them later and get stunning results. The only limits are your imagination and creativity!
Features of Camera FV-5
	All shooting parameters are adjustable and always at hand: exposure compensation, ISO, metering mode, focus...
</description></item><item><title>Download Black Screen: video screen off 1.9.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 16:33:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-black-screen-video-screen-off-8740.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-black-screen-video-screen-off-8740.html
</guid><description>
Black Screen allows you to play videos when the screen is off. Turn off the screen at any time and save battery. The black screen can be used to watch music videos, listen to podcasts, record videos, take selfies, and more. when your screen is off. This helps save battery in AMOLED and OLED devices because the screen turns off completely when displaying black.
Use the floating button to quickly turn off the screen and unlock it by tapping the screen.
Black Screen feature: turn off...
</description></item><item><title>Download NokoPrint - Mobile Printing 5.24.4</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 16:33:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-nokoprint-mobile-printing-8528.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-nokoprint-mobile-printing-8528.html
</guid><description>
Print photos and share them with family and friends. Print documents, PDFs, invoices, receipts, boarding passes, and more. at home, at work or on the go! You can print images, photos, web pages, PDF and Microsoft Office documents without downloading any additional apps or printing tools anytime, anywhere on almost any WiFi, Bluetooth or USB printer .
Features of NokoPrint for Android
	Print directly from your Android phone or tablet to almost any inkjet, laser or thermal...
</description></item><item><title>Download Pixel Studio: pixel art editor 5.35</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 16:33:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pixel-studio-pixel-art-editor-11086.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pixel-studio-pixel-art-editor-11086.html
</guid><description>
Pixel Studio is a new pixel art editor for artists and game developers. Simple, fast and portable. Regardless of whether you are a beginner or a professional.
Create amazing pixel art anywhere and anytime! We support layers and animations, and have lots of useful tools you need to create fun projects. Add music to your animations and export videos to MP4. Use Google Drive to sync your work between different devices and even platforms. Join Pixel Network™ our new pixel art community!...
</description></item><item><title>Download Chat AI - AI Chatbot Assistant 216.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 16:32:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-chat-ai-ai-chatbot-assistant-11260.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-chat-ai-ai-chatbot-assistant-11260.html
</guid><description>
AI Chatbot is a smart artificial intelligence interactive application that brings a unique and convenient experience to users. With AI Chatbot, you can communicate and ask questions directly with a powerful AI system that helps you find information, answer questions, and even provide solutions to complex problems.
Main features of Chatbot AI include
	Natural conversation: Chatbot AI uses advanced natural language technology to understand and respond to your questions and requests...
</description></item><item><title>Download XAPK Installer 4.6.6</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 16:32:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-xapk-installer-14218.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-xapk-installer-14218.html
</guid><description>
Is there an easier way to install apk apps on your device? This all-in-one xapk installer for Android will help you! Our app will help you download and install files seamlessly from apkpure and other sources. No need to search for folders, unzip packages, or use manual methods.
Although this is an apk installer for Android, it is also a full-fledged xapk installer to satisfy all users' requirements for an xapk file downloader. Our tool recognizes both .apk and .xapk files in just a few...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaMonkey 2.1.1.1284</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 16:32:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-mediamonkey-8211.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-mediamonkey-8211.html
</guid><description>
MediaMonkey APK is a media player and management application for Android devices. MediaMonkey lets you organize and play music, podcasts, and audiobooks on your device. It supports multiple audio formats and has a built-in equalizer, sleep timer, and customizable interface.
MediaMonkey can also sync your music library with other devices, including Windows and Mac computers, and allows you to create playlists and play music on a variety of devices. This app is a great way to organize and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Bundled Notes - List, Organize 4.0.1-005</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 16:31:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-bundled-notes-list-organize-13704.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-bundled-notes-list-organize-13704.html
</guid><description>
Organize everything - from personal notes, lists, and projects to movie watchlists, recipes, bookmarks, and more Whether you keep your notes and lists simple or like to customize them to meet all your organizational needs, Bundled Notes is the app for you.
Key Features:
	Beautiful Material Design You Design With Dynamic Themes
	Ad-Free Experience
	Seamless Syncing Across Devices equipped
	Markdown support with visual formatting
	Powerful organization with “bundles”
	Kanban board...
</description></item><item><title>Download Busuu: Learn &amp;amp; Speak Languages 32.24.4(1475937)</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 16:31:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-busuu-learn-languages-8400.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-busuu-learn-languages-8400.html
</guid><description>
Busuu: Learn Languages is a mobile application that allows users to learn and practice various languages ​​on their Android devices. It includes various features such as interactive lessons, flashcards, quizzes, and exercises designed to help users learn and practice vocabulary, grammar, and conversation skills. The app also includes many customizable settings, such as the ability to choose between different languages ​​and set learning goals.
Busuu Features: Learn...
</description></item><item><title>Download Battery HD Pro 1.99.41</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 16:30:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-battery-hd-pro-8140.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-battery-hd-pro-8140.html
</guid><description>
Battery HD Pro is the perfect battery monitor for your phone or tablet. It's simple, beautiful, and can be specially calibrated for your device. Battery HD Pro is an application designed to help users monitor their device's battery usage and optimize device performance. Some features of this application include:
	Monitor battery usage: The app shows the remaining battery percentage and the estimated time remaining until the battery is depleted.
	Charging History: The app tracks the...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDF Viewer Pro 2025.4.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 16:30:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pdf-viewer-pro-9527.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pdf-viewer-pro-9527.html
</guid><description>
Whether you're working alone or collaborating with a team, PDF Viewer Pro maximizes productivity, allowing you to view, search, and annotate PDF documents easily on your phone or tablet. your Android tablet or Chromebook.
Features of PDF Viewer Pro
View documents on the go
	Easily open PDF files from your favorite cloud provider, email, or directly from the website you're browsing.
	Search for the exact text you are looking for in the document.
	Double-tap the screen to Smart Zoom...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cleaner for WhatsApp 3.0.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 16:30:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-cleaner-for-whatsapp-8499.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-cleaner-for-whatsapp-8499.html
</guid><description>
Cleaner for WhatsApp is a tool or application that helps users clean and organize their WhatsApp data and conversations. It usually includes features like deleting old and unnecessary messages, freeing up storage space, and archiving important conversations.
The most important feature of the Cleaner for WhatsApp app is that you can automatically delete WhatsApp media from your Android phone or tablet periodically or according to the storage limit. Using Cleaner for Whatsapp will speed...
</description></item><item><title>Download Magnifier Plus with Flashlight 4.8.14</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 16:28:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-magnifier-plus-with-flashlight-8494.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-magnifier-plus-with-flashlight-8494.html
</guid><description>
Are you tired of trying to read labels with small fonts? Now you can use your Android device as the perfect digital magnifier! No need to use a magnifying glass to read small labels - this app lets you see text large and clearly. The magnifier has on-screen zoom and illumination controls for easy operation. You can also use the flash as a light to get a brighter image, and the negative mode inverts the colors so you can see this differently when they're hard to see.
Features of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Screen Recorder - AZ Recorder 6.7.7</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 16:28:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-screen-recorder-az-recorder-8402.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-screen-recorder-az-recorder-8402.html
</guid><description>
AZ Screen Recorder is the best app to record your Lollipop screen. It requires NO root access, no time limit, no watermark, no ads and very easy to use with one action to start and stop recording. This screen recording app will let you create beautiful screencasts by providing all the features you need in a simple and elegant user experience design.
AZ Screen Recorder allows you to record your screen to HD and FullHD videos, and it is the only screen recording app on the Android market...
</description></item><item><title>Download 7Fon: Wallpapers &amp;amp; Backgrounds 6.0.80</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 16:28:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-7fon-wallpapers-4k-pro-11673.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-7fon-wallpapers-4k-pro-11673.html
</guid><description>
7Fon Wallpapers 4K (PRO) Android is a great application for people who love beauty and art. With thousands of high-quality wallpapers, users can find the perfect photos for their phone screen.
This app offers a huge collection of 4K wallpapers from different categories like nature, animals, art, landscapes and more. Users can easily search for wallpapers by topic or keyword, helping them quickly find their favorite photos.
Outstanding features of the application include:
	More than...
</description></item><item><title>Download Dumbbell Workout at Home &amp;amp; Gym 5.17</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 16:27:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-dumbbell-home-workout-8634.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-dumbbell-home-workout-8634.html
</guid><description>
Dumbbell Workout at Home is a fitness app for Android devices that offers users a variety of workout routines that can be done at home using only weights. This app is designed for people who want to stay fit and healthy but don't have access to a gym or workout equipment.
Features of Weightlifting at Home for Android
	Customizable workout routines: The app offers users a variety of workout routines that can be customized based on their fitness level, goals, and the amount of time they...
</description></item><item><title>Download YoWindow Weather - Unlimited 2.53.9</title><pubDate> Sat, 01 Nov 2025 16:27:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-yowindow-weather-unlimited-8421.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-yowindow-weather-unlimited-8421.html
</guid><description>
YoWindow is a unique new weather app. The magic of YoWindow is a living landscape that reflects your real-life weather. For example, if it rains - it will rain in YoWindow. Sunset and sunrise in YoWindow take place at the same time as in real life. But the cool thing is you can roll time forward. Just swipe the screen and you'll see how the weather changes throughout the day.
YoWindow Weather Features - Unlimited
	All the weather at your fingertips. You see the current weather,...
</description></item></channel></rss>