<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 01:44:18 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 01:44:18 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Paint NET 5.1.11 + Portable</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 00:36:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-paint-net-252.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-paint-net-252.html
</guid><description>
Paint.NET is software photo manipulation and image creation support, photo editing, simple but effective on the computer. With the additional help from Microsoft, and means free replacement for the software MS Paint. Users can totally create photo effects, 3D shadow effect for photo privacy Paint.Net without the need to resort to Photoshop too complicated.
Paint.NET has a clean interface and easy to understand includes all the tools edit downloads, as well as clone stamp and various...
</description></item><item><title>Download MiniTool Power Data Recovery Personal / Business 12.7 All Editions</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 00:34:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minitool-power-data-recovery-1168.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minitool-power-data-recovery-1168.html
</guid><description>
MiniTool Power Data Recovery is software data recovery from hard drives, SD, Smartmedia, compact Flash, memory Cards and other media. Power Data Recovery recovers files and data lost due to random erase, format, attack virus, breakdown when creating the partition or download, turn off the computer, format the storage media, or use FDISK, damage the boot sector MBR,...
MiniTool Power Data Recovery - data recovery
Features of MiniTool Power Data Recovery
	Recover data after accidental...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mozilla Firefox 145.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 00:33:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-firefox-quantum-501.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-firefox-quantum-501.html
</guid><description>
Firefox Quantum is a web browser independently provide the tabbed browsing combined with numerous handy features like pop-up blocker, Bookmarks, direct (integrated RSS), password manager, and more. Functionality can be extended with dozens of plugins available for free (extensions).
Firefox Quantum are interface completely new, beautiful, neat, minimalistic and delicate, eats less RAM to 30% compared with the old version and solve the condition consuming capacity
Firefox can import all...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinToUSB Enterprise 10.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 00:32:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wintousb-enterprise-32.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wintousb-enterprise-32.html
</guid><description>
WinToUSB is the best software that allows you to install and run the Windows operating system on a USB hard drive or USB flash drive, using an ISO image or a CD/DVD drive as a setting source. With WinToUSB, you can copy the current Windows operating system settings (Windows 7 or more) to the USB drive as the WindowsToGo work space. WinToUSB also supports instalability USB WinPE drives, which can help you move WinPE's content to the USB drive and make the drive to boot.
Features of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Perfectly Clear WorkBench 4.8.0.2876</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 00:32:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfectly-clear-workbench-6892.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfectly-clear-workbench-6892.html
</guid><description>
Perfectly Clear Workbench is an application that uses image editing libraries Perfectly Clear by Athentech and is provided to demonstrate the capabilities of the Perfectly Clear processing libraries, which recognize faces and allow quick export of processing settings for use.
One of the key features in Workbench is the ability to "export to API" when saving a Preset. This allows you to make image edits in Workbench and adjust the settings to suit your editing style and needs. You can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Screenpresso Pro 2.1.40</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 00:31:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-screenpresso-pro-1362.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-screenpresso-pro-1362.html
</guid><description>
Screenpresso Pro is a program easy to take great photos on your screen! Screenpresso blocked Print Screen key and screen capture the best in a few seconds. Allows you to capture windows and screen area, roll the part of the screen, edit the images obtained, add effects, resize a group of images, send screenshots by email and post them to Web resources.
Screenpresso Pro - Shooting the computer screen
Features of Screenpresso Pro
	Take the window and screen area. Take a partial screen...
</description></item><item><title>Download TreeSize Professional 9.6.2.2158</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 00:31:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-treesize-professional-390.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-treesize-professional-390.html
</guid><description>
TreeSize Pro is a software to manage hard disk space powerfully and flexibly for Windows 2003/2008 / XP / Vista / 7/8/10. TreeSize will find out which directory the largest on your drives and recover megabytes on disk. TreeSize Professional shows you the size, allocated and wasted space, number of files, 3D charts, last accessed date, file owner and permissions, the speed NTFS compression and much more information for several folders or drives you choose. It also lets you search drives,...
</description></item><item><title>Download 4K Video Downloader Plus 25.4.1 Beta</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 00:30:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-video-downloader-617.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-video-downloader-617.html
</guid><description>
4K Video Downloader Plus is software support downloads video, audio and subtitles from YouTube with high quality up to 4K. Download process video is very simple: just copy the video link from your browser and click Paste Url. Done! If you want that video on your iPad, iPhone or other device, we have protected you.
The feature on 4K Video Downloader Plus
	Download entire playlists and channels from YouTube and save them in MP4, MKV, M4A, MP3, FLV, 3G, create a file .m3u for...
</description></item><item><title>Download ExtraMAME 25.11</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 00:29:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-extramame-2608.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-extramame-2608.html
</guid><description>
ExtraMAME is a simple tool that allows simulation of the arcade game from the most popular platform but is long forgotten, thanks to which the game industry has reached the current level. After launch, you will get 11 games pre-installed, among which are: Super Mario Bros, Pac-Man Plus, Space Invaders II and other games.
The simulation of multiple machine arcade is authored by Nicola Salmoria and team MAME. MAME lets you play thousands of arcade game old school on your computer. ExtraMAME...
</description></item><item><title>Download RAM Saver Professional 25.11.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 00:29:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ram-saver-pro-565.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ram-saver-pro-565.html
</guid><description>
RAM Saver Pro is a professional software optimize RAM is for system stable operation with high performance. RAM Saver Pro aims to provide all the tools necessary to increase the amount of free memory, at any time, also monitor and check the RAM.
When using RAM Saver Pro, you will be allowed to access its main menu by right-clicking on the tray icon. Also, if you want to display the main panel of the program you just double-click the icon. In addition, from the main interface of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download GiliSoft File Lock Pro 15.3</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 00:28:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-file-lock-pro-858.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-file-lock-pro-858.html
</guid><description>
GiliSoft File Lock Pro is program encryption software file power can lock and hide fast and secure files, folders and drives, and it can use AES 256 bit encryption (encryption standard is the government of The United States apply) protect your files located on HDD or any portable media drive such as USB.
GiliSoft File Lock Pro - file encryption
Features of GiliSoft File Lock Pro
	GiliSoft File Lock Pro can hide the folders and drives of your private
	The file / folder / drive locking...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinToUSB Technician 10.2 + Professional</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 00:28:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wintousb-technician-2463.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wintousb-technician-2463.html
</guid><description>
WinToUSB Technician is a handy program that allows you to install Windows on a USB flash or hard drive and run Windows from that drive. The program is easy to use this provide the simple instructions to install the ISO image or CD / DVD into the drive of your USB. After installation, users can easily deploy Windows from the image on the USB drive.
WinToUSB lets you install and run Windows operating system on USB hard drive or USB flash drive, use ISO image or CD / DVD drive as the source...
</description></item><item><title>Download PortableApps.com Platform 30.1.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 00:27:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-portableappscom-platform-1935.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-portableappscom-platform-1935.html
</guid><description>
PortableApps.com Platform is the open source application can be installed directly onto your USB thumb drive. It offers a wide range of mobile apps, including the mobile version of Firefox, Skype and many other applications. None of them comes, but you can download them directly from the application directory integrated.
PortableApps.com Platform - The launch the app
Other features include
	Integrated backup
	Theme modern interface
	Search options
	Support personal files, favorites...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Downloader 9.18.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 00:26:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html
</guid><description>
YTD Youtube Downloader is an application that reliable and intuitive, allowing you to quickly download YouTube videos and save them to your computer. You can also convert the media files to the format desired video or extract audio streams and save separately. YTD Youtube Downloader lets you save your favorite clips of yourself from Youtube, Facebook, Vimeo and Dailymotion to your desktop. The software supports URLS from many web site hosting, multimedia and allows you to download desired...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaMonkey Gold 2024.2.0.3175 RC2</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 00:26:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediamonkey-gold-231.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediamonkey-gold-231.html
</guid><description>
MediaMonkey Gold is music manager and music player multimedia for the music collection and iPod users. MediaMonkey lists the audio file of you as CD, OGG, WMA, MPC, FLAC, APE, WAV and MP3 and includes the edit smart card and an automatic file and folder to arrange your music library.
MediaMonkey Gold also has CD ripper, CD / DVD Burner, and audio converter for saving music, and manual or editor list automatically to create mixed music.
Features MediaMonkey Gold
	Automatically find...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinTools.net Professional / Premium / Classic 25.12.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 00:26:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wintoolsnet-304.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wintoolsnet-304.html
</guid><description>
WinTools.net is an optimal tool working performance of the operating system and delete the unnecessary program from the hard drive and control the start-up process of Windows.
WinTools.net integrates many useful tools, to support increased processing speed and ability, stable operation for the computer include: Clean Uninstaller, Scan Files, Scan Registry, Start Up, Tweak UI, Net Tweaker, The Privacy. Scan Files are often used to scan the hard drive periodically, search for junk files or...
</description></item><item><title>Download HE - Hardware Read and Write Utility 1.25.11.10</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 00:25:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-he-hardware-read-and-write-utility-4287.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-he-hardware-read-and-write-utility-4287.html
</guid><description>
HE - Hardware Read and Write Utility is a powerful utility intended for hardware engineer, engineer, BIOS developer, driver, engineer, QA engineers, performance test engineers, diagnostic, etc., this utility access almost all the computer hardware, including PCI (PCI Express), index / Data, PCI, memory, index memory / Data space I / O, Index I / O / Data, Super I / O, DIMM SPD, CPU The registers MSR, screen, SMART, physical area of the hard drive identification data, ATA, dump tables ACPI...
</description></item><item><title>Download 4K YouTube to MP3 25.4.1 Beta</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 00:24:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-youtube-to-mp3-622.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-youtube-to-mp3-622.html
</guid><description>
4K YouTube to MP3 is a software to convert video youtube to mp3 quickly and easily by the manipulation drag-and-drop simple. With 4K YouTube to MP3 you just drag and drop the link to the favorite songs of you and get the MP3 files to your computer, as easy as that. Transfer songs directly to iPod, iPhone and iPad everywhere you go. No install annoying and complex to solve, just a clean interface, user friendly and functional.
When using 4K YouTube to MP3, users will get the playlists,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Xreveal 2.8.7</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 00:23:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xreveal-7252.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xreveal-7252.html
</guid><description>
Xreveal is an application similar to AnyDVD. This is an interactive research and purpose project. Xreveal does NOT contain any decryption key, it is based solely on the official public AACS specification. You need the decryption key or key database to make it work.
Features of Xreveal
	Remove Blu-ray AACS 1.0 protection
	Remove Blu-ray AACS 2.0 (UHD) protection
	Remove BD+ protection
	Remove BDAV Protection
	Remove DVD CSS protection
	Remove CPRM Protection
	Remove CPPM...
</description></item><item><title>Download Psiphon 186.20251109</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 00:22:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-psiphon-7347.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-psiphon-7347.html
</guid><description>
Psiphon is a firewall bypass tool by Psiphon Inc. Uses VPN, SSH and HTTP Proxy technology to give you uncensored access to Internet content. Your Psiphon app automatically learns about new hotspots to maximize your chances of bypassing censorship.
The way the software works is that Psiphon constantly changes the proxy, so the user's IP address is also constantly changing, the server will not detect the user's real address, so you can feel free. roof. access to websites and software...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT-DL 11.7.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 00:21:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-dl-5876.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-dl-5876.html
</guid><description>
YT-DL is a small program to download videos from YouTube and other video sites. Our goal is to make the program as simple as its name.
The features of YT-DL
	Download the video from YouTube and other video sites
	Increase download speed up to 400%
	Download multiple videos at the same time
	Pause and continue to download at any time
	Preview video content while downloading
</description></item><item><title>Download O&amp;amp;O Defrag Server 30.5.1205</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 00:21:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-defrag-server-2521.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-defrag-server-2521.html
</guid><description>
O&amp;amp;O Defrag Server professional software has the ability to defragment the hard disk and can work with the file system different from FAT / 32 to NTFS / 5, and support for the different arrays Volume / Stripe Sets. You can also set the schedule which O &amp;amp; O Defrag will be booted and perform a number of manipulation certain. Regular defragmentation of the disk partition optimized performance of your computer. The user interface is very easy to use. It has a ribbon bar displays all the...
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Geek YTDL Pro 11.7.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 11 Nov 2025 00:21:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-geek-ytdl-pro-9895.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-yt-geek-ytdl-pro-9895.html
</guid><description>
YT Geek YTDL Pro is software that helps users easily download videos from YouTube and hundreds of other video sites. It is very easy to use, just paste the video URL and you can download the video while keeping the original quality. Not only videos on Youtube, users can download any video from social networking sites like Facebook, Vimeo, Myspace video,...
Features of YT Geek YTDL Pro
	Download videos from YouTube and other video sites.
	Increase download speed up to 400%.
	Download...
</description></item><item><title>Download Digiarty Aiarty Video Enhancer 3.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 10 Nov 2025 21:32:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-digiarty-aiarty-video-enhancer-13862.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-digiarty-aiarty-video-enhancer-13862.html
</guid><description>
Digiarty Aiarty Video Enhancer is an AI-powered desktop software designed to upscale, denoise, deblur, and enhance videos up to 4K resolution with professional quality and speed. It uses advanced AI models optimized for GPU acceleration and Turbo mode, enabling real-time or near-real-time video processing, including frame interpolation for smooth motion up to 90fps, 120fps, or higher. This tool is effective in restoring low-resolution, old, blurry, jerky or underexposed footage,...
</description></item><item><title>Download R-Wipe &amp;amp; Clean 20.0 Build 2535</title><pubDate> Mon, 10 Nov 2025 16:40:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-wipe-clean-891.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-wipe-clean-891.html
</guid><description>
R-Wipe &amp;amp; Clean is software to delete junk files, unnecessary files from your computer to release the storage space and speed up your computer. In addition, R-Wipe &amp;amp; Clean also unleash the capacity of your drive and delete information invasion of privacy on different operations online and offline including your internet history and cookies, the list of downloaded files and documents were open, buffer different data, temporary files and many other items, created by the operating...
</description></item></channel></rss>