<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 17:44:18 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 17:44:18 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download ImageMagick 7.1.2-9</title><pubDate> Mon, 01 Dec 2025 17:17:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-imagemagick-1319.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-imagemagick-1319.html
</guid><description>
ImageMagick is software image processing command line to create, edit, compose, or convert bitmap images. ImageMagick is completely free for users and you easily download it on taiwebs.com. Typical functions most of software is able to read and write images in many formats (over 100) including DPX, EXR, GIF, JPEG, JPEG-2000, PDF, PhotoCD, PNG, Postcript, SVG, and TIFF.
ImageMagick - image Processing
The Windows version of ImageMagick is installed. Just click on the appropriate version...
</description></item><item><title>Download EmEditor Pro 25.4.3</title><pubDate> Mon, 01 Dec 2025 17:11:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-emeditor-pro-69.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-emeditor-pro-69.html
</guid><description>
EmEditor Pro - the professional version of editor text powerful for programmers, web developers and ordinary users with illumination of syntax and Unicode support. The features of the editor such as search and replace in files using regular expressions, automatic code detect, bookmark link and address email, block selection mode, configure the button bar, menu, font and elements color. With each language you can set separate configuration.
EmEditor Pro - text Editor professional
The...
</description></item><item><title>Download Directory Opus Pro 13.20</title><pubDate> Mon, 01 Dec 2025 17:11:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-opus-pro-779.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-opus-pro-779.html
</guid><description>
Directory Opus Pro is a software replacement for Explorer with traditional strength and function more than any manager other files. Directory Opus Pro full support for high DPI screen (for example 4K and 5K) with the rename dialog is redesigned, with new features. Besides being a recording macro only allows you to perform mass renaming complex that don't need regular expressions. In addition, Directory Opus Pro also enhances the ability to script.Better handling of renaming recursive and...
</description></item><item><title>Download RadioBOSS Ultimate 7.1.6.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 01 Dec 2025 17:10:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-radioboss-advanced-599.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-radioboss-advanced-599.html
</guid><description>
The application programming radio professional, tradition designed for the traditional radio can and is expected to pay thousands of dollars for software is extremely complex and complicated. But if that's not you? If you need a simple, affordable, reliable solution to automating demand your broadcast, RadioBOSS is the solution you've been looking for.
Whether it's building and scheduling programming cross for radio ground or your Internet, create sound atmosphere suitable in restaurant...
</description></item><item><title>Download Clean Space Pro 2025 v715</title><pubDate> Mon, 01 Dec 2025 17:10:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-clean-space-pro-545.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-clean-space-pro-545.html
</guid><description>
Clean Space Pro is the professional software remove junk files from the system to release the hard drive and improve computer performance. From time to time when using computer files as buffers, temporary files of various programs, files, internet cookies, internet browsing history, diary, file index.dat, registry entries and even the Windows will gradually increase, occupy wise space your hard drive and make the computer suffer from stagnation. The best solution is to use the Clean Space...
</description></item><item><title>Download RapidRAW 1.4.6</title><pubDate> Mon, 01 Dec 2025 17:09:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rapidraw-13957.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rapidraw-13957.html
</guid><description>
RapidRAW is a modern, high-performance, open-source RAW photo editor, designed to deliver a fast and clean editing experience with a lightweight footprint (under 30MB). Built with performance and usability in mind, the software is aimed at photographers who want a simple, efficient, and fun workflow without compromising performance.
Key Features
	GPU-accelerated processing: Uses a custom WGSL shader to process all image adjustments on the GPU, allowing for smooth, responsive editing...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDFgear 2.1.14</title><pubDate> Mon, 01 Dec 2025 17:09:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdfgear-9049.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdfgear-9049.html
</guid><description>
PDFgear is a PDF reader and editor that combines PDF editing functionality with an AI (artificial intelligence) assistant powered by ChatGPT. The user-friendly product PDFgear offers options that you cannot find in Adobe Acrobat. It's great that you can change the color of your comments with simple clicks.
PDFgear is a full-featured PDF editor that basically helps me do everything I need: edit, convert, form, signature, etc. The interface is intuitive and familiar, and all the features...
</description></item><item><title>Download DiskDigger Pro 2.0.13.4139</title><pubDate> Mon, 01 Dec 2025 17:08:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-diskdigger-pro-435.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-diskdigger-pro-435.html
</guid><description>
DiskDigger Pro is software restore data files, videos, pictures, sounds, media files, from a USB Flash drive, memory card.  DiskDigger can recover all the deleted files from your means, can help even when files or folders lost due to virus attack. It gives users the ability to restore various types of data including: pictures, video, audio, text.
DiskDigger Pro support in multiple files with different formats: JPG, PNG, GIF, BMP, TIFF, ICO, ANI, DOC, DOCX, XLS, PPT, PDF, VSD, PPTX,...
</description></item><item><title>Download OpenCloner Ripper 2024 v7.40.133</title><pubDate> Mon, 01 Dec 2025 17:08:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opencloner-ripper-2004.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opencloner-ripper-2004.html
</guid><description>
OpenCloner Ripper 2019 is a software to convert and extract sufficient features. It can extract DVD movies / Blu-ray / UHD video format standard, at the same time remove protective measures other. Meanwhile, it supports the pre-installation configuration integration rich is optimized for your device. Versatile application OpenCloner Ripper can also transcode the video files of any encoding any of the files, MP4 / MKV and extract the iTunes movies ed into MP4 format, remove the DRM. A...
</description></item><item><title>Download QOwnNotes 25.12.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 01 Dec 2025 17:07:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qownnotes-3178.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qownnotes-3178.html
</guid><description>
QOwnNotes is notes bookmark file simple text (GPL) open source application for GNU / Linux , Mac OS X and Windows of Patrizio Bekerle ( pbek on GitHub and IRC) (optional) activity along with the notes application of ownCloud or Nextcloud. QOwnNote store your notes as plain text files and can be synchronized with synchronization function file of ownCloud / Nextcloud. You can also use other apps like Syncthing or Dropbox . Just write out your thoughts as they appear, and edit them if...
</description></item><item><title>Download lessmsi 2.11.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 01 Dec 2025 17:07:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lessmsi-12392.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lessmsi-12392.html
</guid><description>
Lessmsi (Less MSIerables) is a free and portable application that allows users to view and extract the contents of MSI files.
How does it work? Files with the .msi extension are not as widely used as their .exe cousins, but both contain programs for Windows. The main difference between them is that the latter does not always come with an installer, while it comes standard with the former. However, there will be cases where you just need to view or want to extract specific content from...
</description></item><item><title>Download WonderPen 3.0.5.8206</title><pubDate> Mon, 01 Dec 2025 17:06:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tominlab-wonderpen-7753.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tominlab-wonderpen-7753.html
</guid><description>
WonderPen is a writing app for both professional and amateur writers. WonderPen uses a tree directory to organize documents, supports unlimited levels, and can easily manage both short articles and long works. Documents can be exported to various formats such as images, PDF, Word, Epub and web pages. Multiple chapters can be exported as a book in batches.
WonderPen has a built-in full automatic backup function. By default, it will perform a full database backup every 15 minutes. It also...
</description></item><item><title>Download MapInfo Pro 2023.2.231</title><pubDate> Mon, 01 Dec 2025 17:06:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mapinfo-pro-1872.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mapinfo-pro-1872.html
</guid><description>
MapInfo Pro is the software helps the business analysts and GIS experts get new insights about their markets, by sharing the map and the rich information to improve decision-making strategies. MapInfo Pro is an application that analyzes geography and mapping strong provider of space solutions geography. MapInfo Pro help you presented the results his business in a new way, more intuitive. It clearly demonstrates the relationship between geography and data, thanks to the map and detailed...
</description></item><item><title>Download SmartGit 25.1.100</title><pubDate> Mon, 01 Dec 2025 17:05:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-smartgit-13978.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-smartgit-13978.html
</guid><description>
SmartGit is a cross-platform, graphical Git application designed for professional users to simplify and enhance Git version control workflows. SmartGit supports major Git hosting services like GitHub, Bitbucket, GitLab, and Azure DevOps with built-in features to handle pull requests, comments, and code reviews directly in the app.
Why choose SmartGit as your Git Client?
	One for all.
	SmartGit helps new Git users as well as helps experienced developers work more efficiently.
	SmartGit...
</description></item><item><title>Download Helium Music Manager Premium 17.4.545</title><pubDate> Mon, 01 Dec 2025 17:05:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-helium-music-manager-premium-164.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-helium-music-manager-premium-164.html
</guid><description>
Helium Music Manager is a music manager that can rip, tag, play, browse, search, rename, burn and synchronize your music with the mobile. You can control your music collection with Helium Music Manager. Stop using time looking for the file on your computer or looking through CDS, vinyl records and tapes - instead, simply enjoy and explore your music! Helium Music Manager can replace the ripper, the player, tag editor and related software to audio your other.
Helium Music Manager...
</description></item><item><title>Download C64 Forever Plus Edition 11.2.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 01 Dec 2025 17:04:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-c64-forever-plus-edition-2307.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-c64-forever-plus-edition-2307.html
</guid><description>
C64 Forever is the program is an emulator of Commodore strong, even comes with a set of rich game. Of course, video games have come a long way and so can you and you need more than a lifetime to undergo computer toys alone, not to mention game machines. If you, like me, are nostalgic and want to undergo these difficulties, neurological examination, patience and everything else, you need the emulator for this.
C64 Forever Plus Edition - The emulator game
External application suitable...
</description></item><item><title>Download Toontrack EZmix Bundle 3.2.1</title><pubDate> Mon, 01 Dec 2025 17:04:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-toontrack-ezmix-8929.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-toontrack-ezmix-8929.html
</guid><description>
EZmix is a software plugin designed for music producers and engineers to streamline the mixing process of their music projects. It offers simple yet powerful mixing tools that give you access to a large variety of presets. Whether you need to mix drums, vocals, guitar, bass or keyboards, this is your tool. Simply insert EZmix on a channel strip in your sequencer and choose a preset to apply to your audio source.
Additionally, EZmix comes with a standalone server that you can use to...
</description></item><item><title>Download DirPrintOK 7.48</title><pubDate> Mon, 01 Dec 2025 17:04:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dirprintok-2073.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dirprintok-2073.html
</guid><description>
DirPrintOK allows you to print and save the contents of the folder and / or entire folder structures. You can browse the directory with Explorer-like interface and arbitrary filter folder contents by file extensions or matching the wildcard. You can also right-click to exclude files or folders selected from the printed version.
&amp;nbsp;
Folder contents can be grouped by path, date, size or file extension and you can customize the data columns to be included in the printed book. Very easy...
</description></item><item><title>Download Simple Cutting Software X 2025.11.30</title><pubDate> Mon, 01 Dec 2025 17:03:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-simple-cutting-software-x-12810.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-simple-cutting-software-x-12810.html
</guid><description>
Simple Cutting Software X is a lightweight and practical program that helps you maximize the potential of a material, be it wood, metal, glass or other. It gives you the best cutting options for the parts you need, while minimizing waste.
Key Features
	2D Cutter Optimization: The cuts are made from one side to the other of the material. This feature is useful for glass, wood, tempered glass, etc.
	Adjustable blade thickness: For diamond glass cutting, the blade thickness is 0, but for...
</description></item><item><title>Download Diffchecker 6.6.5</title><pubDate> Mon, 01 Dec 2025 17:03:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-diffchecker-5025.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-diffchecker-5025.html
</guid><description>
Diffchecker is a application compare text, images and powerful file to desktop of your. Available for Windows, macOS. Compare text files, documents, PDF. Compare photos, graphics. Because Diffchecker Desktop running entirely on your computer, so it does not have to communicate with our servers to create your difference. This means that there is no other way in addition you can view your sensitive data, you.
Diffchecker Desktop run offline, that means you can use it anytime, anywhere and...
</description></item><item><title>Download MadCap Flare 2025 R2 v21.1.9396.41248</title><pubDate> Mon, 01 Dec 2025 17:02:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-madcap-flare-9823.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-madcap-flare-9823.html
</guid><description>
MadCap Flare is a professional authoring and publishing tool designed for technical writers and document teams. It was developed by MadCap Software, a company specializing in content development and management solutions. MadCap Flare allows users to create and manage various types of content, such as online help systems, knowledge bases, manuals, and other technical documentation. The software uses a topic-based authoring approach, where content is created and organized into individual...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wing FTP Server Corporate 8.0.8</title><pubDate> Mon, 01 Dec 2025 17:02:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wing-ftp-server-corporate-2752.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wing-ftp-server-corporate-2752.html
</guid><description>
Wing FTP Server Corporate is a highly functional, easy and safe can be used in the operating system Windows, Linux, Mac and Solaris are used. The software supports a number of file transfer protocol such as FTP, HTTP, FTPS, HTTPS and SFTP. Wing FTP Server provides web-based interface to manage the server at any time. You can also get performance server and the online and even send email notifications about various events happening on the server.
Management server multi-function
Wing FTP...
</description></item><item><title>Download ButterScroll 1.3.3</title><pubDate> Mon, 01 Dec 2025 17:01:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-butterscroll-13824.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-butterscroll-13824.html
</guid><description>
Smooth scrolling on Windows just got better. Smooth scrolling for Windows is what ButterScroll is all about. It improves the way your mouse scrolls using customizable speed and ease settings.
Smooth scrolling for all types of mice.
ButterScroll improves your everyday scrolling experience with smooth scrolling precision, customizable controls, and a satisfying feel across all your Windows apps — from browsers to spreadsheets.
ButterScroll Features
	Easy to set up and use
	Smooth,...
</description></item><item><title>Download TrainController Gold 10.0 B3</title><pubDate> Mon, 01 Dec 2025 17:01:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-traincontroller-gold-8296.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-traincontroller-gold-8296.html
</guid><description>
TrainController Gold is a software tool for model railway enthusiasts that allows users to control and schedule trains on a model railway diagram. It can be used to automate the operation of model railway layouts, simulate actual train movements and allow multiple trains to run simultaneously.
This software can control the speed, direction and other functions of a digital model railway system and can also be used to create and edit timetables, transit and control signal. In addition, it...
</description></item><item><title>Download CrawlRhino SEO Crawler PRO 1.0.7</title><pubDate> Mon, 01 Dec 2025 17:00:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-crawlrhino-seo-crawler-pro-14273.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-crawlrhino-seo-crawler-pro-14273.html
</guid><description>
Ensuring your website is properly indexed and has optimal SEO aspects can be more difficult than you think, but luckily, web crawlers like CrawlRhino SEO Crawler can professionally assist you. This application allows you to perform website crawls to analyze site structure, find broken links, duplicate entries, as well as perform in-depth SEO audits and generate reports that can be used to improve performance and resolve upcoming issues.
How CrawlRhino SEO Crawler Works
CrawlRhino SEO...
</description></item></channel></rss>