<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 10:10:06 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 10:10:06 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download AB Download Manager 1.7.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 14 Oct 2025 01:49:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ab-download-manager-12399.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ab-download-manager-12399.html
</guid><description>
With this application, you can easily download files from anywhere. Enjoy fast, free downloads with seamless browser extension support. It is built to be a desktop application that allows you to manage and organize your downloads better than before.
AB Download Manager features
	Simple and modern UI: Simple UI and dark mode by default
	Faster download speeds: Download files using multiple connections to increase your download speed by up to 500%
	Download Queue: Create and manage your...
</description></item><item><title>Download Qalculate! 5.8.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 14 Oct 2025 01:48:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qalculate-7213.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qalculate-7213.html
</guid><description>
Qalculate! is a versatile cross-platform desktop calculator. It's simple to use but offers the power and flexibility typically reserved for complex math packages, as well as useful tools for everyday needs (such as currency converters and fractional calculations). hundred). Features include a large library of customizable functions, unit calculations and conversions, physical constants, symbol calculations (including integrals and equations), arbitrary precision, uncertainty transfer,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Qmmp 2.3.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 14 Oct 2025 01:47:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qmmp-3465.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qmmp-3465.html
</guid><description>
Qmmp is a audio player multi-platform free and open source similar to Winamp. It is written in C ++ using the toolkit widget in Qt for user interface. It officially supports the operating systems Linux, FreeBSD and Microsoft Windows. This program is an audio player, written with help of Qt library. User interface similar to winamp or xmms. User interface alternatives are also available.
Qmmp - audio Playback multi-platform
The features of Qmmp
&amp;nbsp;
	Ogg Vorbis
	Ogg Opus
	Native...
</description></item><item><title>Download DesktopNoteOK 4.41</title><pubDate> Tue, 14 Oct 2025 01:47:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopnoteok-4076.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopnoteok-4076.html
</guid><description>
DesktopNoteOK is a software to create quick notes on desktop Windows, with the random options and the custom options different. The notes on the desktop created at the request of users, mainly because Windows 10, here it only available via MS Store. About privacy, users doubt here and ask me a tool desktop pure. Is a mobile version and / or maybe install!
DesktopNoteOK - notes on your Desktop
The features of DesktopNoteOK
	Many themes for the desktop notes random background and font...
</description></item><item><title>Download XnViewMP 1.9.5</title><pubDate> Mon, 13 Oct 2025 20:29:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xnview-mp-1074.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xnview-mp-1074.html
</guid><description>
XnViewMP "XnView MP" is the enhanced version of XnView Classic. This is the view and convert images multi-platform powerful, compatible with more than 500 image formats, different today. XnView MP easily export images to about 70 file format is different. Similar to XnConvert, XnView MP also features integrated switch at the same time batch file to help you process photos faster. XnView is another version of the photo viewer but with the ability to support formats more limited.
XnView...
</description></item><item><title>Download CPUID HWMonitor Pro 1.56</title><pubDate> Mon, 13 Oct 2025 20:29:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cpuid-hwmonitor-pro-712.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cpuid-hwmonitor-pro-712.html
</guid><description>
CPUID HWMonitor Pro is the powerful solution to hardware monitoring, display of parameters such as system temperature, voltage, fan speed and many factors and variables, other important of your computer. HWMonitor Pro has the read view "tree" so that you can easily monitor each parameter as view and track temperature, CPU core, and analyze other details like temperature assembly of the primary hard drive.
CPUID HWMonitor Pro - hardware Monitoring
HWMonitor Pro can easily connect to a...
</description></item><item><title>Download Allavsoft Video Downloader Converter 3.28.4.9413</title><pubDate> Mon, 13 Oct 2025 20:28:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allavsoft-video-downloader-converter-248.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-allavsoft-video-downloader-converter-248.html
</guid><description>
Allavsoft Video Downloader Converter software supports download movies, music videos, playlist, sport videos from video sharing website for free like Facebook, Youtube and over 100 video sharing sites.
Allavsoft is many users favorite thanks to the combined features simultaneous transmission of multiple videos and speed limit download video. Besides, the program also supports pause and resume data transmission, to help you interfere with the process of transmitting download data to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Aseprite 1.3.15.4</title><pubDate> Mon, 13 Oct 2025 20:28:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aseprite-6901.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aseprite-6901.html
</guid><description>
Aseprite is a pixel art tool that allows you to create 2D animations for video games using a variety of tools. Animations and visual effects are used to enhance nearly any form of multimedia, including video games. They are created by combining many images and effects, with countless applications at your disposal.
Aseprite supports files and smart drawing tools, resulting in an enhanced image or short animation for use in your project. In addition, you can completely change or enhance...
</description></item><item><title>Download reaConverter Pro 8.0.144</title><pubDate> Mon, 13 Oct 2025 20:27:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-reaconverter-pro-403.html
</guid><description>
reaConverter Pro is software image processing feature with batch conversion and image editing periodically becomes simple. eaConverter also provide command line utilities allow you to process images automatically, thus helping you shorten the time for other work.
reaConverter Pro integrated powerful tool of Uber with many great features. It provides advanced solutions to process and adjust images. Management of the conversion process the base image with the latest version of...
</description></item><item><title>Download XnConvert Commercial 1.106.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 13 Oct 2025 20:27:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xnconvert-1060.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xnconvert-1060.html
</guid><description>
XnConvert is software to convert and resize photos in batch by drag-and-drop file simple. XnConvert is a photo processing app multi-platform powerful with more than 500 image formats, different is support and inheritance features batch image processing from XnViewWP.
XnConvert - change image size
The main features of XnConvert
	Support all image format now includes more than 500 different formats
	Drag and drop file easy selection of photos to convert
	Support batch conversion, save...
</description></item><item><title>Download Freemake Video Converter Gold 5.0.0.16</title><pubDate> Mon, 13 Oct 2025 20:26:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-freemake-video-converter-gold-167.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-freemake-video-converter-gold-167.html
</guid><description>
Freemake Video Converter Gold is a software to help convert tail high quality videos with many different formats on many devices. Freemake Video Converter - convert video to AVI, MP4, WMV, MKV, 3GP, DVD, MP3, iPad, iPhone, PSP, Android phone. Video to MP3 just with one click! Rip and burn DVD. Convert YouTube to MP4, AVI, etc. with Freemake! Results guaranteed. Freemake Video Converter has fast conversion speed, guarantee the output quality,support create HTML5 videos have the embed code...
</description></item><item><title>Download O&amp;amp;O Defrag Server 30.0.1061</title><pubDate> Mon, 13 Oct 2025 20:25:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-defrag-server-2521.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-defrag-server-2521.html
</guid><description>
O&amp;amp;O Defrag Server professional software has the ability to defragment the hard disk and can work with the file system different from FAT / 32 to NTFS / 5, and support for the different arrays Volume / Stripe Sets. You can also set the schedule which O &amp;amp; O Defrag will be booted and perform a number of manipulation certain. Regular defragmentation of the disk partition optimized performance of your computer. The user interface is very easy to use. It has a ribbon bar displays all the...
</description></item><item><title>Download O&amp;amp;O Defrag Pro 30.0.1061</title><pubDate> Mon, 13 Oct 2025 20:25:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-o-o-defrag-pro-149.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-o-o-defrag-pro-149.html
</guid><description>
O&amp;amp;O Defrag Pro is the professional software has the ability to defragment the hard disk and can work with the file system different from FAT / 32 to NTFS / 5, and support for the different arrays Volume / Stripe Sets. You can also set the schedule which O &amp;amp; O Defrag will be booted and perform a number of manipulation certain. Regular defragmentation of the disk partition optimized performance of your computer. The user interface is very easy to use. It has a ribbon bar displays all...
</description></item><item><title>Download Pazu Spotify Music Converter 4.9.8</title><pubDate> Mon, 13 Oct 2025 20:24:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pazu-spotify-music-converter-11024.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pazu-spotify-music-converter-11024.html
</guid><description>
Pazu Spotify Music Converter for Windows allows you to download and convert Spotify music to MP3, M4A, AAC, FLAC, WAV and AIFF in high quality. Use it to download Spotify songs, albums, playlists, podcasts, and audiobooks with a free or paid Spotify account. You can then transfer them to any device, such as an MP3 player, and play them without restrictions.
Why should you use Pazu Spotify Music Converter?
Premium Spotify users can save albums, playlists for offline playback, but unlike...
</description></item><item><title>Download CPUID HWMonitor Free 1.60</title><pubDate> Mon, 13 Oct 2025 20:24:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cpuid-hwmonitor-free-8486.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cpuid-hwmonitor-free-8486.html
</guid><description>
CPUID HWMonitor Free is a free system monitoring software that allows users to monitor various hardware components in their computer, such as CPU, GPU, memory memory and temperature. It can be used to monitor performance and troubleshoot problems with the system. The software is compatible with the Windows operating system and can be downloaded from the CPUID website.
Features of CPUID HWMonitor Free
	Real-time monitoring of various hardware components such as CPU, GPU, memory and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Everything 1.4.1.1029</title><pubDate> Mon, 13 Oct 2025 20:24:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-everything-385.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-everything-385.html
</guid><description>
Everything is a search tool on the desktop that lets you find files and folders instantly by entering the name software or certain applications. The interesting thing for Everything that can be indexed for the whole of your computer in a few seconds and automatically updates the index.
The software is split into two main controls: the search box and the results page. When you first run Everything it will create an index of all the files and folders on your machine. Unless you have...
</description></item><item><title>Download VovSoft Desktop Diary 2.6</title><pubDate> Mon, 13 Oct 2025 20:23:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-desktop-diary-6934.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vovsoft-desktop-diary-6934.html
</guid><description>
Vovsoft Desktop Diary is a handy diary application that allows you to lock your account with a password, preventing others from accessing your private data. You can use it to write down your memories, as well as save important appointments. This is a daily diary application for Windows that allows you to save your daily notes on your desktop or laptop computer.
VovSoft Desktop Diary Features
	Write your memories or dates easily
	The program has multiple themes and allows you to...
</description></item><item><title>Download SAPIEN PrimalScript 2025 v8.1.221</title><pubDate> Mon, 13 Oct 2025 20:23:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sapien-primalscript-6923.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sapien-primalscript-6923.html
</guid><description>
PrimalScript is the next generation of our industry-leading Universal Script Environment. As a system, database or network administrator, web developer, or end-user developer, you need to work with multiple technologies, languages, and file formats at the same time. The ribbon interface of PrimalScript has been carefully designed to provide almost all the functions you use every day on the Home tab. Create scenario templates based on your requirements and business needs to drive faster...
</description></item><item><title>Download Retail Plus 5.2</title><pubDate> Mon, 13 Oct 2025 17:22:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-retail-plus-14228.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-retail-plus-14228.html
</guid><description>
Retail Plus is a great platform for creating a user-friendly retail and point of sale management system. The software makes everyday decisions easier and makes it easier for customers to check out quickly and easily. It supports all optional hardware such as cash drawers, receipt printers, scanners, barcode printers, customer displays, and payment card terminals. If you run a home business, you can quickly create a sales and inventory control system by simply adding a computer and monitor....
</description></item><item><title>Download QontrolPanel (QuickSoundSwitcher) 1.9.4</title><pubDate> Mon, 13 Oct 2025 16:45:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quicksoundswitcher-14033.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quicksoundswitcher-14033.html
</guid><description>
QuickSoundSwitcher is a lightweight, open-source Windows utility designed to quickly and easily manage audio input and output devices. It allows users to switch between multiple audio devices (e.g. speakers, headphones, microphones) and control the volume directly from the system tray without navigating to complex Windows settings.
The program also provides an application volume mixer, allowing for volume adjustment and muting for individual programs. This tool is especially useful for...
</description></item><item><title>Download CyberLink PowerDirector Ultimate 2026 v24.0.1009.0</title><pubDate> Mon, 13 Oct 2025 16:43:11 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-powerdirector-ultimate-425.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-powerdirector-ultimate-425.html
</guid><description>
CyberLink PowerDirector Ultimate is software editor, edit video and make movies on the computer from a variety of templates are made available, complete with effects, transitions, animations, and music. CyberLink PowerDirector 17 is a combination of video editing software with advanced video editing features powerful. Cblowing need to add your clips into the time line and click on 'Production'!
The tool design video in CyberLink PowerDirector have the ability to customize helps you...
</description></item><item><title>Download ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro 15.25.1012</title><pubDate> Mon, 13 Oct 2025 16:42:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-videotube-downloader-pro-1276.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chrispc-videotube-downloader-pro-1276.html
</guid><description>
ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro is the professional version support download videos and playlists from YouTube, videos from Dailymotion, BBC iPlayer, ITV Player, ABC,  FOX,CBS.com Vimeo, Prosieben, Metacafe, Blip.tv CBC.ca many more video sites. After the video is downloaded, you can convert them to the formats compatible with iPad, iPhone, iPod, MPEG-4, H. 264, MP3, AC3.
ChrisPC VideoTube Downloader Pro - Download videos on Youtube
This is one of the software download the most...
</description></item><item><title>Download Telegram for Desktop 6.2.3</title><pubDate> Mon, 13 Oct 2025 16:42:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-telegram-3376.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-telegram-3376.html
</guid><description>
Telegram is an instant messaging service and voice over IP services on the cloud platform. Client application Telegram is available for Android, iOS, Windows Phone, Windows NT, macOS, and Linux. Users can send messages and exchange photos, videos, stickers, audio and files of any kind.
Telegram - Messaging and free phone calls
Telegram seamless sync across all your devices and can be used on desktop, tablet and phone. You can send unlimited amount of messages, photos, videos and files...
</description></item><item><title>Download Agisoft Metashape Professional 2.3.0 Build 21427</title><pubDate> Mon, 13 Oct 2025 16:36:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-agisoft-metashape-professional-1731.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-agisoft-metashape-professional-1731.html
</guid><description>
Agisoft Metashape (formerly PhotoScan) is a software product independently perform image processing and digital data creation, 3D space used in GIS applications, material cultural heritage and the production visual effects as well as the indirect measurement of the different subjects scale. Technical digital photography is deployed wisely is applied with the method of computer vision led to the system processor, smart auto, on the one hand, can be managed by a new person in the field of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cutting Optimization Pro 5.18.15</title><pubDate> Mon, 13 Oct 2025 16:36:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cutting-optimization-pro-6573.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cutting-optimization-pro-6573.html
</guid><description>
Cutting Optimization Pro is a cutting software used to obtain the optimal cut layout for one-dimensional (1D) and two-dimensional (2D) pieces. The software also allows you to define and process complex products, such as desks, tables, cabinets, cabinets, bookshelves... Cutting Optimization Pro can be used to cut rectangular panels made of glass, wood, metal, plastic or any other material used in industrial applications.
Features of Cutting Optimization Pro
	Optimize 1D and 2D in the...
</description></item></channel></rss>