<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 17:35:06 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 17:35:06 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Clementine Music Player 1.4.1-55</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Sep 2025 17:49:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-clementine-4762.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-clementine-4762.html
</guid><description>
Clementine is a tools multi-platform software which allows you to listen to music from hard drive, library, audio CDS or the Internet, as well as manage it, edit the card and see the lyrics. Clementine is inspired by Amarok 1.4, focusing on a easy to use interface for searching and playing your music.
Clementine also allows you can view track information such as length, bit rate, sample rate, size, file type, number of times played and your ranking, as well as complete the card...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tablacus Explorer 25.9.7</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Sep 2025 17:48:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tablacus-explorer-3674.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tablacus-explorer-3674.html
</guid><description>
Tablacus Explorer is a file manager open-source is designed to help you arrange the contents of your folders. Tablacus Explorer has a user interface very simple and you will be familiar with working with this program immediately. Folders and files can be sorted or grouped by name, type, size and date when they were last modified. App can automatically remember to set your tab if you close it and allows you to copy or move items to different positions and save the settings to format an XML...
</description></item><item><title>Download Perfectly Clear WorkBench 4.8.0.2852</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Sep 2025 17:46:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfectly-clear-workbench-6892.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-perfectly-clear-workbench-6892.html
</guid><description>
Perfectly Clear Workbench is an application that uses image editing libraries Perfectly Clear by Athentech and is provided to demonstrate the capabilities of the Perfectly Clear processing libraries, which recognize faces and allow quick export of processing settings for use.
One of the key features in Workbench is the ability to "export to API" when saving a Preset. This allows you to make image edits in Workbench and adjust the settings to suit your editing style and needs. You can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Internet Download Manager (IDM) 6.42 Build 43</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Sep 2025 17:46:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-inetnet-download-manager-161.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-inetnet-download-manager-161.html
</guid><description>
Internet Download Manager is the download acceleration software, the best download support now, it can help you speed up the download up to five times, continue and schedule downloads. The latest version of IDM adds the compatibility of Windows 10 and Windows 11, it has supported all current popular browsers such as Internet Explorer, Mozilla Firefox, Opera, Google Chrome, ..
Download IDM with the latest version on taiwebs.com making it easy to download and manage your downloaded files...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wise Care 365 Pro 7.3.1.713</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Sep 2025 17:45:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wise-care-365-pro-106.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wise-care-365-pro-106.html
</guid><description>
Wise Care 365 pro is a package of utilities registry, disk, and other systems important for your PC. Easy to use and effective, Wise Care 365 is the best solution to improve the performance of your computer. Get Wise Care 365 and your computer will never run slow again!
Wise Care 365 pro is what?
Wise Care 365 Pro
	Check PC a clicks
	Pc cleaning &amp;amp; speed up
	Inventory hardware
	Protecting your privacy
	Protect real-time system
	Silent mode
	Boot speed faster
	Freeing up disk...
</description></item><item><title>Download IDM Retail 6.42 Build 43</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Sep 2025 17:44:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-internet-download-manager-retail-3609.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-internet-download-manager-retail-3609.html
</guid><description>
IDM - Internet Download Manager Retail is a reliable utility and high efficiency will help you to increase your download speed and manage download at better. The program allows you to easily schedule, pause and resume downloads with a single click. Moreover, the application provides error resilience robust and can restart the download at the interrupted or broken. You can restore the download is interrupted due to network problems, lost connections, unexpected power outages, computer...
</description></item><item><title>Download ZoomIt 9.01</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Sep 2025 17:43:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zoomit-3162.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zoomit-3162.html
</guid><description>
ZoomIt is a tool zoom and annotate on desktop, allows you to zoom the screen by mouse roller or arrow keys up and down on the keyboard. It is activated by a keyboard shortcut can be customized and can also be used to draw on the computer to your desk (with or without zoom), using a customizable color and pen width.
ZoomIt - Zoom in and annotate the screen
ZoomIt helps you highlighted in red highlight the segment points, the text is important. Thanks to this, the other people easily...
</description></item><item><title>Download K-Lite Codec Pack Full 19.2.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Sep 2025 17:43:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-115.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-115.html
</guid><description>
K Lite Codec Pack Full brings pc users an optimal solution for watching movies, listening to music, support most popular format today by using collection codec rich. This software also allows you to refine the quality of videos and music to enjoy, create a list of music and video to comfortable enjoy.
Prompt to software, listen to music, watch movies, currently, part, user will prompt to programs like VLC or KMP ... With VLC, it was too familiar with users, not just watch videos, listen...
</description></item><item><title>Download EaseUS Todo PCTrans Pro 14.2.1 + Technician</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Sep 2025 17:43:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-todo-pctrans-pro-1291.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-todo-pctrans-pro-1291.html
</guid><description>
EaseUS Todo PCTrans Professional is powerful software helps transfer data, apps and settings of your account from one computer to another easily. EasUS Todo PCTrans put everything into a new PC and ready to use . Transfer tool PC this easy move safe files, folder files, program and account your existing to a new computer. In just a click of the mouse, making PC your new is loaded with everything you need. Instead of copy and paste, you can transfer to new PC in a seamless way.
EaseUS...
</description></item><item><title>Download XYplorer 27.10.0900</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Sep 2025 17:42:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-533.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-533.html
</guid><description>
XYplorer - File Manager for Windows is software that supports users to manage files on the Window quickly and to arrange the folder tidy. XYplorer features tabbed browsing, search, files, powerful, preview, flexible, highly customizable interface, dual frame options and a variety of unique ways to automate effective tasks often repeat. It's fast, lightweight, and portable.
Features XYplorer
	XYplorer is a file manager mobile. It does not require any settings, store all configuration...
</description></item><item><title>Download Streamlabs OBS 1.19.5</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Sep 2025 17:42:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-streamlabs-obs-6531.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-streamlabs-obs-6531.html
</guid><description>
Streamlabs OBS is a free video and video game livestream. Streamlabs OBS uses the same OBS source code but is improved with a better user experience. The software is also free and provides the setup process even more easily than the OBS Studio. Thanks to a built-in editor, Streamlabs OBS allows you to create and preview your flow interface with only a few clicks. Streamlabs OBS offers you various layers of coating to customize and design your flow for a few minutes. Obviously, after you...
</description></item><item><title>Download CSVFileView 2.65</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Sep 2025 17:42:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-csvfileview-1383.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-csvfileview-1383.html
</guid><description>
CSVFileView is a simple software to help view and convert CSV file to easily view the content of CSV ma you have. CSVFileView is a tool free software simple allows you to view and convert the CSV file, even if you do not have full spreadsheet. The program can open CSV file, or file delimited by tab, the option automatically detect delimiter and quote and download some or all of the lines. Files are displayed in a table where you can sort, rearrange or hide the columns as...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wondershare Recoverit 13.6.3.6</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Sep 2025 17:41:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-recoverits-374.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wondershare-recoverits-374.html
</guid><description>
Wondershare Recoverit is a data recovery software that is easily lost at a rapid rate and is used by many people. You will do what happens if one day your data is suddenly lost due to the virus or deleted it, .. Wondershare Recoverit will provide you with an environment to protect important data.
Wondershare Recoverit has all the scanning processes that are divided into multiple types, from the typical recovery of the deleted files that are deleted to the recovery of missing files due...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinPaletter 1.0.9.5</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Sep 2025 17:41:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winpaletter-7537.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-winpaletter-7537.html
</guid><description>
WinPaletter lets you color the accents of Windows 10 and 11 without restrictions thanks to an easy-to-use interface. Personalizing your Windows PC made easy with WinPaletter; it gives you the ability to change almost every aspect of how your screen appears. The interface is modern and lists color change options for title bars, accents and more.
WinPaletter makes changing the color of Windows elements as simple as possible. You can also save your mix to a theme file. You can have...
</description></item><item><title>Download iTop Data Recovery Pro 5.4.0.840</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Sep 2025 17:40:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-itop-data-recovery-pro-7139.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-itop-data-recovery-pro-7139.html
</guid><description>
iTop Data Recovery Pro is a powerful data recovery tool that speeds up scanning and data recovery processes due to iTop's unique recovery algorithm. In just a few minutes, you can get your deleted files back perfectly as expected. Besides, Scan options are diverse for different needs. You can quickly find your lost data by Location and File Type.
iTop Data Recovery allows you to easily perform file recovery without limitations. More than 1000 file formats are supported. Meanwhile, this...
</description></item><item><title>Download Internet Download Manager Portable 6.42 Build 43</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Sep 2025 17:39:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-internet-download-manager-portable-11965.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-internet-download-manager-portable-11965.html
</guid><description>
Internet Download Manager (IDM) is a popular software tool that helps users download files from the internet at faster speeds. It is designed to increase download speeds up to five times, resume and schedule downloads, and support multiple download queues. IDM also has many features that make it easy to use and customize to fit your needs.
IDM has a simple and friendly interface that makes it easy to use. The software integrates seamlessly with popular web browsers such as Google Chrome,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mozilla Thunderbird 143.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Sep 2025 17:39:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thunderbird-1788.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-thunderbird-1788.html
</guid><description>
Thunderbird is an email program full featured with controls spam integration, mail filter, address book, news groups and more. It provides a clean interface and easy to use (customizable). Thunderbird also provides the security features such as S / MIME, digital signing, message encryption, support for certificates and security devices.
Before using this feature, you should review the settings IMAP, SMTP, and SSL/TLS his. Now, what all you need to do is provide your name, email address,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Macro Expert Enterprise 4.9.8.6</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Sep 2025 17:38:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-macro-expert-enterprise-3558.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-macro-expert-enterprise-3558.html
</guid><description>
Macro Expert Enterprise is a powerful tool that will help you save time and money by empowering you to automate fully the work repetitive and regular. Macro Expert Enterprise can simplify a lot of work your computer, providing more than 260 action will meet most all your needs, automate your task. To keep they have the ability to access and organize high Macro Expert Enterprise split these actions into separate groups: Email, Excel document, database, Text, window, FTP, Internet, File,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sysinternals Suite 2025.9.16</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Sep 2025 17:38:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sysinternals-suite-1447.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sysinternals-suite-1447.html
</guid><description>
Sysinternals Suite is a software monitoring and control system helps to find and fix errors most impressive. The software includes more than seventy utilities aimed at overcoming the problem related to managing files and disks, network problems and security, as well as information about processes and systems. Because of this very rich, the analysis of each ministry will take a significant period of time and therefore, we decided to focus on the most popular.
Sysinternals Suite - Set of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Viber for PC 26.2.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Sep 2025 17:37:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-viber-2406.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-viber-2406.html
</guid><description>
Viber is a software of instant messaging, based on VoIP protocols, multi-platform due to the Viber Media development for smart phones used to send sms and make calls over the internet. Along with text messaging, users can exchange images, video and audio.
Viber - software news message, chat online
This is a program that is quite popular is mainly designed for mobile phones, but now we are talking about the version for Windows, so immediately. It will allow you to send messages to other...
</description></item><item><title>Download MaxCut Business Edition 2.9.5.5</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Sep 2025 17:37:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-maxcut-business-edition-3912.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-maxcut-business-edition-3912.html
</guid><description>
MaxCut Business Edition is a software to create cutting diagrams, accurate, and cost estimate for the wood industry, cabinets and metal,.. You enter the size and material, MaxCut will do the rest! Produce optimized cutting diagrams, create estimates, orders, and labels - it's just a click. Run the application MaxCut Business Edition brings a pretty clean interface and slick quickly get you up and running. Most space represents the editing area, with the main function are stored cleverly in...
</description></item><item><title>Download K-Lite Codec Pack Mega 19.2.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Sep 2025 17:36:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-mega-3202.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-mega-3202.html
</guid><description>
K-Lite Mega Codec Pack is a collection of components needed for audio playback and the video in the player DirectShow like Windows Media Player, Media Center, and Media Player Classic. This is the latest beta version, Pack Codec K-Lite latest stable. The Mega variant is the biggest of the four variants of the codec pack. It provides everything you need to play all audio and video files. In addition, it also contains some codecs ACM / VFW can be used by the application coding / video...
</description></item><item><title>Download MassTube 2026 v21.0.2.164 Ultra</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Sep 2025 17:35:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-masstube-plus-461.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-masstube-plus-461.html
</guid><description>
MassTube Plus is a small utility used to download the favorite videos of you on youtube on your computer. This is a software compact, has a simple design with few options to download videos fastest. The you complete peace of mind because the software is easy to use, built exclusively for a single goal: to retrieve the video file from YouTube, so it doesn't pack the other useful features such as search engine integrated and a download audio file.
MassTube can work with multiple output...
</description></item><item><title>Download DriverHub 1.4.0</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Sep 2025 17:34:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-driverhub-6486.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-driverhub-6486.html
</guid><description>
DriverHub  is a tool that helps provide the user an efficient way to keep the drivers in the computer up to date. The driver storage facility in the cloud keeps updating the latest drivers and ensures that you always get the most relevant and latest.
DriverHub quickly scans your pc for any outdated drivers, then finds and displays the latest available drivers to install. It's important to make sure you have all the latest drivers installed, etc. on your device to keep it working...
</description></item><item><title>Download Directory Opus Pro 13.18.4 Beta</title><pubDate> Wed, 17 Sep 2025 17:34:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-opus-pro-779.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-directory-opus-pro-779.html
</guid><description>
Directory Opus Pro is a software replacement for Explorer with traditional strength and function more than any manager other files. Directory Opus Pro full support for high DPI screen (for example 4K and 5K) with the rename dialog is redesigned, with new features. Besides being a recording macro only allows you to perform mass renaming complex that don't need regular expressions. In addition, Directory Opus Pro also enhances the ability to script.Better handling of renaming recursive and...
</description></item></channel></rss>