<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 11:56:30 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 11:56:30 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download RapidRAW 1.3.6</title><pubDate> Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:59:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rapidraw-13957.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rapidraw-13957.html
</guid><description>
RapidRAW is a modern, high-performance, open-source RAW photo editor, designed to deliver a fast and clean editing experience with a lightweight footprint (under 30MB). Built with performance and usability in mind, the software is aimed at photographers who want a simple, efficient, and fun workflow without compromising performance.
Key Features
	GPU-accelerated processing: Uses a custom WGSL shader to process all image adjustments on the GPU, allowing for smooth, responsive editing...
</description></item><item><title>Download WinToUSB Enterprise Portable 9.9</title><pubDate> Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:56:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wintousb-portable-11910.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wintousb-portable-11910.html
</guid><description>
WinToUSB Portable (Windows To USB) is a handy tool that allows you to install and run a fully functional Windows operating system on an external hard drive, USB flash drive or Thunderbolt drive. It has a user-friendly interface that makes it easy for users to install and run Windows on a USB drive. It is suitable for both beginners and advanced users.
It's easy and effective, in just 3 steps and a few minutes you can create your first Windows 11/10/8/7 or portable Windows Server...
</description></item><item><title>Download ACDSee Luxea Video Editor Pro 8.0.0.3317</title><pubDate> Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:56:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-acdsee-luxea-video-editor-5312.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-acdsee-luxea-video-editor-5312.html
</guid><description>
ACDSee Luxea Video Editor is a software simple and effective to edit and edit all types of video files (with the ability to record video from the screen), unlike the video editing software professional and heavy the other, with the environment simple and easy, the task video editing for non-professional users he's doing that. Using software ACDSee Luxea Video Editor, you can edit or mixed film and do things like quickly edit audio and video of the video file, set video effects, simple to...
</description></item><item><title>Download IObit Uninstaller Pro Portable 14.4.0.3</title><pubDate> Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:55:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iobit-uninstaller-pro-portable-4487.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-iobit-uninstaller-pro-portable-4487.html
</guid><description>
IObit Uninstaller Pro Portable is the portable version has activation available version Pro helps you to uninstall program and remove unwanted software installed on your computer very easily. Even if you have trouble uninstalling and cannot uninstall them from the applet control panel, Programs and features (Add or Remove Programs). IObit Uninstaller Pro Portable is an option faster and more efficient for option Add or Remove Programs in the Windows control Panel. The program is packed...
</description></item><item><title>Download proDAD Hide 2.0.214.3</title><pubDate> Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:54:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-prodad-hide-6054.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-prodad-hide-6054.html
</guid><description>
proDAD Hide is a real problem recetor when something that gets into your frame can cause loss of focus or not in the right place. In most cases, these problems became apparent in the editing process. After an analysis process, proDAD Hide will replace the object with its original background-all automatically performed in the shortest time without any manual effort. For this process, proDAD Hide will need a few moments before and after the object needs to be removed from view.
The...
</description></item><item><title>Download ApowerREC Portable 1.8.1.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:54:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-apowerrec-portable-12165.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-apowerrec-portable-12165.html
</guid><description>
ApowerREC Portable (an unofficial portable version) can record anything on your screen, including desktop activities, live streaming video, web meetings, and more. You can record your activity in full screen or in a custom zone, specifically placed on the screen along with the audio, and it has the great ability to keep the video synchronized with the audio. In addition, recording a webcam or taking screenshots with a webcam is also possible, you can record chat videos or make tutorial...
</description></item><item><title>Download proDAD Mercalli V6 SAL 6.0.632.3</title><pubDate> Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:53:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-prodad-mercalli-v5-sal-6435.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-prodad-mercalli-v5-sal-6435.html
</guid><description>
proDAD Mercalli V5 SAL+  is the piece of software that will optimize your footage! No matter the sport, whatever type of shot, no matter what type of camera you are using, it processes shake, shake and distortion individually and in combination! Compared with the camera's internal stabilizer, proDAD Mercalli V5 SAL+ clearly produces outstanding results and allows for a wider viewing angle. With additional features, comprehensive CMOS tuning and further optimization in the most stable and...
</description></item><item><title>Download DriverStore Explorer 0.12.110</title><pubDate> Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:53:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-driverstore-explorer-2892.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-driverstore-explorer-2892.html
</guid><description>
DriverStore Explorer RAPR is software for dealing with drivers Windows more easily. The supported operations include enumeration, adding driver package (stage), add and install, delete and delete force from the store drivers.
DriverStore Explorer - drivers
The features of the DriverStore Explorer
	Listed / Listed all the packages are held in the store current drivers.
	Export the list as CSV.
	Added package drivers catalog drivers (called staging)
	Install &amp;amp; Add driver package...
</description></item><item><title>Download XnView Portable 2.52.2 Complete</title><pubDate> Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:52:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xnview-portable-3548.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xnview-portable-3548.html
</guid><description>
XnView Portable is a great software for reading, viewing, and processing all your images. XnView Portable allows you to read almost 500 format (Multi-page and animated still formats, TIFF, APNG, GIF, ICO, etc.). Some formats may require Plug-in. XnView Portable also offers modular Capture useful screen interface and Microsoft Windows TWAIN and WIA to retrieve images.
XnView Portable - Supports viewing and editing photos
Features of XnView Portable
	Mode viewing thumbnails
	Mode watch...
</description></item><item><title>Download Rocrail Build 5976</title><pubDate> Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:52:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rocrail-3193.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rocrail-3193.html
</guid><description>
Rocrail is a free software to control the training model for the operating system Linux , Apple macOS , Windows and Raspbian / Armbian . Rocrail bear all responsibility in the control of a railway model, and accessories of them. Trains can be controlled manually or fully controlled by software in automatic mode. A mixed operation, i.e. control a number of ships and other vessels at high speed fully automatic is possible.
Rocrail - control layout for the operating system
With Rocrail,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Device Cleanup Tool 1.5.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:51:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-device-cleanup-tool-6911.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-device-cleanup-tool-6911.html
</guid><description>
Device Cleanup Tool is a free tool that allows you to see what devices are attached to your computer like USB, Modem, CDROM, NET,.. and it allows you to choose easily and delete multiple device entries at once. It also tells you when the device was last used to help you ensure the right ones are discarded.
Before using the Device Cleanup Tool software, you need to run it as an administrator so that you can erase the devices connected to the computer without errors. Device Cleanup Tool...
</description></item><item><title>Download AnyMP4 Blu-ray Player 6.5.78</title><pubDate> Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:51:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anymp4-blu-ray-player-1113.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anymp4-blu-ray-player-1113.html
</guid><description>
AnyMP4 Blu-ray Player software is a Blu-ray Player wonderful and this unique ability to play any Blu-ray which are released in different regions, all folder Blu-ray files and ISO image backup on your hard drive. It also features the function of HD software Video Player, can play 1080p HD video and AVCHD video in picture effect, video quality, fluent and high.
AnyMP4 Blu-ray Player - The video player Blu-ray
In addition, software Blu-ray Player works as a software Universal Media...
</description></item><item><title>Download SimpleMind Pro Portable 2.7.0 Build 6568</title><pubDate> Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:50:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-simplemind-pro-portable-11988.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-simplemind-pro-portable-11988.html
</guid><description>
SimpleMind Pro Portable is professional mind mapping software that allows users to create, edit and organize their ideas and thoughts visually. It offers a wide range of advanced features and functionalities to enhance the mind mapping process. The software provides an intuitive interface that makes it easy to add branches, nodes, and connect ideas. Users can also customize the look of their mind maps by changing colors, fonts, and styles.
In addition, SimpleMind Pro offers additional...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wipe Pro 2025.09</title><pubDate> Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:50:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wipe-pro-710.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wipe-pro-710.html
</guid><description>
Wipe Pro is software that helps clean up litter, increase in hard drive space besides also protect your privacy on the Internet, it removes records about personal activity on the computer. You will be able to delete browser history and the cache, the file index.dat, registry, files, cookies, internet history, auto complete, temporary internet files and many other items. This program also delete all activities other individuals that you made when using the PC and regardless of which...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tipard Blu-ray Player 6.3.62</title><pubDate> Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:49:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tipard-blu-ray-player-3780.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tipard-blu-ray-player-3780.html
</guid><description>
Tipard Blu-ray Player is software play Blu-ray comprehensive, noteworthy, capable of the kind of disk / folder / file image ISO, HD video 1080P and the format video / audio to other popular, including MP4, MXF, MTS, MKV, AVI, FLV, MPEG, MP3 etc. powerful functions into one software but no loss of quality. Tipard Blu-ray Player comes with user-friendly interface suitable for both advanced users and inexperienced. The program provides support for a wide variety of formats audio and video...
</description></item><item><title>Download CapCut PC 6.8.1.2758</title><pubDate> Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:49:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capcut-pc-9995.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-capcut-pc-9995.html
</guid><description>
CapCut PC is a simple video editing tool that you can freely use anywhere. You can create videos on your browser, desktop and laptop, or on your phone. Versatile editing, magical AI tools, team collaboration, and built-in assets. Create videos in a whole new way.
You can edit videos based on editing the timeline, in the process you can add different elements and effects to the video to give the best effect to your work. It is a simple and intuitive set of editing tools and effects that...
</description></item><item><title>Download Hardentools 2.6</title><pubDate> Sun, 10 Aug 2025 23:48:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hardentools-6763.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hardentools-6763.html
</guid><description>
Hardentools is a collection of simple utilities designed to disable certain "features" displayed by the operating system (currently Microsoft Windows) and major consumer applications. These features, which are generally assumed to be for Enterprise customers, are often useless to ordinary users and are instead dangerous because they are very often abused by attackers to execute malicious code on computers of the victim.
Features of Hardentools:
	Disable Windows Script Server.
	Turn...
</description></item><item><title>Download SkinFiner 5.7.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 10 Aug 2025 15:51:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-skinfiner-6346.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-skinfiner-6346.html
</guid><description>
SkinFiner  is photo editing software designed to free you from tedious manual work in skin retouching. It helps to smooth and strengthen the skin easily and quickly.
Features of SkinFiner
	Smartly smooths skin and removes blemishes while preserving skin texture to give portraits a natural and professional look
	Skin tone adjustment helps you to improve skin tone, change skin color, refine skin light with shadows and highlights, adjust skin brightness and contrast, make skin look...
</description></item><item><title>Download dBpoweramp Video Converter Premier R2025-08-08</title><pubDate> Sun, 10 Aug 2025 15:50:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbpoweramp-video-converter-6953.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbpoweramp-video-converter-6953.html
</guid><description>
dBpoweramp Video Converter is a video conversion software, reliable, quick, and given the highest quality results. dBpoweramp Video Converter is based on technology similar to its sister product dBpoweramp Music Converter, which is more than 30 million trusted users.
dBpoweramp Video Converter supports 8K, 4K and HD conversion to mp4 (h264, h265), Windows Media Video, Webm (VP9), Apple Quicktime (mov), AVI to name some. It will complete the work in the fast time twice as it uses your...
</description></item><item><title>Download ExamDiff Pro Master Edition 16.0.1.8</title><pubDate> Sun, 10 Aug 2025 15:50:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-examdiff-pro-master-312.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-examdiff-pro-master-312.html
</guid><description>
ExamDiff Pro Master is a tool to compare files and folders intuitive and easy to use, intuitive and easy to use for Windows. ExamDiff Pro Master has unique features distinguishes ExamDiff Pro with the program compare other. ExamDiff Pro Master to help perform reviews of code and share other reports with your colleagues and compare local website with FTP server by plug-ins more integrated.
ExamDiff Pro Master can create a snapshot folder for comparison and storage in the future, compare...
</description></item><item><title>Download K-Lite Codec Pack Update 19.1.3</title><pubDate> Sun, 10 Aug 2025 15:49:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-update-5145.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-k-lite-codec-pack-update-5145.html
</guid><description>
K-Lite Codec Pack Update is the update of the set of codecs and related tools. Codec stands for Compressor-decompressor. Codec is necessary to encode and decode (play) audio and video. K-Lite Codec Pack Update is designed as a user-friendly solution with users to play all movie files your. With Codec Pack K-Lite, you can play 99% of all the movies found on your computer. A number of packages codec is not friendly with computers, as they tend to slow down Windows, break down multimedia...
</description></item><item><title>Download Picture Window Pro 8.0.522</title><pubDate> Sun, 10 Aug 2025 15:48:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-picture-window-pro-7452.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-picture-window-pro-7452.html
</guid><description>
Picture Window Pro is a powerful image editing tool designed for serious photographers with strict creative and quality standards. Its comprehensive set of photo editing and editing tools let you control and shape every aspect of your images.
Picture Window Pro 8 is a complete rewrite of Picture Window Pro 7. It features non-destructive image editing through a novel interface based on an image tree. It also fully supports large, high-resolution displays and can be used in dual monitor...
</description></item><item><title>Download Software Companions GerbView 11.16.0.612</title><pubDate> Sun, 10 Aug 2025 15:48:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-software-companions-gerbview-1484.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-software-companions-gerbview-1484.html
</guid><description>
GerbView is a file, advanced, but easy to use, convert, print, and view files HPGL, HPGL / 2, Excellon and raster. It supports both RS274D and RS274X. You can use this software to convert the old format and RS274D standard to the new RS274X have default data. Gerbview is used to represent and illustrate the intricate design of you.
Software Companions GerbView - conversion, printing, and viewing HPGL, HPGL / 2, Excellon
You don't need to wait for rendered images to see the picture of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wing FTP Server Corporate 8.0.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 10 Aug 2025 15:47:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wing-ftp-server-corporate-2752.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wing-ftp-server-corporate-2752.html
</guid><description>
Wing FTP Server Corporate is a highly functional, easy and safe can be used in the operating system Windows, Linux, Mac and Solaris are used. The software supports a number of file transfer protocol such as FTP, HTTP, FTPS, HTTPS and SFTP. Wing FTP Server provides web-based interface to manage the server at any time. You can also get performance server and the online and even send email notifications about various events happening on the server.
Management server multi-function
Wing FTP...
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 7.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 10 Aug 2025 15:47:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-11-7760.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tweaknow-winsecret-plus-for-windows-11-7760.html
</guid><description>
TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 is a program that allows users to discover hidden settings in Windows 11. This application is specially designed for Windows 11, groups many registry settings and distribute them from the easy and secure user interface. With TweakNow WinSecret Plus for Windows 11 you can move the Windows taskbar to the top and resize the taskbar by editing the registry value. With any application that modifies the registry, we recommend that you have a backup copy...
</description></item></channel></rss>