<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 13:47:19 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 13:47:19 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Topaz Photo AI Pro 4.0.3</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 16:33:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-photo-ai-8105.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-photo-ai-8105.html
</guid><description>
What is Topaz Photo AI?
Topaz Photo AI is a professional software that automatically adjusts for your image quality needs. Simply import images into Topaz Photo AI and it will use specially trained AI models to first detect unique details, clarity, and resolution issues before applying the intelligently adjusts to maximize your image quality.
For users experienced with Topaz Labs image quality applications, it combines the functionality of DeNoise AI, Sharpen AI and Gigapixel AI into...
</description></item><item><title>Download XYplorer 27.10.0500</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 16:33:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-533.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xyplorer-533.html
</guid><description>
XYplorer - File Manager for Windows is software that supports users to manage files on the Window quickly and to arrange the folder tidy. XYplorer features tabbed browsing, search, files, powerful, preview, flexible, highly customizable interface, dual frame options and a variety of unique ways to automate effective tasks often repeat. It's fast, lightweight, and portable.
Features XYplorer
	XYplorer is a file manager mobile. It does not require any settings, store all configuration...
</description></item><item><title>Download UniFab 3.0.2.5</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 16:32:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-unifab-10377.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-unifab-10377.html
</guid><description>
UniFab is software to efficiently convert, compress and edit more than 1000 video formats for playback on any device without losing quality. Enlarge video/audio to 1080p/DTS 7.1 and upgrade video to HDR10 or Dolby Vision with AI Enhancer. UniFab Pro provides the best AI-powered zoom tool that allows you to enlarge videos from low resolutions, such as 360p, 480p and 720p, to 1080p without losing any quality. Clearer and sharper image details will bring you an exceptional viewing...
</description></item><item><title>Download Easy System Utility 1.1.47.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 16:32:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easy-system-utility-10906.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easy-system-utility-10906.html
</guid><description>
Easy System Utility is a powerful, all-in-one program designed for Windows 10 and 11 users. This versatile tool will be your main choice for your computing experience. better! You can see your operating system, CPU model, GPU, Memory, Motherboard, Network, and drivers all in one place, saving you time. Easy System Utility's interface is arranged in a tabbed menu, allowing you to access features.
You can analyze files first, then easily clean and delete them from your PC or laptop. You...
</description></item><item><title>Download Realtek Ethernet Controller All-In-One Drivers 11.26.0722.2025</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 16:31:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-realtek-ethernet-controller-all-in-one-drivers-6485.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-realtek-ethernet-controller-all-in-one-drivers-6485.html
</guid><description>
Realtek Ethernet All-In-One Controller Driver is the software driver for the Realtek Ethernet cards. It is a program used to communicate from the Windows PC OS to the device. This software is required in most cases for the hardware device to function properly. In most cases, drivers come with Windows or can be found by going to Windows Update in Control Panel and checking for updates as well as downloaded from the Realtek support website.
</description></item><item><title>Download Gilisoft DRM Protection 8.6.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 16:31:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-video-drm-protection-5260.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-video-drm-protection-5260.html
</guid><description>
Gilisoft Video DRM Protection is software that helps you can protect your videos and the E-Learning content to another by secure, encrypted the files, your content and distribute them to the target audience authorized of you. Very easy to make video / sound / pictures of you can't see are for anyone except those you allow. Gilisoft Video DRM Protection can encrypt and pack video &amp;amp; codec &amp;amp; player into exe.
Gilisoft Video DRM Protection can easily encode almost any kind of Video...
</description></item><item><title>Download Easy System Utility Pro 1.1.47</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 16:30:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easy-system-utility-pro-12380.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easy-system-utility-pro-12380.html
</guid><description>
Easy System Utility Pro is a powerful, all-in-one program designed for Windows 10 and 11 users. This versatile tool should be your primary choice to improve your computing experience ! This is the complete version with additional and enhanced features. It will help you easily determine your computer's hardware specifications with a system overview. You can view the operating system, CPU model, GPU, Memory, Motherboard, Network and even drivers.
It also supports launching programs,...
</description></item><item><title>Download QuickSoundSwitcher 1.6.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 16:30:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quicksoundswitcher-14033.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quicksoundswitcher-14033.html
</guid><description>
QuickSoundSwitcher is a lightweight, open-source Windows utility designed to quickly and easily manage audio input and output devices. It allows users to switch between multiple audio devices (e.g. speakers, headphones, microphones) and control the volume directly from the system tray without navigating to complex Windows settings.
The program also provides an application volume mixer, allowing for volume adjustment and muting for individual programs. This tool is especially useful for...
</description></item><item><title>Download DVDFab 13.0.4.6</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 16:30:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dvdfab-67.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dvdfab-67.html
</guid><description>
DVDFab All-In-One is a multi-purpose combo of nearly all powerful DVDFab products-DVD replication, Ripper DVD, Blu-ray Ripper, Blu-ray Ripper, Copy UHD, Blu-ray to DVD, DVD to Blu-ray Transaction, DVD Creator, Blu-ray Creator, video conversion, Cinavia DVD removal, Windows DVD removal, DRM elimination for Apple, Screen Recorder and Editor for iOS, Hi-Fi Sound and File Transfer. It provides a complete solution to all of your DVD/Blu-ray/video problems and the perfect execution.
DvDFab -...
</description></item><item><title>Download Python 3.13.7</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 16:29:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-python-4355.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-python-4355.html
</guid><description>
Python is a programming language high-level for the purpose of programming multi-function, due to Guido van Rossum created and first launched in 1991. Python is designed with strong advantages is easy to read, easy to learn and easy to remember. Python is a language can form very bright, clear structure, convenient for new people to learn programming. Python fully create a dynamic and user mechanisms to allocate the memory automatically; so it is similar to Perl, Ruby, Scheme, Smalltalk,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Awesome Miner Ultimate 11.2.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 16:28:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-awesome-miner-9041.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-awesome-miner-9041.html
</guid><description>
Awesome Miner is a software application designed to manage and monitor cryptocurrency mining operations. It supports a wide variety of mining hardware, including ASICs and GPUs, and can be used to manage mining for a variety of cryptocurrencies, including Bitcoin, Ethereum, and Litecoin.
Powerful tool to manage and monitor cryptocurrency mining activities. With support for a wide variety of mining hardware and cryptocurrencies, mobile apps, and customizable alerting and performance...
</description></item><item><title>Download IsMyTouchScreenOK 2.88</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 16:28:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ismytouchscreenok-11229.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ismytouchscreenok-11229.html
</guid><description>
With IsMyTouchScreenOK you can simply but very quickly check if there are any bad contacts on your touch screen. It can be used to test the functionality of a new touch screen before purchasing or to test a purchased touch screen during the warranty period. You may receive a replacement product after the manufacturer reports a contact failure.
By touching and testing all areas of the touchscreen with one or more fingers, you can ensure that the touchscreen is...
</description></item><item><title>Download Listary Pro 6.3.5.94</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 16:27:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-listary-pro-7495.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-listary-pro-7495.html
</guid><description>
Listary Pro is a great search utility that makes it easy to find items in an unmanageable list of Windows applications. It works with entries in Windows Explorer, Task Manager, Registry Editor, Windows Desktop, File Open/Save dialogs, and others.
Features of Listary Pro
	Speed ​​up your work with instant access to your favorite folders and files.
	Quick Switch lets the file dialog switch to the folder you're viewing in your favorite file manager instantly, or vice versa.
	Browse...
</description></item><item><title>Download HE - Hardware Read and Write Utility 1.25.08.14</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 16:27:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-he-hardware-read-and-write-utility-4287.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-he-hardware-read-and-write-utility-4287.html
</guid><description>
HE - Hardware Read and Write Utility is a powerful utility intended for hardware engineer, engineer, BIOS developer, driver, engineer, QA engineers, performance test engineers, diagnostic, etc., this utility access almost all the computer hardware, including PCI (PCI Express), index / Data, PCI, memory, index memory / Data space I / O, Index I / O / Data, Super I / O, DIMM SPD, CPU The registers MSR, screen, SMART, physical area of the hard drive identification data, ATA, dump tables ACPI...
</description></item><item><title>Download KORG ARP 2600 1.1.6</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 16:26:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-korg-arp-2600-13864.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-korg-arp-2600-13864.html
</guid><description>
The KORG ARP 2600 is a semi-modular synthesizer, a faithful replica and modern version of the iconic ARP 2600 synthesizer, widely considered a classic in major studios and highly regarded on the second-hand market. Now, KORG is pleased to introduce the first truly accurate software reproduction of this essential synthesizer: the KORG Collection ARP 2600.
Sounds and Features
	The synthesizer includes multiple oscillators with classic waveforms (sawtooth, square, pulse, triangle, sine),...
</description></item><item><title>Download Cyberduck 9.2.0.43571</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 16:26:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberduck-2637.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberduck-2637.html
</guid><description>
Cyberduck is a browser, file open-source and the client transferred to the hosting account FTP, SFTP, WebDAV, Cloud Files, Google Docs and Amazon S3. In addition to file transfers it offers features account management includes installing ACL, version group S3 configuration, Akamai and CloudFront, and more.
In addition, the Cyberduck also helps you can create bookmarks to quickly access favorite locations, edit files remotely using the editor you choose, import bookmarks from popular...
</description></item><item><title>Download Easy Gamer Utility Pro 1.3.80</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 16:26:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easy-gamer-utility-pro-12381.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easy-gamer-utility-pro-12381.html
</guid><description>
Easy Gamer Utility Pro is an easy-to-use program for Windows that can do a lot on your PC to help fix gaming problems, performance problems, and general optimization! The best tool to improve your Windows gaming experience! Is your game laggy and slow? If so, you can use the built-in game accelerator in Easy Gamer Utility, which boosts system performance, makes games run smoother, and increases FPS.
Additionally, this handy utility deletes and cleans unwanted and unnecessary temporary...
</description></item><item><title>Download HFS: HTTP File Server (version 3) 0.57.11</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 16:25:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hfs-http-file-server-11851.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hfs-http-file-server-11851.html
</guid><description>
HFS is a web file server to run on your computer. Share a folder or even a file thanks to the virtual file system. Essentially, this application turns your computer into an HTTP server and all users who want to connect and download files can do so by loading a simple website in their browser. HFS includes many configuration settings, so you can basically change each part of the application, starting with how users download files and ending with the appearance of the created website.
HFS...
</description></item><item><title>Download KORG VOX Super Continental 1.1.4</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 16:24:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-korg-vox-super-continental-13425.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-korg-vox-super-continental-13425.html
</guid><description>
KORG VOX Super Continental is an extremely accurate software reproduction of the classic Vox Super Continental combo organ, originally a two-neck organ from the 1960s and 1970s renowned for its distinctive sound and design. KORG's version uses their proprietary CMT (Component Modeling Technology) to digitally simulate every aspect of the original instrument's unique circuitry and mechanical behavior, including the subtle imperfections of hundreds of individual key contacts and the rare...
</description></item><item><title>Download KORG EP-1 1.1.4</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 16:24:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-korg-ep-1-13423.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-korg-ep-1-13423.html
</guid><description>
KORG EP-1 is a software electronic piano sound engine originally developed for KORG's flagship workstation synthesizer KRONOS in 2011. It uses KORG's proprietary Multi-Dimensional Synthesis (MDS) technology, allowing for extremely realistic and dynamic tonal changes that respond precisely to each key, surpassing traditional sample playback methods.
Key features of the EP-1 include includes:
	Reproduces seven classic reed and reed-type electric pianos from the 1970s and 1980s with...
</description></item><item><title>Download Network Notepad 6.1.6</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 16:23:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-network-notepad-1665.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-network-notepad-1665.html
</guid><description>
Network Notepad is a software tool built to help you design network diagrams and save them to analyze and safe guard. Network Notepad is a major rewrite using Microsoft .NET, so it provides compatibility and stability better with the Windows operating system. Network Notepad offers management features can determine a user's, such as telnet and FTP, HTTP and Ping. The objects can be chosen from the provided library and drag into diagram, where they can be linked together with the link type...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ant Download Manager Pro 2.15.9.91212</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 00:47:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ant-download-manager-pro-137.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ant-download-manager-pro-137.html
</guid><description>
Ant Download Manager Pro is software support download has the same features as IDM, even it has many prominent features, more user friendly more and have speed download data incredible. Ant Download Manager is a Internet content downloader quickly with support download at video! Function: fully Integrated with the web browsers most popular: Internet Explorer 8+, Mozilla Firefox 32 +, Google Chrome 31+ and the copies of them (Pale Moon, Opera, Vivaldi, Slimjet, ComodoDragon, etc.). you...
</description></item><item><title>Download VirtualBox 7.2.0 + Extension Pack</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 00:46:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-virtualbox-285.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-virtualbox-285.html
</guid><description>
VirtualBox is a virtualization software open source allows you to run one or more operating system in a virtual machine while running Windows. It is used for purposes such as experience app or try to play the game new in a safe environment, do not affect the main operating system of you. With this software, users will better control multiple virtual machines at the same time.
VirtualBox - Create virtual drive allows running multiple operating systems at the same time
The program comes...
</description></item><item><title>Download Clean Space Pro 2025 v713</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 00:45:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-clean-space-pro-545.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-clean-space-pro-545.html
</guid><description>
Clean Space Pro is the professional software remove junk files from the system to release the hard drive and improve computer performance. From time to time when using computer files as buffers, temporary files of various programs, files, internet cookies, internet browsing history, diary, file index.dat, registry entries and even the Windows will gradually increase, occupy wise space your hard drive and make the computer suffer from stagnation. The best solution is to use the Clean Space...
</description></item><item><title>Download Batch Image Converter 2.1.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 00:44:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-batch-image-converter-7430.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-batch-image-converter-7430.html
</guid><description>
Batch Image Converter is software that helps you batch convert image files. It can work with many image types (*.bmp, *.gif, *.jpg, *.png, *.tiff, *.tif, *.psd, *.pcx, *.pbm, *.pgm , *. ppm, *.tga, *.tpic, etc.).
Features of Batch Image Converter
	Easy, intuitive, one-click configuration.
	Save/load session for easy use again.
	Support command line execution.
	Execute automatically at specific time.
</description></item></channel></rss>