<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 13:43:14 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 13:43:14 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Listen Audiobook Player 5.3.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 24 Aug 2025 16:42:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-listen-audiobook-player-8511.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-listen-audiobook-player-8511.html
</guid><description>
Listen Audiobook Player is a mobile app for playing audiobooks on your phone or tablet. It lets you play, pause, rewind, and fast-forward audiobooks with ease, while also providing a convenient way to track your listening progress.
Some key features of Listen Audiobook Player include:
	Library Management: Allows you to store and organize your audiobooks in a virtual library for easy access.
	Bookmark: Automatically saves your listening position so you can pick up where you left...
</description></item><item><title>Download Duplicates Cleaner 4.1.2</title><pubDate> Sun, 24 Aug 2025 16:42:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-duplicates-cleaner-9126.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-duplicates-cleaner-9126.html
</guid><description>
Are you facing memory problems on your device? Is your device running out of memory? Do you want to increase the storage space on your device?, if "yes" then look no further and hit that "install" button.
Efficient Duplicate Cleaner: Find and clean up "Genuine" duplicate images, duplicate audio files, duplicate Videos and duplicate documents in the simplest way!, Our Duplicate Cleaner app uses advanced proprietary techniques to quickly identify and remove "Genuine Duplicates" from your...
</description></item><item><title>Download DAVx⁵ – CalDAV CardDAV WebDAV 4.5.3-gplay</title><pubDate> Sun, 24 Aug 2025 16:41:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-davx-caldav-carddav-webdav-8633.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-davx-caldav-carddav-webdav-8633.html
</guid><description>
DAVx is the only all-in-one app for everything CalDAV, CardDAV and WebDAV! This is a full-featured synchronization solution for your contacts (CardDAV), calendar (CalDAV), and tasks (based on VTODO). The app is easy to install and integrates seamlessly with your favorite calendar/contacts apps (including default apps). It can also be used separately if you have CalDAV, CardDAV or just Tasks. DAVx can also be used to access your remote WebDAV files.
Features of DAVx for Android
	Sync...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDF Scanner app - TapScanner 3.0.80</title><pubDate> Sun, 24 Aug 2025 16:40:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pdf-scanner-app-tapscanner-12104.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pdf-scanner-app-tapscanner-12104.html
</guid><description>
TapScanner is a mobile application that allows you to scan documents with your smartphone camera and convert them into PDF files or image formats. It essentially turns your device into a portable scanner, making capturing and digitizing physical documents convenient on the go.
TapScanner Features
	Scan documents, receipts, QRs and business cards
	Document Scanner App - Automatic Border Detection
	Tweak your images with multiple filters to achieve perfection
	Easily manage your...
</description></item><item><title>Download QRbot: QR &amp;amp; barcode reader 3.2.4</title><pubDate> Sun, 24 Aug 2025 16:36:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-qrbot-qr-barcode-reader-8737.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-qrbot-qr-barcode-reader-8737.html
</guid><description>
Scan all types of QR codes and barcodes with QRBot's QR code reader. Quickly access your scanning-related functions: For example, add contact data to your address book or connect to a WiFi hotspot with just one click. Easily share arbitrary data such as website links by displaying them on your screen as QR codes and scanning them with another device.
Supported QR codes 
	Website links (URLs)
	Contact data (Mecard, Vcard, VCF)
	Calendar events
	WiFi hotspot access...
</description></item><item><title>Download The Guardian - Live World News 6.187.21898</title><pubDate> Sun, 24 Aug 2025 16:35:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-the-guardian-news-sport-8572.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-the-guardian-news-sport-8572.html
</guid><description>
Read the best news stories, hot news &amp;amp; comments along the way. The Guardian app gives you access to the latest politics, business and sports news through award-winning journalism.
World news, live updates &amp;amp; opinion - take your news feed with you wherever you go. Explore US stories, headlines, content and media on a variety of topics; from business to music, politics, sports, culture &amp;amp; more.
5 reasons to download The Guardian App
	Breaking news alerts, sent straight to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Balance: Meditation &amp;amp; Sleep 1.185.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 24 Aug 2025 16:35:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-balance-meditation-sleep-8559.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-balance-meditation-sleep-8559.html
</guid><description>
Improve stress, sleep and more with the world's first personalized meditation program. Balance is your personal meditation coach. Each day, you will answer questions about your meditation experience, goals, and interests. Using an audio library of thousands of files, Balance puts together the perfect daily meditation for you. The more you share over time, the more personalized and effective your meditation becomes.
Balance's daily meditation sessions are organized according to a 10-Day...
</description></item><item><title>Download RateX Currency Converter 3.8.12</title><pubDate> Sun, 24 Aug 2025 16:31:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ratex-currency-converter-10968.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-ratex-currency-converter-10968.html
</guid><description>
RateX is an all-in-one currency converter app that helps you track global exchange rates.
Features of RateX Currency Converter
	130 currencies to choose from, including Euro and Dollar
	Instant currency conversion based on online exchange rates
	Offline mode for on-the-go access
	Convert multiple currencies at once
	Historical charts for trend analysis
	Latest financial news
	Custom exchange rates for personalized conversions
	Home screen widget for easy access
	User-friendly...
</description></item><item><title>Download NYTimes: US and Global News 11.38.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 24 Aug 2025 16:27:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-the-new-york-times-8235.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-the-new-york-times-8235.html
</guid><description>
Understand the world around you with original reporting from The New York Times. Free to download, The Times app gives you access to expert news from 1700 journalists in 160 countries worldwide. From breaking news to opinion, business, technology and the arts, subscribers get unlimited access to groundbreaking reporting, analysis and commentary.
Features of The New York Times
	Wake up with The Morning, your morning guide to what's happening and why it matters. It's the news you need...
</description></item><item><title>Download VAG DPF 4.43.15</title><pubDate> Sun, 24 Aug 2025 16:27:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-vag-dpf-8892.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-vag-dpf-8892.html
</guid><description>
VAG DPF shows you the most important data related to the DPF particulate filter and its regeneration phases using the ELM327 Bluetooth/WiFi adapter. With this app you can find out whether the filter is actually in the regeneration process, if a regeneration is waiting to be completed, how many kilometers you have traveled since the last regeneration, etc.
Attention! This app only works with VAG (Audi Volkswagen SEAT SKODA) equipped with the engines listed below; For diesel engines not...
</description></item><item><title>Download 9GAG: Funny GIF, Meme &amp;amp; Video 8.13.5</title><pubDate> Sun, 24 Aug 2025 16:26:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-9gag-funny-gif-meme-video-11500.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-9gag-funny-gif-meme-video-11500.html
</guid><description>
9GAG has the best funny, cute, weird, wacky, cosplay photos, GIFs, videos, memes, photos on the web. We are your greatest and happiest source. With millions of visitors every day, 9GAG is an application that helps you play LOL, kill time and make new friends around the world.
9GAG features
	The 9GAG app loads quickly and allows for easy scrolling. Don't waste time picking me up or just having a good laugh.
	Carry unlimited fun in your pocket. Enjoy 9GAG anytime, anywhere and...
</description></item><item><title>Download BetterSleep: Sleep tracker 25.15</title><pubDate> Sun, 24 Aug 2025 16:26:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-bettersleep-sleep-tracker-8274.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-bettersleep-sleep-tracker-8274.html
</guid><description>
BetterSleep is a sleep tracking app that helps users track and improve their sleeping habits. The app uses the phone's sensors to track movement and sounds during sleep, then provides users with detailed sleep reports and analysis. It also includes features such as a sleep log, smart alarm, and white noise generation to help users fall asleep and wake up more refreshed. Additionally, BetterSleep allows users to set sleep goals, track their progress, and receive personalized...
</description></item><item><title>Download ET Optimizer 6.07.20</title><pubDate> Sun, 24 Aug 2025 16:18:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-et-optimizer-9574.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-et-optimizer-9574.html
</guid><description>
ET-Optimizer is a free, open source script to improve your computer's overall performance and optimize it for your workflow through optimized scripting. With this optimization, setup takes little effort. The script is developed from many sources found on the Internet, tested and updated for different versions of the system. The whole script is contained in 1 file, it uses: command prompt, powershell, power plan configuration, startup configuration, registry changes, network interface...
</description></item><item><title>Download HandBrake 1.10.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 24 Aug 2025 16:05:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-handbrake-2935.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-handbrake-2935.html
</guid><description>
HandBrake is a free app, and advanced lets you easily convert a variety of video formats to a variety of codec popular and modern. The program allows you to handle the video file with speed and accuracy, higher than, provides a collection of configuration is optimized for each device. The program allows you to tweak many kinds of advanced features to switch top quality and advanced encryption.
HandBrake - The video transcoding powerful 
HandBrake support most popular video formats. The...
</description></item><item><title>Download HandBrake for macOS 1.10.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 24 Aug 2025 16:04:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/mac/download-handbrake-for-mac-3306.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/mac/download-handbrake-for-mac-3306.html
</guid><description>
HandBrake for Mac is a multi-platform, multi-threaded, multi-stream video transcoder for converting video from virtually any format to a selection of modern, widely supported codecs. A stable version is also available. With HandBrake for Mac, you can convert from many popular multimedia file formats, including unprotected DVD or BluRay sources, to a number of modern output file formats.
HandBrake for Mac - Powerful Video Transcoder
HandBrake for Mac is the ideal tool for converting...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDF Utility - Merge, Split PDF 1.6</title><pubDate> Sun, 24 Aug 2025 13:39:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pdf-utility-merge-split-pdf-14098.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-pdf-utility-merge-split-pdf-14098.html
</guid><description>
PDF Utility - Merge, Split PDF is a powerful, lightweight and easy-to-use PDF tool application that provides everything you need to manage PDF files efficiently. Whether you want to merge multiple PDF files, split files, extract specific pages, lock PDF with password or add watermark — this all-in-one PDF editor &amp;amp; converter can do it all.
Perfect for students, professionals or anyone who frequently works with PDF files. Perform all tasks offline with complete privacy and no need to...
</description></item><item><title>Download GPS Locker 2.5.0 build 250</title><pubDate> Sun, 24 Aug 2025 13:34:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-gps-locker-14097.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-gps-locker-14097.html
</guid><description>
GPS Locker is made to keep GPS signal locked when switching between apps and when your device screen is off. GPS Locker helps to lock GPS signal faster and fix your GPS error.
Useful application
	In mobile games, the use of GPS positioning in the game is necessary.
	GPS Locker will be useful for those who use GPS positioning (for example, everyone is familiar with the situation where the device cannot catch the GPS signal immediately when exiting a tunnel in a car, etc.).
	Helps...
</description></item><item><title>Download GPS Compass Navigator 2.20.35</title><pubDate> Sun, 24 Aug 2025 13:31:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-gps-compass-navigator-14096.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-gps-compass-navigator-14096.html
</guid><description>
When you are traveling, hiking or fishing, save your location such as a parked car, shelter or hotel, and navigate back following the arrows.
GPS Compass Navigator is a navigation app for Android devices that combines GPS-based location tracking with digital compass functionality, allowing users to save locations, navigate back to saved waypoints and display directions even if the device does not have a physical compass sensor. The app is designed for hiking, fishing, traveling and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Intel Graphics Driver for Windows 10 / 11 32.0.101.7026</title><pubDate> Sun, 24 Aug 2025 00:01:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intel-graphics-driver-for-windows-10-5954.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-intel-graphics-driver-for-windows-10-5954.html
</guid><description>
Intel Graphics Driver for Windows 10 supports Intel ' s latest 8th-generation Core processor, introducing the Intel ® UHD graphics, with the ability to immerve in the top 4K UHD entertainment from your laptop for a maximum of 10 hours. Along with some security fixes, this driver also optimised the system's inactivity to reduce power consumption.
Look at the complete new interface of gameplay.intel.com, where you will find the proposed game settings for many of your favorite PC games....
</description></item><item><title>Download Universal Media Server 14.13.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 23 Aug 2025 23:54:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-universal-media-server-2364.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-universal-media-server-2364.html
</guid><description>
Universal Media Server is a media server UPnP compatible multi-platform DLNA. The purpose of this software is to give you a chance to stabilize to make the exchange quick and convenient files necessary. Server the device supports the different output and facilitate the process of exchanging information between a computer and necessary equipment. The development is based on PS3 Media Server, which means you can interact with the Playstation 3, Xbox 360, as well as TV Samsung or...
</description></item><item><title>Download Windows XP Professional SP3 x86 Integral Edition August 2025</title><pubDate> Sat, 23 Aug 2025 23:52:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-xp-professional-4484.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-xp-professional-4484.html
</guid><description>
Windows XP Professional SP3 x86 Integral April 2020 based on the images original English with automatic installation and updates and latest patches for Windows XP and POSReady 2009 until January 4, 2020. Includes more than 350 MB drivers, LAN, WLAN, Chipset, SATA / AHCI and NVMe. Windows XP Professional goes beyond the benefits of XP Home Edition with advanced capabilities designed specifically to optimize productivity using the latest advancements in the digital world. Built on the solid...
</description></item><item><title>Download Agisoft Metashape Professional 2.2.2 Build 21026</title><pubDate> Sat, 23 Aug 2025 23:46:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-agisoft-metashape-professional-1731.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-agisoft-metashape-professional-1731.html
</guid><description>
Agisoft Metashape (formerly PhotoScan) is a software product independently perform image processing and digital data creation, 3D space used in GIS applications, material cultural heritage and the production visual effects as well as the indirect measurement of the different subjects scale. Technical digital photography is deployed wisely is applied with the method of computer vision led to the system processor, smart auto, on the one hand, can be managed by a new person in the field of...
</description></item><item><title>Download BitComet 2.16</title><pubDate> Sat, 23 Aug 2025 23:45:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bitcomet-1220.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bitcomet-1220.html
</guid><description>
BitComet is the program that supports the download of torrent files quickly supports multiple security protocols and modern interface. BitComet is free software file-sharing p2p fully compatible with Bittorrent, this is one of the p2p protocols the most popular is designed for high-speed distribution of files with size 100MB or GB. BitComet is a bittorrent client powerful, clean, fast and easy to use. It support to download at the same time, download queue, downloads the selected in...
</description></item><item><title>Download Calcpad 7.3.4</title><pubDate> Sat, 23 Aug 2025 23:45:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-calcpad-12576.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-calcpad-12576.html
</guid><description>
Calcpad is free software for mathematical and engineering calculations. It is a flexible and modern programmable calculator with Html report generator. Calcpad uses a simple programming language that is fast and easy to learn. It does not require any special programming skills, which makes it suitable for engineers without any computer programming background. You can create calculation notes simply by writing your formula and text, enclosed in 'quotation marks'.
The program includes...
</description></item><item><title>Download MusConv Ultimate 4.10.409</title><pubDate> Sat, 23 Aug 2025 23:44:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html
</guid><description>
MusConv transfers playlists, albums, followed artists and liked songs across a variety of services – Spotify, Apple Music, Amazon Music, YouTube, YouTube Music, iTunes, Deezer, Tidal, SoundCloud, Pandora and more 125 music services!
Features of MusConv Ultimate
	Transfer playlists, albums, followed artists and liked tracks between over 125 music servicesManage playlists (Delete, Merge, Split, Copy...)
	More than 125 music services supported
	Access DAILY updated music charts on...
</description></item></channel></rss>