<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 15:42:50 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 15:42:50 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Qalculate! 5.8.2</title><pubDate> Tue, 18 Nov 2025 17:14:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qalculate-7213.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qalculate-7213.html
</guid><description>
Qalculate! is a versatile cross-platform desktop calculator. It's simple to use but offers the power and flexibility typically reserved for complex math packages, as well as useful tools for everyday needs (such as currency converters and fractional calculations). hundred). Features include a large library of customizable functions, unit calculations and conversions, physical constants, symbol calculations (including integrals and equations), arbitrary precision, uncertainty transfer,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Tray Weather 1.37.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 18 Nov 2025 17:14:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tray-weather-7091.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tray-weather-7091.html
</guid><description>
Tray Weather is a simple application to retrieve and display weather information for a given geographical location in a small dialog box and in the Windows OS system tray. Weather and map information is obtained from OpenWeatherMap. To get weather information from OpenWeatherMap you need to register on their website and enter the given API Key in Tray Weather configuration dialog.
when executed, the application will reside in the system tray, showing the current weather icon. Tooltip...
</description></item><item><title>Download Google Chrome 142.0.7444.176</title><pubDate> Tue, 18 Nov 2025 17:13:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-chrome-1012.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-google-chrome-1012.html
</guid><description>
Google Chrome web browser is the most used today. Support surf the web, listen to music, watch movies, play web game effective no jerky lag with the internet connection stable. When you are surfing the web or performing an important task, whether it is operation big or small, work or entertainment, then Chrome has the smart features and the speed you need to make, create and explore on the net.
The latest version of Google Chrome is the third 114. But we are providing for users Google...
</description></item><item><title>Download EaseUS Todo PCTrans Pro 14.2.3 + Technician</title><pubDate> Tue, 18 Nov 2025 17:09:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-todo-pctrans-pro-1291.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-todo-pctrans-pro-1291.html
</guid><description>
EaseUS Todo PCTrans Professional is powerful software helps transfer data, apps and settings of your account from one computer to another easily. EasUS Todo PCTrans put everything into a new PC and ready to use . Transfer tool PC this easy move safe files, folder files, program and account your existing to a new computer. In just a click of the mouse, making PC your new is loaded with everything you need. Instead of copy and paste, you can transfer to new PC in a seamless way.
EaseUS...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mirillis Action! 4.46.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 18 Nov 2025 17:09:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mirillis-action-213.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mirillis-action-213.html
</guid><description>
Mirillis Action! is a game video recording software,  screen recording, take screenshot with impressive sharpness and 4K quality. It's a simple, reliable and effective software solution that's worth it when you need to access features like streaming and recording and work on desktop with unique HD video quality.
Mirillis Action makes exporting and uploading your recordings to popular services and social networks like YouTube and Facebook very easy. Work! provides predefined export...
</description></item><item><title>Download Android Studio 2025.2.1.8</title><pubDate> Tue, 18 Nov 2025 17:09:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-android-studio-3890.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-android-studio-3890.html
</guid><description>
Android Studio is an Android development environment, completely new, provides many improvements and new features compared to Eclipse ADT. This software solution will is IDE the official Android when is finishing. This tool provides many tools and features such as editing, layout, rich set of tools to capture usability, compatibility version, performance and other issues, create a lot APK, build system based on Gradle flexibility, extended support for Google Services, integrated support...
</description></item><item><title>Download Bluebeam Revu 21.8.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 18 Nov 2025 17:08:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bluebeam-revu-extreme-629.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bluebeam-revu-extreme-629.html
</guid><description>
Bluebeam Revu eXtreme is support software file converter Microsoft® Office and CAD drawings into a pdf file and supports editing, markup and collaboration PDF. Bluebeam Revu eXtreme will help you increase productivity by leveraging data markers across the entire project lifecycle, and streamline processes to get more done in less time.
Features Bluebeam Revu eXtreme
Create
	Convert the number of Microsoft® Office documents and CAD drawings without limitation of PDF file in 2D or 3D...
</description></item><item><title>Download Serato DJ Pro 4.0.0</title><pubDate> Tue, 18 Nov 2025 17:07:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-serato-dj-pro-169.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-serato-dj-pro-169.html
</guid><description>
Serato DJ Pro is software mix DJ music, professional support, sound effects, and combined to create music, Great DJ. Serato DJ Pro supports the sound effects such as Delay, Reverb, Flanger, Echo, PingPong Delay, Phaser, Distortion, High and Low Pass Filter, as well as combinations of them. Supports MIDI in full, be made in the program, providing the ability to adapt to the controller and program for every need. It allows you to use at the same time from two to four floors. Program Serato...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wipe Pro 2025.14</title><pubDate> Tue, 18 Nov 2025 17:07:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wipe-pro-710.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wipe-pro-710.html
</guid><description>
Wipe Pro is software that helps clean up litter, increase in hard drive space besides also protect your privacy on the Internet, it removes records about personal activity on the computer. You will be able to delete browser history and the cache, the file index.dat, registry, files, cookies, internet history, auto complete, temporary internet files and many other items. This program also delete all activities other individuals that you made when using the PC and regardless of which...
</description></item><item><title>Download Light Image Resizer 7.4.0.129</title><pubDate> Tue, 18 Nov 2025 17:06:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-light-image-resizer-945.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-light-image-resizer-945.html
</guid><description>
Light Image Resizer or also known as VSO Image Resizer. This is a software support thumbnail resolution images or move images in your hard drive. Light Image Resizer helps people store photos and digital images on their PC and who want to resize, compress, convert, create copies, import or organize photos. Light Image Resizer is integrated into Windows Explorer, right-click on your pictures and start working on your photos.
Light Image Resizer - miniature high-resolution photos and sort...
</description></item><item><title>Download Marvelous Designer Enterprise 2025.2.81</title><pubDate> Tue, 18 Nov 2025 17:05:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-marvelous-designer-1339.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-marvelous-designer-1339.html
</guid><description>
Marvelous Designer is one of the program best designed to help the 3D design and fashion design. A simulation system revolutionary use of physics. Now, you can create the correct clothes only using Marvelous Designer without help of the other CAD app. Marvelous Designer supports polylines, draw the curved lines connected for free. Any amendments and / or modifications will be displayed immediately on the model clothing 3D in real time.
Marvelous Designer - fashion design
The main...
</description></item><item><title>Download Remo Video Repair 1.0.0.33</title><pubDate> Tue, 18 Nov 2025 17:05:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-remo-video-repair-2920.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-remo-video-repair-2920.html
</guid><description>
Remo Video Repair the software is built with a powerful algorithm designed to fix the video format files such as MOV, AVI, MP4, XVID, DIVX, etc. Remo Video Repair is considered a utility flexibility to repair video files corrupted to be shot on camera of the brand such as Canon, Nikon, Sony, GoPro, DJI Phantom, etc.
To avoid damaging the added video file is broken, Remo Video Repair Tool works on corrupted files in read-only Mode to repair and create video files can be played. With option...
</description></item><item><title>Download FanControl v248</title><pubDate> Tue, 18 Nov 2025 17:04:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fancontrol-5749.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fancontrol-5749.html
</guid><description>
FanControl is a highly customizable fan control software for Windows. Stay in control of every aspect of your PC's GPU and CPU fan with the help of this highly customizable fan control app.
Features of FanControl
	Save, edit and load multiple configurations
	Multiple temperature sources (CPU, GPU, motherboard, hard drive, ".sensor" files)
	Custom fan curve
	Fine tune fan control response with steps,% start,% stop, response time and delay
	Mix different curves and sensors...
</description></item><item><title>Download Telegram for Desktop 6.3.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 18 Nov 2025 17:04:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-telegram-3376.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-telegram-3376.html
</guid><description>
Telegram is an instant messaging service and voice over IP services on the cloud platform. Client application Telegram is available for Android, iOS, Windows Phone, Windows NT, macOS, and Linux. Users can send messages and exchange photos, videos, stickers, audio and files of any kind.
Telegram - Messaging and free phone calls
Telegram seamless sync across all your devices and can be used on desktop, tablet and phone. You can send unlimited amount of messages, photos, videos and files...
</description></item><item><title>Download Silhouette Studio Business Edition 5.0.414</title><pubDate> Tue, 18 Nov 2025 17:04:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-silhouette-studio-business-edition-9753.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-silhouette-studio-business-edition-9753.html
</guid><description>
Silhouette Studio Business Edition is a software program developed by Silhouette America, a company known for its electronic cutters and related accessories. This software is designed to work in conjunction with Silhouette cutters, such as the Silhouette Cameo and Portrait, to create and edit designs intended to cut various materials such as vinyl, paper, fabric, etc.
With dozens of design tools and easy integration with Silhouette cutters, Silhouette Studio is the ultimate tool for...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mullvad Browser 15.0.1</title><pubDate> Tue, 18 Nov 2025 17:03:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mullvad-browser-12254.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mullvad-browser-12254.html
</guid><description>
Mullvad Browser is a privacy-focused web browser developed through a partnership between Mullvad VPN and Tor Project. This browser is designed to minimize tracking and fingerprinting. You can say that this is the Tor browser to use without the Tor Network. Instead, you can use this browser with a reliable VPN. The idea is to provide one more alternative – besides the Tor Network – to browse the internet with more privacy. To get as many people as possible together against today's big...
</description></item><item><title>Download Glary Disk Cleaner 6.0.1.37</title><pubDate> Tue, 18 Nov 2025 17:02:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-disk-cleaner-1341.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-disk-cleaner-1341.html
</guid><description>
Glary Disk Cleaner is the software helps to erase the file system temporarily, cleanup your browser cache, or release the folder. Glary Disk Cleaner show scan results in detail, help you pick exactly each file to delete. The list file is much more wide open, with temporary files, user-generated, or the file system, cache, bug report, log files, data in recycle bin, the shortcut expires.
Glary Disk Cleaner - garbage system
Glary Disk Cleaner is designed to be simple as possible in use....
</description></item><item><title>Download Diving Log 6.0.35</title><pubDate> Tue, 18 Nov 2025 17:01:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-diving-log-4735.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-diving-log-4735.html
</guid><description>
Diving Log is a logbook solution dive perfect to manage your dives. You can import the data log your dives from almost every dive computer, by importing from your software manufacturer, or by direct download from the dive computer. All data can be exported to several formats, synchronized to iPhone, Windows Phone and Android, or uploaded web for online presentation.
Create print your own diary with the report designer, powerful, integrated, and share design your diary with other users....
</description></item><item><title>Download HTTP Logs Viewer 7.01</title><pubDate> Tue, 18 Nov 2025 17:01:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-apache-logs-viewer-5363.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-apache-logs-viewer-5363.html
</guid><description>
HTTP Logs Viewer (Formerly named: Apache Logs Viewer) is an apache log viewer you can easily filter and analyze log files Apache/IIS/nginx. Built-in search and filter functions. Custom log formats are also supported. Apache Logs Viewer (ALV) is a free and powerful tool that allows you to monitor, view and analyze Apache/IIS/nginx logs more easily. It provides search and filter functionality for log files, highlighting different http requests based on their status codes.
There is also a...
</description></item><item><title>Download Glary Tracks Eraser 6.0.1.30</title><pubDate> Tue, 18 Nov 2025 17:01:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-tracks-eraser-1342.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-glary-tracks-eraser-1342.html
</guid><description>
Glary Tracks Eraser is security software privacy when browsing the web, allows you to delete all traces of network access and trace number, including browser cache, cookies, the website is already open, the URL has been entered, the document new mines, temporary files,... Glary Tracks Eraser that helps you free up space in hard disk drives, scan entire junk files in the drive with the speed of processing is extremely fast. Data deleted by Glary Tracks Eraser will not be able to restore,...
</description></item><item><title>Download EstlCAM 12.155</title><pubDate> Tue, 18 Nov 2025 17:00:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-estlcam-13476.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-estlcam-13476.html
</guid><description>
EstlCAM is a user-friendly CNC and CAM (Computer-Aided Manufacturing) control software, designed to generate toolpaths and G-code for CNC machines, especially suitable for 2D, 2.5D and 3D milling operations. The software supports importing a variety of design file formats, including 2D drawings (.dxf, .svg, .png, .jpg) and 3D models (.stl), allowing users to position, scale, and rotate designs before generating toolpaths.
The software is especially popular among enthusiasts and...
</description></item><item><title>Download iTop VPN 7.1.0.6723</title><pubDate> Tue, 18 Nov 2025 17:00:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-itop-vpn-5733.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-itop-vpn-5733.html
</guid><description>
iTop VPN is software that encrypts your Internet traffic and hides your IP address from hackers and trackers, protecting your privacy and security. Just click the Connect button, we will choose the fastest and most stable server for you. You can change different Network Solutions according to your needs. Safeguard mode gives you higher security protection, Game Mode offers unlimited bandwidth and speed, so you can stream your favorite movies and TV shows at High definition and enjoy the...
</description></item><item><title>Download KeyScrambler Premium 3.18.0.9 + Professional</title><pubDate> Tue, 18 Nov 2025 17:00:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-keyscrambler-premium-professional-143.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-keyscrambler-premium-professional-143.html
</guid><description>
KeyScrambler Premium / Professional allows users to search for and remove the malicious program, the spy program on the computer system. This program support users to handle a number of spy programs send user information to the server by way thoroughly remove them from the system.
KeyScrambler Premium Key key encryption real-time encryption key, every key you type deep in the Windows. It protects the personal information of you against all malware keylog already know and not know on...
</description></item><item><title>Download Disk Sorter Ultimate 17.5.12 + Server + Pro</title><pubDate> Tue, 18 Nov 2025 16:59:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-disk-sorter-ultimate-1464.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-disk-sorter-ultimate-1464.html
</guid><description>
Disk Sorter Ultimate is the utility classification file lightweight and simple helps people detect files on most types of drives, as well as manage them according to many different criteria to create more capacity on the disc. This app allows you to search through the 500,000 files, have storage capacity of 2TB. To start sorting, all what you have to do is select a directory, drive or server and click the button "Classification". You should know that you can search for the type specific...
</description></item><item><title>Download GOM Player Free 2.3.114 Build 5384</title><pubDate> Tue, 18 Nov 2025 16:59:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gom-player-994.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gom-player-994.html
</guid><description>
GOM Player is a program to listen to music for free with the ability to play all format music and video now without the need to install additional codec. GOM Media Player brings all video codecs needed to play multiple video formats and various audio. Simple interface, light volume but powerful function is the factor which makes GOM Player famous in the music software.
GOM Media Player according to the reviews is considered the listen to music, watch video best. The user can control GOM...
</description></item></channel></rss>