<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 13:44:06 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 13:44:06 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Adobe Premiere Pro 2025 v25.4.0.099 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Sat, 16 Aug 2025 16:23:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-premiere-pro-0021-1361.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-premiere-pro-0021-1361.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Premiere Pro is the leading video editing software for film, TV, and the web. Creative tools, integration with other Adobe apps and services, and the power of Adobe Sensei help you turn footage into finished movies and videos in a seamless workflow. It offers high-quality video editing at 4K x 4K resolution and beyond, with 32-bit color, in both RGB and YUV color spaces. Edit audio samples, support for VST audio plug-ins (plug-ins), and 5.1 surround sound tracks. The Premiere Pro...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe After Effects 2025 v25.4.0.086 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Sat, 16 Aug 2025 16:22:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-after-effects-0001-2793.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-after-effects-0001-2793.html
</guid><description>
Adobe After Effects is a powerful digital visual effects, motion graphics, and compositing application developed by Adobe Inc. The software is widely used in the film, television, and video game industries to animate and enhance video content.
After Effects allows users to create stunning motion graphics and visual effects by animating text, images, and video clips. Its capabilities include keying, tracking, compositing, and basic audio editing, making it a versatile tool for...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Media Encoder 2025 v25.4.0.090 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Sat, 16 Aug 2025 16:21:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-0010-adobe-media-encoder-1360.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-0010-adobe-media-encoder-1360.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Media Encoder 2024 is a professional audio and video converter that allows you to encode audio and video files into various distribution formats for applications different uses and audiences. Such video and audio formats are characterized by a high degree of compression. By downloading this program on taiwebs.com, you can export videos in formats supported by various devices, from DVD players and websites to mobile phones, portable media players and High Definition and High...
</description></item><item><title>Download Free YouTube Download 4.4.36.815 Premium</title><pubDate> Sat, 16 Aug 2025 16:20:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-download-1177.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-download-1177.html
</guid><description>
Free YouTube Download Premium is the most popular application to download videos from YouTube. The program was released in 2006 and regularly updated since then. Use the program to download and convert YouTube videos to view offline anytime.
Free YouTube Download - added Support to download youtube
Download more videos! Save whole playlists and YouTube channels, videos from a playlist individually (history, video be favorite, favourites, Watch later), videos from many different...
</description></item><item><title>Download Scooter Beyond Compare 5.1.3.31238</title><pubDate> Sat, 16 Aug 2025 16:20:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-scooter-beyond-compare-2649.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-scooter-beyond-compare-2649.html
</guid><description>
Scooter Beyond Compare is a powerful tool to compare quickly and easily the files and folders. This program provides you with a full report on work done so you can compare the complete data on the file, folder, folder with speed and file size, very fast and incredible, time changes on the file as well as the compared bytes Do byte this information. With the strong command of this program, you can merge the changes, synchronize files, create a report to record.
Scooter Beyond Compare -...
</description></item><item><title>Download GoodSync Enterprise 12.9.6.6</title><pubDate> Sat, 16 Aug 2025 16:19:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-goodsync-enterprise-163.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-goodsync-enterprise-163.html
</guid><description>
GoodSync Enterprise is a software that saves files and files easily and is reliable. It automatically analyts, synchronize and backup your email, family photos, contacts, MP3, financial documentation and other important files-between desktop computers, laptops, servers, external drives and Windows Mobile devices as well as remotely via FTP , SFTP, WebDAV and more. The GoodSync synchronized software combines bulletproof reliability with an extremely easy interface to compare, synchronize...
</description></item><item><title>Download Photo Supreme 2025.3.1.8015</title><pubDate> Sat, 16 Aug 2025 16:18:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photo-supreme-430.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-photo-supreme-430.html
</guid><description>
Photo Supreme is a software product management professional pictures of idimager. With Photo Supreme you can arrange, manage back stock photo archive of yourself and share them with you here and relatives easily via Email or Facebook. Photo Supreme provides users method to sort images effective, logical, as well as edit and share your photos with friends and relatives in the family. Especially the Photo Supreme allows to work with multiple image formats and support mounting support,...
</description></item><item><title>Download DeskSoft EarthView 7.13.7</title><pubDate> Sat, 16 Aug 2025 16:18:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desksoft-earthview-184.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desksoft-earthview-184.html
</guid><description>
With software DeskSoft EarthView you can easily create wallpapers to your computer or select screen saver of your favorite. the program can change day and night, the clouds will also change according to weather conditions current on one or another part of the earth, you can see the lights of the city.
Features of DeskSoft EarthView can be interesting, because of DeskSoft EarthView support for day and night, you can view atmospheric phenomena, light city can see, the cloud is displayed,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium 4.4.36.815</title><pubDate> Sat, 16 Aug 2025 16:17:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-to-mp3-converter-premium-844.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-to-mp3-converter-premium-844.html
</guid><description>
Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium version is a software used to convert YouTube to MP3, extract audio from playlists YouTube, show listings, charts, video responses, channels, favorites of the user. With Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium, you can download and convert playlists, channels, stream original tv series and get them into iTunes at the same time.
Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium - convert YouTube to MP3
Features Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium from the...
</description></item><item><title>Download RainbowTaskbar 3.2.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 16 Aug 2025 16:17:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rainbowtaskbar-6740.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rainbowtaskbar-6740.html
</guid><description>
RainbowTaskbar is an open source, customizable Windows taskbar that includes colors and transitions. Add some color to your taskbar by changing the color shift on the spectrum, you can like it visually. The program allows you to customize the colors; Instructions can be found on the author's website.
</description></item><item><title>Download YT Downloader 9.15.6</title><pubDate> Sat, 16 Aug 2025 16:16:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ytd-youtube-downloader-4771.html
</guid><description>
YTD Youtube Downloader is an application that reliable and intuitive, allowing you to quickly download YouTube videos and save them to your computer. You can also convert the media files to the format desired video or extract audio streams and save separately. YTD Youtube Downloader lets you save your favorite clips of yourself from Youtube, Facebook, Vimeo and Dailymotion to your desktop. The software supports URLS from many web site hosting, multimedia and allows you to download desired...
</description></item><item><title>Download My Music Collection 2.3.15.158</title><pubDate> Sat, 16 Aug 2025 16:16:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nuclear-coffee-my-music-collection-1242.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nuclear-coffee-my-music-collection-1242.html
</guid><description>
Nuclear Coffee My Music Collection is a software directory the most comprehensive music designed to organize and manage the music collection of any kind, including CD discs, MP3 files or vinyl records. Organizer music this allows you to create a database CD is to order and view its contents, even when the disk is located on the shelf or being a friend of you borrow. You can now forget about creating the music database on a paper, in Excel or text file. Just insert a disc, scan barcode or...
</description></item><item><title>Download Antivirus Removal Tool 2025.08 (v.1)</title><pubDate> Sat, 16 Aug 2025 16:16:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-antivirus-removal-tool-4936.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-antivirus-removal-tool-4936.html
</guid><description>
Antivirus Removal Tool is removal tool virus was designed to detect and remove completely software anti-virus. It will help you determine the current setting and the past, and it will give you the uninstall specialized official. They are designed by the manufacturer program anti-virus to delete completely all the files, drivers, services, and registration records were left by the programs that they create.
The features of the Antivirus Removal Tool
	Determine program anti-virus is...
</description></item><item><title>Download EarthTime 6.30.7</title><pubDate> Sat, 16 Aug 2025 16:15:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-earthtime-185.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-earthtime-185.html
</guid><description>
EarthTime is software that displays the time and date local time of any place in the world. This application has database integration good for 3000 city, users can manually add, download at EarthTime if you want to. EarthTime allows you to install for the time zone and current local time.EarthTime displays the Earth according to the view night and day, you can view the map in full screen mode.
EarthTime
The feature on EarthTime
	EarthTime allows users to interact with visualization...
</description></item><item><title>Download HardCopy Pro 4.18.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 16 Aug 2025 16:10:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hardcopy-pro-1018.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hardcopy-pro-1018.html
</guid><description>
HardCopy Pro is the screen capture utility, multipurpose, easy-to-use for Windows. Easy screen capture desktop and save easy.  DeskSoft HardCopy Pro can capture the screen area rectangle and the entire window. Images can be printed, saved, copied to clipboard, emailed, edited with any editing program, photos, etc. Many options allow the customization of all these actions with the needs of individual users.
HardCopy Pro - screen Capture Desktop
In addition, The captured images can be...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft Edge 139.0.3405.102</title><pubDate> Sat, 16 Aug 2025 16:09:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-edge-3940.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-edge-3940.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft Edge is web browser developed specifically for Windows operating system 10 alternatives to Internet Explorer is the default browser on Windows. Browser Microsoft Edge built-in assistant Cortana brings content and website based on the user's preferences, there are also system utilities quite extensive help you to customize according to individual. Microsoft Edge has the similarity with Google Chrome quite large, except the target is marked more of the interface and the rounded...
</description></item><item><title>Download Lazesoft Recovery Suite Unlimited WinPE 5.0.0.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 16 Aug 2025 16:09:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lazesoft-recovery-suite-winpe-12621.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lazesoft-recovery-suite-winpe-12621.html
</guid><description>
With a series of easy-to-use utilities on Lazesoft Recovery Suite, you can recover data even if files are deleted, partitions have been formatted, you can repair Windows even if Windows crashes , you can reset your Windows login password even if you forget, etc.
Bootable WindowsPE ISO file for CD/DVD or USB drive.
Main functions of Lazesoft Recovery Suite
	Windows Recovery: Fix all Windows startup and crash issues including startup errors, virus effects, blue/black screens,...
</description></item><item><title>Download SEO Checker 10.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 16 Aug 2025 16:08:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-seo-checker-2514.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-seo-checker-2514.html
</guid><description>
SEO Checker (A product of genuine VOVSoft) is a tool to analyze all type of web site or personal web page. The software works in many different ways, it can help you discover the content that you have specifically chosen to analyze from suitable site. As the authors write, the program, as this program allows you to plan for your SEO strategy by providing information about the function of it, you will get a set of keyword analysis and tracking the reverse link.
SEO Checker - Support SEO...
</description></item><item><title>Download HTML Compiler 2025.15</title><pubDate> Sat, 16 Aug 2025 16:08:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-html-compiler-2548.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-html-compiler-2548.html
</guid><description>
HTML Compiler is a program for Microsoft Windows (tm) allows you to put an entire HTML application (including HTML, CSS, JavaScript, images, etc.) into a Windows application independent can be executed like any other application window the application. HTML Compiler allows you to customize file real exam results by changing the icon of them and set some other options. For example, you can allow or not allow the ability to print the HTML pages, allow or disallow the text selection and many,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Danil Pristupov Fork 2.11</title><pubDate> Sat, 16 Aug 2025 16:07:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fork-6879.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-fork-6879.html
</guid><description>
Fork is a great Git client app that allows you to keep tabs on every file line so you can know who is the last person to make changes. The simple and intuitive design of this app helps the management of all of your warehouses much easier. The Fork interface is extremely friendly to users. There is a long list of repositories, branches, origins, tags and archives on the left side of the screen.
With Fork, you can also search and open any of the repositories quickly, from the top of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download WindowManager 10.22.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 16 Aug 2025 16:07:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desksoft-windowmanager-573.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desksoft-windowmanager-573.html
</guid><description>
WindowManager is a software by DeskSoft dedicated to providing software utilities for windows. DeskSoft WindowManager is the window manager window to ensure your windows are placed exactly where you want. Software will help you to help you improve your work flow by remembering and restoring the position and size of the program and your window. The processing window can completely customize and you can set the special rules for the windows favorite or used most often.
WindowManager send...
</description></item><item><title>Download REVisionFX REZup 2.0.1 for OFX</title><pubDate> Sat, 16 Aug 2025 13:14:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-revisionfx-rezup-for-ofx-14051.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-revisionfx-rezup-for-ofx-14051.html
</guid><description>
REVisionFX REZup for OFX is a plugin designed to enhance and enhance video quality using advanced image processing and machine learning techniques. REZup supports temporal denoising and several AI-based enhancement methods, providing flexibility for different source qualities and desired results. This tool is used in professional video processing and visual effects workflows to improve image quality during upscaling or enhancement.
Key Features and Capabilities
	AI Resizing
	Uses...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mp3Tag 3.31</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 23:51:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mp3tag-150.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mp3tag-150.html
</guid><description>
Mp3tag is a powerful tool and easy to use to edit ID3 tags and OGG comments about the files MP3 - and Ogg Vorbis. It can rename files based on the tag information, replace characters or words from tags and filenames. Help users create and add the tag information for MP3 files to manage the information that is reasonable.
The program supports lookup database freedb online for the selected files, allowing you to automatically gather tag information appropriate for the files or CD selection....
</description></item><item><title>Download EaseUS ClipAce (ScreenShot) 1.5.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 23:50:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-screenshot-7937.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easeus-screenshot-7937.html
</guid><description>
Capture everything on your screen easily through this tool, EaseUS ScreenShot provides users with a powerful set of screen capture tools to meet all their needs. The app is easy to start and use, and it does exactly what you'd expect: it helps you take screenshots without much effort.
You can capture the entire screen or just an area of ​​it. To help improve usability, double-pressing the Alt key automatically captures the full screen, while pressing Ctrl twice will let you select...
</description></item><item><title>Download Stablebit Scanner 2.6.13.4088</title><pubDate> Fri, 15 Aug 2025 23:49:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stablebit-scanner-5563.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-stablebit-scanner-5563.html
</guid><description>
Stablebit Scanner is the software that scans all your hard drives, ensuring that every precious bit remains readable. It allows you to easily connect to any other copy of it running on your LAN. Rest assured that the Stablebit Scanner is completely safe using the standard Windows Kerberos Authentication. In addition to making sure every bit on your hard drive is readable, the scanner will automatically check the integrity of your file system and notify you as soon as any problems are...
</description></item></channel></rss>