<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 13:44:03 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 13:44:03 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download WiFi Direct + 10.0.28</title><pubDate> Sun, 23 Nov 2025 16:44:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wifi-direct-10153.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-wifi-direct-10153.html
</guid><description>
Wi-Fi Direct is a Wi-Fi standard for peer-to-peer wireless connections that allows two devices to establish a direct Wi-Fi connection without the need for an intermediate wireless access point, router, or Internet connection.
Features of WiFi Direct +
	Fast
	Completely free, no intrusive ads.
	Supports all file transfers.
	Supports multiple file transfers.
	Supports folder transfer.
	Supports file transfer to and from external sdcard.
	Tested on many devices.
	Advanced file chooser.
</description></item><item><title>Download Total Launcher 3.3.8</title><pubDate> Sun, 23 Nov 2025 16:43:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-total-launcher-8673.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-total-launcher-8673.html
</guid><description>
Total Launcher is a custom launcher for Android devices. The launcher is the interface that controls the home screen, app drawer, and overall look and feel of your Android device. Total Launcher offers a high level of customization and allows users to personalize their device to suit their personal needs and preferences.
Total Launcher Features
	Customizable home screen: Users can arrange icons, widgets, and shortcuts on the home screen to their liking.
	Themes and icon packs: Total...
</description></item><item><title>Download Easy Notes - Note Taking Apps 1.3.30.1112</title><pubDate> Sun, 23 Nov 2025 16:43:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-easy-notes-notebook-notepad-8388.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-easy-notes-notebook-notepad-8388.html
</guid><description>
Easy Notes - Great note taking app, Notepad, Notebook, Free Notes is a free easy to use note taking app for notes app. With this easy notebook and notepad app, take quick notes with colorful backgrounds and checklists to organize notes and tasks easily. Use this aesthetic note taker and note taker to add photos or audio to your notes. Easy Notes is a useful notebook and note-taking app for taking notes and organizing work.
Features of Easy Notes - Notebook, Notepad
	Free Notepad and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Email Aqua Mail - Fast, Secure 1.56.0 build 105600587</title><pubDate> Sun, 23 Nov 2025 16:43:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-email-aqua-mail-fast-secure-8329.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-email-aqua-mail-fast-secure-8329.html
</guid><description>
Aqua Mail is the right app for all your email needs! Whether it's a work or personal email, a company exchange server, or even a rarely used secondary account, Aqua Mail lets you easily access all your emails from one complete app. edit.
No complicated setup required, just enter your email and password and you're done. With flexibility and diverse customization options, Aqua Mail's goal is to reflect the needs of modern users and provide a platform that anyone can tailor to their needs...
</description></item><item><title>Download Chess Studio 3.0.6</title><pubDate> Sun, 23 Nov 2025 16:42:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-chess-studio-11206.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-chess-studio-11206.html
</guid><description>
Chess Studio represents an exciting and portable new way of reading chess books, designed by chess players for chess players. Overseeing every aspect of the app's design is Grandmaster John Nunn, one of the most respected figures in the chess world and a three-time World Chess Champion.
Main features:
	text is presented in the usual clear Gambit style
	play through the moves and variations on the screen
	auto-scrolling accompanying text
	touch any move and position that appears on the...
</description></item><item><title>Download AppKiller: close apps 25.11.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 23 Nov 2025 16:41:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-appkiller-close-apps-11977.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-appkiller-close-apps-11977.html
</guid><description>
AppKiller: close apps allows users to quickly and effectively kill background applications that are consuming system resources, such as RAM and CPU, which can help improve overall speed and performance. device responsiveness. By freeing up system resources, users can also see increased battery life because their devices are no longer consuming power on unnecessary background processes. This can be especially beneficial for users who use their devices throughout the day and need to...
</description></item><item><title>Download AdGuard Ad Blocker 4.14.9 Nightly</title><pubDate> Sun, 23 Nov 2025 16:41:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-adguard-block-ads-without-root-8215.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-adguard-block-ads-without-root-8215.html
</guid><description>
AdGuard for Android is the only root-free ad blocker for Android that removes ads in apps and browsers, protects your privacy, and helps you manage your apps. Adguard is designed to block unwanted ads, pop-ups and banners while you browse the web on your device. It uses a combination of local VPN technology and a custom DNS server to block ads, meaning it can block ads in apps as well as in web browsers.
In addition, Adguard also blocks tracking scripts from collecting information about...
</description></item><item><title>Download BubbleUPnP for DLNA/Chromecast 4.6</title><pubDate> Sun, 23 Nov 2025 16:40:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-bubbleupnp-for-dlnachromecast-8657.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-bubbleupnp-for-dlnachromecast-8657.html
</guid><description>
BubbleUPnP is a mobile app for Android and iOS devices that allows you to stream media from a UPnP/DLNA media server or Chromecast device to your mobile device or to a compatible renderer. like other UPnP/DLNA on your local network.
UPnP (Universal Plug and Play) is a set of network protocols that allows different devices on a network to communicate with each other and share data. DLNA (Digital Living Network Alliance) is a technology standard that allows devices to share multimedia...
</description></item><item><title>Download AccuBattery 2.1.8</title><pubDate> Sun, 23 Nov 2025 16:40:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-accubattery-11317.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-accubattery-11317.html
</guid><description>
Batteries have a limited life. Each time you charge your device, the battery wears out, reducing its total capacity. Scientific research shows that battery life can be extended up to 200%, when you only charge your device to 80%. Accu​Battery protects battery health, displays battery usage information, and measures battery capacity (mAh) based on science.
Accu​Battery measures actual battery usage using information from the battery charge controller. Per-app battery usage is...
</description></item><item><title>Download Simple Radio: Live AM FM Radio 6.1.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 23 Nov 2025 16:39:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-simple-radio-live-am-fm-radio-10456.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-simple-radio-live-am-fm-radio-10456.html
</guid><description>
Simple Radio: Live AM FM Radio is the easiest way to tune in to FM radio, AM radio and amp; Radio online. You can access music, news &amp;amp; Live sports radio in seconds with our free radio station app. With over 50,000 stations, you can follow the ones you already love or sit back and discover exciting new things from around the world.
Listen to FM radio &amp;amp; AM stations include: NPR Radio, BBC Radio, MRN, 77 WABC, La Mega 97.9, KNBR &amp;amp; WNYC. Keep up with the news, listen to music or...
</description></item><item><title>Download Podcast Addict: Podcast player 2025.10.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 23 Nov 2025 16:39:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-podcast-addict-podcast-player-8373.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-podcast-addict-podcast-player-8373.html
</guid><description>
Podcast Addict is a popular podcast streaming application for Android devices. It allows users to listen to and manage their favorite podcasts, audiobooks, live streams, and YouTube channels. The app provides an easy way to discover and subscribe to new podcasts, while also allowing users to create playlists and customize the listening experience. Podcast Addict allows you to manage your Podcast, Radio, Audiobook, Live streaming, YouTube, SoundCloud channels and RSS News feeds from a...
</description></item><item><title>Download ISS Live Now: Live Earth View 8.1.9</title><pubDate> Sun, 23 Nov 2025 16:39:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-iss-live-now-live-earth-view-14128.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-iss-live-now-live-earth-view-14128.html
</guid><description>
ISS Live Now: Live Earth View provides a live HD video stream of Earth from the International Space Station (ISS), real-time tracking of the ISS with interactive maps, and notifications to know when the ISS will be visible from your location. The app also features live astronaut missions, spacewalks, rocket launches, and docking events, plus an immersive virtual tour inside the ISS using Google Street View.
	See Earth 24/7 – Live HD streaming from space.
	Follow the ISS in real time...
</description></item><item><title>Download MyFitnessPal: Calorie Counter 25.45.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 23 Nov 2025 16:38:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-myfitnesspal-calorie-counter-8502.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-myfitnesspal-calorie-counter-8502.html
</guid><description>
MyFitnessPal is a mobile app and website that allows users to track their daily food intake, workouts, and weight loss progress. The app includes a calorie counter that allows users to easily log and track their daily calorie intake. Our members have lost more than 200 million pounds, and 88% of those who followed for at least 7 days on MyFitnessPal lost weight. Sign up for FREE and start living a happier and healthier life today! See for yourself why MyFitnessPal is the world's most...
</description></item><item><title>Download 365Scores: Live Scores &amp;amp; News 14.4.5</title><pubDate> Sun, 23 Nov 2025 16:38:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-365scores-live-scores-news-8220.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-365scores-live-scores-news-8220.html
</guid><description>
365Scores is a sports app that provides users with real-time scores, statistics, and news for many sports including football, basketball, soccer, and more. Some features of the application include:
	Live scores and notifications: 365Scores provides live scores and push notifications for many sports, including football, soccer, basketball, baseball, etc.
	Match statistics: The app includes detailed match statistics such as ball control, number of shots on goal, etc.
	Latest News:...
</description></item><item><title>Download HiEdu Calculator He-580 Pro 1.6.3</title><pubDate> Sun, 23 Nov 2025 16:38:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-hiedu-calculator-he-580-pro-8206.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-hiedu-calculator-he-580-pro-8206.html
</guid><description>
HiEdu Calculator He-580 Pro is the perfect tool for everyday calculations. With a memorization function similar to a small handheld calculator. Now, there is no need to write paper notes to remember math formulas, just let this app save all the formulas on your favorite phone. This app has over 1000 math formulas and more.
The layout of the buttons in this app is very scientific, making entering math operations as simple and convenient as possible. The numeric and function buttons in...
</description></item><item><title>Download Smart AudioBook Player 11.6.1</title><pubDate> Sun, 23 Nov 2025 16:37:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-smart-audiobook-player-8181.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-smart-audiobook-player-8181.html
</guid><description>
Smart AudioBook Player is a type of application that allows users to listen to audiobooks on their mobile devices. This app is designed to improve the listening experience by providing features such as automatic bookmarking, adjustable playback speed, and sleep timer. The program is specially designed to play audio books. Let's say you have audiobooks and have copied them to your phone.
Smart AudioBook Player Features
	Supports Chromecast.
	Control playback speed.
	Categorize books...
</description></item><item><title>Download Elevate - Brain Training Games 5.215.0</title><pubDate> Sun, 23 Nov 2025 16:37:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-elevate-brain-training-games-8564.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/androids/download-elevate-brain-training-games-8564.html
</guid><description>
Elevate is a brain training program designed to improve speech, processing speed, memory skills, mental math, and more. Each person is provided with their own personalized learning program, which is adjusted over time to maximize results.
The more you practice with Elevate, the more you'll improve key cognitive skills proven to increase productivity, earning potential, and confidence. More than 90% said their vocabulary, memory, math skills and overall acuity improved when they...
</description></item><item><title>Download KMPlayer (KMP) 2025.11.14.11 x64 / 4.2.3.29 x86</title><pubDate> Sat, 22 Nov 2025 18:28:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kmplayer-kmp-902.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kmplayer-kmp-902.html
</guid><description>
KMPlayer (KMP) is software watch movies listen to music multi-function for video enthusiasts. KMPlayer development is many types of the format different. KMPlayer has improved on sound quality, images when listening to music and watching movies, the playback speed of video is faster, more codec player is added to the software video decoder is optimized.
KMPlayer also supports a variety of audio formats and video and offers a the interface can be customized with the preview coverflow and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Internet Download Manager (IDM) 6.42 Build 53</title><pubDate> Sat, 22 Nov 2025 18:18:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-inetnet-download-manager-161.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-inetnet-download-manager-161.html
</guid><description>
Internet Download Manager is the download acceleration software, the best download support now, it can help you speed up the download up to five times, continue and schedule downloads. The latest version of IDM adds the compatibility of Windows 10 and Windows 11, it has supported all current popular browsers such as Internet Explorer, Mozilla Firefox, Opera, Google Chrome, ..
Download IDM with the latest version on taiwebs.com making it easy to download and manage your downloaded files...
</description></item><item><title>Download FastStone Image Viewer 8.2 Corporate</title><pubDate> Sat, 22 Nov 2025 18:17:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-faststone-image-viewer-278.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-faststone-image-viewer-278.html
</guid><description>
FastStone Image Viewer software is manager, converter and editor image fast, stable, user-friendly. FastStone Image Viewer has the features include image viewing, management, comparison, red-eye removal, emailing, resizing, cropping and color adjustments. Full screen mode innovative but intuitive its provides quick access to EXIF information, browse the thumbnails and the main functions via hidden toolbars that pop up when your mouse touch the four edges of the screen.
FastStone Image...
</description></item><item><title>Download Free YouTube Download 4.4.44.1120 Premium</title><pubDate> Sat, 22 Nov 2025 18:17:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-download-1177.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-download-1177.html
</guid><description>
Free YouTube Download Premium is the most popular application to download videos from YouTube. The program was released in 2006 and regularly updated since then. Use the program to download and convert YouTube videos to view offline anytime.
Free YouTube Download - added Support to download youtube
Download more videos! Save whole playlists and YouTube channels, videos from a playlist individually (history, video be favorite, favourites, Watch later), videos from many different...
</description></item><item><title>Download IDM Retail 6.42 Build 53</title><pubDate> Sat, 22 Nov 2025 18:16:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-internet-download-manager-retail-3609.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-idm-internet-download-manager-retail-3609.html
</guid><description>
IDM - Internet Download Manager Retail is a reliable utility and high efficiency will help you to increase your download speed and manage download at better. The program allows you to easily schedule, pause and resume downloads with a single click. Moreover, the application provides error resilience robust and can restart the download at the interrupted or broken. You can restore the download is interrupted due to network problems, lost connections, unexpected power outages, computer...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Premiere Pro 2025 v25.6.2.001 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Sat, 22 Nov 2025 18:16:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-premiere-pro-0021-1361.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-premiere-pro-0021-1361.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Premiere Pro is the leading video editing software for film, TV, and the web. Creative tools, integration with other Adobe apps and services, and the power of Adobe Sensei help you turn footage into finished movies and videos in a seamless workflow. It offers high-quality video editing at 4K x 4K resolution and beyond, with 32-bit color, in both RGB and YUV color spaces. Edit audio samples, support for VST audio plug-ins (plug-ins), and 5.1 surround sound tracks. The Premiere Pro...
</description></item><item><title>Download VCap Downloader Pro 0.1.41.6837</title><pubDate> Sat, 22 Nov 2025 18:15:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vcap-downloader-pro-8474.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vcap-downloader-pro-8474.html
</guid><description>
VCap Downloader Pro (VCapDL) is a popular piece of software that allows you to record video and audio from websites on the internet. The interface of the software is similar to a normal browser, making it easy for users to get used to and work with this software. User just need to copy video url from favorite browser and convert it to VCap Downloader Pro. It will capture the video and make the quality available for download. You can also extract the audio track from any video and convert...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Substance 3D Sampler 5.1.2.8523 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Sat, 22 Nov 2025 18:14:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-substance-3d-sampler-6625.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-substance-3d-sampler-6625.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Substance 3D Sampler allows you to create and iterate on collections of materials by refining and blending existing materials or by extracting new materials from scans ( one or more images). A new set of powerful tools that combine different technologies and creation methods (AI-based and manual) will help you manage your entire document library and export them to other applications.
Features of Adobe Substance 3D Sampler
	AI-powered scan processing
	Use your content everywhere....
</description></item></channel></rss>