<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 11:39:30 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 11:39:30 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Mp3Tag 3.32</title><pubDate> Sat, 15 Nov 2025 20:23:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mp3tag-150.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mp3tag-150.html
</guid><description>
Mp3tag is a powerful tool and easy to use to edit ID3 tags and OGG comments about the files MP3 - and Ogg Vorbis. It can rename files based on the tag information, replace characters or words from tags and filenames. Help users create and add the tag information for MP3 files to manage the information that is reasonable.
The program supports lookup database freedb online for the selected files, allowing you to automatically gather tag information appropriate for the files or CD selection....
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Lightroom Classic 2026 v15.0.1 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Sat, 15 Nov 2025 20:18:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-photoshop-lightroom-classic-0004-734.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-adobe-photoshop-lightroom-classic-0004-734.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Photoshop Lightroom Classic is a desktop-optimized photo editing and organizing software. Lightroom Classic gives you powerful one-click tools and advanced controls to make your photos look great. Easily organize all your photos on your desktop and share them in a variety of ways.
In addition, Lightroom Classic has a powerful import process that allows users to preview images before importing. It supports many camera raw formats and includes a database system for efficient photo...
</description></item><item><title>Download Activation Program 1.15</title><pubDate> Sat, 15 Nov 2025 20:17:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-activation-program-12767.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-activation-program-12767.html
</guid><description>
Activation Program is a Windows and Office activator from Ratiborus for Windows 7 to 11. The program is created based on the MASSGRAVE code.
What advantages does this method have over other activation methods?
It offers the most advantages for activating older versions of Windows, such as Windows 7 to 8.1, as it can permanently activate any version of the versions This without modifying the Windows system boot process or executable files. This is the only public activator that provides...
</description></item><item><title>Download Topaz Gigapixel Pro 1.0.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 15 Nov 2025 20:16:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-ai-gigapixel-1318.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-ai-gigapixel-1318.html
</guid><description>
Topaz ONE Gigapixel is the first app and only use the power of artificial intelligence to enhance your photos, add natural details, for great results. Use technology to learn deep, AIGigapixel ™ can zoom in and fill in the details that the products change in size other are not included. The traditional method this created blurred image, a non-realistic and do not have the detail present in the image have high resolution.
Topaz A.I. Gigapixel - enhance image quality
The content of...
</description></item><item><title>Download ZD Soft Screen Recorder 12.0.9</title><pubDate> Sat, 15 Nov 2025 20:15:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zd-soft-screen-recorder-136.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zd-soft-screen-recorder-136.html
</guid><description>
ZD Soft Screen Recorder supports user taping the game in 2D or 3D, film screen, the content is screened in the multimedia. The Videos are saved in a list and popular formats with best quality.
ZD Soft Screen Recorder is a program recording software screen high performance. It works just like a camera really. A camcorder can record many things in the real world including computer screen, while ZD Soft Screen Recorder can only record computer screen but can do much better than a camcorder...
</description></item><item><title>Download System Mechanic Pro 25.7.2.74 + Standard</title><pubDate> Sat, 15 Nov 2025 20:15:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-system-mechanic-434.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-system-mechanic-434.html
</guid><description>
System Mechanic Pro is tool cleanup and repair errors on the system and restore hard drive and operating speed window.  System Mechanic helps you to clean your entire computer system, delete the unnecessary files, detect and repair the incident occurred due to virus attack or due to mistakenly deleted system files.
System Mechanic offers many useful features such as Registry cleaning, defragmenting computer memory, protect your privacy while accessing the Internet. With programs this...
</description></item><item><title>Download System Mechanic Ultimate Defense 25.7.2.74</title><pubDate> Sat, 15 Nov 2025 20:15:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-system-mechanic-ultimate-defense-1974.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-system-mechanic-ultimate-defense-1974.html
</guid><description>
System Mechanic Ultimate Defense is software provides tracking features anti browser and protect your online privacy, management, encryption and secure password protection, anti-virus certified, VB100, detect and remove malware on demand, technology, erase hard drive military grade, award-winning optimize PC, software, file recovery advanced.
Malware threats is growing fast now because of almost a million new viruses, worms, trojan horses, rootkits and other types of spyware, and...
</description></item><item><title>Download UniFab 3.0.3.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 15 Nov 2025 20:14:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-unifab-10377.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-unifab-10377.html
</guid><description>
UniFab is software to efficiently convert, compress and edit more than 1000 video formats for playback on any device without losing quality. Enlarge video/audio to 1080p/DTS 7.1 and upgrade video to HDR10 or Dolby Vision with AI Enhancer. UniFab Pro provides the best AI-powered zoom tool that allows you to enlarge videos from low resolutions, such as 360p, 480p and 720p, to 1080p without losing any quality. Clearer and sharper image details will bring you an exceptional viewing...
</description></item><item><title>Download dbForge Studio for SQL Server Enterprise 2025.2.109</title><pubDate> Sat, 15 Nov 2025 20:13:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbforge-studio-for-sql-server-4710.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbforge-studio-for-sql-server-4710.html
</guid><description>
dbForge Studio 2019 for SQL Server is the program that will help the developer SQL management database, change database version control in the source control system downloads, speed up routine tasks, as well as perform the change database complicated.
A handy tool to analyze the status of the index SQL and troubleshoot issues with fragmentation index. dbForge Studio 2019 for SQL Server allows you to quickly collect statistical data fragmentation index and the current database needs...
</description></item><item><title>Download XL-Connector 3.6.25.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 15 Nov 2025 20:12:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xl-connector-12415.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-xl-connector-12415.html
</guid><description>
XL-Connector is a popular plugin that securely integrates Excel and Salesforce to export, import, refresh and transform data seamlessly with ultra-fast api connection. It provides Salesforce administrators with a comprehensive toolbox that easily performs data and metadata management activities in a familiar Excel environment.
Features
Export from Salesforce to Excel
	Get data from existing Salesforce reports or build your own SOQL queries directly into Excel.
Import data into...
</description></item><item><title>Download DesktopOK 12.23</title><pubDate> Sat, 15 Nov 2025 19:29:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopok-1635.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopok-1635.html
</guid><description>
DesktopOK is software save and restore the positions of icons. DesktopOK also offers a solution small but effective for the user to change the screen resolution often. DesktopOK is not installed and can be executed easily from the desktop, and can be carried on a small USB or memory device to another. Start of the program. The first time you use the program, the program will show you screen license. Free program and license info is only displayed the first time (on each PC).
DesktopOK -...
</description></item><item><title>Download Topaz Photo Pro 1.0.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 15 Nov 2025 18:53:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-photo-ai-8105.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-topaz-photo-ai-8105.html
</guid><description>
What is Topaz Photo AI?
Topaz Photo AI is a professional software that automatically adjusts for your image quality needs. Simply import images into Topaz Photo AI and it will use specially trained AI models to first detect unique details, clarity, and resolution issues before applying the intelligently adjusts to maximize your image quality.
For users experienced with Topaz Labs image quality applications, it combines the functionality of DeNoise AI, Sharpen AI and Gigapixel AI into...
</description></item><item><title>Download CyberLink PowerDirector Ultimate 2026 v24.0.1113.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 15 Nov 2025 18:53:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-powerdirector-ultimate-425.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-powerdirector-ultimate-425.html
</guid><description>
CyberLink PowerDirector Ultimate is software editor, edit video and make movies on the computer from a variety of templates are made available, complete with effects, transitions, animations, and music. CyberLink PowerDirector 17 is a combination of video editing software with advanced video editing features powerful. Cblowing need to add your clips into the time line and click on 'Production'!
The tool design video in CyberLink PowerDirector have the ability to customize helps you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Hasleo Disk Clone Professional 5.5.2.2 / Enterprise / Technician</title><pubDate> Sat, 15 Nov 2025 18:52:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hasleo-disk-clone-professional-14012.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-hasleo-disk-clone-professional-14012.html
</guid><description>
Hasleo Disk Clone Professional is a comprehensive disk and partition cloning software for Windows, which allows users to clone entire disks, specific partitions, and migrate Windows operating system from one disk to another without reinstalling the application. It is a professional Windows cloning software, providing multiple disk alignment modes, sector-by-sector copy of disks and partitions, flexible partition adjustment (location/size on target disk), and MBR/GPT disk conversion during...
</description></item><item><title>Download HTTP Toolkit 1.23.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 15 Nov 2025 18:52:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-http-toolkit-6246.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-http-toolkit-6246.html
</guid><description>
HTTP Toolkit is software that provides the ability to automatically block HTTP and HTTPS traffic from most client applications, including web browsers such as Chrome and Firefox, most CLI tools and auxiliary languages such as Node.js, Python, Ruby etc. You can browse through traffic by marking the content type, status, and source or search by URL, status, and title to find important notifications.
You can check the URL, status, title, and content of each request or feedback, along with...
</description></item><item><title>Download Find.Same.Images.OK 5.82</title><pubDate> Sat, 15 Nov 2025 18:51:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-find-same-images-ok-113.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-find-same-images-ok-113.html
</guid><description>
Find.Same.Images.OK lets find the images identical or similar in the folder of you, even if they were to rotate, change size or change.
Just select one or more folders that you want the program to scan and it will return a list of all the duplicate images or very similar, as indicated by the percent the same and the preview is built.Then, you can select images from the list and then copy, move or delete them.
Find.Same.Images.OK
In addition, there are other options smart option allows...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ashampoo Backup Pro 27.5.11</title><pubDate> Sat, 15 Nov 2025 18:51:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-backup-pro-716.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-backup-pro-716.html
</guid><description>
Ashampoo Backup Pro is software to backup and restore data professional to save the file, the important data for your computer. Ashampoo Backup Pro will remove the fear of viruses, ransomware, or hardware errors. Ashampoo® Backup Pro offers you various options to backup individual files or entire disk partitions on any storage media or on the cloud. User friendly, intuitive, fast. Even in case an error occurs the entire system, application integrated emergency can bring your...
</description></item><item><title>Download EmEditor Pro 25.4.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 15 Nov 2025 18:50:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-emeditor-pro-69.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-emeditor-pro-69.html
</guid><description>
EmEditor Pro - the professional version of editor text powerful for programmers, web developers and ordinary users with illumination of syntax and Unicode support. The features of the editor such as search and replace in files using regular expressions, automatic code detect, bookmark link and address email, block selection mode, configure the button bar, menu, font and elements color. With each language you can set separate configuration.
EmEditor Pro - text Editor professional
The...
</description></item><item><title>Download Novabench 5.6.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 15 Nov 2025 18:50:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-novabench-5406.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-novabench-5406.html
</guid><description>
Novabench is a calculator benchmarking utility for Microsoft Windows and macOS. The program tests the performance of computer components and assigns exclusive scores, with higher scores indicating better performance. An online archive is available where scores can be compared. You can calibrate your PC in just a few minutes by testing CPU and GPU speed, Direct3D 11 / Metal graphics performance, OpenCL calculation, memory transfer rate, and disk read and write speed.
Once the tests are...
</description></item><item><title>Download DVDFab 13.0.5.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 15 Nov 2025 18:49:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dvdfab-67.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dvdfab-67.html
</guid><description>
DVDFab All-In-One is a multi-purpose combo of nearly all powerful DVDFab products-DVD replication, Ripper DVD, Blu-ray Ripper, Blu-ray Ripper, Copy UHD, Blu-ray to DVD, DVD to Blu-ray Transaction, DVD Creator, Blu-ray Creator, video conversion, Cinavia DVD removal, Windows DVD removal, DRM elimination for Apple, Screen Recorder and Editor for iOS, Hi-Fi Sound and File Transfer. It provides a complete solution to all of your DVD/Blu-ray/video problems and the perfect execution.
DvDFab -...
</description></item><item><title>Download AITextTune 1.4.1.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 15 Nov 2025 18:49:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aitexttune-12973.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aitexttune-12973.html
</guid><description>
AITextTune is an AI-powered tool designed to enhance and refine text content. It offers features such as improving clarity and coherence, generating summaries, and translating text into multiple languages. Users can easily adjust their writing style from formal to creative. This tool is very flexible and can be used on many different software and platforms.
AITextTune Features
	WRITE PERFECTLY: Improve the clarity and coherence of your writing! Create summaries and...
</description></item><item><title>Download n-Track Studio Suite 10.2.3.10350</title><pubDate> Sat, 15 Nov 2025 18:48:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-n-track-studio-2991.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-n-track-studio-2991.html
</guid><description>
n-Track Studio is a recording software allows you record and create MIDI music and sounds top quality. The software allows you to add effects, VST3, DirectX, AU (Mac), VST and ReWire different on each track or channel. This program also allows you to automatically fade out, fade in and fade out or increase the volume of the music to indicate the voice of the singer.
n-Track Studio can record and playback the number of audio, MIDI and sound unlimited. In addition, you can handle the...
</description></item><item><title>Download AndroidDrive 2.4.12</title><pubDate> Sat, 15 Nov 2025 18:48:30 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-androiddrive-10400.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-androiddrive-10400.html
</guid><description>
AndroidDrive is a program that allows mounting Android smartphones/tablets as drives on Windows. When AndroidDrive is running and you connect an Android device, AndroidDrive automatically mounts the drive containing that device's internal storage (files, folders).
Once you have started AndroidDrive, the connected Android smartphone/tablet will be recognized as a new drive in Windows Explorer. This way, any files, photos, or other media can be moved back and forth between your Windows...
</description></item><item><title>Download WonderPen 3.0.4.8170</title><pubDate> Sat, 15 Nov 2025 18:48:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tominlab-wonderpen-7753.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tominlab-wonderpen-7753.html
</guid><description>
WonderPen is a writing app for both professional and amateur writers. WonderPen uses a tree directory to organize documents, supports unlimited levels, and can easily manage both short articles and long works. Documents can be exported to various formats such as images, PDF, Word, Epub and web pages. Multiple chapters can be exported as a book in batches.
WonderPen has a built-in full automatic backup function. By default, it will perform a full database backup every 15 minutes. It also...
</description></item><item><title>Download Windows 11 Pro Lite 24H2 Build 26100.7171 Ghost Spectre</title><pubDate> Sat, 15 Nov 2025 18:47:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-11-lite-6621.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-windows-11-lite-6621.html
</guid><description>
Windows 11 Lite is a Windows 11 build that has been customisable to remove applications that do not need Windows 11 smoother operations, support for low-profile machines. The Windows 11 interface is quite similar to Windows 10X (a version of Windows 10 discontinued). Windows 11 will now place icons on the Start Menu bar, including the Start button and search button (Cortana) in the middle, rather than on the left as on the current version of Windows. Microsoft, however, allows users to...
</description></item></channel></rss>