<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 21:28:13 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 21:28:13 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download ASUS GPU Tweak III 2.0.3.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Sep 2025 23:03:00 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-asus-gpu-tweak-3252.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-asus-gpu-tweak-3252.html
</guid><description>
ASUS GPU Tweak is a tools overclocking powerful and full-featured allows you to significantly enhance the performance of the graphics processor ASUS. Utility that allows you to get the best results just by few mouse clicks. ASUS GPU Tweak has a number mode allows you to adjust the parameters of graphics according to the specific needs of his. Mode OC allows you to benefit from maximum performance supplied by your graphics card. Game play mode allows you to play the game using the default...
</description></item><item><title>Download USB Device Tree Viewer 4.6.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Sep 2025 23:02:04 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-usb-device-tree-viewer-3286.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-usb-device-tree-viewer-3286.html
</guid><description>
USB Device Tree Viewer provides detailed information for all the ports and USB hub on the computer in the format tree. If a device is connected to a port, it also provides detailed information for the properties of the device and connection. USB Device Tree Viewer analyze your system configuration and display details about the controller server is connected, such as the manufacturer, drivers, bus types, list, location, devices, drive letters, COM ports, and debugging and statistics bus...
</description></item><item><title>Download CyberLink PowerDirector Ultimate 2026 v24.0.0910.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Sep 2025 23:00:26 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-powerdirector-ultimate-425.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-powerdirector-ultimate-425.html
</guid><description>
CyberLink PowerDirector Ultimate is software editor, edit video and make movies on the computer from a variety of templates are made available, complete with effects, transitions, animations, and music. CyberLink PowerDirector 17 is a combination of video editing software with advanced video editing features powerful. Cblowing need to add your clips into the time line and click on 'Production'!
The tool design video in CyberLink PowerDirector have the ability to customize helps you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sigil 2.6.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Sep 2025 22:59:55 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sigil-1764.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sigil-1764.html
</guid><description>
Sigil is editor ebook full of features for the EPUB file, which you can use to create electronic books of his own from scratch and export them to EPUB format. Sigil offers editing, WYSIWYG, similar to a word processor, as well as edit the code directly for advanced users. The program provides a complete set of tools allows you to insert headings, specify fonts, add numbered list or bulleted, iamges, videos, Internet links and more, without having to write any HTML code whatsoever.
Sigil...
</description></item><item><title>Download DesktopImages3D 2.51</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Sep 2025 22:59:28 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopimages3d-7387.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-desktopimages3d-7387.html
</guid><description>
DesktopImages3D is a desktop 3D visualization tool for MS Windows that is great for displaying images in an interlaced and creative way! Basic functions: total transparency, size settings, fonts, as well as a selection of different 3D themes are available and can be customized.
Features of DesktopImages3D
	3D box's optional transparency
	Several themes to display images
	Resizable
	Fixed position on screen
	Freely selectable position on screen.
</description></item><item><title>Download MusConv 4.10.417 Lifetime</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Sep 2025 22:59:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-musconv-ultimate-10733.html
</guid><description>
MusConv transfers playlists, albums, followed artists and liked songs across a variety of services – Spotify, Apple Music, Amazon Music, YouTube, YouTube Music, iTunes, Deezer, Tidal, SoundCloud, Pandora and more 125 music services!
Features of MusConv Ultimate
	Transfer playlists, albums, followed artists and liked tracks between over 125 music servicesManage playlists (Delete, Merge, Split, Copy...)
	More than 125 music services supported
	Access DAILY updated music charts on...
</description></item><item><title>Download WACUP (Winamp Community Update Project) 1.99.39.22656 Preview</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Sep 2025 22:59:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wacup-winamp-community-update-project-3880.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wacup-winamp-community-update-project-3880.html
</guid><description>
WACUP (Winamp Community Update Project). Get new features and bug fixes for release Winamp 5.666 have patch of you from those who are interested keep Winamp in existence and operate through the new plugin and replace. Build preview latest available is # 5118 (28 January 2, 2020) and build current beta is # 5118 (28 January 2, 2020)
WACUP (Winamp Community Update Project) - bug Fixes Winamp
WACUP (can be pronounced as wakeup or WAC-up or however you like it in your native tongue) is...
</description></item><item><title>Download Software Companions GerbView 11.20.0.615</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Sep 2025 22:57:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-software-companions-gerbview-1484.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-software-companions-gerbview-1484.html
</guid><description>
GerbView is a file, advanced, but easy to use, convert, print, and view files HPGL, HPGL / 2, Excellon and raster. It supports both RS274D and RS274X. You can use this software to convert the old format and RS274D standard to the new RS274X have default data. Gerbview is used to represent and illustrate the intricate design of you.
Software Companions GerbView - conversion, printing, and viewing HPGL, HPGL / 2, Excellon
You don't need to wait for rendered images to see the picture of...
</description></item><item><title>Download Drives Monitor 18.4</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Sep 2025 22:57:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-drives-monitor-6969.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-drives-monitor-6969.html
</guid><description>
Drives Monitor is a Windows 10 utility that provides a lot of useful information about the activity of each physical disk, and a real-time graph is also provided. With Drives Monitor, you can view detailed information about the physical drive type, capacity, type, number of partitions and more. If the free space is running low, the disk space usage bar will turn red, so let you know about the problem and take appropriate measures.
If you run CrystalDiskInfo in the background, the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Any Video Downloader Pro 9.5.5</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Sep 2025 22:56:03 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-video-downloader-pro-3731.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-video-downloader-pro-3731.html
</guid><description>
Any Video Downloader Pro is software support you can download video HD 720p, 1080p, 2K, 4K and 8K from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion, Vimeo, Metacafe and thousands of video sharing sites, other. It is a tool to speed up multi-threading can speed up your download faster up to 5 times. This helpful program support download at the same time. Any Video Downloader Pro lets you download multiple videos at the same time. Moreover, it allows you to pause and resume downloads if you need more...
</description></item><item><title>Download TeXstudio 4.8.9</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Sep 2025 22:55:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-texstudio-7399.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-texstudio-7399.html
</guid><description>
TeXstudio is an integrated writing environment for creating LaTeX documents. The goal of TeXstudio is to make writing LaTeX as easy and comfortable as possible. Therefore TeXstudio has many features such as syntax highlighting, built-in viewer, reference checking and various assistants.
Features of TeXstudio
	Advanced Syntax Highlighting
	Checking direct references
	Built-in PDF viewer
	Live Preview
	Complete Latex Command and Check Syntax
	Live grammar check
	Local and global...
</description></item><item><title>Download MagicMouseTrails 4.44</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Sep 2025 22:54:54 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-magicmousetrails-2721.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-magicmousetrails-2721.html
</guid><description>
MagicMouseTrails is a free software created the sheet music mouse Magic on desktop Windows, with nice effects and different themes to customize individually. The streak of the mouse are customizable and can be adjusted from the streak of the mouse very discreet to very spectacular, depending on the needs of Windows users.
MagicMouseTrails - Create a hover effect
The features of MagicMouseTrails
	A number of topics for trail mouse
	The transparency of the mouse options
	Track length...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaMonkey Gold 2024.2.0.3167 Beta</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Sep 2025 22:54:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediamonkey-gold-231.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediamonkey-gold-231.html
</guid><description>
MediaMonkey Gold is music manager and music player multimedia for the music collection and iPod users. MediaMonkey lists the audio file of you as CD, OGG, WMA, MPC, FLAC, APE, WAV and MP3 and includes the edit smart card and an automatic file and folder to arrange your music library.
MediaMonkey Gold also has CD ripper, CD / DVD Burner, and audio converter for saving music, and manual or editor list automatically to create mixed music.
Features MediaMonkey Gold
	Automatically find...
</description></item><item><title>Download CyberLink Screen Recorder Deluxe 4.4.1.31427</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Sep 2025 22:53:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-screen-recorder-deluxe-401.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-cyberlink-screen-recorder-deluxe-401.html
</guid><description>
CyberLink Screen Recorder Deluxe is software dedicated to film, movie, screenshot, video editing or live streaming.  CyberLink 3 is the perfect combination of editing features, easy-to-use PowerDirector - no. 1 Choice for The video editor - with technology turning and shooting high-quality screen. This will be a single software to record or play online games, vlogging or share screen content with the online audience.
Features CyberLink Screen Recorder Deluxe
	Found online in the...
</description></item><item><title>Download MediaPortal 2.5 / 1.38.3</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Sep 2025 22:53:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediaportal-2627.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mediaportal-2627.html
</guid><description>
MediaPortal is a media player and open source software project, digital video recorders, are often considered as an alternative solution for Windows Media Center. MediaPortal is a media center, it is open source after launch, not only can view the different video formats, but also view photos in a convenient form.
MediaPortal is written on the website of the developer, as a Microsoft Windows application, this program can be called safely is a project quite unique on the network, because...
</description></item><item><title>Download VSO ConvertXtoDVD 7.5.0.136</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Sep 2025 22:52:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vso-convertxtodvd-182.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vso-convertxtodvd-182.html
</guid><description>
VSO ConvertXtoDVD is specialized software used to convert video and burn to DVD with many formats including AVI, MKV, MOV, DivX, WMV, MTS, MPEG... and you can watch it on any player whatsoever, in general is convenient. ConvertXtoDVD supports work with a large number of video formats among them MPEG, AVI, DV, MOV and so on, you can see on the official website, also support working with video online.
VSO ConvertXtoDVD
In addition, the use of VSO ConvertXtoDVD to edit the audio files as...
</description></item><item><title>Download AnyViewer 5.3.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Sep 2025 22:51:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anyviewer-8000.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-anyviewer-8000.html
</guid><description>
AnyViewer is free yet powerful remote desktop connection software for Windows PC and Windows Server. AnyViewer helps you to complete a stable and fast remote connection, transfer files from one PC to another or multiple PCs at the same time with high image quality. With an intuitive and concise interface that guides you to access your remote computer easily. Meanwhile, the remote desktop manager has flexible connection methods, automatic updates, and support for multiple...
</description></item><item><title>Download Aiseesoft Video Converter Ultimate 10.9.18</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Sep 2025 22:51:31 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aiseesoft-video-converter-ultimate-613.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-aiseesoft-video-converter-ultimate-613.html
</guid><description>
Aiseesoft Video Converter Ultimate software is the powerful converter to assist you convert DVD and video to / 3D / video 2D HD with the video editing features and great support iPhone / iPad / iPod and other mobile devices most popular. Aiseesoft Video Converter Ultimate make update of his great to support more audio tracks and music, multi-sounds, to fully meet your needs. Compatible with audio formats and various video (check tracking technology, audio multi-audio / external), you can...
</description></item><item><title>Download Internet Download Accelerator Pro 7.2.1.1737</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Sep 2025 22:50:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-internet-download-accelerator-pro-234.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-internet-download-accelerator-pro-234.html
</guid><description>
Internet Download Accelerator Pro is software acceleration support download support users in the download file like IDM running on multiple network protocols, including FTP. Internet Download Accelerator will help your computer be file download speed is fast even when the transmission line do not have high speed. Internet Download Accelerator Pro is completely compatible with most web browsers such as Internet Explorer, Firefox, Mozilla, Opera,..
Internet Download Accelerator also...
</description></item><item><title>Download DroidKit 2.3.7.20250912</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Sep 2025 22:50:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-droidkit-6578.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-droidkit-6578.html
</guid><description>
DroidKit is data recovery software for your mobile device, it will quickly scan your phone memory and save photos, WhatsApp chats and files, messages Messages, contacts and more essential data up to 13 categories, covering almost everything you need every day. All Android phones and tablets are supported. Without rooting your device. No tech skills required. No need to wait many days. You can get back what you've lost with just a few simple clicks, instantly.
Besides, DroidKit also has...
</description></item><item><title>Download Vivaldi Browser 7.5.3735.74</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Sep 2025 22:49:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vivaldi-159.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vivaldi-159.html
</guid><description>
Vivaldi is a browser designed for users who have power and offer the option to customize high. You can choose the location of the tabs and the address bar, put the hotkeys for the common tasks and many other features. Also, Vivaldi also provides a number of improvements such as Tab Stacks to group multiple open tabs into a tab, leads to interface less cluttered. Can notes and added a screenshot of a web page while browsing, storing an attachment, and add the URL to easily sort and locate...
</description></item><item><title>Download Vivaldi for macOS 7.5.3735.74</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Sep 2025 22:49:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/mac/download-vivaldi-for-macos-3443.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/mac/download-vivaldi-for-macos-3443.html
</guid><description>
The Vivaldi for MacOS browser does not track users and offers more features than any other modern browser. Managed by Jon von Tetzchner (co-founder of Opera browser), Vivaldi for MacOS is driven by the real needs of today's users and ensures that they have the best tools to browse and get work done.
Vivaldi for MacOS - Modern web browser
Users can adjust Vivaldi to suit their browsing needs them without limiting customization options. Vivaldi takes the browser to the next level with a...
</description></item><item><title>Download priPrinter Professional 7.0.0.2609 Beta</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Sep 2025 22:48:09 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-priprinter-professional-633.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-priprinter-professional-633.html
</guid><description>
priPrinter Professional is the printer driver allows you to manipulate the output of the printer before being printed. PriPrinter is installed and select the same as the printer driver other. After printing it automatically displays the preview in where you can preview his print, change the layout, page position back, cut them, and much more. Then, you print it to printer or save your document for later use. With PriPrinter you will always be sure his prints will look like. You can measure...
</description></item><item><title>Download TubeDownload Pro 6.29.5</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Sep 2025 22:47:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubedownload-pro-12035.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-tubedownload-pro-12035.html
</guid><description>
TubeDownload Pro is a professional Windows application for downloading your favorite videos from YouTube and hundreds of other video sites. TubeDownload Pro can increase download speed up to 500% or even more.
Features of TubeDownload Pro
	Download your favorite videos from YouTube and hundreds of other video sites.
	Increase download speed up to 500% or even more.
	Download 720p, 1080p, 2K, 4K and 8K HD videos from YouTube.
	Download entire playlists in just a few clicks.
	Download...
</description></item><item><title>Download Flyby11 1.11.361</title><pubDate> Sat, 13 Sep 2025 22:47:08 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-flyby11-12467.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-flyby11-12467.html
</guid><description>
Flyby11 is a simple patcher that removes annoying restrictions that prevent you from installing Windows 11 (24H2) on unsupported hardware. Do you have an old PC? No TPM, Secure Boot or your processor is not supported? Flyby11 allows you to install Windows 11 24H2. There are no complicated steps. Just run the tool and you'll be running Windows 11 on your outdated machine in no time.
Technical overview
Flyby11 takes advantage of a feature of the Windows 11 setup process that uses the...
</description></item></channel></rss>