<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 14:15:17 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 14:15:17 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Zortam Mp3 Media Studio Pro 33.80</title><pubDate> Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:14:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zortam-mp3-media-studio-pro-135.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zortam-mp3-media-studio-pro-135.html
</guid><description>
Zortam Mp3 Media Studio Pro brings you rich processing tools music includes extract and convert music from CD to Mp3 format, edit, music cards, music download....You can also create discs CD high-quality music, with Zortam Mp3 Media Studio search music files duplicated to remove them from the system, rename music files, switch back and forth between formats.
Zortam Mp3 Media Studio Pro is rated as perfect software in the processing of the MP3 files on the computer. First of all, you can...
</description></item><item><title>Download O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro 22.1.243 / Server</title><pubDate> Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:13:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-diskimage-pro-218.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oo-diskimage-pro-218.html
</guid><description>
O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro is software backup data comprehensive and effective is provided to protect the data of the computer system, it creates images for individual drives or the entire system that still does not affect your system.
O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro allows the user to backup the entire computer or drive, the and files whenever you want even while the computer is being used. Or can use O&amp;amp;O DiskImage Pro to create a copy chinh sac of computer disk drives, can be used instead of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download AVS Media Player 26.0.1.176</title><pubDate> Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:13:17 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs-media-player-1890.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs-media-player-1890.html
</guid><description>
AVS Media Player is software media player brings you a space to enjoy music, video, vivid. AVS Media Player supports all audio formats, different image is a necessity. AVS Media Player allows you can open to near 100 format sounds, different images from common to most rare. Name the audio format, video, audio that programs can read, including: .AVI, .MPEG, .MP3, or .FLV, .JPG, .PNG ... and so very many other formats again.
AVS Media Player - The Media player
Features of AVS Media...
</description></item><item><title>Download Darktable 5.4.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:12:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-darktable-3959.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-darktable-3959.html
</guid><description>
Darktable is an application process work, photography, open source and developer rough. A lighttable virtual and Darktable for the photographer. It manages the negative of your digital in the database, lets you view them through a lamp can zoom and allows you to develop raw images and enhance them. Original image of you never be modified! Features color management professional to ensure fidelity in all the way in and handle GPU acceleration means you can speed up the process of his work by...
</description></item><item><title>Download AVS Video ReMaker 26.0.1.176</title><pubDate> Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:10:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs-video-remaker-1196.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs-video-remaker-1196.html
</guid><description>
AVS Video ReMaker is software that support quick editing of video files without reducing the video quality. Detection algorithm scenes used in AVS Video ReMaker will save time when processing video images and split it into the set. So, no need to preview every frame of the video file to find the transitions manually. With the help of AVS Video ReMaker, you can delete the unwanted parts and TV commercials from video files or file format DVD, recorded by various cameras, various video...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ahnenblatt 4.42.0.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:10:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ahnenblatt-3844.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ahnenblatt-3844.html
</guid><description>
Ahnenblatt is a genealogy software full-featured, easy to use suitable for beginners and even pedigree has the experience to organize genealogy research by you. Use plausibility checks to find out the inaccuracies in your family and create the chart impressive with just a few mouse clicks.
Ahnenblatt - Create family tree,
Recently, there has been strong increase of the general interest of the public for genealogical tree. Users who desire to track their heritage have many tools at...
</description></item><item><title>Download AVS Image Converter 26.0.1.176</title><pubDate> Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:09:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs-image-converter-4021.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs-image-converter-4021.html
</guid><description>
AVS Image Converter is a comprehensive application and have the ability to allow you to switch quickly and easily the digital images of yourself between many formats, including RAW, JPEG, GIF, TGA, PNG, PDF, TIFF, RAS, JPEG 2000. and many other types . The application comes with a variety of presets to change image size will allow you to easily resize your photos to the different print formats. You can also use the presets this to adjust their images for slideshows can be shared on social...
</description></item><item><title>Download Zentimo xStorage Manager 3.3.1.1303</title><pubDate> Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:09:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zentimo-xstorage-manager-33.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zentimo-xstorage-manager-33.html
</guid><description>
Zentimo xStorage Manager comprehensive management of your devices on the manage drive letter, launch the mobile app is installed on device, custom functions run automatically, more convenient. Besides, users can check the speed for the drive in ability file, including the file capacity from small to large, at the same time watch information, total capacity and available space on the drive.
</description></item><item><title>Download UWPSpy 1.5.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:08:45 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-uwpspy-10357.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-uwpspy-10357.html
</guid><description>
UWPSpy is a testing tool for UWP and WinUI 3 applications. Seamlessly view and manipulate UI elements and their properties in real time.
It allows users to observe how changes affect the structure and functionality of their UWP app. This is beneficial for helping with user interface design tasks during application development. When you select specific properties, the associated elements will be highlighted and any changes will update in real time.
How to use:
	Run UWPSpy.exe and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Bondware Poser Pro 14.0.227</title><pubDate> Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:08:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-smith-micro-poser-pro-526.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-smith-micro-poser-pro-526.html
</guid><description>
Smith Micro Poser Pro provides tools to create character and animation powerful 3D and includes models Poser the 3D character. The image is built so that the artist can click and drag to create the body parts, sculpting the face. Thousands of pose, shape, clothing, hair, materials and accessories are included.
Poser brings the power of design, interactive 3D animation, brings limitless opportunities to portray the diversity, form and expression of the human. Design with the human form...
</description></item><item><title>Download DM Disk Editor and Data Recovery (DMDE) 4.4.4.842</title><pubDate> Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:07:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dm-disk-editor-and-data-recovery-9139.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dm-disk-editor-and-data-recovery-9139.html
</guid><description>
DM Disk Editor and Data Recovery (abbreviated as DMDE) is a great program for searching, editing and recovering data on disk. This software is used to search, edit and recover data on disk. File system: FAT12/16, FAT32, NTFS. OS: Windows 9x/ME/2K/XP/Vista, Console versions for DOS, Linux. Direct disk access under DOS.
DMDE has many freeware features such as a disk editor, a simple partition manager (i.e. allowing partition recovery), a disk image and clone tool, a RAID creator and...
</description></item><item><title>Download AVS Video Converter 26.0.1.176</title><pubDate> Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:07:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs-video-converter-427.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs-video-converter-427.html
</guid><description>
AVS Video Converter is a software to convert video format, burn VCD, SVCD, DVD, editor video raise.  AVS Video Converter can convert the formats AVI, MPEG, WMV, DVD to the formats AVI, MPEG, WMV, RM, burn DVD, SVCD or VCD, package conversion, editing, effects and filters, video overlay, extract audio from video and save in a file, separate audio, extract a frame (frame) and save as images, split into segments and connect video, rotate video, more in the form of text, banners, logos,...
</description></item><item><title>Download MiniTool Video Converter 4.6.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:06:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minitool-video-converter-5358.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minitool-video-converter-5358.html
</guid><description>
MiniTool Video Converter is the most direct solution for converting audio and video files to a wide variety of formats. This free video converter is available to convert audio to video and convert video to audio. This free video converter supports over 1000 conversion formats including 4K / FHD / HD files MP4, MOV, MKV, AVI, WMV, M4V and audio formats like MP3, WAV, M4A, WMA High Quality, AAC, AC3.
MiniTool Video Converter allows you to convert batches of files at the same time. Just...
</description></item><item><title>Download Easy Gamer Utility Pro 1.3.90</title><pubDate> Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:06:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easy-gamer-utility-pro-12381.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easy-gamer-utility-pro-12381.html
</guid><description>
Easy Gamer Utility Pro is an easy-to-use program for Windows that can do a lot on your PC to help fix gaming problems, performance problems, and general optimization! The best tool to improve your Windows gaming experience! Is your game laggy and slow? If so, you can use the built-in game accelerator in Easy Gamer Utility, which boosts system performance, makes games run smoother, and increases FPS.
Additionally, this handy utility deletes and cleans unwanted and unnecessary temporary...
</description></item><item><title>Download Transcend SSD Scope 4.29</title><pubDate> Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:05:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-transcend-ssd-scope-7662.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-transcend-ssd-scope-7662.html
</guid><description>
Transcend SSD Scope is an advanced and user-friendly software that makes it easier than ever to clone and maintain a healthy and efficient SSD. It brings together the latest technology to determine the health and optimize the performance of your SSD.
Useful features of Transcend SSD Scope include:
	View drive information
	View SMART status
	Diagnostic scan
	Clear Security
	Updating the firmware
	Enable TRIM, Health Indicator, and System Clone.
</description></item><item><title>Download NTFS Permissions Reporter Enterprise 5.1.644</title><pubDate> Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:05:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ntfs-permissions-reporter-enterprise-6370.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ntfs-permissions-reporter-enterprise-6370.html
</guid><description>
System administrators are constantly required to check user rights for specific files and folders. This is often a time-consuming work, with multiple NTFS classes and repetitive adjustments over time creating a security maze. NTFS Permissions Reporter Enterprise allows you to confirm the security status of the entire file system quickly and efficiently. All have multiple export formats, command line support, integration scheduling, advanced filtration, and more.
Features of NTFS...
</description></item><item><title>Download Microsoft Edge 144.0.3719.115</title><pubDate> Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:05:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-edge-3940.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-microsoft-edge-3940.html
</guid><description>
Microsoft Edge is web browser developed specifically for Windows operating system 10 alternatives to Internet Explorer is the default browser on Windows. Browser Microsoft Edge built-in assistant Cortana brings content and website based on the user's preferences, there are also system utilities quite extensive help you to customize according to individual. Microsoft Edge has the similarity with Google Chrome quite large, except the target is marked more of the interface and the rounded...
</description></item><item><title>Download DBF Converter 7.75</title><pubDate> Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:04:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbf-converter-6362.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbf-converter-6362.html
</guid><description>
DBF Converter is a common solution for all your DBF format conversion needs. Whenever you need to extract data from the DBF file to CSV, XLS, XLSX, SQL or pure text, the software will provide a simple way to do this with minimal effort.
Features of DBF Converter
	Work with DBF Converter is easy. You specify a DBF file or a directory with DBF files that you want to convert, select the fields and filter out the records you need. Then, just a click to DBF Converter to turn the source...
</description></item><item><title>Download SecretDNS 3.8.5</title><pubDate> Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:04:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secretdns-12481.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-secretdns-12481.html
</guid><description>
SecretDNS provides a quick means to deploy DNS over HTPS, meaning it allows DNS (short for Domain Name Server) resolution to be performed remotely using the HTTPS protocol to encrypts data between the client and the DNS resolver. Its purpose, obviously, is related to data security and user privacy, to prevent unauthorized interception and manipulation of DNS data.
Default DNS settings in SecretDNS use CloudFlare to ensure security. You can change DNS configuration in the dedicated tab...
</description></item><item><title>Download AVS Audio Editor 26.0.1.176</title><pubDate> Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:03:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs-audio-editor-1194.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-avs-audio-editor-1194.html
</guid><description>
AVS Audio Editor is editor audio professional allows you to edit, record and encode music. The program has more than 20 effects and filters built in, including delay, flanger, chorus, reverb, filters to remove irritating sounds such as "vuvuzelas", new sound effects, strange, unique.
AVS Audio Editor - audio editing
Features of AVS Audio Editor
Save to all major formats
	Edit and save audio files into MP3, FLAC, WAV, M4A, WMA, AAC, MP2, AMR, OGG and other files with the help of AVS...
</description></item><item><title>Download Health Break Reminder 2.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:02:50 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-health-break-2524.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-health-break-2524.html
</guid><description>
Today, most of us spend at least few hours per day before a computer screen, as the author claims, this may have adverse effects on mental and physical. Often difficult to remember when to stay, so there are special apps that can be helpful for this. Health Break is a program that has been created so you can create a calendar to stay fixed while working on PC. The software displays the stopwatch on the computer to your desk to tell you when to next vacation, it will provide a reminder...
</description></item><item><title>Download Playnite 10.50</title><pubDate> Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:02:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-playnite-6972.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-playnite-6972.html
</guid><description>
Playnite is an open-source video game library manager and manager with support for third-party libraries such as Steam, GOG, Origin, Battle.net and Uplay. Includes supporting the game, providing a unified interface for your game. With Playnite, you can comfortably enter the game from Steam, Battle.net, Origin, GOG and Uplay services, including uninstalled games.
You have three options to view when using Playnite. You also have the custom game option or add any game or program with...
</description></item><item><title>Download dbForge Studio for SQL Server Enterprise 2025.3.61</title><pubDate> Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:01:41 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbforge-studio-for-sql-server-4710.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-dbforge-studio-for-sql-server-4710.html
</guid><description>
dbForge Studio 2019 for SQL Server is the program that will help the developer SQL management database, change database version control in the source control system downloads, speed up routine tasks, as well as perform the change database complicated.
A handy tool to analyze the status of the index SQL and troubleshoot issues with fragmentation index. dbForge Studio 2019 for SQL Server allows you to quickly collect statistical data fragmentation index and the current database needs...
</description></item><item><title>Download Q-Dir 12.48</title><pubDate> Fri, 06 Feb 2026 00:20:46 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-q-dir-348.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-q-dir-348.html
</guid><description>
Q-Dir is software to manage the entire file and folder on the computer, allowing to see file in same time 4 different positions (viewport quadro) while still maintaining all the standard features of the Explorer.
It also provides a variety of management features, additional files included the filter file color-coding, layouts and columns can be customized, quick access to file and folder favorites and more.
Other features of Q-Dir , including directory listings (.txt, .doc .html .csv),...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe Acrobat Pro DC 2025.001.21151 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Thu, 05 Feb 2026 23:48:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-001en-adobe-acrobat-pro-458.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-001en-adobe-acrobat-pro-458.html
</guid><description>
Adobe Acrobat Pro DC is a comprehensive software that helps you create and edit the PDF&amp;nbsp;document, or create form, sign, protect PDF, connect, split PDF, export PDF to various formats. The Acrobat Pro DC is the latest version of Adobe with improvements in the interface with the polished ribbon bar and the ability to create and handle pdf files as well as its male versions.
The highlight of the Acrobat Pro DC is probably the ability to connect, store documents on the cloud, you can...
</description></item></channel></rss>