<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 17:37:01 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 17:37:01 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download ChromePass 1.61</title><pubDate> Sat, 09 Aug 2025 18:03:59 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chromepass-3315.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chromepass-3315.html
</guid><description>
ChromePass is a tool to recover password for Windows, allows you to view user names and passwords stored by Google Chrome browser Web. For each password entry, the following information is displayed: the root URL, action URL, username Field, password Field, user Name, password and Time created. It allows you to retrieve the password from the system running your current or from a user profile stored on the external drive. You can select one or more items and then save them into text / html...
</description></item><item><title>Download Custom Context Menu 5.6.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 09 Aug 2025 17:55:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-custom-context-menu-12534.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-custom-context-menu-12534.html
</guid><description>
Custom Context Menu is a handy tool that allows you to customize the right-click context menu on Windows 11 system. This means you can add, remove or modify context menu items for quick access to your favorite apps, settings, or websites.
Features:
	Add new menus to execute the commands you need
	Customize the title and icon of the new custom menu
	Supports sharing and importing custom menu configurations
	Various configurations are provided for easy menu command...
</description></item><item><title>Download NxFilter 4.7.3.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 09 Aug 2025 17:53:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nxfilter-50.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nxfilter-50.html
</guid><description>
NxFilter is a server filter DNS have the ability to filter Internet traffic based on domain names and content types. In addition, it can use check package DNS to protect your network from malware and botnet activity.
NxFilter is installed on a single computer, where it acts as a proxy server, DNS. To route Internet traffic through NxFilter, you will need to change the DNS settings on all the machines that you want to protect to use the IP address of the individual NxFilter (instead of the...
</description></item><item><title>Download ON1 Resize AI 2026 v20.0.0.17265</title><pubDate> Sat, 09 Aug 2025 17:51:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-on1-resize-2055.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-on1-resize-2055.html
</guid><description>
ON1 Resize 2019 is the edited final image when you need to zoom in the highest quality - with technology genuine Fractals® - to resize your photo to print. You can quickly change the image size without losing sharpness or detail. ON1 Resize also includes one of the fastest ways to view, remove and edit photos.
ON1 Resize - Zoom, change photo size
The features of ON1 Resize
	ON1 Resize using interpolation algorithm based on fractal - helps quickly change the image size without losing...
</description></item><item><title>Download Easy Gamer Utility Pro 1.3.79</title><pubDate> Sat, 09 Aug 2025 17:51:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easy-gamer-utility-pro-12381.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-easy-gamer-utility-pro-12381.html
</guid><description>
Easy Gamer Utility Pro is an easy-to-use program for Windows that can do a lot on your PC to help fix gaming problems, performance problems, and general optimization! The best tool to improve your Windows gaming experience! Is your game laggy and slow? If so, you can use the built-in game accelerator in Easy Gamer Utility, which boosts system performance, makes games run smoother, and increases FPS.
Additionally, this handy utility deletes and cleans unwanted and unnecessary temporary...
</description></item><item><title>Download Room Arranger 10.2.0.727</title><pubDate> Sat, 09 Aug 2025 17:50:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-room-arranger-3779.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-room-arranger-3779.html
</guid><description>
Room Arranger is a 3D application lets you easily plan for the room, office or his apartment just a few mouse clicks. The application comes with a simple interface will significantly simplify your work. You can draw many kinds of objects and items to create furniture of your own. This app also includes a library of object rich.
Software Room Arranger enables you to view your project in 3D form. You can also upload the 3D scene interact on your blog or your website. The application uses...
</description></item><item><title>Download Bforartists 4.5.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 09 Aug 2025 17:50:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bforartists-7643.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-bforartists-7643.html
</guid><description>
Bforartists is a complete, free and open source 3D suite for creating CG content. It gives you the full 3D art pipeline for creating game graphics, pre-rendered movies, and stills. From modeling, sculpting, texturing, design, animation, rendering, to post processing. The main goal of Bforartists is to provide a refined graphical user interface and better usability. This means a complete shift in usage philosophy away from hotkey-focused usage towards an intuitive and user-friendly...
</description></item><item><title>Download Magic Data Recovery Pack 4.9</title><pubDate> Sat, 09 Aug 2025 17:44:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-magic-data-recovery-pack-5146.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-magic-data-recovery-pack-5146.html
</guid><description>
Magic Data Recovery Pack is a program that provides the ability to recover data fast, easy, and powerful in one convenient package. Provides the ability to restore data from the drive is broken, broken, broken and is re-partition the deleted partitions and formatted, the hard drive is corrupt and can not visit, Magic Data Recovery Pack helps recovering documents, compressed archives and many other types of data in just few clicks. Photo recovery tool comes allows recovering digital...
</description></item><item><title>Download Rainbow Analyst add-in Professional 25.08.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 09 Aug 2025 17:44:10 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rainbow-analyst-add-in-professional-11122.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-rainbow-analyst-add-in-professional-11122.html
</guid><description>
Rainbow Analyst add-in Professional is a powerful tool designed to enhance data analysis in Microsoft Excel. This add-on provides many advanced features and visualizations to help users gain valuable insights from their data.
One of the key features of Rainbow Analyst is the ability to create color-coded reports and charts. Users can assign specific colors to different data values, making it easier to identify patterns, trends, and outliers. This visual representation of data enhances...
</description></item><item><title>Download Magic Photo Recovery 6.9</title><pubDate> Sat, 09 Aug 2025 17:43:44 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-magic-photo-recovery-3275.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-magic-photo-recovery-3275.html
</guid><description>
Magic Photo Recovery is a powerful application and features provide you the ability to recover digital images and RAW images of camera be lost. The program allows you to get back photos from memory card or hard drive is formatted with minimal effort. The program supports a variety of image formats, including RAW images. Using Magic Photo Recovery, you will be able to recover digital photos from local drive, many different memory cards or directly from internal memory of camera. The program...
</description></item><item><title>Download Magic Partition Recovery 5.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 09 Aug 2025 17:40:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-magic-partition-recovery-5155.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-magic-partition-recovery-5155.html
</guid><description>
Magic Partition Recovery is the software helps to recover files and restore information from the disk is damaged, formatted, corrupted and inaccessible media and solid state storage formatted with any version of FAT or NTFS. Restore files and folders, repair the partition broken, and rebuilt the file system is damaged and missing in the automatic mode completely. With both analysis modes, quick and comprehensive, Magic Partition Recovery restore be careful of your files and rebuild the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Comfy Photo Recovery 6.9</title><pubDate> Sat, 09 Aug 2025 17:37:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-comfy-photo-recovery-3292.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-comfy-photo-recovery-3292.html
</guid><description>
Comfy Photo Recovery is a comprehensive application and strong allows you to recover the deleted photos accidentally, lost images after format hard drive, USB drive or memory card photos lost due to system malfunction, etc. Comfy Photo Recovery is very easy to use interface, accessible to both novice and expert. The step by step instructions integration will help you to restore digital photos with just a few simple steps. Using this program, you will be able to easily search, recover and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Magic Office Recovery 4.9</title><pubDate> Sat, 09 Aug 2025 17:36:32 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-magic-office-recovery-5992.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-magic-office-recovery-5992.html
</guid><description>
Magic Office Recovery provides sophisticated data recovery algorithms that enable reliable recovery of documents stored on damaged devices, formated, and inaccessible. An easy step guide and a miniature library view mode helps the recovery process as easily as possible.
Magic Office Recovery restored documents, spreadsheets, and other files created by Microsoft Office applications such as Word and Excel, as well as documentation in OpenOffice format and Adobe PDF. Combining low-level...
</description></item><item><title>Download Mario Nieto Harmony Bloom 1.3.5</title><pubDate> Sat, 09 Aug 2025 17:35:40 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mario-nieto-harmony-bloom-13897.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-mario-nieto-harmony-bloom-13897.html
</guid><description>
Harmony Bloom by Mario Nieto World is an innovative MIDI creation plugin that combines polyrhythmic pattern creation with a visually appealing geometric interface to inspire musical creativity. It is designed for both Windows and macOS, available as a VST3 plugin, AU, and standalone application.
Key Features:
	Multi-Rhythm MIDI Creation: Create complex, evolving melodic and rhythmic sequences based on geometric shapes such as spirals and nested stars, allowing users to create hypnotic...
</description></item><item><title>Download Comfy File Recovery 7.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 09 Aug 2025 17:35:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-comfy-file-recovery-3294.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-comfy-file-recovery-3294.html
</guid><description>
Comfy File Recovery is a powerful and comprehensive allowing you to easily restore files accidentally deleted and lost information after format hard drive, memory card or USB drive. Program Te provides user-friendly interface, like Explorer lets you easily view files can recover. The integrated guide of the program allows you to easily access and recover files, save data to any folder, burn the recovery files on CD or DVD, upload the file to your FTP server or create a ISO disk...
</description></item><item><title>Download Comfy Data Recovery Pack 4.9</title><pubDate> Sat, 09 Aug 2025 17:33:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-comfy-data-recovery-pack-5771.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-comfy-data-recovery-pack-5771.html
</guid><description>
Program package contains deleted image recovery utility, programs to recover data regardless of the type of information to be recovered, the method of information deletion, or the service provider from which the files were deleted . The interface of the program is developed based on the principle of making the program accessible to ordinary users. Extremely complex information recovery algorithms are cleverly concealed below a step-by-step wizard that helps users find, recover, and save...
</description></item><item><title>Download Magic RAID Recovery 2.8</title><pubDate> Sat, 09 Aug 2025 17:33:06 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-magic-raid-recovery-5784.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-magic-raid-recovery-5784.html
</guid><description>
Magic RAID Recovery is RAID 0 repair software, RAID 1, RAID 4, RAID 5, RAID 6 is broken and many other array types by connecting disk with your computer. Recovery of data from storage devices is attached to a disk and multiple disk and server NAS servers. Extracts data from the hard drive used in the NAS Technology system, QNAP, ASUSTOR, Western Digital, Thecus, TerraMaster and Buffalo.
Magic RAID Recovery of East Imperial Soft is designed to help users fix multiple types of broken RAID...
</description></item><item><title>Download Comfy Partition Recovery 5.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 09 Aug 2025 17:32:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-comfy-partition-recovery-3293.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-comfy-partition-recovery-3293.html
</guid><description>
Comfy Partition Recovery is a powerful application and reliable will help you restore files and lost data from the logical drive is broken, damaged, or normal. Porgram can recover lost files due to situations and various accidents, such as delete partition, deleted by accident, system malfunction, malfunctioning hardware, power failure and many other bugs.
Comfy Partition Recovery will thoroughly analyze the content of your hard drive to get the files of the file system NTFS or FAT your....
</description></item><item><title>Download Magic Browser Recovery 4.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 09 Aug 2025 17:31:53 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-magic-browser-recovery-5781.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-magic-browser-recovery-5781.html
</guid><description>
Magic Browser Recovery is software to find and recover deleted web browsing history records, while also helping to analyze the user's Internet operations by providing access to existing browsing history and deleted.
Online Activity Analytics
	The extract of the user's login and password information
	Explore social network activities, accounts, and login information
	Access search and browsing history of the user-even in Hidden mode
	Perform comprehensive analysis of user online...
</description></item><item><title>Download Magic Uneraser 7.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 09 Aug 2025 17:31:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-magic-uneraser-3272.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-magic-uneraser-3272.html
</guid><description>
Magic Uneraser is a handy, simple but powerful, allowing you to easily retrieve files accidentally deleted. The program can recover any type of file from the disk partitions NTFS and FAT. The application supports many storage media including hard disk, digital cameras, flash drives, memory cards and many other things.
Magic Uneraser - Restore deleted files
Magic Uneraser allows you to easily recover documents, photos, movies, music, and other files deleted, with minimum effort. This...
</description></item><item><title>Download LostMyPassword 1.00</title><pubDate> Sat, 09 Aug 2025 15:01:12 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lostmypassword-14028.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lostmypassword-14028.html
</guid><description>
LostMyPassword is a tool for Windows that allows you to recover a lost password if it was stored by a software installed on your system. LostMyPassword can extract passwords from popular programs, including web browsers (Chrome, Firefox, Microsoft Edge, Brave, Internet Explorer, Opera, etc.), POP3/IMAP/SMTP passwords stored by email software (Microsoft Outlook, Thunderbird, Windows Mail), Dialup/VPN passwords stored by Windows operating system, remote computer login passwords stored by...
</description></item><item><title>Download Techivation M-Exciter 1.0.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 09 Aug 2025 14:49:01 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-techivation-m-exciter-14027.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-techivation-m-exciter-14027.html
</guid><description>
Techivation M-Exciter is a high-fidelity spectral harmonic enhancement plugin designed for audio mixing and mastering. It creates high-frequency content as an organic extension of the original sound by creating new overtones for the fundamental tones in the input. This results in enhanced brightness, air, and presence with master-quality clarity, while avoiding harshness or distortion. This plugin applies intelligent spectrum shaping technology and features a real-time spectrum suppression...
</description></item><item><title>Download UJAM Symphonic Elements BRAAASS 1.1.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 09 Aug 2025 14:46:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ujam-symphonic-elements-braaass-14026.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ujam-symphonic-elements-braaass-14026.html
</guid><description>
UJAM Symphonic Elements BRAAASS is a virtual instrument plugin that provides access to Hans Zimmer's world-class collection of brass pieces, recorded at Remote Control Studios. It is designed to program authentic and epic brass pieces quickly, easily and with creative flexibility, suitable for both film soundtracks and modern music genres such as rap, hip hop and techno.
BRAAASS Features
	78 Play Styles with 6 built-in phrases per Style, for a total of 468 unique phrases, plus 4...
</description></item><item><title>Download uJAM Symphonic Elements STRIIIINGS 1.2.2</title><pubDate> Sat, 09 Aug 2025 14:42:36 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ujam-symphonic-elements-striiiings-14025.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ujam-symphonic-elements-striiiings-14025.html
</guid><description>
UJAM Symphonic Elements STRIIIINGS is a virtual instrument plugin with world-class string sections recorded at Hans Zimmer's Remote Control Studio. The plugin allows easy, one-touch playback of simple and complex string sections, designed for users with no string arrangement skills. The plugin includes 60 playing styles and over 200 sound designer presets, with UJAM's all-new creative performance and sound design engine, allowing for modern, cinematic, and expressive string textures with...
</description></item><item><title>Download UJAM Symphonic Elements DRUMS 1.2.1</title><pubDate> Sat, 09 Aug 2025 14:39:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ujam-symphonic-elements-drums-14024.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ujam-symphonic-elements-drums-14024.html
</guid><description>
DRUMS brings Hans Zimmer's personal collection of percussion samples and phrases to you. Proven in Hollywood, this rhythmic companion from STRIIINGS makes cinematic drumming accessible to anyone. Unleash the natural power of rhythm with DRUMS! It offers a powerful, easy-to-use tool for creating bold rhythmic layers, from subtle beats to powerful cinematic explosions, recorded at Hans Zimmer's Remote Control Studios and arranged by Boris Salchow.
Key features include:
	Over 50 playing...
</description></item></channel></rss>