<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 03:34:01 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 03:34:01 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Personal Backup 6.4.4.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 00:54:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-personal-backup-1117.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-personal-backup-1117.html
</guid><description>
Personal Backup is software to backup data on computer hard drive professional with the ability to copy data on the hard drive and save any folder. Personal Backup is the most optimal solutions to ensure safety for data on avoid computer viruses, malicious code, intrusion and data loss because you can restore lost data at any time if it has to be backed up and stored on the folder of the computer.
Personal Backup - backup computer data
Features of Personal Backup
	Backup cross data...
</description></item><item><title>Download PDFCreator 6.2.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 00:53:33 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdfcreator-1304.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-pdfcreator-1304.html
</guid><description>
PDFCreator is free software that easily creates PDF files from any Windows program. Users can use PDFCreator as a printer in Word, StarCalc or any other Windows application. PDFCreator is free, even for commercial purposes! It is Open Source and released under the terms of the GNU General Public License.
Features of PDFCreator
	Create PDF files from any program that can print
	Security: Encrypt PDF files and protect them from being opened, printed, etc.
	Email generated files
	Create...
</description></item><item><title>Download R-Studio 9.5 Build 191648 Network / Technician</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 00:52:15 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-studio-1415.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-r-studio-1415.html
</guid><description>
R-Studio is a group of software data recovery and data recovery powerful and effective. -STUDIO is the solution to recover most comprehensive data for the file restored from the variants NTFS, NTFS5, ReFS, FAT12 / 16/32, exFAT, HFS / HFS + (Macintosh), Little and Big Endian of UFS1 / UFS2 (FreeBSD / OpenBSD / NetBSD / Solaris) and Ext2 / Ext3 / Ext4 partition FS (Linux).
R-Studio is also used to recover file raw (scan known file types) for the file system is damaged or not determined. It...
</description></item><item><title>Download Nitro Pro Enterprise 4.42.0.34</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 00:51:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nitro-pdf-pro-34.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nitro-pdf-pro-34.html
</guid><description>
Nitro Pro Enterprise create, edit and convert PDF files easily with the help of the visual program this also allows users to accurately extract text from PDF files thanks to OCR function of it. Nitro Pro is one of the software solutions, create and edit PDF most advanced, providing basically all the tools you need to help you in this area. Although it is called 'Professional', this app has been developed to target beginners and advanced users, so you won't feel too hard to use.
Direct...
</description></item><item><title>Download WYSIWYG Web Builder 20.4.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 00:51:16 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wysiwyg-web-builder-177.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wysiwyg-web-builder-177.html
</guid><description>
WYSIWYG Web Builder : The construction of the website from scratch using HTML code isn't a pleasant process, even when you know what you are doing. The website can be built using WYSIWYG Web Builder with using the element similar to the package published on the desktop: text and images placed in frames and tables on the page, so very little surprised when most of the efforts to make the web become a experience user-friendly than. the controls do you use to build your pages.
WYSIWYG Web...
</description></item><item><title>Download Duplicate File Finder Professional 2025 v408</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 00:50:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-duplicate-file-finder-professional-4425.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-duplicate-file-finder-professional-4425.html
</guid><description>
Duplicate File Finder Professional is a compact application helps you quickly find and remove files duplicate on the computer. With Duplicate File Finder Professional you can choose any folder on the hard drive or use the folder standard user and our app will analyze the deep content of the selected folder to copy. It will take only a few seconds. The files will be compared by the hash algorithm MD5, which means they will be compared by content, not by name. Then, use our convenient...
</description></item><item><title>Download Adobe InDesign 2026 v21.0.2 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 00:49:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-001en-adobe-indesign-334.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-001en-adobe-indesign-334.html
</guid><description>
Adobe InDesign is the industry-leading page design and layout software for print and digital media. Create beautiful graphic designs with typography from the world's leading foundries and images from Adobe Stock. Quickly share content and feedback as PDFs. Easily manage production with Adobe Experience Manager. InDesign has everything you need to create and publish books, digital magazines, eBooks, posters, interactive PDFs, and more.
Adobe InDesign was developed by Adobe Systems, first...
</description></item><item><title>Download Nitro Pro 4.42.0.34 Retail</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 00:48:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nitro-pro-379.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nitro-pro-379.html
</guid><description>
Nitro Pro is software that provides features to create, edit and convert PDF files or share PDF files standard.  This is a simple software, easy to understand and intuitive to use so you can work more efficiently. Nitro Pro you can share your files with others, regardless of whether they are using the platform or device, and Nitro Pro helps convert easily.
Nitro Pro convert one or multiple files into PDF with just one or two clicks. Re-use and re-use content based on the PDF with higher...
</description></item><item><title>Download Wise Disk Cleaner 11.3.0.850</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 00:47:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wise-disk-cleaner-392.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-wise-disk-cleaner-392.html
</guid><description>
Wise Disk Cleaner software to clean hard drive by finding and deleting junk files downloads accumulate over time. Wise Disk Cleaner is pre-configured with about 50 types of extension files can usually be considered disposable, and you can extend the range by adding the file types of their own.
Wise Disk Cleaner to use the advanced algorithm with the ability to quick scan and comprehensive scan of hard drive space. Users can delete browsing history as well as the personal data important...
</description></item><item><title>Download UPDF 2.0.14</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 00:47:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-updf-14160.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-updf-14160.html
</guid><description>
UPDF for Windows is easy-to-use PDF software for Windows! Enjoy powerful editing tools for text, images, links, and more in your PDFs. Customize backgrounds, watermarks, and page sizes as easily as in Word. AI-powered PDF editor and manager that offers a wide range of features including editing, annotating, converting, OCR (Optical Character Recognition), organizing, protecting, sharing, printing, summarizing, translating, and interpreting PDF files.
Features of UPDF
Analyze PDFs with...
</description></item><item><title>Download OpenVPN 2.6.17</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 00:46:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-openvpn-4245.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-openvpn-4245.html
</guid><description>
OpenVPN provides the VPN solution flexible to secure communication of your data, whether it is the right to privacy on the Internet, remote access for employees, security, IoT, or for the data center cloud. Solution VPN software, our Server can be deployed in place by standard server or virtual device or on the cloud.
OpenVPN - VPN Solution flexible
Though built with the open source OpenVPN, the solution of our additional functionality to meet the needs of business customers, the...
</description></item><item><title>Download LrToolbox 2026.0.0.18</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 00:45:56 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lrtoolbox-13054.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-lrtoolbox-13054.html
</guid><description>
LrToolbox is a comprehensive Windows software designed to handle your Lightroom catalog with ease. Whether you are a professional photographer or an amateur, this tool will help you streamline your workflow and increase your productivity. Whether you need to extract previews from a catalog, convert your photo ratings to sidecar files, or convert RAW images to JPG, LrToolbox is here to help you with just a few clicks.
Key Features
	Compatible with Adobe Lightroom Classic 14.2 (February...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ashampoo Backup Pro 27.5.21</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 00:45:29 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-backup-pro-716.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ashampoo-backup-pro-716.html
</guid><description>
Ashampoo Backup Pro is software to backup and restore data professional to save the file, the important data for your computer. Ashampoo Backup Pro will remove the fear of viruses, ransomware, or hardware errors. Ashampoo® Backup Pro offers you various options to backup individual files or entire disk partitions on any storage media or on the cloud. User friendly, intuitive, fast. Even in case an error occurs the entire system, application integrated emergency can bring your...
</description></item><item><title>Download GiliSoft File Lock Pro 15.5</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 00:44:24 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-file-lock-pro-858.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-gilisoft-file-lock-pro-858.html
</guid><description>
GiliSoft File Lock Pro is program encryption software file power can lock and hide fast and secure files, folders and drives, and it can use AES 256 bit encryption (encryption standard is the government of The United States apply) protect your files located on HDD or any portable media drive such as USB.
GiliSoft File Lock Pro - file encryption
Features of GiliSoft File Lock Pro
	GiliSoft File Lock Pro can hide the folders and drives of your private
	The file / folder / drive locking...
</description></item><item><title>Download Prevent Restore Pro 2025 v115</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 00:43:48 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-prevent-restore-pro-1473.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-prevent-restore-pro-1473.html
</guid><description>
Prevent Restore Pro is software prevent restore files deleted in any drive: external hard drives and hard drives mounted in hard drive, SSD, Flash drives, except CD-ROM and CD-RW. The software uses many security algorithms can be used to get data.Our program includes some of the most reliable and accepted as standard.
Prevent Restore Pro - Prevent restore files deleted
The features of Prevent Restore Pro
Mode to clean up quickly
	In this mode, the program will not overwrite the free...
</description></item><item><title>Download SlickEdit Pro 2025 v30.0.0</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 00:43:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-slickedit-pro-5576.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-slickedit-pro-5576.html
</guid><description>
SlickEdit Pro is designed by developers for developers, SlickEdit's award-winning source code and text editor is respected for its rich set of coding tools and programming features. a powerful time saver. As a true multi-language, cross-platform editor, SlickEdit offers programmers the ability to code in more than 70 languages ​​across 9 platforms.
SlickEdit Pro: Build and debug large or complex projects. Stay in sync with built-in version control and powerful file diff tools. All...
</description></item><item><title>Download Eltima USB Network Gate 11.0.2736</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 00:41:58 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-eltima-usb-network-gate-4457.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-eltima-usb-network-gate-4457.html
</guid><description>
Eltima USB Network Gate is a software can help you share effective many USB devices over Ethernet and connect with them on the remote machine as if the device is plugged in the computer, regardless of location or distance between them. With Eltima USB Network Gate any user can also print, scan, access, license key USB and USB hub via Ethernet from any computer in your office, regardless of it how big and occupy much floor. It provides a number of handy features to help share USB over...
</description></item><item><title>Download Sync Breeze Ultimate 17.5.18 + Enterprise + Pro</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 00:41:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sync-breeze-ultimate-enterprise-1462.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-sync-breeze-ultimate-enterprise-1462.html
</guid><description>
Sync Breeze Ultimate / Enterprise is software sync files fast, powerful and reliable for the local disk, shared network storage devices, NAS and storage systems business. Users are provided with multiple modes sync files one-way and two-way sync files periodically, sync file real time sync file-level bits, sync files multi-threading, synchronization, files, wallpaper and more.
Sync Breeze Ultimate / Enterprise - synchronize files
App GUI main Sync Breeze Ultimate allows a person to...
</description></item><item><title>Download Calcpad 7.5.6</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 00:40:27 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-calcpad-12576.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-calcpad-12576.html
</guid><description>
Calcpad is free software for mathematical and engineering calculations. It is a flexible and modern programmable calculator with Html report generator. Calcpad uses a simple programming language that is fast and easy to learn. It does not require any special programming skills, which makes it suitable for engineers without any computer programming background. You can create calculation notes simply by writing your formula and text, enclosed in 'quotation marks'.
The program includes...
</description></item><item><title>Download ProtonVPN 4.3.7</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 00:39:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-protonvpn-10433.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-protonvpn-10433.html
</guid><description>
ProtonVPN app for Windows is the best way to stay safe and private while surfing the internet. It is open source, easy to use, and packed with useful security features. ProtonVPN will secure your connection by routing your traffic through multiple servers to protect you against advanced network-based attacks.
It helps keep your IP address safe if something goes wrong with your VPN connection. If your VPN connection fails, the kill switch feature will prevent your device from connecting...
</description></item><item><title>Download Blumentals Program Protector 4.15.0.28</title><pubDate> Sat, 29 Nov 2025 00:39:18 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blumentals-program-protector-6171.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-blumentals-program-protector-6171.html
</guid><description>
Blumentals Program Protector is the number one tool in the world to protect programs with passwords on the Windows system. You can easily protect by password for any Windows application. Program Protector is easy to use and does not require any special computer knowledge. Your password can protect the programs with a few clicks.
Features of Blumentals Program Protector
	The password protects any Windows application
	Pull and drop the program file and the shortcuts to protect...
</description></item><item><title>Download TweakNow QR Code Maker 3.7.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 28 Nov 2025 21:17:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qr-code-maker-9760.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-qr-code-maker-9760.html
</guid><description>
QR Code Maker is a simple app to generate QR Code for text, link, email, Whatsapp, SMS, Call and Wifi. With QR Codes, you have complete flexibility, because only a short URL points to the encrypted content. So you can modify the links or stored files without having to generate and reprint the Codes. This will save resources and allow you to respond to any campaign changes as quickly as possible.
Features of QR Code Maker
	Generate QR Code for Text, Link, Email, Whatsapp, SMS, Call and...
</description></item><item><title>Download Vivaldi Browser 7.7.3851.56</title><pubDate> Fri, 28 Nov 2025 20:45:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vivaldi-159.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-vivaldi-159.html
</guid><description>
Vivaldi is a browser designed for users who have power and offer the option to customize high. You can choose the location of the tabs and the address bar, put the hotkeys for the common tasks and many other features. Also, Vivaldi also provides a number of improvements such as Tab Stacks to group multiple open tabs into a tab, leads to interface less cluttered. Can notes and added a screenshot of a web page while browsing, storing an attachment, and add the URL to easily sort and locate...
</description></item><item><title>Download Vivaldi for macOS 7.7.3851.56</title><pubDate> Fri, 28 Nov 2025 20:45:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/mac/download-vivaldi-for-macos-3443.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/mac/download-vivaldi-for-macos-3443.html
</guid><description>
The Vivaldi for MacOS browser does not track users and offers more features than any other modern browser. Managed by Jon von Tetzchner (co-founder of Opera browser), Vivaldi for MacOS is driven by the real needs of today's users and ensures that they have the best tools to browse and get work done.
Vivaldi for MacOS - Modern web browser
Users can adjust Vivaldi to suit their browsing needs them without limiting customization options. Vivaldi takes the browser to the next level with a...
</description></item><item><title>Download NxFilter 4.7.4.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 28 Nov 2025 20:44:42 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nxfilter-50.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-nxfilter-50.html
</guid><description>
NxFilter is a server filter DNS have the ability to filter Internet traffic based on domain names and content types. In addition, it can use check package DNS to protect your network from malware and botnet activity.
NxFilter is installed on a single computer, where it acts as a proxy server, DNS. To route Internet traffic through NxFilter, you will need to change the DNS settings on all the machines that you want to protect to use the IP address of the individual NxFilter (instead of the...
</description></item></channel></rss>