<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns="" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"><channel><title>Download free software, update daily!</title><description>
Taiwebs.com - Download free software applications, full version, latest updates!
</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:08:58 +0700</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:08:58 +0700</lastBuildDate><generator>Download free software, update daily!</generator><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/</link><atom:link href="https://en.taiwebs.com/sitemap/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download Foxit PDF Editor Pro 2025.2.1.33197 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 00:23:39 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-foxit-pdf-editor-pro-162.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-foxit-pdf-editor-pro-162.html
</guid><description>
Foxit PDF Editor Pro (formerly Foxit PhantomPDF Business) is a PDF toolkit dedicated to the creation of professional PDF documents and forms. You can do that for tasks such as personal document development, working group collaboration, company model design. Manufacturing the company's collateral, completing the agreements, applying the signature number or document storage.
Foxit PDF Editor Pro is the perfect solution for family/family offices, small and medium enterprises and large...
</description></item><item><title>Download Free YouTube Download 4.4.40.924 Premium</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 00:23:05 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-download-1177.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-download-1177.html
</guid><description>
Free YouTube Download Premium is the most popular application to download videos from YouTube. The program was released in 2006 and regularly updated since then. Use the program to download and convert YouTube videos to view offline anytime.
Free YouTube Download - added Support to download youtube
Download more videos! Save whole playlists and YouTube channels, videos from a playlist individually (history, video be favorite, favourites, Watch later), videos from many different...
</description></item><item><title>Download 4K Video Downloader Plus 25.3.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 00:22:25 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-video-downloader-617.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-video-downloader-617.html
</guid><description>
4K Video Downloader Plus is software support downloads video, audio and subtitles from YouTube with high quality up to 4K. Download process video is very simple: just copy the video link from your browser and click Paste Url. Done! If you want that video on your iPad, iPhone or other device, we have protected you.
The feature on 4K Video Downloader Plus
	Download entire playlists and channels from YouTube and save them in MP4, MKV, M4A, MP3, FLV, 3G, create a file .m3u for...
</description></item><item><title>Download Foxit PDF Editor Pro 14.0.1.33197 Multilingual</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 00:21:57 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-foxit-pdf-editor-pro-13375.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-foxit-pdf-editor-pro-13375.html
</guid><description>
Foxit PDF Editor Pro is a professional PDF editing software designed for personal and business users who need advanced capabilities to create, edit, secure and manage PDF documents. This Foxit software can combine, split or repackage multiple PDF files. Documents can be merged or split based on page numbers, page layout or bookmarks. Additionally, this Suite can batch convert existing documents into one or more PDF files.
Features of Foxit PDF Editor Pro 
Advanced PDF editing with...
</description></item><item><title>Download Ant Download Manager Pro 2.15.11 Build 91416</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 00:21:19 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ant-download-manager-pro-137.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-ant-download-manager-pro-137.html
</guid><description>
Ant Download Manager Pro is software support download has the same features as IDM, even it has many prominent features, more user friendly more and have speed download data incredible. Ant Download Manager is a Internet content downloader quickly with support download at video! Function: fully Integrated with the web browsers most popular: Internet Explorer 8+, Mozilla Firefox 32 +, Google Chrome 31+ and the copies of them (Pale Moon, Opera, Vivaldi, Slimjet, ComodoDragon, etc.). you...
</description></item><item><title>Download Flyby11 1.23.445</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 00:20:43 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-flyby11-12467.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-flyby11-12467.html
</guid><description>
Flyby11 is a simple patcher that removes annoying restrictions that prevent you from installing Windows 11 (24H2) on unsupported hardware. Do you have an old PC? No TPM, Secure Boot or your processor is not supported? Flyby11 allows you to install Windows 11 24H2. There are no complicated steps. Just run the tool and you'll be running Windows 11 on your outdated machine in no time.
Technical overview
Flyby11 takes advantage of a feature of the Windows 11 setup process that uses the...
</description></item><item><title>Download SoftMaker FlexiPDF Professional 2025.414.0924</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 00:20:21 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-softmaker-flexipdf-professional-1513.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-softmaker-flexipdf-professional-1513.html
</guid><description>
SoftMaker FlexiPDF Professional is the perfect software to edit and create pdf files. With this program, you can easily open any pdf file in environment task simple and easy. Change the text you want. Change the color of text and paragraphs. Like software Word, you can create a section of text or italics. Can you are not satisfied with the font of the pdf, you can open the file and save it with the font you want to pdf. In addition to text, you can add forms, graphics, photos, comments,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Flyoobe 1.23.445</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 00:19:34 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oobelux-13956.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-oobelux-13956.html
</guid><description>
Flyoobe was born out of the frustration many users felt with the Windows 11 setup experience. Whether it was the mandatory online account, the endless "Next, next, next..." screens, or the incomplete configuration options when you finally reached the desktop, the current setup lacked focus on what users really wanted.
Why choose Flyoobe?
	Simplifies the Windows 11 setup process right out of the box.
	Allows easy local account creation without need to hunt for hidden options.
	Includes...
</description></item><item><title>Download KMPlayer (KMP) 2025.9.25.11 x64 / 4.2.3.25 x86</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 00:19:14 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kmplayer-kmp-902.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-kmplayer-kmp-902.html
</guid><description>
KMPlayer (KMP) is software watch movies listen to music multi-function for video enthusiasts. KMPlayer development is many types of the format different. KMPlayer has improved on sound quality, images when listening to music and watching movies, the playback speed of video is faster, more codec player is added to the software video decoder is optimized.
KMPlayer also supports a variety of audio formats and video and offers a the interface can be customized with the preview coverflow and...
</description></item><item><title>Download 4K YouTube to MP3 25.3.2</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 00:18:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-youtube-to-mp3-622.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-4k-youtube-to-mp3-622.html
</guid><description>
4K YouTube to MP3 is a software to convert video youtube to mp3 quickly and easily by the manipulation drag-and-drop simple. With 4K YouTube to MP3 you just drag and drop the link to the favorite songs of you and get the MP3 files to your computer, as easy as that. Transfer songs directly to iPod, iPhone and iPad everywhere you go. No install annoying and complex to solve, just a clean interface, user friendly and functional.
When using 4K YouTube to MP3, users will get the playlists,...
</description></item><item><title>Download Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium 4.4.40.924</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 00:18:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-to-mp3-converter-premium-844.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-free-youtube-to-mp3-converter-premium-844.html
</guid><description>
Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium version is a software used to convert YouTube to MP3, extract audio from playlists YouTube, show listings, charts, video responses, channels, favorites of the user. With Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium, you can download and convert playlists, channels, stream original tv series and get them into iTunes at the same time.
Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium - convert YouTube to MP3
Features Free YouTube to MP3 Converter Premium from the...
</description></item><item><title>Download Any Video Downloader Pro 9.6.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 00:17:35 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-video-downloader-pro-3731.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-any-video-downloader-pro-3731.html
</guid><description>
Any Video Downloader Pro is software support you can download video HD 720p, 1080p, 2K, 4K and 8K from YouTube, Facebook, Dailymotion, Vimeo, Metacafe and thousands of video sharing sites, other. It is a tool to speed up multi-threading can speed up your download faster up to 5 times. This helpful program support download at the same time. Any Video Downloader Pro lets you download multiple videos at the same time. Moreover, it allows you to pause and resume downloads if you need more...
</description></item><item><title>Download Coolmuster iPhone Data Recovery 5.3.13</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 00:17:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-iphone-data-recovery-6599.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-iphone-data-recovery-6599.html
</guid><description>
Coolmuster iPhone Data Recovery is a useful tool designed to help users retrieve all lost data in the iPhone, iPad, or iPod quickly and efficiently. This professional software provides users with a safe way to find lost or deleted data on the Windows system. It can be used in any situation, both online and offline.
Features of Coolmuster iPhone Data Recovery
	Quickly restore the missing or deleted files from the iOS device and the iTunes backup.
	The processing of your iPhone data in...
</description></item><item><title>Download Advanced Installer Architect 23.1.0</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 00:16:51 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-installer-128.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-advanced-installer-128.html
</guid><description>
Advanced Installer is a Windows utility designed to help you build the package Windows Installer in a working environment clean and intuitive.
Although it has many parameters dedicated but the user interface is very simple and gives users the ability to create new projects by selecting the type, namely installer (for example: application Visual Studio or .NET, pack 32/64-bit mixture), Java , updates, support, mobile devices, and other things.
Advanced Installer - An environment for...
</description></item><item><title>Download Quick Surface 2025 v7.0.46</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 00:16:22 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quick-surface-3724.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-quick-surface-3724.html
</guid><description>
Quick Surface is the optimal solution for reverse Engineering compatible with any 3D scanner export mesh in STL or point cloud PTX. Model parameter future for both organic shapes and prismatic. Export data in IGES standard or file format STEP or build full parameter tree history directly into SOLIDWORKS.
Quick Surface - pattern design, 3D product
The features and characteristics of Quick Surface
	Interactive selection of the user instead of the dynamic segment on grid...
</description></item><item><title>Download ZD Soft Screen Recorder 12.0.5</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 00:15:52 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zd-soft-screen-recorder-136.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-zd-soft-screen-recorder-136.html
</guid><description>
ZD Soft Screen Recorder supports user taping the game in 2D or 3D, film screen, the content is screened in the multimedia. The Videos are saved in a list and popular formats with best quality.
ZD Soft Screen Recorder is a program recording software screen high performance. It works just like a camera really. A camcorder can record many things in the real world including computer screen, while ZD Soft Screen Recorder can only record computer screen but can do much better than a camcorder...
</description></item><item><title>Download Foxit PDF Reader 2025.2.1.33197</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 00:15:20 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-foxit-reader-1898.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-foxit-reader-1898.html
</guid><description>
Foxit Reader is the software support people, office, create, edit and read PDF files, create notes, create a signature, set password protection and print PDF files quickly and easily. Foxit Reader is already supported on many different platforms on PC. Mac or Mobile, particularly on iPhone, Android with called Foxit MobilePDF, allowing reading material in many languages, this software creates a processing environment PDF convenient, moreover also is integrated with service cloud storage to...
</description></item><item><title>Download RegRun Reanimator 17.60.2025.923</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 00:14:47 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-regrun-reanimator-1205.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-regrun-reanimator-1205.html
</guid><description>
RegRun Reanimator is a software supports to Remove Trojan / adware / spyware and rootkits, as well as the types of other malicious software. RegRun Reanimator is not just a set of standard tools, but also have a reporting feature in-depth. This can create a detailed report about the current state of your PC, including applications, drivers, codecs, browser settings, extensions, Explorer, network settings, link file the details, Windows services, startup programs, scheduled tasks, running...
</description></item><item><title>Download Coolmuster iCloud Backup Recovery 1.4.25</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 00:14:23 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-icloud-backup-recovery-10586.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-icloud-backup-recovery-10586.html
</guid><description>
Want to select files from your iCloud backup? Now, with the help of this iCloud Backup Restore tool, you can do it directly. With this iCloud backup restore program, you can save iCloud backup files to your computer in readable formats. So you can view and access them easily.
Coolmuster iCloud Backup Recovery can log in directly to iCloud there and preview your backup contacts. So, you have regained your contacts from your iCloud backup. By the way, this tool also supports other files....
</description></item><item><title>Download Coolmuster iOS Assistant 4.6.17</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 00:14:02 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-ios-assistant-2476.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-ios-assistant-2476.html
</guid><description>
You want to backup data from iPhone / iPad / iPod to computer? You want to import a file from your computer to your iOS device? You want to restore backup on your iDevices? You want to have full control over the data stored on your iDevices? This iOS Assistant pro integrates all these features in a and sure is the best manager for your iOS device.
Coolmuster iOS Assistant - backup for IOS devices
Coolmuster iOS Assistant is a whole program feature allows you to freely backup contacts,...
</description></item><item><title>Download CHITUBOX Pro 3.0.1</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 00:13:37 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chitubox-pro-7800.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-chitubox-pro-7800.html
</guid><description>
CHITUBOX Pro is professional 3D printing preprocessing software widely used in dentistry, consumer electronics, character modeling, footwear, jewelry and other industries. other areas. It offers model pre-processing, intelligent assisted editing, high-speed cutting, user-friendly design, excellent algorithms, and smooth use. Also compatible with SLA/DLP/LCD 3D printing technology makes any creation easier.
Features of CHITUBOX Pro
	CAD File Formats Support: In addition to traditional...
</description></item><item><title>Download Opera GX (Gaming Browser) 122.0.5643.79</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 00:13:07 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-gx-3170.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-opera-gx-3170.html
</guid><description>
Opera GX is a special version of the Opera browser is built to complement gamers avid. Browser this game comes with the unique features to help users make maximum use of both the game and their browser. Opera GX is built specifically to support the game. This browser includes the unique features to help users have the best experience when gaming and surfing the web.
Opera GX - special browser for gamers
GX Control allows you to set a limit on the level of use RAM, CPU and network where...
</description></item><item><title>Download Minimal Firewall 2.2.3</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 00:12:38 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minimal-firewall-13877.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-minimal-firewall-13877.html
</guid><description>
Minimal Firewall works in conjunction with Windows Firewall to block all unknown connections by default, prompting you to create application-based rules to mitigate malware, telemetry, and data leaks. Completely eliminate applications that call home without your knowledge. Minimal Firewall provides a more secure and integrated approach by interacting directly with the native Windows Firewall, eliminating the need for risky system modifications.
Core Features
	Lockdown Mode: The core...
</description></item><item><title>Download Coolmuster iPhone SMS + Contacts Recovery 4.0.24</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 00:12:13 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-iphone-sms-contacts-recovery-8524.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-iphone-sms-contacts-recovery-8524.html
</guid><description>
Coolmuster iPhone SMS + Contacts Recovery is professional software that helps to recover all contacts and SMS from iPhone. It recovers not only phone numbers and text messages, but also contact names, addresses, companies, emails, SMS attachments, and more. The 100% read-only and safe recovery process provided by the iPhone data recovery program allows you to back up your recovered iPhone text messages and contacts on your computer without any quality loss.
Features of Coolmuster iPhone...
</description></item><item><title>Download Coolmuster iPhone WhatsApp Recovery 1.1.16</title><pubDate> Fri, 26 Sep 2025 00:11:49 +0700 </pubDate><link>https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-iphone-whatsapp-recovery-12378.html</link><guid>
https://en.taiwebs.com/windows/download-coolmuster-iphone-whatsapp-recovery-12378.html
</guid><description>
Coolmuster iPhone WhatsApp Recovery provides effective recovery of WhatsApp messages and attachments from iPhone and iPad devices, ensuring you never lose important chats. View and access WhatsApp chat history and attachments conveniently on your PC, giving you complete control over your WhatsApp data.
Recover WhatsApp data in accessible formats for seamless management and use. Coolmuster iPhone WhatsApp Recovery ensures high retrieval speed and wide compatibility with many devices for...
</description></item></channel></rss>